Old guard, what are you doing?
Lotus roots can heal his wounds.
The Third Crown Prince
dismembered himself to repay his parents.
Then his master used lotus stems and roots
to regrow his flesh and bones.
How many milk caps did he use this time?
No idea.
Everything was on fire when I arrived.
The Nine Dragons Divine Fire Barrier
has the worst side effects.
When will he come to?
Don't worry. He won't die.
AGENT FROM ABOVE
INTO THE ABYSS
Baby, don't go.
Han Chieh.
You're awake?
How do you feel now?
Sure you want to take on
so many cases at once?
Screw it, I'm going all in.
Han Chieh, what are you doing?
DEMON KING ENTICES MAN
But you said the Demon King
has a new agent.
-You don't know anything about him.
-I don't give a fuck.
If I don't stop that scumbag,
more innocent people will die.
CHIEH
Happy now?
Hey.
Hey!
"Go to Buddha Mountain
for a healthy hike."
Buddha Mountain?
Chen Chi-sha.
Fuck.
BUDDHA
After I defeated Chen Chi-sha,
I locked all his magical weapons
in a safe.
Stop practicing sorcery.
Retire.
I'll protect you
from any demons or ghosts.
Do you really think you're invincible?
You got lucky this time.
If the Demon King regains his full power,
you're dead meat.
Doesn't sound like
there's anything good in this safe.
Sure he isn't messing with you?
He sent me that message for a reason.
He wouldn't mess with me
just for the sake of it.
Fuck, I think you're messing with me.
How much farther is it?
Hey.
Have you got the key?
What the fuck.
ZERO, ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE
What the fuck is that?
What the…
Mother of…
What's that?
Come on… let's go.
Go.
Incense ash.
Did Chen Chi-sha put you in that safe?
Why?
Me?
He wants to tell me something?
Wu…
Wu Tien-chi?
Wu Meng-hsueh.
Wu Meng-hsueh?
Look up Wu Meng-hsueh.
-I'll do a search back at the station.
-Okay.
On the left…
Hide…
Cut it out, cut it out…
Cut it out-- Go…
-Okay, go.
-Wang Hsiao-ming.
Yes.
Who pays for the internet?
Watch out. Grenade!
You do.
Fire in the hole!
Be a big brother
and look after the little ghost.
-What?
Okay… sure.
-I'm off.
-Bye.
Let's play.
What do you want?
I need to pee.
Fuck, he needs to pee. What do I do?
Hey!
CRIMINAL FILE
Wu Meng-hsueh changed his name
to Wu Tien-chi. He's in finance now.
Rumor has it
he can predict the stock market
and how shares will perform.
He even committed murder as a minor.
Chen Chi-sha said Wu's the new agent.
That they were just using him.
Now Chen Chi-sha is dead,
Wu Tien-chi probably has Wang Yu-ching.
What for?
Mr. Wang.
You'll wear yourself out like this.
Go home and get some rest.
We'll inform you
the second we get any news.
I'm fine. I'll wait here for Ching.
There's no one else back home anyway.
Hello?
Is this Yu-ching's dad?
Yes, it is.
I'm her friend.
Have you heard
how she's being bullied at school?
She's being bullied at school?
She never mentioned it before.
Are you her classmate?
I know where to find her,
but I don't want to get in trouble.
So you must promise me
not to call the cops.
-That's the only way I can help.
-Okay, I promise.
CRIMINAL FILES
I handled Wu Meng-hsueh's case back then.
Some 20 years ago.
You still remember the case,
Prosecutor Chen?
I'll never forget it.
I was outraged by the verdict.
PRESIDING JUDGE: CHANG HO-CHENG
What is it?
Please continue.
Wu Meng-hsueh was 15.
The victim was a 16-year-old girl.
She and her grandma
were found dead in their own home.
-What was the motive?
-A crime of passion.
The girl had been sexually assaulted.
He claimed they were in love,
but the grandma opposed the relationship.
Wu Meng-hsueh's dad was a famous lawyer.
He assembled a big legal team
to to exonerate him.
They used his status as a minor
to exploit legal loopholes.
The victim's grandpa was always in court,
but couldn't speak because of a stroke.
His dad also used his connections
to put pressure on the presiding judge.
He got off with a light sentence
and there was nothing I could do about it.
The girl's grandpa
refused to eat or drink after the verdict.
He died not long after.
Wu Meng-hsueh
didn't stay inside for long either.
He was released in his twenties
and regained his freedom.
I'm angry at myself
for failing to get justice for her.
But I'm even angrier at this world.
Those with power and influence
get away with anything.
PRESIDING JUDGE, CHANG HO-CHENG
I asked his dad's secretary
to meet me nearby.
You've been acting weird.
What's the matter?
Wu Meng-hsueh's presiding judge,
Chang Ho-cheng, was my dad.
He didn't talk to us about work often.
When I was in high school,
he suddenly became depressed.
He died not long after that.
In the days before he died,
he kept saying, "I'm sorry."
I finally found out why today.
He couldn't get over the verdict.
It haunted him to his death.
Even gods make mistakes,
what hope do humans have?
Fuck. I swear to god
I'll throw that asshole in jail.
Jail?
Men like him should go straight
to the 18th level of hell.
The 100th level.
Secretary Liu, I'm Chang Min.
We spoke on the phone.
This is my partner.
Today, I came to ask you about
Mr. Wu's son, Wu Meng-hsueh.
Secretary Liu.
What do you want to know?
After Wu Meng-hsueh was released,
he got a new identity.
Is there anything
he was hiding from or avoiding?
His family was already powerful.
Why did he learn the Wumeng Technique?
Because…
he saw that girl's grandpa in jail.
Go away.
Get lost.
You killed my wife and granddaughter.
I'll haunt you until the day you die.
I'll settle this score with you
in the Underworld!
I'll personally see you go down
to the 18th level of hell!
Wu Meng-hsueh asked his dad for help,
so Mr. Wu found a master
who kept the grandpa's spirit
in a sandalwood incense burner,
and sealed it inside with talismans.
Do you know where it is now?
No, I don't.
I just know
that after Wu Meng-hsueh got out,
he traveled the world.
His goal was to find a way
to act with impunity, free from punishment
in both the Human Realm and hell.
He started studying
black magic and sorcery,
including the worst magic of all,
the Wumeng Technique.
What have you done?
We had four competitors. All of which
had staff members involved in accidents.
But we're in a great position now.
What are you unhappy about?
Meng-hsueh.
Stop engaging in these shady practices.
If you keep this up…
I'll change my will.
When the time comes,
you won't get a single penny.
Try me.
If you change your will,
the next one to have an accident
might well be you.
You…
I should've let them
throw the book at you!
Later, Mr. Wu closed the law firm.
And I left my job after he retired.
I never heard from them again.
Let's find that incense burner.
Why?
The only thing he fears is karma.
Being reported to the Underworld.
You mean that if the girl's grandpa
reports him to Yama,
he'll have to face up
to all his crimes when he dies?
Yeah. Can you find where it's hidden?
I asked the station to pull his records.
He has a foreign passport.
His assets are all held overseas.
It'll take some time.
The Demon King sure knows how to pick
them. This guy's cunning and has brains.
So what if he has brains?
He only uses them for evil.
You're brainless, but better than him.
You're the fucking brainless one.
Touchy.
INVESTIGATION UNIT ONE
-Damn it, you bastard!
-Calm down.
Where's my daughter?
Good job.
The beat-up guy is a drug user
called Hsieh Kun-hao.
A man phoned Wang Cheng-nan saying
Mr. Hsieh was bullying his daughter.
So he assumed
he must be the one who kidnapped her.
How did he find him?
The man on the phone told him.
He found him at an apartment
Wu Tien-chi bought three years ago.
The same place the girl and grandma died.
Using others
while keeping safely out of it.
Seems to be his MO.
Chao already invited him over for a chat.
I bought that apartment ages ago
and it's been empty for years.
God knows why anyone would break in.
So why did you buy the property?
It's in a good location
and bound to gain value in the future.
I only bought it for investment purposes.
Officers, is there anything else
you'd like to ask?
-Thank you.
-Take care.
-You're just letting him go?
-We can't detain him.
We have no evidence connecting him
to the girl's disappearance.
And the number used to call Wang Cheng-nan
wasn't even a Taiwanese number.
So we can't be sure he made the call.
But…
All right, have him tailed 24-7.
Got it.
Hello.
Cut the act.
Oh.
I'm impressed.
You went to see Chen Chi-sha
and actually got out alive.
Tell the Demon King
I know he's coming up here for me.
I'm happy to play along,
but you must release Wang Yu-ching first.
And let's set some rules.
Leave innocent people out of this.
You love messing with black magic, right?
Then let's fight.
If you win, you can take my life.
That sounds pretty tempting.
Shame you don't know me so well.
Let me tell you something.
There's nothing I hate more
than obeying stupid rules.
See those people in there?
They bow and scrape,
always following the rules,
and live out lives of drudgery.
In search of what?
Freedom.
Nothing beats freedom.
I hear your milk caps are pretty fancy.
Can't wait to see for myself.
Hello.
This way, please.
The VIP has arrived.
It's getting cold.
Add an extra blanket at night.
I know, I'm not five.
You'll be reminding me
to wear socks to bed next.
-Bye.
What are you back for?
Leafy.
Go on, jump.
Jump.
Hurry up and jump.
You bastard! Stay away from her!
Leafy.
Chieh.
What do you want?
Wait…
I just sent my cute secretary
to case the joint and check things out.
I feel bad for Master Chen.
I wanted to find him a goddaughter.
Maybe Yeh Chih-ling?
You dare touch my people?
I'll end you right now!
You've never killed a human, have you?
Lots of demons and ghosts,
but never a living human being?
Want to give it a go?
You want to kill me, right?
See. We're the same.
We're the same.
-Chieh…
-We're the same.
-Calm down, Chieh.
-Come on.
Chieh.
Fuck, you've got some mouth on you,
but all you do is talk.
All talk and no action. Relying on
Chen Chi-sha to do all your dirty work.
Officer, who do you think you are?
You think your corrupt, incompetent unit
has what it takes to arrest me?
Maybe in your next life.
That it? Is that all you've got?
Guess that's your idea of an insult?
Why'd the Demon King
choose a loser like you?
Try harder, will you?
Chen Chi-sha was just a pawn.
I told him who to kill.
That old fart
isn't even on the same level, okay?
You're a bunch of losers.
I know the law. I know black magic.
Think you're a match for me?
I might just kill Yeh Chih-ling first.
Chieh, let's go.
Chieh. Come on, let's go.
What? Don't go!
There, there now. Calm down.
It's okay. I'll open the door for you.
Get in the car. Watch your head.
Sit properly and be good.
Low blood sugar makes you irritable.
Chao.
Listen, thanks to Han Chieh,
we can file for a search warrant.
I'll send it over later.
What's so funny?
Chen Chi-sha was just a pawn.
I told him who to kill.
That old fart--
Prosecutor Chen approved
a search warrant for Wu Tien-chi's home.
Beside the recording,
he was also seen entering a private room
with Chen Chi-sha at the nightclub.
This sandalwood incense burner
with talismans on it was kept well hidden.
Is this what you're looking for?
Yes.
Chieh, that's evidence.
Remember to return it after you're done.
So what are you planning to do with it?
I'll hold onto it
and help the girl's grandpa
request a Black Command Token.
We finally got something on him.
Screw that Wu Tien-chi.
TAIPEI CITY STREET MAP
Hey, I don't get it.
Wu Tien-chi tricked Wang Cheng-nan
into going after that other guy.
He even chose the apartment
where he committed his first murder
as the location.
What's he up to?
The location… of his first murder.
Wu Tien-chi's objective…
That girl isn't here.
Wang Yu-ching has other uses.
Wu Tien-chi's apartment.
Heilung HQ.
Those stolen primal souls.
PAOAN TEMPLE, LANTE TEMPLE, FUHE TEMPLE
The deaths at each location
happened in the same weird way.
Give me a pen…
HEILUNG HQ
FUHE TEMPLE
LANCHEN TEMPLE
PAOAN TEMPLE
This is…
It's an array.
Fuck.
I missed it.
While Chen Chi-sha grabbed primal souls,
Wu set up the array
with live sacrifices.
He'll break the seal and help
the Demon King enter the Human Realm.
"Corpselords will rise
and attack at full moon."
The full moon?
It was a full moon last time too.
You got lucky.
If the Demon King
regains his full power, you're dead meat.
Full moon, magic array, center.
I get it now.
Five years ago, I only managed to win
because I stopped
the Demon King's entry just in time.
The magic array was complete,
but he was waiting
for midnight
when the moon is at its height.
Only then could he regain his full power
through the portal.
If you dare get in my way,
I'll drag you down to hell with me.
It's the same this time.
WANG YU-CHING, HEILUNG HQ
Where's the portal?
At the center of the array,
Dongfeng Market.
So he targeted you and Dongfeng Market
right from the start.
That bastard, Wu Tien-chi.
But the array is incomplete.
The sacrifice at the final location
must be Wang Yu-ching.
GOLDEN LAKE PLAZA
Can't we just survey the place?
It's surrounded by high-rises
with thousands of households.
He could be anywhere.
A human is sacrificed
either by suicide or brutal murder.
The array's dark power is fueled by the
victims' terror and resentment in death.
He's keeping Wang Yu-ching alive
for the final sacrifice
a few days before the full moon.
We still have time.
GOLDEN LAKE PLAZA
-Do we still have a deal?
-You're pathetic.
Are you that scared of an old man
filing a complaint against you?
Just do this right,
and even Yama of the Underworld
won't be able to touch you,
no matter what you did in the Human Realm
and even if you die and end up in hell.
Do you have what I asked for?
How are preparations going?
It's all set.
I tried it out today.
Chieh, Leafy has been possessed
by a female ghost.
What do you want?
That little shit really cares about her.
If we put it in that girl,
even if Han Chieh finds out,
he won't dare do anything rash.
Don't underestimate him.
He defeated Chen Chi-sha.
You'd better mind yourself.
This is the final stretch.
Raise the corpselords first.
Find a way to exhaust his magic weapons.