SHEN-LUNG TEMPLE
SHEN-LUNG WATER
INFINITE LIFE
LIFE
SHEN-LUNG TEMPLE
-Is that him?
-Yes.
Stealing my money's one thing,
but fucking my wife?
You scammer. Let's go!
Shen-Lung Crown Prince, you're dying.
I can save you.
But you must pay the price.
Just take my hand,
and your fate will be changed.
AGENT FROM ABOVE
SOUL HARVEST
DONGFENG MARKET
Everyone, time to eat.
-Thank you.
-Wow, what a feast.
What a feast.
Oh my god, that really hits the spot.
-It's delicious!
-Have as much as you want.
Welcome, new neighbors.
Anything you'd like, I can cook.
-You're so nice.
-Get me one.
-There's plenty. Help yourselves.
-You're too kind.
We've got desserts and snacks here.
C cup?
Hi, I'm Mei-na. Welcome to the community.
Hi, I'm Wang Hsiao-ming.
Interested in a ghost marriage?
Wang Hsiao-ming.
What's up?
Take your pick.
I can't believe it!
You shouldn't have.
That one's no good.
But the suit has style.
Nah, makes no difference.
He looks tacky in anything.
Madam.
You shouldn't give him such a hard time.
Let's go try on the clothes.
Get changed together?
-Together?
-You two together? Don't you dare.
-Why don't you join us?
-Hurry up.
Han Chieh, have you seen Ms. Chiang?
She moved in next to you last week.
No, but I've seen her daughter.
I think she might be deaf.
Seems Ms. Chiang has had a hard life.
Oh well. I'll invite her
to dinner at my restaurant.
And you should check in on her
when you have time.
Everyone.
Oh my, Wang Hsiao-ming.
Is that you, Wang Hsiao-ming?
-He looks so old.
-Like a sleazy old man.
-No, he doesn't.
-Grandpa Wang.
-Hsiao-ming, you look sublime,
but aren't worth a dime.
Everyone's getting along so well.
Thanks to the old guard and Sister Lo.
Did their families die in that fire too?
Yeah.
Sis Lo's younger brother
and the old guard's son and grandson.
They all wanted to stay together,
so I opened their third eyes.
But Sis Lo's younger brother
never showed up.
I hope she can move on soon.
Han Chieh.
You might seem cold on the outside,
but you're a good guy really.
You spend all your time here.
Still taking your medication?
Of course.
Han Chieh, smile.
What are you doing?
A gang called the Heilung Clan
was wiped out last night.
They died insane deaths.
I'll drop by tomorrow. Help me out.
BLESS THIS HOUSEHOLD
Seems Ms. Chiang has had a hard life.
Check in on her when you have time.
I'm Han Chieh. I live next door.
Sister Lo mentioned you.
You're the agent from above, right?
Everyone's having dinner on the rooftop.
Sister Lo was asking about you.
-Why don't you take your daughter?
-I couldn't.
Yuan-yuan is deaf and can't speak.
I don't want to impose.
I saw her a few days ago.
She loves to draw and is such a cute kid.
I'll leave you to it.
Master Han.
I've been ill for years
and my daughter is deaf.
-Do you know of any…
-I'm not some master.
I'm just an ordinary guy.
I'm sorry.
LINGERING SPIRIT
SHEN-LUNG CROWN PRINCE
FORCED BY OCCULTIST TO COMMIT CRIMES
TEMPLE FIRE CLAIMS TWO LIVES
FENGYUAN TEMPLE
TEMPLE EVICTION DISPUTE TURNS FATAL
LIU KUAN-FU DENIES INVOLVEMENT
TEMPLE ARSON LINKED TO LAND DISPUTE?
LIU KUAN-FU: "WHERE'S THE PROOF?"
"WHERE'S THE PROOF?"
CHANG MIN
Why didn't you take my call?
You never have good news.
Hey.
Look.
The Demon King?
Eleven members
of the Heilung Clan taken out like this.
Chen Chi-sha?
They had lots of enemies.
Anyone could have hired a hitman.
Chen Chi-sha wouldn't kill for money.
And why's the Demon King's symbol there?
No way this was just triads feuding.
Don't say I didn't warn you
when the shit hits the fan.
I know a guy
who used to run with the triads.
I'll go sound him out.
Maybe he knows something.
This way.
-Fu.
-Have a seat.
You've done well for yourself?
The temple's huge now.
Not back in that business, are you?
Of course not.
Han Chieh, you've got it all wrong.
Hey, I don't give out false tips
or run scams on people anymore.
All the money
comes from donations to the temple.
I take a cut for expenses,
then donate the rest to charity.
I even help clean the beach
and feed the homeless.
-I'll get the account books.
-No need.
This isn't about you.
That thing I asked you to look into?
So, a friend at another temple told me
that the Heilung Clan won a 100 million
government construction project.
Liu Kuan-fu and the Heilung Clan
had a deal.
The Heilung Clan would subcontract
the work to Liu Kuan-fu's supplier.
Maybe they fell out
over the split or whatever,
but the Heilung Clan took the lot.
Everyone knew they hated each other.
It was bound to happen sooner or later.
It's just… I never thought Liu Kuan-fu
would be quite so ruthless.
Ruthless?
Of course he's ruthless.
He took the deeds
to our little temple and set it on fire.
He got me addicted to drugs
so he could take my family's land.
He made sure I owed him big.
FENGYUAN TEMPLE
Then he tricked me into handing over
the deeds as collateral.
LAND OWNERSHIP CERTIFICATE
Kneel!
Tell the Third Crown Prince
what you've done.
The construction company
says our land is theirs now!
-You'll be the death of me!
-That's enough.
I wish you'd never been born!
Stop it!
My dad wouldn't cooperate,
so Liu Kuan-fu burned the place down.
-How could this happen?
-Our stuff is inside.
Did anyone get out?
The fire suddenly broke out.
Heavens, what should we do?
-Hey!
-Calm down!
FENGYUAN TEMPLE
In the end,
both my mom and dad perished in that fire.
They've been in hell ever since
suffering because of me.
My boss wants me to kill evil ghosts.
But if someone is even worse than a ghost,
how could killing them violate my orders?
I know it sucks.
But he gave you a chance
to redeem yourself
because he knows what you've been through.
It's a big responsibility.
As if.
Don't be like that. Hey.
Have you seen the Marvel movies?
Ever see Iron Man
kill without good reason?
Iron Man only became a hero
after he redeemed himself.
You're actually a superhero.
With great power
comes great responsibility.
If you abuse your power,
you're no better than Liu Kuan-fu.
If I'm a superhero, what are you?
Me?
I'm this guy.
A truck driver?
Come on. I'm Doctor Strange.
Don't you see it? I'm Doctor Strange.
Hey.
It does look like I'm driving.
Hey, wait for me.
Boss.
Boss, why'd Chen Chi-sha want to meet
out here in the middle of nowhere?
What's his game?
Mr. Liu.
Hey… the money's all here.
I didn't do it for the money.
Those Heilung punks were perfect
for testing my hellspawn on.
Nasty way to go, right?
The money's here.
I don't want anything
to do with you from now on.
Think you can ditch me so easily?
When you first came to me,
you seemed to appreciate my skills.
Stay away from us from now on!
-Hand it over…
-Boss.
-Give him the money.
-Here.
You came,
so you must have taken care of things?
I'm old, getting rusty.
You're too modest.
Anyone chosen by the Demon King
is someone to be reckoned with.
The way your hellspawn took out
those Heilung punks was terrifying.
I only worked for the Demon King
to get revenge.
Triads killed my family.
They don't deserve to live.
But this is different.
You two are working together
to control me and forcing me to kill.
I know I'm beyond pardon,
but I never killed innocent people before.
As an evil person,
I know that evil has many faces.
But you and I are different.
What do you want from me next?
CHIANG HUA-CHIH
Based on the birth chart,
your illness and your daughter's condition
are predestined.
Master, can't I change my destiny?
A person's destiny
is determined by their birth.
It can't be changed.
However…
there is a way to eliminate bad karma.
Really?
How?
Shen-Lung Crown Prince.
What do you get as a petty fraudster,
sex and money?
If you work for me,
I'll give you everything you want.
What do I need to do?
Have you brought your daughter?
Master.
I have.
I didn't tell you this last time,
but there is a strong
negative energy in your home.
Someone close to you
is most likely causing you harm.
When was your daughter born?
She was born on February 21st, 2009.
FEBRUARY 21ST, 2009, OX
February 21st, 2009. Year of the Ox?
I need some hellspawn
refined from people's primal souls.
Find me people born on this day…
FEBRUARY 21ST, 2009, OX
…and kill them.
Listen.
Your daughter is the one
hindering your recovery.
Your birth charts are incompatible.
She makes you ill and you make her mute.
That's why she'll never speak
and you'll never recover.
It can't be my daughter, Master.
Are… are you sure?
I'm absolutely certain.
Then what should I do?
Step outside. Leave her with me.
-Just step outside. Get out.
-Wait.
-What are you going to do to her?
-Get out!
-Yuan-yuan, come here.
-Get out.
-Out!
-Yuan-yuan, come here.
-Get out!
-Yuan-yuan!
Han Chieh, here's the lighter you wanted.
SHEN-LUNG CROWN PRINCE HARMS PEOPLE
Another one.
What?
That's the third one
with his name on this month.
First is for fraud.
Then for working with an occultist.
You've been ignoring this for a while now
and it just keeps getting worse.
So it's my fault?
I've still got tons of tasks to do.
I can't be in two places at once.
I can't catch all the scammers out there.
Now you want me to stop the Demon King.
I'm human, not a god.
I can barely take care of myself.
Fuck all this shit.
Fuck it.
Han Chieh, where are you going?
Yuan-yuan?
Han Chieh.
Why is she…
Who did this?
Where's your mom?
I'm going down to hell. Give me a hand.
Me?
I've been there many times.
I use the milk caps' side effects
to knock myself out.
Play this music
after I've been under for three minutes.
Shock me with this.
I'm counting on you.
Ms. Chiang.
What happened?
I can't find Yuan-yuan.
I can't find Yuan-yuan anywhere.
She died before I did.
I can't find her.
Where's her primal soul?
I don't know.
She can't come down here
or be reborn without it.
Who did this?
The Shen-Lung Crown Prince.
Open the door!
Yuan-yuan!
I got my daughter killed.
And I got myself killed.
-Where is he?
-In his temple.
My time's up.
-Where are you going?
-To throw out the trash.
How… how will you get there?
-Are you still alive?
-Strictly speaking, I'm dead right now.
Who exactly are you?
I work for him.
You set it too high.
You never told me how high to set it.
Grab me a shirt.
And the lotus seeds from the fridge.
Tell Chang Min
there's been a murder at Shen-Lung Temple.
What about you?
I'm going to settle a score.
QIANKUN HOOP
SHEN-LUNG TEMPLE
Out!
Look who it is,
the Third Crown Prince's agent from above.
I'm honored.
I'll give you one chance.
Hand over her primal soul,
and I'll spare you.
He really is such a spoiled brat.
Even his agent from above
is just a loudmouthed punk.
Fine.
I'll beat you senseless first,
then make you wish you'd never been born.
Third Crown Prince!
Tell the big man
to come and collect your corpse.
Thought you were a badass, huh?
Serves you right for mouthing off.
You can't even beat a fraudster.
Is that all you've got?
You think I want this?
-Where are the milk caps I gave you?
-I used them.
Didn't you see?
Those milk caps you gave me
are like playthings to them.
So you're here to bitch?
You won't let me smoke or drink.
Just give me something I can work with.
I don't let you smoke or drink.
Yet you used the Qiankun Hoop to light up.
Don't forget,
the more power I give you,
the more it'll hurt after.
Never stopped me before.
I'll give you one more.
Great. I told you, they don't work on him.
I blessed this one.
Are you done yet?
It's my turn now.
We've been onto this fraudster for a while
now, but never had any evidence.
Good thing
the Third Crown Prince tipped you off.
He won't get away this time.
I should've seen it sooner.
SHEN-LUNG TEMPLE
DONGFENG MARKET
Yuan-yuan, you can be with your mom now.
HEAVEN, WIND, WATER
DAD: EXAM OVER YET?
ARE YOU COMING HOME?
I'M ALMOST THERE