[man] Pangu separates heaven and earth,
so that all things may flourish.
One thousand years ago,
demonic flames surged to the heavens.
Hell's Demon King, Vasavatti,
barged into the Human Realm,
and devoured living beings,
increasing his demonic power.
The Crown Prince,
a god from the Celestial Realm,
descended to the world
to subdue this demon,
and return him to the hell
from which he came.
In the ensuing war,
the Human Realm was torn apart.
Thereafter, the Celestial Realm
established a rule
that neither a god nor a demon
can enter the Human Realm
in their true form.
[growls]
Since then, any god or demon
who wishes to enter the Human Realm
can only do so by channeling
their spirits through humans.
And only a few humans are equipped
to be their supernatural agents.
- [grunts]
- [dramatic music playing]
[groans]
Some of these
supernatural agents are endowed
with immense power and responsibility.
[battle cries]
They are called…
…agents from above.
AGENT FROM ABOVE
[theme music playing]
THE SINNER
[thunder cracking]
DONGFENG MARKET
[low, eerie music playing]
[snoring]
Can I ask you a question?
[man continues snoring]
If you be human, stop there.
Or are you a ghost?
[snores]
[thunder cracking]
[eerie music continues]
[growls in the background]
UNIT 4-9 NO. 56 LANE 114 DONGFENG ST.
MASTER HAN CHIEH
[growls intensify]
UNIT 4-9 NO. 56 LANE 114 DONGFENG ST.
[doorbell rings]
- [man] Who is it?
- Are you Han Chieh?
[Han] What do you want?
Hello, Master Han. I'm Yeh Tzu.
I'm told you can help
with ghosts and spiri--
- Sorry, I don't take on new--
- Hang on. Please wait.
I know you only do the work
of the Crown Prince.
But there's nowhere else for me to turn.
- This was placed under my father's pillow.
- [sniffs]
The ghost was a woman.
Go away and don't bother me again.
[door slams]
[ringing doorbell repeatedly]
Didn't you hear me? I told you to go.
Why are you so cruel?
Maybe you're not a master.
You're just a pretender!
I told you to go away. Now go!
[loud ticking]
[crackling]
[dramatic music playing]
[music intensifies]
- [Yeh] Hey!
- [Han] Come with me!
What are you doing?
[theme music playing]
[ghosts growling]
[music fades]
Hey, you there. How old are you?
Uh, 21.
- [whimsical music playing]
- [scoffs]
When are you free again?
I'm not sure.
She's only 21.
Be nice to her or the heavens
will punish you.
I'm off then.
I'll see you next time.
[door opens and closes]
[whimsical music continues]
[lighter clicking]
[chirps softly]
What now, you lousy bird?
I still have work to do,
and you won't even let me smoke?
[bell rings]
Thanks a lot.
[music ends]
[sighs]
[Yeh Tzu] Master Han.
A feng shui master haunts my mother.
And so he wants to harm
my father with this.
It's a fake.
No, it's real.
I've seen it myself many times.
He practices the technique
of Wumeng Maoshan.
[dramatic music playing]
Wumeng Maoshan?
HO CHUN-LAI
ONLY SUCCESSOR OF WUMENG MAOSHAN TECHNIQUE
PASSED DOWN FROM MASTER CHEN CHI-SHA
WUMENG OCCULTIST DRIVES
WHITE-CLOTHED FEMALE GHOST TO HARM PEOPLE
[dramatic music continues]
- Why didn't you show me this earlier?
- Do you know him?
No, I don't.
PASSED DOWN FROM MASTER CHEN CHI-SHA
But his master, Chen Chi-sha,
is quite famous.
[sighs]
It seems like your family is in trouble.
I have my orders.
You take your orders
from the Crown Prince?
[exhales]
Take me to your house tomorrow.
Thank you, Master Han!
Don't call me "Master".
I'll just take a look. Nothing else.
Yes, Mr. Han.
What happened outside before?
[sighs]
[theme music builds]
There was once a man
in love with a woman who lived here.
When the romance ended,
he set a fire so they'd die together.
[screams]
In the end, he lived,
but the residents here weren't so lucky.
Their unjust death destined them
to become earthbound spirits.
And so they're stuck here.
Every night after 11p.m.,
they become frightened again.
They think he's returning
to set yet another fire like what you saw.
You get it?
[groans] Mr. Han, what was that for?
[music fades]
I'm opening your third eye,
so you won't startle my old neighbors.
[eerie music playing]
[growls]
I can see them, your neighbors.
[Han Chieh] It's okay.
Don't be frightened.
[Yeh Tzu chuckles nervously]
- [Yeh Tzu] Sorry to disturb you.
- [music ends]
[siren wailing]
TAIPEI CITY POLICE DEPARTMENT
CENTRAL DISTRICT PRECINCT
[telephone rings]
[man 1] She was crying.
She was begging me to send her the money.
[man 2] Sir, I don't recommend that.
Don't send any money.
Let the police sort it out
when they arrive.
What if it is true?
She said she's in love with me.
- Look. I'm not a mind reader, okay?
- [curious music playing]
I can only tell you what I know,
that most people who behave
like this are scammers.
- She loves me.
- [beep]
Hello?
You there? Hello, sir? You there?
[sighs] Some people are so stupid.
[curious music continues]
Restroom Peeping Tom.
Cameras don't pick up anyone.
Ask Han Chieh to check for a ghost.
[gasps] Any spirit causing trouble
will not escape my eyes.
[chuckles] Yeah, for sure.
You could see ghosts from birth.
Giving this case to you
seems only natural, hey?
Don't worry, Chao. Leave this case to me.
It's people I can't cope with,
but ghosts are easy enough.
- [door beeps]
- [music ends]
[door closes]
First time I saw her,
she was standing over there.
Then the second time, she was there.
[suspenseful music plays]
[ghost screams]
[tense music playing]
LAST TIME TRAVELING TO JAPAN
BEFORE GETTING SICK.
LEAFY, YOU CAN DO IT!
GET BETTER SOON, BEAT YOUR ILLNESS!
[music fades]
BEI KANG UNITED HOSPITAL, YEH CHIH-LING
[poignant piano playing]
Hey. There's nothing here.
Are you okay?
I have leukemia.
Look. Cool, hey?
[poignant music continues]
Mmm.
[Yeh Tzu] I found that red packet here.
Strange, it's here again.
[music turns suspenseful]
No smell. It's fake.
I don't understand. I know I saw her.
If there was a ghost,
I'd see it, and smell it too.
- [sniffs]
- This has no smell.
Perhaps you just imagined it.
[front door beeps]
Please come in, Master Ho.
I'm sorry to trouble you again.
[suspenseful music continues]
Yeh Tzu?
Oh. Is this your friend?
- Yes.
- Hello.
He's my senior at film school.
[Mrs. Yeh] I asked Master Ho
to come and give you a checkup.
Have a seat. I'll slice up some fruit.
Come and help me.
Please.
[suspenseful music builds]
Master Ho, apart from feng shui,
you're a doctor too?
[Ho Chun-lai scoffs]
I came to read her palms
to see how she can avoid disaster.
Disaster?
Like finding this?
How is Chen Chi-sha?
[exhales] Master Chen is long retired.
He sunbathes, enjoys life.
This is to help Mrs. Yeh
save her relationship with her husband.
I know about Wumeng Maoshan Technique.
I should warn you. Be careful.
[suspenseful music continues]
You know, I only charge
for my services if I think I can help.
I'm not here to cause trouble.
RED-CLOTHED FEMALE GHOST AND
WHITE-CLOTHED FEMALE GHOST HARM PEOPLE
HSIAO-MING LINGERS IN WOMEN'S ROOM
Mr. Han, I don't trust that man.
Why are you back?
You should be resting.
I told my mother we were shooting a movie.
I convinced her to let me come out.
You can't hang out with me. I'm too busy.
How are you busy?
Is it for the Crown Prince?
[excitedly] Can I come along too?
My house is still haunted.
I really need you.
Are you just going to abandon me?
That would make me very sad.
You don't want me to make a scene, do you?
People will stare,
and think we're an angry couple fighting.
[whimsical music playing]
You made a friend? Won't you introduce me?
You're mistaken. She's a client.
- We're not close.
- Hi. He's wrong, we are friends.
[whimsical music continues]
[chuckles] Han is always funny.
His friend is my friend.
So, what'll it be?
- I'll have spareribs.
- Two.
Sure.
[Han Chieh sighs]
[music fades]
Who's she?
Hey, this is out of line.
- Isn't she underage?
- [intriguing music playing]
- He's helping me with my ghost.
- Oh, I need his help as well.
You eaten?
Not yet.
So, don't ask me anything
that puts me off my food.
[inhales]
I'm on a case.
What do I care?
Police can always use
the help of good citizens.
Who said I'm a good citizen?
Oh, you are. You're a very good citizen.
I'll buy you a milk tea.
I love milk tea.
Oh, you do?
I love it.
[chuckles softly] Ms. Lo, three milk teas.
[music ends]
Peeping Tom?
Mmm. We have four reports of a pervert
in the restroom of an internet café.
Nothing on cameras.
Could be a ghost.
- Why you need me?
- [officer] Mm-hmm.
HSIAO-MING LINGERS IN WOMEN'S ROOM
[comical music playing]
From the Crown Prince. I'll handle it.
- [officer] I'll go with you.
- No way. Police'll scare the ghost away.
- Then I'll go.
- No way.
You're too young.
It's okay. You can come.
[comical music continues]
[keyboard clacking]
- Hey! This is rude of you.
- [funky music playing]
Why are you looking at sights
like this in front of a girl?
It's not for you to see. It's for him.
If he sees the girls here,
it could lure him out.
That sounds a dumb idea.
You need to help with this.
You go and log on.
Bait the pervert.
- [women moaning over the computer]
- [whimsical music playing]
[moaning continues]
[music fades]
[Yeh Tzu] Mr. Han,
why do you want to be
the Crown Prince's agent?
Hey, I've told you the secret of my wig.
So you should tell me why.
For family.
Your family? Where are they?
In hell.
- [dramatic music playing]
- [Yeh Tzu] Huh?
[Han Chieh] When I was young,
I made a big mistake.
It got them killed.
So I decided to take my own life.
[screaming]
[music intensifies]
[groans]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[theme music playing]
You think jumping off a building
and dying will make everything fine?
Because of you, my assistant's dead,
and it's your fault.
Wh… Who was your assistant?
Your dad.
[music continues]
Your father was my assistant.
So what? What now?
My dad?
[nervously] Take my life.
I'll give my life in exchange.
Your lousy life
is worth less than the filthy rag
your father used to wipe the table.
You want to die? Not that easy.
[groaning]
[pulsing music playing]
[sobbing]
[coughing]
- Dad!
- [chain rattles]
Mom!
This is your so-called hell.
Your parents failed to teach you well,
so this is their punishment
on your behalf,
until you atone for all their sins.
It was my mistake.
Let them go.
Take me instead.
That won't work. I can't make an exchange.
But perhaps we can negotiate,
so it's more comfortable
for them there, hmm?
[breathing heavily]
I'll do anything you want. Anything.
I'll do anything. Anything.
Who are you?
[theme music playing]
You've forgotten me?
I'm the handsome guy
you've burned incense for… [chuckles]
…since you were little.
[theme music continues]
You're the…
…Crown Prince?
So kid, you caused your father to die.
So starting today,
you must repay his debt to me.
And be prepared.
This debt… is very heavy.
FIRE-TIPPED SPEAR
QIANKUN HOOP
RED ARMILLARY SASH
NINE DRAGONS DIVINE FIRE BARRIER
QIANKUN HOOP
He said that I must use up
3,600 of these pogs,
and my debt would be cleared,
and my parents can reincarnate.
It was ten years ago.
It will be finally over soon.
You communicate with
the Crown Prince through that bird,
and then you beat up whoever he says?
That's kind of it.
Like religious scammers
or ghosts who hurt people.
It's not a nice story.
Get to work now. Turn on the computer.
Okay.
So you beat people up?
I thought it was only ghosts.
People are good and bad.
Ghosts are no different.
Whether they're humans or ghosts,
I try to reason with them. And if I can't…
I will beat 'em up.
Wouldn't gods rather use love?
The Crown Prince
gave me these to fight with,
not for loving.
[tense music playing]
You stop that.
I don't want to use these on you.
Use what?
You can hear me.
I'm talking to you.
I'm listening.
You see me. Wow!
[screams]
[groans] Fuck, my glasses!
[Han Chieh] You've got a beating coming.
Just wait!
[grunts] You leave me no choice.
Ninjutsu Third Gear. [inhaling]
[upbeat electronic music playing]
[struggling]
- [music stops]
- [deflating and yelping]
[rhythmic music playing]
Ooh!
Take that.
[screams]
[music stops]
[all clamoring]
[static buzzing]
[eerie music playing]
[music intensifies]
Mr. Han!
[music stops]
Jesus.
Wait a second.
Don't laugh. Um… [struggles] I was--
[comical music playing]
You're Wang Hsiao-ming.
You're who?
I don't know you. I didn't offend you.
You didn't offend me.
You're hiding in the restroom.
A peeping Tom.
Ugh. You're so sleazy.
I'll never be able
to use a restroom again.
Right. I'm a pervert.
What were you expecting?
That I'd help old ladies cross the road?
- [groans]
- [music stops]
I don't care if you're a pervert.
The gig's up.
I'll give you two choices.
First, you behave.
- Return to the underworld.
- Or?
Or I'll beat you senseless.
My life was meaningless,
and now my death is meaningless too.
Fine. Do it.
Mister, kill me quick.
Get me to dissipate.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, do it, okay? Okay? [groaning]
[comical music continues]
Hold on, hold on! Wait. Just wait. Stop.
Mister, do you think
there's a quicker way than this?
I'll be in pain if I use a pog.
- So just take it--
- Hey, hey. Wait on! Wait on!
Wait! Wait!
I'll… I'll do what you want.
- Hey! No, no!
- [music stops]
Mr. Han! He said
he'll do what you want, okay?
[whimpers]
Where should I go now then?
Not my problem.
You find a place and wait
for the Underworld Messenger.
How long for?
[Han Chieh] How would I know?
A few days or maybe years.
[wind blowing]
- [sobbing]
- [sad guitar playing]
You want me to stay in some dark
place for how many years?
I want Internet.
I want anime. I wanna watch porn.
I wanna have fun.
- [funky music plays]
- One time, I almost won a billion dollars.
Mmm, yeah! Fuck.
- [sobs]
- Why did you kill yourself?
You had a good life.
Hsiao-jou dumped me.
I took it hard, so…
You are a ghost now.
Why not date female ghosts?
I'm not handsome, so they don't want me.
- I know one who could be interested.
- Hey, don't say that.
Instead of her bothering my dad,
why don't I introduce them?
It's a win-win for everyone.
She's hot, right?
She is. Quite a good figure, actually.
- Oh, perfect--
- All right. We're going home.
I don't want to go yet.
I want to find my dad
and deal with that ghost.
I told you. There's no smell. It's a fake.
- [funky music playing]
- Hsiao-ming, come with me.
- I'll introduce you.
- Okay. Let's go.
Hey, excuse me.
Could you pull me out, please?
I'm a little stuck here.
Look, I have work to do.
Then if he can't come with me,
I'll do it alone.
Hey. Hey, is she your girlfriend?
Isn't she underage?
Hey, hey. Wait, wait, wait. No, no, no!
[music ends]
[chirping]
[moans]
- Come here.
- [chirping]
Listen to me.
Mr. Han's actually a very nice man.
Why don't you act more like he does,
and maybe then, girls will like you?
Um, excuse me.
Can I ask,
what's your secret with the ladies?
Why would a ghost need to know?
Shut up and behave.
- [laughter]
- [Yeh Tzu] Hey, there's my dad.
Is that the ghost for me?
That's no ghost, only a woman.
We're done. Let's go.
No, wait.
I want to see what my dad's up to.
What can you do?
This is your parents' business.
I want to see who that woman is.
[Hsiao-ming clears throat]
[eerie music plays]
[tense music playing]
[both giggle]
- [doorbell rings]
- Hey, the wine.
[both chuckle]
- [woman] Hey, I ordered two bottles.
- Okay.
[tense music continues]
You and her should talk. I'll get going.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[automated voice] Door closing.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
Strange, it's here again.
[Hsiao-ming breathes heavily]
Hey, Han Chieh.
Who are those ghosts with her?
[Han Chieh] Yeh Tzu got it wrong.
Her mother placed the red packet,
but the target isn't her father.
It's this woman.
The two packets have no smell.
This one's very clever.
Oh. Hey, what smell? What smell?
[music continues]
[blowing]
[music turns intriguing]
[Han Chieh] Why did Master Ho
send you both here?
[music fades]
I can free you guys.
- You know Chen Chi-sha, he was--
- [growls]
[car alarms blaring]
[continues growling]
[action music playing]
[screams]
Come out of there!
[action music continues]
- [music stops]
- [groaning]
[car alarms continue blaring]
- [growls]
- [Han Chieh struggling]
[pulsing music playing]
[engine revving]
[music stops abruptly]
[theme music playing]
[music continues]
[music ends]