The final location is Golden Lake Plaza.
One last step
and you'll make the headlines tomorrow.
GOLDEN LAKE PLAZA
Fuck you, Wu Tien-chi.
Yu-ching, Daddy's coming for you.
Wang Cheng-nan!
Stay away from me! Stay away.
Okay.
-Stay away from me.
-Calm down.
Don't do anything stupid. Come down.
I'm sick of this corrupt world.
The cops are useless fools too.
I only need to jump.
It'll go viral online and the police
will have to take her death seriously.
Listen, we don't know
if it's Wang Yu-ching yet.
We'll find the culprit soon.
There's still hope.
-Come down.
-Stay away from me.
I killed someone.
I killed that bastard.
-Chao, Wang Cheng-nan is going to jump.
-DNA confirms it wasn't Wang Yu-ching.
We've got a new lead on his daughter.
Stop him now.
Fuck you, Wu Tien-chi.
That guy isn't dead. He's in hospital.
You didn't kill anyone.
So don't do anything stupid.
You're all lying to me.
My daughter is dead.
I killed someone.
It's too late.
-Too late.
-Wang Cheng-nan!
I tried to kill myself once.
I wanted it all to be over.
But trust me.
You'll regret it afterwards.
I guarantee it.
Think about your daughter.
What will happen to her if you die?
-Yu-ching.
-Come down.
Wait!
She's alive! The DNA results are back.
It's not your daughter.
Don't jump.
Hey!
AGENT FROM ABOVE
THE DESCENT
-Call an ambulance!
-Abductee found. Send an ambulance.
-All units, abductee found.
-Get ready to clear a route.
Wang Yu-ching.
Wang Yu-ching!
The guy you stabbed
wasn't fatally wounded.
He's been moved out of ICU.
Hey. Wipe your hands.
Yu-ching.
I'm here now.
Wait a moment.
Here. Take this.
-Sister Lo.
-What?
You really won't leave?
I want to stay here. You should go.
Remember to eat properly. Got it?
-Try not to miss me too much.
-I'm sure I'll get by.
Sis.
You've been hiding from me for so long.
You finally came to see me?
I was staying away,
in the hope you'd forget about me
and move on.
I thought that with time,
you'd start to get over it.
But it's been two years
and you still can't let me go.
Stop being such a crybaby.
And stop repeating my name
each morning like it's a sutra.
It drives me nuts.
Are you kidding? I'll never forget you.
Idiot.
I was never the smartest kid.
Sis, I pray every day to the gods
to keep you safe and sound.
How can I rest in peace
never knowing if you're safe?
Do as Chieh says
and leave Dongfeng Market.
I can't just leave you here.
You're an earth-bound spirit.
You can't leave.
It's not like we just
became ghosts yesterday.
And the Third Crown Prince's
agent from above has our back.
He won't let anyone hurt us.
Will you come back and see me again?
If you promise me one thing.
What?
Get used to life without me.
And then get on with your life.
Don't think about me too much. Just…
Just every now and again.
If…
If fate permits it…
we'll meet here again.
Okay.
I'll leave tomorrow.
That was close.
Yeah, good thing we pulled him back.
Go ahead.
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, got it.
Fuck.
Some guy who'd lost all his money
jumped off a building
near the one Wang Cheng-nan was at.
-What was the time of death?
-Around an hour ago.
This is the deceased.
GENDER: MALE
The elevator's broken.
Am I really doomed?
-That bastard had a backup plan.
-Fuck.
The magic array is complete.
He's channeling the Demon King's spirit.
I finally made it up here.
The full moon is tomorrow.
The battlefield is Dongfeng Market.
Fuck. Is this Stranger Things?
Han Chieh.
-Everyone's left. Why haven't you?
-The ghosts are still here.
I got snacks for Hsiao-ming
and the grannies.
I'm going to get some weapons from Fu.
Go home.
Tonight's the showdown, isn't it?
Yes.
Can I tag along today?
Just during the daytime.
It's a free world. Do as you please.
There's somewhere I want to go.
Can you come with me?
After I got sick,
I started coming here to clear my head
and wish upon this tree.
It's become a ritual.
I always finish with a prayer.
All done.
-What did you wish for?
-World peace.
-You really think this works?
-I do.
The old guard told me
that magic can't overcome divine power,
divine power can't overcome karma
and karma can't overcome willpower.
So someone with a wish
is even stronger than Doctor Strange.
You really think a wish
can bring about world peace?
You never know.
My love for the world
is woven into that wish.
If it makes you happy.
Make a wish too.
-I don't want to.
-Just one.
Hey, just make one wish.
TAIPEI CITY POLICE DEPARTMENT
CENTRAL DISTRICT PRECINCT
Come on.
We need to be ready.
GOLDEN BRICK
FUCK YOU AND DIE DEMON KING
Han Chieh, will this really work?
Works with ghosts, why not demons?
Give me a hand. There's a lot to write.
GO BACK TO HELL
All done over there?
DONGFENG RULES
THIRD CROWN PRINCE'S
AGENT FROM ABOVE WAS HERE
INVINCIBLE THIRD CROWN PRINCE
DONGFENG RULES
CHIEH KICKS ASS
FUCK OFF BACK TO HELL
Fuck. Eight won't be enough.
Han Chieh.
It's almost time. You should go home.
Is there anything else I can do?
You can go home and take your meds.
That's all I ask of you.
Han Chieh.
You think the wishing tree is dumb.
Make a wish to the Third Crown Prince.
Wish for victory tonight.
Okay?
Whether he helps or not,
I'm not going to beg.
Also,
having hope
only hurts more after it's gone.
Old guard, what are you doing?
Why haven't you left yet?
This is my home. Why should I leave?
-Why are you staying?
The agent from above has to stay.
Perfect. I'm applying to be
Lord Guan's agent from above.
Have you met him?
He doesn't want you. Just drop it.
If the old guard's staying,
I'm not going either.
Stay out of this.
You have to go. Fighting is for men.
Fried chicken.
Spareribs.
Spring rolls. Fried chicken.
-I told you to wait at home, why--
-Spring rolls… Fried chicken.
Spareribs.
Spring rolls.
Fried chicken.
Spare--
I was getting takeout.
What am I doing here?
Chieh?
-Why am I back here?
-What's going on?
They grew a conscience and came back?
No, they've been possessed.
Must be Wu Tien-chi's doing.
What's the bastard up to?
Should everyone leave or go home?
It's getting dark.
Come up, all of you.
Go to Dongfeng Market.
Say hello to Han Chieh for me.
This time,
no one can stop me
from getting my demonic power back.
DONGFENG RESIDENTS ONLY
Watch the steps.
-Have some water.
-Here.
Chieh.
What's going on out there?
Are they coming?
They should be here soon.
He's waiting for the moon to rise.
Old guard, this will last all night.
Can you make it through?
Hey, I've got your back.
I'll hold on as long as it takes.
-Got a kitchen knife?
-What for? Killing ghosts?
Yes.
I only have a few milk caps left.
I have to save them for the Demon King.
Get the talismans I gave you before.
Putting them on weapons will help.
Leafy, Sister Lo, Mei-na.
Get everyone's keys.
Get any supplies that we can use.
Prepare for battle!
We're going into battle.
What's with the idols and blankets?
Han Chieh!
Something's gotten in.
-What gun is that?
-The gun of kindness.
Kindness, my ass. Our guns and bullets
have been blessed by Lord Guan.
Fu taught us.
Why aren't you using your milk caps?
I wish I could.
Get lost.
Why are they leaving?
-They're gone.
-What's going on?
Ms. Wang. Open the door.
Open the door.
Wu Tien-chi's coming.
Get in there and protect them.
-Good thing Fu taught us this.
-And Chieh opened my third eye.
Chieh, my heart's about to give out.
This is freaking terrifying.
Where's Leafy?
Where is she?
Protect them.
Have you seen Leafy?
Isn't she with you?
First floor.
Let's get inside.
Wu Tien-chi.
Not so fast.
You think those female ghosts
appeared in her home
because her mom went to see
some lame feng shui master?
Hi, Master Han. I'm Leafy.
Someone put this under my dad's pillow.
A female ghost enchanted him.
She has always been
a pawn the Demon King placed beside you.
I sent those ghosts
to her home every night
to blow demonic energy
into her body.
And refine her liver
into my demonic liver.
It's been a while, little punk.
You've matured since our last encounter.
My punches hit harder now too.
Wanna find out for yourself?
Compared to the other agents
I've fought in the past,
the feel of your fist on my face
is so much more…
satisfying.
Cut the bullshit.
You sucked Chen Chi-sha dry
and used Leafy to refine a liver
to cultivate a new assistant,
Wu Tien-chi, right?
Wu Tien-chi?
He's evil enough,
but doesn't have the talent.
Surely a demonic liver
would be wasted on someone like him.
I want you to have it.
Me?
You're younger than Chen Chi-sha
and stronger than Wu Tien-chi.
Why not you?
I'm so jealous of the Third Crown Prince.
How did he find such a great assistant?
Come work for me.
I'll treat you better
than the Third Crown Prince does.
You can have anything you want.
You can kill whoever you want.
I prefer messing with scum like you.
Like I prefer scraping shit off my shoe.
So you only fight bad guys, right?
Hang on.
You got your whole family killed.
You're just as much of a bad guy.
That's why I'm
fucking slaving away for him.
You know,
if you accept this demonic liver,
you will gain immense demonic power,
and finally be rid
of the Third Crown Prince.
You can become my agent
and conquer all three realms with me.
Fuck you. I'm not interested.
Do you think you have a choice?
It's too late.
The demonic liver has fully grown.
It could burst out of her body
at any moment and rip her to pieces.
Do you want her
to suffer such a tragic death?
I'll trade livers,
but only on two conditions.
Spare all the humans and ghosts here.
And two.
Give her my liver.
She must live.
But she's already doomed to die.
Didn't you know?
What do you mean?
Her leukemia has spread.
All this time,
only the power of the demonic liver
has been keeping her alive.
She didn't tell you?
After I got sick,
I started coming here to clear my head.
You really think a wish
can bring about world peace?
You never know.
Han Chieh, smile.
My love for the world
is woven into that wish.
Every extra day is worth it.
Okay, I'll do it.
But you must give her my liver.
I have to know she's still alive
before I accept your demonic liver.
I've killed so many people,
but this is my first time saving one.
Once you're working for me,
don't ever talk to me like that again.