Fuck.s
Fuck me. You caught two?
Sir, want to buy a lottery ticket?
Do I look lucky to you?
I haven't caught a thing.
Ask someone else.
Might as well buy one.
Your luck could change.
See my face?
Look lucky to you?
Meeting me was lucky.
I have a powerful amulet.
Guarantee it'll turn your luck around.
Keep it for yourself.
Don't believe me?
How about this?
If it doesn't work, you'll be doing me
a favor taking it off my hands.
But if it does,
come work for me.
The hell you talking about?
AGENT FROM ABOVE
A LIFETIME OF LUCK
-The demon's coming.
-No riding in the corridor.
Wang Hsiao-ming!
-You're supposed to be the adult here.
-He started it, not me.
It's all your fault.
You still at it?
The demon's coming.
-I'm going.
-Take care.
Old guard. Delivery.
Thank you.
FEITI TEMPLE
Brother Yu, Silly Chiang is back.
Brother Yu. Look.
I'm telling you,
I'm on such a roll. It's like I'm blessed.
This lucky amulet
is bringing you good luck.
Bro, what else can I do now I'm so lucky?
Chiang.
With such good luck,
you should be asking what can't you do?
Right. I'll get going then.
DONGFENG MARKET
I told you to hide it properly.
Who's to blame now it's been stolen?
Damn, it must be Wu Tien-chi.
He sent someone to steal it
as soon as we found it.
What does that prove?
He's desperate.
Of course he's desperate.
Did you find the thief yet?
Su Chih-chiang, aka Silly Chiang.
Prior convictions for gambling and theft.
Silly enough to leave fingerprints
when he's got a record.
Got an address?
I checked the surveillance footage.
He always comes here.
He loves to gamble.
Yes, I won again.
Look.
I'm winning big time.
-Why does he always win?
-Look.
It can't be down to luck.
Either he's cheating
or he's running some kind of scam.
Chao says they're already outside.
All the exits are blocked.
Let's get him.
It's the jackpot… It's gonna be mine…
I got it! Look.
-I hit it big!
-Look, incredible!
-Police.
-Scram!
Fuck.
Trying to run?
Out of the way!
-Stop!
-What the heck?
I'm sorry.
Come catch me!
You got a death wish?
-Where are you going?
-Let go.
-Where's the incense burner?
Serves you right.
Get up…
Where did you go? Where's Chao?
Not here. I sent the wrong address.
He really tore me a new one.
-Fuck.
-Damn it, how are we this unlucky?
-The stars are against us.
-Or Mercury in retrograde.
-So what should we do?
-Eat some lucky pork noodles.
WANG YU-CHING:
I'M ALMOST THERE
LET'S GRAB A SNACK
-Hello?
-Mr. Wang.
You're the guy from last time.
You let that thug Hsieh Kun-hao get away.
The police let him go.
They said he has nothing to do
with her disappearance
Why would you believe them?
They never took this case seriously.
Your daughter is outside Water Gate No. 7.
Go now.
Or it'll be too late.
-You reported it?
-Yes.
The body's over there.
Thanks.
Chang Min,
this is the info we have so far.
Chao.
Jane Doe, about the same age
as Wang Yu-ching.
But there's no head.
We'll need the DNA analysis to know more.
-Stop! This is a crime scene.
-Sir! What are you doing?
-Fuck.
-Hey, stop him.
Mr. Wang.
-Mr. Wang.
-Is it Ching?
-She's the same age.
-Tell me. Is it her?
-But it might not be her.
-Calm down, Mr. Wang.
Calm down.
-Is it her?
-We don't know for sure.
Mr. Wang, calm down first.
What use are the police?
Aren't you supposed to catch the bad guys?
Aren't you supposed to
bring criminals to justice?
You useless piece of shit!
You're all useless!
My daughter's dead because of you.
She's dead because of you.
I'm going to kill him.
Damn it. It's all your fault.
It's all your fault.
I'm going to kill him!
Boss, I got the incense burner.
What should I do next?
Look after it for me.
Don't let Han Chieh find it.
Okay, got it.
Also…
You could…
Stir things up at Dongfeng Market.
Keep Han Chieh busy for me.
No problem. That's my area of expertise.
Hi, Little Leafy. We meet again.
-Waiting for Chieh?
-Yeah.
He seems in a pretty bad mood today.
I don't dare go upstairs.
Oh please, he just likes to act all moody.
He's a big softie really.
I used to have a psychopathic sugar daddy
who'd beat me for no reason.
I couldn't take it,
so I tried to leave him.
But that psychopath wouldn't let me go.
Chieh helped me deal with him in the end.
Why aren't you together?
Things are pretty chill
between us right now. It suits us both.
Is that a wig you're wearing?
Yeah.
From the chemo.
In all the years I've known Chieh,
I've only ever seen him fall for one girl.
She was sick like you.
Huh?
She was terminally ill.
You know,
Chieh tried to take his own life.
She didn't have much time left.
They both lost hope in life,
yet still wanted something to hold onto.
Chieh stayed with her
until her time was up.
Since then, he's never gotten
seriously involved with another girl.
He'd rather pay for it.
It keeps things simpler.
Wow, look.
Incredible…
Come on, to us. Cheers.
A TV, air-con, deck chairs.
I even got a coconut tree for you.
This isn't hell. It's basically a resort.
Kid, you've worked hard
to rack up merit with me over the years.
But you never use it on yourself.
I find that interesting.
I owe them this.
Besides, the Demon King's new agent
is tough.
I'll probably settle down here soon too.
Settle down, my ass.
I want you all in on this.
I didn't choose you
for being young and a good fighter.
Then why did you choose me?
Take a guess.
Han Chieh.
Why are you here again?
Mei-na and I are eating with Sister Lo,
then I'm playing games with the old guard.
-You're keeping busy.
-Yep.
Everything all right? How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
You're the one acting all weird and moody.
I don't even dare feed Javvy,
in case I annoy you.
I've got so much going on.
It's driving me nuts.
What?
Han Chieh.
If I get a boyfriend someday,
I hope he's just like you.
And I thought you were just an idiot.
Turns out you're an idiot with bad taste.
Chieh! Someone's causing trouble.
Go and help the old guard.
How dare you touch my stuff?
I'll kick your ass!
Chieh, these hooligans
want to have a barbecue on the rooftop.
They even demanded
that you have a drink with them.
-I…
-Old guard!
I…
A barbecue upstairs?
FEITI TEMPLE
You have to defeat me first.
You're Han Chieh, right?
What've you done to piss off the big man?
The big man?
I don't usually piss off any big men,
just scumbags down below.
Finish him.
Wang Hsiao-ming!
-What?
-What are you doing?
What the fuck? Are you blind?
-What? It wasn't me.
-Fuck you.
Granny said this is our turf
and I should scare them off.
-She'll take responsibility.
-How?
I'll get back to it.
Not again!
Damn you.
-Old guard.
-Little punk.
What the hell? Fuck.
-What the hell?
-Kill him!
Charge!
-Naughty boys.
-Dare show up here?
Don't run. Come here.
I'm going to kill you.
Enough… Stop hitting me…
Take this! And this!
I've got you. Can't run now.
-Just you try.
-You won't get away.
What do you want?
Who sent you here?
Are you stupid?
I wouldn't tell you even if I knew.
What an embarrassment.
Let's go!
Come on.
Get lost!
-Look at them run.
-Don't you dare come back.
-What? Haven't you done enough fighting?
-There's another one, one more.
Haven't you taken enough?
Okay… Right away…
Hurry up.
What happened?
Some troublemakers turned up.
Why are you here?
We found a Jane Doe this morning.
Age and appearance match Wang Yu-ching.
Is it her?
Not sure yet.
We're waiting for the DNA report.
But if it is her, then the final sacrifice
for the array must be someone else.
The full moon is in three days.
What should we do?
-One more.
-Think they can mess with us? No chance.
Humans and ghosts
are united in Dongfeng Market.
We sent those punks packing in no time.
The magic array was complete,
but he was waiting
for midnight
when the moon is at its height.
Only then could he regain his full power
through the array portal.
Where's the portal?
At the center of the array,
Dongfeng Market.
-The other side…
-The other side? Okay…
Better not think of coming back
while we're here.
-Harder.
-The back too…
The back.
-Harder.
-That's it, squeeze…
Everyone.
I wanted to tell you individually,
but since you're all here,
I may as well tell you all.
A demon is coming for me
and coming for Dongfeng Market.
For everyone's safety, I want you
to leave Dongfeng Market for a while.
I'll stay and protect
the ghosts who can't leave.
You want us to go
and leave you here all by yourself?
I'm the Third Crown Prince's agent.
I have to stay.
If I defeat him,
you can all come back.
But even if I lose,
there's no need to worry.
Another agent will handle it.
Han Chieh.
-Wait…
-What should we do?
-This is our home.
-We can't leave.
-Where can we go?
-He wants us gone.
I'm not going anywhere.
-I'll die without the internet.
-Aren't you already dead?
CORPSELORDS WILL RISE
AND ATTACK AT FULL MOON
What?
You've really upset them this time.
What would your parents think
if they knew?
My parents?
They're in hell because of me.
I'm still atoning for my sins.
It's been over ten years.
The more it hurts after completing a task,
the better I feel.
At least I can sleep.
Do you think my dad was a bad judge?
Sure. Based on the verdict
in Wu Tien-chi's trial, he probably was.
But that isn't the way I remember him.
He took his job seriously
and handled every case with care.
He demanded perfection from himself.
But judges are human, not gods.
He buckled under the pressure
and gave Wu Tien-chi a light sentence.
He couldn't forgive himself
and carried that guilt for years.
He couldn't take it anymore
and committed suicide.
How much do you think
people should pay for their mistakes?
My dad handed out sentences all his life.
Finally, he sentenced himself to death.
It pains me to think
he treated himself that way.
I'm sure your parents are the same.
Must tear them apart seeing you like this.
Time to forgive yourself.
You've suffered enough, haven't you?
Mr. Wang.
You finally agreed to see me.
Mr. Wang, I'm so sorry.
Your daughter didn't make it.
There's really nothing
I can do for you anymore.
I will make the killer pay for this.
I don't trust the police.
I'm going to put this on social media.
Then what?
All anyone cares about is gossip,
rumor and scandal.
What happened to you
would blow over in two days.
A week tops.
Then what?
I won't allow it.
My daughter's death can't go unpunished
like this. I won't allow it.
I know exactly how you feel. I do.
There is something you can do.
I didn't want to tell you
because it's extreme
and could cost lives.
What do you say?
TAIPEI CITY POLICE DEPARTMENT
CENTRAL DISTRICT PRECINCT
Come in and have a seat.
What's up?
The owner's factory caught fire,
killing two workers.
-I'll leave you to it.
-Hey.
You're coming too. Come on, inside.
Officer, it was an accident.
Nothing I could do about it.
The fuck… How was this an accident?
Just how much flammable material
was in your illegal factory?
The workers reeked of gasoline.
Nothing to do with you?
I won! I made a fortune!
When was your last inspection?
We've never had one.
-So, you fucking bribe the inspectors?
-I do not.
How dare you? I just worship the gods.
Who do you worship?
What's that thing you keep touching?
A lucky amulet from Feiti Temple.
I heard they're very effective.
I especially went to request one.
That's not against the law, is it?
This isn't a lucky amulet. It's a curse.
Sorcery like this gives someone
a lifetime of luck,
but within a tiny period of time.
I've not seen one before.
Back when illegal gambling was the craze,
this kind of sorcery was super popular.
While your luck's in, you're on a roll.
Practically invincible.
But once it runs out, you lose everything.
-Really?
-Yep.
So that boss lady used up all her luck,
then her factory burned down
and two workers died.
How did she get the lucky amulet?
She said she requested it
from Feiti Temple.
You're Han Chieh, right?
What've you done to piss off the big man?
FEITI TEMPLE
Those troublemakers
in Dongfeng Market were from there.
I guess Wu Tien-chi sent them,
just like he sent Su Chih-chiang.
Maybe we can find some clues there.
But we've got no evidence
to apply for a search warrant.
I can't show the judge this amulet
and say it's illegal.
And we can only charge
Su Chih-chiang with burglary.
He's so lucky, we'll never catch him.
Hey.
You lose your cool
at the slightest setback.
You need a strong mindset
to overcome bad luck.
Got it?
Listen, I'll tell you
how to reverse your luck in one word.
Resilience.
-Utter bullshit.
-Hey.
You've got to have patience.
Be patient, got it?
Fuck.
Fuck. What the heck?
Young man, need a ride?
Of course.
Why's my luck turned to shit?
Watch what you're doing.
Don't break my car.
FARE: $435
FARE: $440
Bro, I can't find my wallet.
Uh… I'll withdraw some cash up ahead.
FARE: $480
STOP
Why'd you stop?
It's just a few hundred dollars.
Tell them that.
TAIPEI CITY POLICE DEPARTMENT
CENTRAL DISTRICT PRECINCT
Su Chih-chiang said Brother Yu, the head
of Feiti Temple, told him to steal it.
Seems Brother Yu's the one
working for Wu Tien-chi.
Let's go get him.
I'll go and make him talk.
See what he knows about Wu Tien-chi.
Give me half an hour.
You can show up then.
FEITI TEMPLE
-Hey, Chang Min.
-Cuffs.
-How many can you take on?
-Huh? What do you mean?
Are we going to fight?
Of course not.
Cops don't knowingly break the law.
They're just a bunch of punks.
But if any innocent citizens ask us for
help later, we have to stick up for them.
We're going to save them with this.
Love.
-Look at this chick.
-What's he doing here?
Why's he here? Stop him.
-What, me?
-I'll call for help.
-Where's Brother Yu?
-Fuck, what do you want?
-Hey, let him go!
-Let him go!
-Let him go.
-Ming, are you okay?
-Ming.
Stop that.
Fuck you.
Hey, get down.
-Fuck you!
-Get down.
Let's fight one-on-one!
-Get down!
-Get down, fuck!
-Fuck you, get down!
-Feiti?
What god is this? Never heard of him.
What the fuck?
Put it down.
Fuck, I said put it down.
-Get him down!
-Fuck.
Go get help.
Stay back.
-Where's the incense burner?
-Fuck you, it's inside.
I'll get it. Just let me go, okay?
Is Wang Yu-ching still alive?
Who? How would I know?
-Brother Yu!
-I'm over here!
Brother Yu, where are you?
Fuck.
-Fucking idiot!
-Sorry, Brother Yu.
Who called for help?
I did.
They're beating my bat with their hands
and attacking my fists with their faces.
Who is?
This guy.
He's using his stomach to kick my foot.
-Police!
-Freeze.
Freeze. Still trying to run?
-Hands behind your head, crouch down!
-Cuff them.
You're still moving.
Idiots. Look at the state of me. Fuck.
Fucker took on so many people.
Only an idiot wouldn't run.
Fuck.
FEITI TEMPLE
Go easy. What if I get hurt?
Cut the crap.
You let one guy beat you all?
Hsieh Kun-hao!
You killed Yu-ching, you bastard.
You deserve to die!
The police are incompetent.
It's up to me to punish you!
236 reporting. Perimeter searched,
nothing suspicious. Over.
You found it?
Yeah.
Any leads on Wang Yu-ching?
No.
836 calling. We've just received a report.
Wang Cheng-nan stabbed Hsieh Kun-hao.
Suspect at large near Golden Lake Plaza.
Repeat, Golden Lake Plaza.
Requesting assistance.
I'll be right over.
Fuck. Wu Tien-chi's been playing us.
-It was all a distraction.
-What do you mean?
The sacrificial offering
isn't Wang Yu-ching.
The final location on the magical array
is Golden Lake Plaza.
Fuck, it's Wang Cheng-nan.
He kidnapped Yu-ching
to torment Wang Cheng-nan.
A father's hatred and despair
will enhance the offering.
Have you heard
how she's being bullied at school?
I'm going to kill him.
I'm going to kill him!
There is something you can do.
It could cost lives.
But it will draw attention
to your daughter.
What do you say?
I…
I'm begging you.
Tell me what to do.
I'll do anything.
Yu-ching.
I killed him for you.
What are you waiting for, Mr. Wang?
This is the final step.
The media will love this.
One last step
and you'll make the headlines tomorrow.
GOLDEN LAKE PLAZA
Over there.
-Suspect on the rooftop, east side.
-Inform Chao now.
The elevator's broken.
Am I really doomed?
Chao, Wang Cheng-nan is going to jump.
Fuck you, Wu Tien-chi.
Yu-ching, Daddy's coming for you.