- [horns honking]
- [engine starts]
[upbeat electronic music playing]
[groaning]
[tires screeching]
RED ARMILLARY SASH
[music stops]
[dramatic music playing]
- [growl]
- [groaning]
[theme music playing]
[cries]
AGENT FROM ABOVE
KARMA
[exhales deeply]
You're both the ghosts
that Master Ho has been keeping.
[comical music playing]
Sorry about him. Does it hurt?
Let me tell you about myself.
I'm Hsiao-ming.
I'm also a ghost.
My main interests are anime
and comic books. [groans]
[music stops]
He controls you using a spell.
I can lift it and free you.
But first you must tell me
what Master Ho wants.
- His Majesty threatened Uncle Chi--
- [growls]
[heavy breathing]
Once His Majesty comes out, he'll eat you.
He will dig your heart out and eat it.
[tense music playing]
By His Majesty, you mean Vasavatti?
Chen Chi-sha is your uncle?
He will dig your heart out.
[laughing hysterically]
[tense music continues]
Huh?
[dramatic music playing]
The spell is gone.
Go now, both of you.
They're gone.
You want to chase them? Go ahead.
Um… They're both ghosts. I'll stay here.
- You're a ghost.
- Not like that.
I think their heads are not quite there.
I'll keep looking for the one.
DONGFENG MARKET
[singing] Life is full of partings
like Orion and Scor--
- I'm back.
- Oh, hey.
[Han Chieh] Mmm.
[male player] Pung.
Han.
Why'd you bring him?
Huh?
You see me? Wow!
- Oh!
- I've opened their third eye.
Everyone here sees you.
So be nice.
- Oh.
- Old man.
- I'll leave him to you.
- Mmm.
A good evening to you, sir.
- You're new here?
- I am.
- I'll give you a tour later.
- [Hsiao-ming] Great.
Hey, can I ask, do you have internet here?
[old man] Yes. Fiber optic.
- [tense music playing]
- [breathing heavily]
Why are you still here?
It's almost 11 p.m.
- Come inside.
- [heavy door opens and closes]
[Yeh Tzu] Mr. Han,
I had a talk with my father.
[groans]
[tense music continues]
He was crying. He asked me to forgive him.
He said he and my mother stopped
loving each other a long time ago.
And that they're planning
to get a divorce now.
[continues groaning]
[tense music intensifies]
Mr. Han?
What?
Don't come near me.
[tense music continues]
FENGYUAN TEMPLE
Dad!
Mom!
[poignant music playing]
[lighter clicking]
Your doing?
[exhales deeply]
Want to break your vow of abstinence?
What do you want?
[the Crown Price sighs]
Today, I'm here
to tell you some good news.
[poignant music continues]
I could tell you anything. [chuckles]
The lotto numbers?
[scoffs]
The girl you're worried about,
she will reincarnate.
Don't say I never help you.
You were there for her
through her terminal illness.
So this will be a good end for her.
You must let go, when the time comes.
[Han Chieh's ex] Promise me.
After I die,
you will live well, okay?
I will find you.
After you reincarnate.
[chuckles softly]
How will you possibly find me?
I won't remember you,
and you won't recognize me either.
I will find you.
[poignant music continues]
Why are you being nice to me?
[the Crown Price] Consider it
a gesture of goodwill.
Do your tasks well from now on.
[exhales]
Why are you still here?
You're awake now?
[exhales]
I said we were filming yesterday,
and I wouldn't be back.
Last night, what happened to you?
It's the side effect of my work.
You worked hard for the Crown Prince.
Why are there side effects
for using magical tools?
He keeps me alive,
so I may atone for my sins.
He is strict.
If I misbehave, I'm punished.
All right.
Where's that lousy geek?
- [urinating]
- [comical music playing]
- [old man] Hey.
- [gasps]
How did you sleep last night?
[sighs] Fuck.
Can't you knock?
- [breathes deeply]
- Hey!
This place looks good. But thin walls.
These are all modest houses
full of yin energy.
For ghosts like you,
the feng shui is perfect.
My computer desk would go well here.
And then my bed is one, two…
[chuckles]
I'll find time to clean it
and make the room nice.
[Hsiao-ming] Thanks so much.
Hey, I don't want a mattress
that's too soft, or old furniture.
- I'll text you about it later.
- [music ends]
My mother admitted
that she hired the feng shui master
to help save their marriage,
but she didn't know he'd hurt anyone.
How did she find him?
She was introduced by a friend.
They always met at a restaurant,
but she doesn't know his real name.
Han brings wandering ghosts like you
back here from time to time.
- Oh.
- Some leave after a while.
And some live here.
They become fond of the lifestyle.
Oh. Any females?
- [funky music playing]
- Behave yourself.
So, what are your plans for him?
He has nowhere to go.
There are rooms here.
He can take his pick.
There are many female ghosts.
If he is good, I'll introduce him.
Well that's much better
than beating him up.
He's an idiot, but not evil.
I'm not meant to kill every ghost.
I'm not a sadist.
Let's go.
[music ends]
[Yeh Tzu] What tasks do you have
for today, Mr. Han?
Which ghost are you planning to capture?
Why on earth did I bring you?
Because you're a good person.
You don't want me
locked up waiting to die.
You want me to enjoy life, don't you?
Stop talking about death.
And we're not here for fun.
Okay, sure thing.
[children yelling]
- [dad] Wow. Nice work, son.
- [mom] Come on.
Let's go home and eat. Did you have fun?
[intriguing music playing]
[Han Chieh] I temporarily opened
this family's third eye.
Tonight, I will deal with the ghosts
who are bothering them.
Both these ghosts have deep obsessions.
It's not going to be easy.
- [eerie music playing]
- [buzzing]
[music intensifies]
Son.
You hired a new master
to deal with us again?
[dad] Godmothers,
I want to talk to you both.
- [Han] These women don't have kids.
- This isn't the way to go.
They've treated this nephew
as their godson.
And he lets his son
call them god-grandmothers.
- [yelps]
- That's my boy!
[woman] Why are you learning English?
They couldn't bear to part
with the boy after they died
so they stayed in the Human Realm.
After a while,
their enthusiasm became overwhelming.
The couple started dreaming of them.
They kept giving instructions,
but they would argue between themselves.
They would fight each other
in the middle of the night.
The family couldn't stand it.
Didn't I teach you?
You can't line your bed up like that.
- Are you helping the boy?
- Why haven't you changed the direction?
- It's bad feng shui.
- Ladies.
[music stops]
The boy, he doesn't know who to listen to.
Me, of course. I'm the eldest--
Wrong. I was a teacher.
He should listen to me.
[water drips]
- Shouldn't a kid listen to his parents?
- Who says?
When we were little,
we had to listen to our grandparents.
We're his parents' parents.
Young parents have
their own ways these days.
You're depriving the boy of sleep.
Let him be a kid.
Ghosts can affect the lifespan of kids,
you know?
Please, I studied science.
Who would believe that?
- Sis.
- Hmm?
- We're already ghosts.
- Oh.
[eerie music playing]
I'm telling you,
if a ghost gets near my grandson,
I'll be the first one to chase it away.
I can understand why you feel this way.
Who are you, huh?
[growls in the background]
When adults are speaking,
how can you interrupt?
- Ill-mannered.
- Mmm. So rude.
- The type who doesn't give up their seat.
- Bad etiquette. Ill-mannered.
[music stops]
Please. I thank both of you.
[poignant music playing]
But this can't go on.
Feng is pregnant with our second child.
Hsiao-chi will start school soon.
Our family just want
to live an ordinary life.
[poignant music continues]
Thank you for everything you've done
for us. But this needs to end now.
[screaming excitedly]
- You're so dirty now, and you stink!
- Ooh, what smells?
Ooh, I love you, love you, love you.
[dad] Please leave us alone.
[eerie music playing]
[growls in the background]
Mr. Han, do you think it's fixed?
Stay close.
[elevator dings]
- Who told you to meddle in our business?
- [Han Chieh] Let's go.
[grandma 1 laughs]
You've made us homeless.
Where are you going?
[laughing]
[eerie music intensifies]
I thought we just came past here.
[Han Chieh] Fuck.
We're going around in circles.
- [intriguing music playing]
- [door opening]
[music stops]
You're so ruthless.
You actually kicked us out.
If we're not around,
who will take care of him?
You're both long dead.
[gasps] Sis, don't listen to him.
- Break his legs.
- Let's get him.
GOLDEN BRICK
[dramatic music playing]
[music intensifies]
[grandma 1 wails]
[grandma 2 yelps]
You already ruined our afterlife.
Now you even want to kill us?
Have you no respect for the elderly?
[music ends]
There are laws in the Human Realm
and in the Ghost Realm.
Don't you both know
these laws are to be obeyed?
No one told us. How are we meant to know?
Yes. That's why my boss wanted me
to have a talk with you.
But if you can't see reason…
then you'll never see the boy again.
- [grandma 2 sobbing]
- [sad music playing]
I died without fulfilling my wish.
It's so unfair!
[crying] My life is so hard.
Some people say
our ideas don't change when we die.
That's why it might not be
clear to you right now,
that what you're doing's
not good for the boy.
[sad music continues]
Ladies.
It can be difficult
to let go of earthly things.
But if you must, you must.
Anyone can talk big.
But you don't understand.
Let go of someone you love?
How can you say that?
[sad music continues]
I have an idea.
Why not find another godson?
Or god-grandson?
Another boy to love.
[grandma 2] You say it so casually,
like getting a pet.
Where can we get a god-grandson?
There's a guy that I know.
He's actually over 30, and quite childish.
Is he afraid of ghosts?
[comical music playing]
Um, Han Chieh, I don't understand.
Why does he look like that?
He looks weird.
Mr. Han, didn't you say
there are many kids in this building?
Why'd you pick a weirdo?
[Han Chieh] Don't judge him, ladies.
You may come to like him.
My neighbors may know other kids
who need your care.
Oh! As if!
If this is the only option, I don't think
I can be bothered. It's so messy in here.
- I don't like it. Why has no one cleaned--
- What's the deal here?
- Do me a favor. Be a good grandson.
- So dirty, and it stinks.
- Try to get on their good side.
- At least we have each other.
- [sighs]
- If you do, I'll buy you a computer.
[grandma 1] Hey, you.
Turn around. What's your name?
Honored to meet you.
I'm Wang Hsiao-ming.
What can I do for you? [chuckles]
[comical music continues]
[grandmas and Hsiao-ming chuckle]
[eerie music playing]
Boss, that's Chi-sha.
[man] He's playing mysterious.
Sir.
Last time our groups fought
many people were killed.
Alerting the police is not
in either of our interests.
You sure?
Currently, Mr. Liu wants to deal
with Heilung Hall.
Recommend you keep a low profile.
- [eerie music continues]
- [muffled groans]
Tell Mr. Liu
the next time he wants something
to come here himself.
[exhales deeply]
Boss, are you okay? Come on. Let's go.
- [man 2] Go, go, go!
- Let's get outta here.
[eerie music continues]
WUMENG OCCULTIST COLLUDES WITH GANGSTERS
WUMENG OCCULTIST REFINES MALICIOUS SPIRITS
DEMON KING OF THE SIXTH HEAVEN ENTICES MAN
His Majesty threatened Uncle Chi--
By His Majesty, you mean Vasavatti.
Chen Chi-sha is your uncle?
DRUNKARD DIED WITHOUT PEACE
AND SEEKS REVENGE
[doorbell buzzes]
[door closes]
The guy you asked me to investigate,
he's definitely a fake.
Yes, I've met him.
He's not that powerful.
The one behind the scenes is Chi-sha.
Chen Chi-sha?
You said he's big trouble.
He's a problem.
His master is even more terrifying.
Vasavatti.
Vasavatti is hell's demon king.
Five years ago now,
he bewitched Chi-sha to summon him back.
- [growls in the background]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[thunder cracking]
It's you.
Vasavatti.
What does Chi-sha want to do?
Since the Crown Prince defeated him,
Vasavatti has always been sealed in hell.
To return to the Human Realm,
a human must help summon him,
remove the seal, and become his agent.
[dramatic music playing]
[animalistic groaning]
The scent of the Human Realm.
I missed it.
[action music playing]
Do you know who I am?
You're the ugly one from below.
I want you to return.
[action music continues]
[thunder cracking]
[music intensifies]
[groans]
[screams demonically]
[demonically] If you delay me,
I'll bring you to hell.
[action music playing]
[groans painfully]
NINE DRAGONS DIVINE FIRE BARRIER
[Han Chieh battle cries]
[fire whooshes]
[sound fades]
[Chi-sha] You brat.
I shall not forget you.
[somber music playing]
[breathing heavily]
You got lucky this time.
But in this world, there will always
be people who will help Vasavatti.
- Next time--
- There won't be a next time.
[somber music continues]
At that time, he promised me he'd retire,
and never use
the Wumeng Maoshan Technique again.
But now he's secretly pulling new tricks.
If Vasavatti is returning,
I fear he'll give Chi-sha
more power this time.
[sighs]
[music fades]
Soon, I'll retire.
Are you trying to kill me?
[soft chirping]
Don't scare my bird like that.
This trouble with Vasavatti,
it wouldn't exist
if you had killed him back then.
- Huh?
- [traditional music plays]
Buddhist adherents
don't kill indiscriminately. Hmm.
[scoffs]
- I don't see anyone.
- [traditional music continues]
You have an untrained third eye.
- He's really here?
- No.
It's just a psychic connection.
He can't show his true form.
Oh. I'll leave you guys to chat.
- Hey, wait.
- Oh.
The police should know
about his workplace bullying,
the crazy long hours, no health insurance.
Complaints like that are for
the Ministry of Labor, not Police.
He's right. I really think
you should take your complaints elsewhere.
[chuckles] You should bear in mind
your tasks are not complete.
Before I replace you, Vasavatti wants
to invade this world again.
So I still need you.
Fuck you. Handle it yourself.
Oh, kid. That's why I have you.
I'm not up for this.
So hire another person then.
This guy's a policeman.
He's very capable,
and he has a good sense of justice.
- He's a perfect candidate.
- No, no. Not me.
And he's no fan at all.
He worships another.
[upbeat music playing]
Here. Worship the Crown Prince.
He's there.
Prove your devotion.
[gasps]
Like he said, I worship other gods,
and I could never really give up
my job as a police officer.
So, I doubt I'd be devoted enough.
[Crown Prince] Okay,
let's cut the crap.
Just sign the task.
You'll be glad you did.
No, I won't. That's it.
You scared of dying?
[scoffs]
Negative. I just don't like you.
[laughs] I like that.
It's what I expect
from my agent from above.
Naturally rebellious.
Don't blame me for not reminding you
when things become troublesome.
WUMENG OCCULTIST REFINES MALICIOUS SPIRITS
DEMON KING OF THE SIXTH HEAVEN ENTICES MAN
- [whistling]
- [eerie music playing]
[music intensifies]
You're back? It's been so hard on you.
[ghosts growl and shriek]
[man laughing]
Huh.
[eerie music continues]
Your curse, it's lifted.
It was Han.
Now calm down.
Let's play nice.
You used us to threaten our uncle.
Only if you die can uncle be free.
[man groans]
I envy Chi-sha.
He has two beautiful girls who love him.
He's so lucky.
Just a word of advice.
Humans must not be too emotional.
Ghosts as well.
[screams]
[groans]
[growls]
[suspenseful music playing]
[whispering]
[chuckling]
[eerie vocalizations]
[man] Now then,
you know what to do, right?
[sirens wailing in the distance]
[chanting in the background]
ASCENT TO HEAVEN
Mr. Liu asked, are you lost?
Do you need help?
Fuck!
[suspenseful music playing]
Fuck! What the hell?
[suspenseful music continues]
[music intensifies]
[ghost growls]
Han took the bait.
[ghost] Back then, Chi-sha
failed to summon me because of him,
the Third Crown Prince's agent from above.
Don't worry.
This time will be different.
I will not fail.
If this plan succeeds,
my demonic power will strengthen again.
And you can have whatever you want.
[theme music playing]
[music continues]
[music ends]