Finally.
I finally got my power back.
Once my demonic liver has fully grown,
I will be unstoppable!
AGENT FROM ABOVE
TURNING THE WHEEL
Han Chieh.
What's wrong?
Wu Tien-chi said
he put a demonic liver inside me.
It isn't inside you anymore.
Then why aren't I…
I gave you mine.
I'm the Third Crown Prince's agent.
I can't die.
One of the perks of the job.
The doctor said my cancer
has already spread.
I only have a few months left to live.
You shouldn't waste your energy on me.
I should've died over ten years ago.
Every extra day is a gift.
I got more than I deserved.
Han Chieh.
Can you win this time?
When I win,
We'll go back to the tree.
The Demon King has regained his power.
I'm going to find him.
-Take care of Leafy.
-I'll help you.
How? You don't stand a chance
against that thing.
I could at least
get a few rounds off at him.
Take care of the neighbors and Leafy.
I'm counting on you.
DONGFENG MARKET
You're really something else,
you little punk.
Still standing
even without a liver.
Once you get the demonic liver,
physical pain like this
will be a distant memory.
When that happens,
I doubt I'll still be human.
I'm warning you.
If you don't let the others go,
I won't let you put that liver inside me.
You never planned on letting me
do it, did you?
Nine Dragons Divine Fire Barrier.
Same old trick again?
Spit it out!
Fuck you.
I know I don't have much choice.
But I don't think I'd win.
I want you all in on this.
I didn't choose you
for being young and a good fighter.
Why did you choose me?
You can save those innocent people.
It's all up to you.
When I win,
we'll make your wish come true.
How many have you hidden?
I swallowed one just now.
Got four in my stomach.
See for yourself
how many dragons are inside me.
I can't beat you,
but I can destroy the demonic liver.
You really don't know what's good for you.
You'd rather burn to death
than be my agent.
I'll ask you one last time.
Will you
be my agent?
Or would you rather have
everyone here die along with you?
Fall back. Now.
Fuck! I'm one of you!
The golden spells aren't working anymore.
They're about to get in.
It's okay.
They're everywhere.
Hang in there, everyone!
Who are you?
-I've never seen you before.
-Yeah, who are you?
-It's Leafy.
-The red ghost!
Leafy!
Stop her! She's lifting the spell!
Sis Lo! Get the golden ink!
Move!
Go find Han Chieh!
Release him!
Was it you, weakling,
who killed my hellspawn?
You're in over your head.
You decided to show up, little punk.
I thought you hated
these lousy sacks of skin?
What? Feeling desperate?
Demon King.
How many times have I told you?
You eat like a filthy pig. It's gross.
Can't kill you on an empty stomach!
All these years, I've been imagining
how I'm gonna chop off your arms,
break your legs,
tear you to pieces
and finally get my vengeance.
Fine.
So when are we going to screw
those heavenly rules
and have a proper fight
using our true forms?
Soon.
When I've devoured
every soul in the Human Realm,
I'll become more powerful than the gods
and rule over heaven, earth and hell.
Not in this lifetime.
Damn it.
Wu Tien-chi's body is too weak.
Otherwise, I'd easily defeat you.
You're complaining
about using a human body.
Then why not use your true form?
If I use my true form,
your agent from above will die.
Could you live with that?
Demon King,
you're on the verge of defeat.
So you want to provoke me
into using my true form
and violating the heavenly rule?
I've already committed countless sins.
But you're different.
Violate the heavenly rule
and you'll be in deep trouble.
You're too rebellious.
The gods will make you pay.
Hey.
Who do you think
channeled my spirit down here?
The gods think I'm rebellious?
That's just for show.
In private, they actually adore me.
You gods are all hypocrites.
Trying to play good cop, bad cop with me.
The righteous path is hard to walk.
So the gods
must be even more ruthless than demons.
You little punk.
Your agent from above
may be one in a million,
but there are far more evil people
than good in the Human Realm.
Cut the crap.
Sooner or later I will defeat you,
Third Crown Prince.
You're a lousy fighter,
but a pretty good escape artist.
Please, have mercy on me.
Give me a chance.
I… I will mend my ways.
I will do your bidding.
I… I'll help you…
You've been
a real pain in my ass recently.
You know all those privileges
the Demon King promised you in hell?
I've taken care of them for you.
They're all gone.
You must know what you deserve.
Do me a favor.
Jump.
I can't go to hell, wait.
I can't go to hell.
Third Crown Prince, I beg you.
Give me another chance.
Give me another chance. I beg you.
Please, I really can't go to hell now.
The gods have already
given you so many chances.
But you always choose the most evil path.
You brought this on yourself.
I can't help you.
Han Chieh is a sinner.
But he spent over ten years
atoning for his sins.
He's even willing
to sacrifice himself to save others.
What about you?
Bad boy.
Humans should deal with their own affairs.
This old man again?
Unsanctioned revenge
gets you punishment down there too.
COMMAND
A Black Command Token?
Sorry. It's all above board.
The gods have already
given you so many chances.
You brought this on yourself.
You're Wu Meng-hsueh?
PURE EVIL
You are…
I'm Ox Head.
Ox Head? Then this must be…
Quit with the fucking questions.
Can't you see this is hell?
You'd better behave.
With your record,
you'll be here for hundreds of years.
Han Chieh.
Han Chieh!
Am I dead?
Kid.
Let me show you something.
Where are my parents?
Were they reborn?
They stepped on the Wheel of Life
and were reborn
when you agreed to become my agent.
What?
What you saw down here was an illusion.
I deceived you.
So they didn't suffer in hell
because of me?
You're the one who suffered.
Chieh, we're about to be reincarnated.
We won't remember you
after we drink the Soup of Oblivion,
so this is our only chance to say goodbye.
We worry about you
and we're going to miss you.
We don't want you blaming yourself
and suffering needlessly.
Chieh, let bygones be bygones.
I want you to know
that even if I don't remember you
in the next life,
you'll always be our beloved son.
Always.
Remember that.
Your parents
may not have raised you properly,
but they didn't deserve
punishment in hell.
So right from the start,
I helped them be reborn.
But as you know,
that required pulling some strings.
There's a price to pay.
Your hard work these past years
served as repayment for your initial debt.
Congratulations.
Initial debt?
How much more do I owe you?
Life and death are predestined.
This girl is terminally ill.
Not even I can prolong her life.
I can't save her.
But you saved me.
You were determined to die back then.
I just made the most of it.
Not everyone can become an agent
to pay off their debts.
However…
I can give her a new liver.
Because her suffering
is the Demon King's doing.
This golden liver can relieve the pain
caused by her illness,
but it can't cure her or extend her life.
How long she has left is down to fate.
So she might not survive
even with this new liver?
There's a price to pay for this too.
MILK CAPS
THIRD CROWN PRINCE'S AGENT
IN THE HUMAN REALM
What's that?
Contract renewal.
As I said,
you owe me more than that initial debt.
I, HAN CHIEH, AM WILLING
TO RENEW THE CONTRACT
AND BE THE THIRD CROWN PRINCE'S AGENT
IN THE HUMAN REALM
This golden liver is included in the deal.
Final offer. Take it or leave it.
I'll sign.
HAN CHIEH
THIRD CROWN PRINCE'S AGENT
IN THE HUMAN REALM
Remember.
Fumigate it with incense every day.
After 49 days,
Javvy will hatch.
Before that happens,
consider yourself on an extended vacation.
Damn, am I nice or what?
Third Crown Prince.
There's one thing I don't get.
Why me?
You had so many better options.
Why give me a second chance?
FENGYUAN TEMPLE,
MARSHAL OF THE CENTRAL ALTAR
You might not know it,
but I've always been by your side.
When you were little,
you loved riding bikes.
You'd cycle around in front of me all day.
-Chieh, why won't you listen?
-Stop running.
The first time you defied your parents
was when you tried to keep a stray cat.
-Listen!
-I want to keep it!
Don't yell at him like that.
You got your way that time.
Hey!
Let's go.
Your first fight
was defending a classmate from bullies.
FENGYUAN TEMPLE
And on that day that haunts you,
I was there too.
I watched you grow up.
I know the real you.
Even though
you went astray and made mistakes,
you never shirked responsibility.
Who could possibly deserve
a second chance more than you?
Do your best. I'm watching.
QIANKUN HOOP
FIRE-TIPPED SPEAR
GOLDEN BRICK
RED ARMILLARY SASH
LEOPARD-SKIN POUCH
WIND FIRE WHEELS
NINE DRAGONS DIVINE FIRE BARRIER
DONGFENG MARKET
Han Chieh, here's the lighter you wanted.
Any regrets?
For what?
Renewing your contract.
In the end, Leafy…
No regrets.
It was a good deal.
At least she was happy
for those last few months.
FROM: LEAFY
TO: HAN CHIEH
How are you doing, Han Chieh?
I'll already be gone
by the time you read this.
This is the last time I'll write so much,
so bear with me here
and read until the end.
After I got sick, I often thought
that I should do something
to give my life meaning.
Confused and lost, I went to
Dongfeng Market for the first time.
I met you and everyone else.
There, I realized that death
is just another form of existence,
so I stopped being afraid.
A new friend? Won't you introduce us?
I felt so much love in my final moments.
It was the happiest time of my life.
GET WELL SOON!
LEAFY, GET WELL SOON!
LET'S GO ABROAD AGAIN!
Han Chieh, I didn't have time
to do all the things I wanted.
I want someone to do them for me.
Please play some video games
with the old guard for me.
Please be kinder to yourself.
And lastly, I have one small favor to ask.
Please love this world for me
with all your heart.
Even if it can be chaotic
and the gods
don't seem to do anything about it.
I believe what really changes the world
is the hopes and dreams
of ordinary people like us.
I did good, right?
IN LOVING MEMORY OF MY LATE FATHER
CHANG HO-CHENG
-Self-draw.
-A White Dragon? Wow.
Come and have some food.
-Good thing I didn't discard mine earlier.
-You should've done. Why keep it?
You're pretty good at this.
Third Crown Prince,
please watch over my son.
Bless him with success at work
and with good health.
Hear my prayer.
Han Chieh.
Would you believe it
if I said there really was world peace?
WORLD PEACE
Make a wish.
MARSHAL OF THE CENTRAL ALTAR
I believe
that magic can't overcome divine power,
divine power can't overcome karma
and karma can't overcome willpower.
So the most powerful person in the world
is someone with a wish.
WORLD PEACE, MARSHAL OF THE CENTRAL ALTAR
DONGFENG MARKET
Who are you?
Hello there.
You brought a ghost?
No way, you can actually see him?
I'm impressed, Master Han.
I'm Mr. Li.
-I have some--
-Hold up.
-Mr. Li, right?
-Yes.
MR. LI HIRED A GHOST
TO KILL HIS ELDERS
AND INHERIT THEIR MONEY
KICK HIS ASS
Wait!
I came to discuss business with you.
Shouldn't you ask your boss first?
I don't need to ask him.
His instructions have never changed.
QIANKUN HOOP
Eliminate evil.
AGENT FROM ABOVE
Money makes the world go round.
Hell is even more corrupt
than the Human Realm.
All your debts can be paid off.
With this Hell Talisman…
you can alter karma
any way you please.
HELL TALISMAN
Come!
There is somebody
I want you to kill.