DAD: COMING HOME?
I'm almost there.
YU-CHING: I'M ALMOST THERE
Let's grab a snack.
OKAY! I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
READ: 10:37 p.m.
Yu-ching.
Wang Yu-ching!
AGENT FROM ABOVE
THE GHOST FORGE
TAIPEI CITY POLICE DEPARTMENT
CENTRAL DISTRICT PRECINCT
You again?
We've been waiting so long
and you still fob us off
with small-time cops.
Where's the captain?
The precinct chief?
I'm in charge of this case. Let's talk.
When did you last have a run-in
with the leader of the Heilung Clan?
My client runs a legitimate business.
He has no links to the triads.
We have records showing
that since 2018,
there have been three turf disputes
and dozens of brawls.
My client is just a passive shareholder.
He's not privy to these minor disputes.
Minor disputes?
The Heilung Clan just won
a bid worth 100 million,
but got wiped out before seeing a dime.
Mr. Liu, you're a ruthless devil.
You can't catch the culprit
so you harass innocent citizens instead.
It's taxpayer's money
that pays your wages.
Do you know
how much I pay in taxes each year?
-Mr. Shen.
-Yes.
Take a note of this.
The next time I pay taxes,
buy some dog food while you're at it
to feed to these dogs!
Sorry, excuse me.
Hurry, let's go.
SHE DIDN'T COME HOME
SO I WENT LOOKING FOR HER
AND FOUND HER BACKPACK
Please. You must find my daughter.
It's just the two of us now. She…
She's all I have.
I'm begging you.
FOUND HER BACKPACK IN LANE 48
No… no!
According to the Shen-Lung Crown Prince,
Chen Chi-sha is likely behind all this.
He promised him
all sorts of rewards and powers.
But first he had to
find primal souls for him.
What's a primal soul?
Heard of three souls and seven spirits?
The primal soul is one of the three souls.
Hellspawn are refined
from the primal souls of innocent victims.
The way those triads died.
I bet Chen Chi-sha used hellspawn.
And it has to be linked to the Demon King.
Take a look at this.
A girl called Wang Yu-ching went missing.
I found signs of the Demon King nearby.
WUMENG OCCULTIST KIDNAPS GIRL
What's this?
The Demon King
wants to enter the Human Realm
before your tasks are complete
and your successor takes over.
-Did you handle it?
-That's between me and him.
A girl's life is at stake.
I'll look into it for you.
Thanks.
Actually, there's one more thing.
Chao got a search warrant for Liu's place.
Maybe you can take a look.
Check for any evidence
of sorcery or ghosts.
I know he probably burnt down your home.
But we've been working really hard lately
to get all the evidence we can,
so that scumbag,
Liu Kuan-fu, will finally--
You're worried I'll kill him?
You'll be there. What can I do?
And I'm trying to atone for my sins.
I can't go adding to them.
-Hurry, Chao's already on his way.
-Okay.
Han Chieh.
Can I ask you something?
Is Hsiang still around here somewhere?
He didn't go when the time came,
so remained earthbound.
He can't be far away.
But I've never seen him,
even with my third eye opened.
-I really don't under--
-Sister Lo.
You were both very close.
But for both your sakes,
you should move on with your life.
He might be staying away,
so that you can forget
about the fire and move on.
How about you?
You've been down to see your parents.
How are they doing?
I can't face them.
That's why
whenever I encounter tricky family issues,
I always tell people to cherish
their family while they can.
Because they won't be around forever.
But people always take offence.
-If you're all right, I'd better be off.
-Okay.
DONGFENG SNACKS
-Sis.
-Yes?
-Stop cleaning. Come and eat.
-Okay.
A different dish every day.
-You're a genius.
-That goes without saying.
What choice did I have
with a glutton like you for a sis?
Don't pinch me.
Eat up. See if it's any good.
Any idea how lucky you are
having a genius kid brother
cook for you every day?
Holy shit.
Why is Liu's place
full of wronged spirits?
-Captain, this is all we've found so far.
-Okay.
Hey, I've looked everywhere
and can't find a thing.
-Chao, this place is full of ghosts.
-Oh?
…CLAIMS TWO LIVES
…DISPUTE TURNS FATAL
What do you want?
I want him dead.
He got me killed.
COMMAND
Black Command Token?
The Underworld permitted me
to take his life.
Wherever he goes, I go.
Same for them.
Hey, what kind of a hellhole is this?
They're all people
that Liu Kuan-fu killed.
-They want revenge.
-Can't we perform a cross-over ritual?
They have a Black Command Token.
Retribution is banned in the Human Realm,
but not down in hell.
The Underworld has jurisdiction
over revenge there.
Even gods can't interfere.
All right, let's call it a day.
Let's go.
DONGFENG MARKET
Who is she?
What do you want?
Something weird happened
while I was handling a case
in the Third Crown Prince's temple.
-We couldn't find this dead guy's soul.
-I've handled that already.
The culprit's been caught
and the primal souls returned.
I helped out too.
Yes, I heard.
That's why I thought it was weird.
Hey, I asked around at other temples.
There are other victims.
How many?
At least six.
Is it who I think it is?
Chen Chi-sha?
I thought he'd retired already?
Why would he do this?
-It must be the Demon King's doing.
-What?
That's messed up. We're in big trouble.
Why don't the gods
get rid of these demons themselves?
Why do they let them run loose?
Miss, the gods cannot
meddle directly in human affairs.
Especially those
humans must face themselves.
However, when demons
try to commit evil through others,
the gods can issue orders
allowing agents from above to handle it.
So I'm the unlucky sucker.
What if you lose to the demon?
Then I lose. What else can I do?
Hey, show a little backbone, will you?
Hey, Chen Chi-sha killed so many people.
Don't you care?
I'm retiring soon.
A superior god or agent from above
should take care of this.
What use am I?
Listen to you.
You're right. You're useless.
The Demon King's back
and people keep dying.
-And you do nothing?
-You think it's a game?
It's not that simple.
As gods,
we have all these rules to follow.
Those nagging fuddy-duddies up there
are so strict.
If I make a move
without their permission,
then I'll be breaking the rules.
Do you want me to get trapped
under a mountain like that monkey?
Why do gods and demons
treat everyone like pawns in a game?
Always making lackeys or agents
do your dirty work.
War between gods and demons
is the last thing anyone wants.
If we were to fight in our true forms,
then the world would come to an end.
You just don't want
to get your hands dirty.
You don't care if we die.
Are you really that scared
of fighting the Demon King again?
I know I don't have much choice.
But I don't think I'd win.
Fair enough.
The Demon King came prepared this time.
I don't think you will either.
Hey, aren't you supposed to root for me
and tell me I've got this?
But then I'd be lying to you.
Gods don't interfere with human free will,
much less tell you what to do.
You're afraid of taking responsibility.
If things go badly,
you can just hold your hands up and say
the Third Crown Prince made you do it.
But don't forget,
for every task Javvy brings you,
you have the right to decide
whether to accept it or not.
You can save those innocent people.
It's all up to you.
You hopeless brat.
Be quick and make up your mind.
I retrieved surveillance footage
from the area where the girl went missing.
There's no sign of Chen Chi-sha.
But we can infer from
these three crime scenes
that Chen Chi-sha's whereabouts
should be within this triangle.
WANG YU-CHING,
HEILUNG HQ, SHEN-LUNG TEMPLE
There were other victims. At least six.
Fu said there were other souls
that couldn't be summoned.
It could be the work of Chen Chi-sha too.
I'll find out if they were in this area.
-What?
-You saw Liu Kuan-fu again.
Didn't it make you mad?
Of course.
But catching bad guys is your job.
What if the law can't touch him?
He might escape the law,
but he can't escape karma.
With so many wronged spirits
out for revenge, I'd have to get in line.
Let's go.
Hey, go and get the tea Chan sent me.
-I'll compare the two.
-Yes, boss.
This is so good.
TAIPEI CITY POLICE DEPARTMENT
Officer Chao!
I want to turn myself in. Officer Chao!
-Yes?
-Officer Chao!
I'm turning myself in. Lock me up.
-Officer Chao--
-Mr. Shen, talk to me properly.
Ghosts are haunting me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry…
Officer Chao, save me.
Those ghosts drove him crazy.
Officer Chao, I'll confess
to all of Liu Kuan-fu's crimes.
-I'll turn state witness.
-You'll lose your license if you do.
It's no use to me if I'm dead.
I mean it. Save me.
Save me.
Where is Chen Chi-sha?
I know where.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you everything.
Shit, you were actually right.
Those ghosts drove Mr. Shen crazy.
He even told us where Chen is.
I'll send you the location.
It's been a while, my old friend.
Didn't you promise to retire?
Must have taken a lot of lives
to refine so many hellspawn.
That girl isn't here.
Wang Yu-ching has other uses.
So she's with your new apprentice?
He's not my apprentice.
Suppose not.
He's more powerful than you.
His magic is scentless.
Almost fooled even me.
Two female ghosts work for him.
One calls you uncle?
She said the Demon King threatened you.
What's that all about?
Save me.
-Dad.
-Uncle.
-Save me.
-Those two female ghosts.
The one in white is my niece.
The one in red is my daughter.
Wu Tien-chi dug up their corpses.
With the Demon King's power,
he controlled their souls
and turned them into hellspawn.
Long time no see, Master Chen.
Why the cold reception?
They're threatening me
and monitoring my every move.
If I don't cooperate,
Wu Tien-chi will let the souls
of those two girls dissipate.
Wu Tien-chi?
DEMON KING ENTICES MAN
Five years ago,
you promised to tell me
if the Demon King came back.
And what if I had told you?
If you hadn't sealed away
all my magical weapons back then,
I wouldn't be in this state.
If you defeat
the Third Crown Prince's agent from above,
I will free
your precious daughter and niece.
Dad.
Save me.
Dad, save me.
Karma's caught up with me now.
It's my fault
that the Demon King came back
-to hurt you--
-I don't care.
I'm beyond forgiveness.
But those two girls are innocent.
I'm not here to fight you.
They turned me into a living corpse
so that I can defeat you.
Where's Wang Yu-ching?
-I don't want to kill you.
-You're saying that to a dead man?
See you in hell.
Nine Dragons Divine Fire Barrier?
I knew this day would come.
Full moon, magic array, center.
That must have been tough, Master Chen.
DONGFENG MARKET