[somber music playing]
[sighs]
[shudders]
- [monitor beeping]
- [respirator hissing]
[suctioning]
[panting] Ha-gyeong.
Min-beom.
Where's Gang-yong?
His brain has a hemorrhage.
He's having surgery now.
MIN GANG-YONG: PROCEDURE IN PROGRESS
[whimpering]
[crying]
Oh.
Woo-jin, what's wrong?
K… Kang In-beom has…
Yeah?
[cries]
He took Mom. He has her.
What?
- I'm so sorry.
- [Gun-woo] Oh.
- [Gun-woo sighs]
- [Woo-jin sobbing]
[Woo-jin] I tried,
but I couldn't protect her.
I don't…
I should just die.
No, no. Woo-jin, no. It's okay.
You tried. It's not your fault.
Oh, Mom!
- [breathes heavily]
- [Woo-jin sobs]
GWANG-MU: THE BOYS ARE IN TROUBLE
I COULDN'T PROTECT THEM
[tense music playing]
[tense electronic music playing]
BLOODHOUNDS 2
[music stops]
[knocking on door]
[man] Enter.
DIRECTOR OF INVESTIGATIONS
[somber music playing]
We need to move Yun Tae-geom's
family to a safe house.
Isn't Im Baek-jeong wanted?
He won't have time for revenge
if he's busy running.
Im Baek-jeong will never stop,
even if he's running,
Enough. That's too much.
In what world is it too much?
Yun Tae-geom was murdered
while helping the police.
He was working with us.
Isn't it our duty
to ensure that his family will be safe?
They can hire private security.
Who will take responsibility
if that team fails?
That security team will.
That's why they'll handle it.
[gasps]
Don't cause any trouble
and protect a criminal's family.
Instead, try to get the bastard.
[gasps]
If security's so important to you,
figure it out yourself.
We need to eat. Woo-jin?
[tender music playing]
Have a couple of bites.
Eat a bit to take your medicine.
[Gun-woo sighs]
[cell phone buzzing]
LEE WOO-JEONG
Excuse me.
Yes, Woo-jeong?
[Woo-jeong] Gun-woo,
is everything all right?
Yes.
[Woo-jeong] I was told Mr. Min
came out of surgery and he's in the ICU.
His condition's stable,
but we'll need to wait and see.
We're trying to find
your mother's location.
Since it's an area without CCTVs,
we're having difficulties.
I'll keep you updated about it.
Thanks for letting me know.
And how's Mr. Moon doing?
[Woo-jeong] He's awake now.
You should give him a call.
Okay.
[Woo-jeong] Gun-woo,
do you know where you might want to stay
after you're discharged?
I haven't thought about it yet.
Could Yun Tae-geom's family stay with you?
If you're planning on being home?
Just his mom and young daughter?
Yes. I have a spare room there.
Im Baek-jeong killed him
once he found out he also helped us.
Im Baek-jeong might try
murdering Tae-geom's family.
I think it's only right
if we protect them.
We don't have any resources available
so I can only protect them myself now.
It's okay. They're welcome to stay.
[music fades]
[Sin-hyeong] Our employees
work with Special Forces
for their anti-terrorism exercises.
That must be when Lee Dong-hyeon
first met Yun Tae-geom.
Yun Tae-geom introduced him
to Im Baek-jeong later on.
Can you locate him?
Lee Dong-hyeon was a black ops agent.
He's an expert at hiding
so he can't be found.
He might be getting ready to go overseas,
because he's wanted.
We won't let him.
I'll give you the support you need
to stop him from running off.
[ominous music plays]
Im Baek-jeong has made a lot of money
from illegal boxing online.
I have an offer.
We could work together and help society.
[tense music playing]
We'll set up a match so Im Baek-jeong
will gamble everything he has in one go.
How?
We'll offer him
another round with Gun-woo.
You'll put in 100 billion won.
Im Baek-jeong will put down
100 billion won too.
And the winner will take it all.
You think he'll go for this?
If he thinks he can win everything.
If it's something he wants,
he'll be there.
He's not the type to be scared easily.
And since he has a hostage,
he will believe
that he has a shield from the police.
[music fades]
[Mr. Moon] I fractured my collarbone.
And my cheekbone
is caved in, according to the doctors.
[sighs] I feel really bad.
I should've been there with you guys too.
Gun-woo,
you're not Superman.
No one is.
Just be a good friend to Woo-jin, Gun-woo.
[poignant music playing]
Just remember that
no one's always a hero.
Okay.
That's good. What are you gonna do?
I'll go back to the house tomorrow.
I contacted a friend.
He's gonna help you out
while I recover here.
Who is it?
When you see him, you'll know who it is.
Thanks.
Let's go.
[Gun-woo sighs]
[music fades]
- [doorbell chimes]
- [vacuum stops]
[gentle music playing]
- [Woo-jeong] Gun-woo.
- Hello.
Okay, let's go inside.
Please, watch your step.
Hello.
I know you!
Min-a.
It's you.
You're okay?
Yeah.
Do you like stickers?
[chuckles softly] Yeah.
Let's do it.
[music fades]
His intracranial pressure was high from
the injury he sustained in the explosion.
They'll have to wait until he wakes up.
He's not in any condition to move, and it
might take time for him to fully recover.
[somber music playing]
From now on,
we'll do things on our own.
I've thought about ways
we might rescue your mother.
[tense music playing]
And how we can stop Im Baek-jeong
from fleeing Korea.
My uncle's the director
of the National Intelligence Service.
He's willing to help.
Gun-woo, this won't be easy.
Could you fight Im Baek-jeong again?
It can draw him out of hiding.
But if he knows he's wanted,
would he show up?
He won't care if he gets caught.
And if the cops arrive,
he'll threaten to hurt Ms. Yoon.
But he won't.
I'll offer 100 billion won.
Im Baek-jeong will do this.
Yes. I'll do what it takes.
[chuckles softly]
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
[music fades]
- [Min-a giggles]
- [Woo-jeong] It's your bedtime.
[tense music playing]
[Woo-jeong] This one's yours. [laughs]
Gun-woo, someone's here.
He's outside.
[Min-a giggles]
[sighs]
[Gun-woo cries]
I've missed you guys.
[sobs]
I lost the courage to show up here.
Du-yeong.
I'm sorry.
- [Woo-jin] Du-yeong!
- [cries]
[cries] Du-yeong.
[all cry]
Why are you crying like that?
[crying continues]
[Woo-jin] Du-yeong.
[music fades]
He's a big guy with a lot of scars.
You can see them over his face.
[somber music playing]
Then,
Kang In-beom showed up.
He's the one who kept hitting me again.
So Ms. Yoon came out of her room.
[cries]
She told him to quit hitting me.
[sniffs] And Ms. Yoon…
said she'd go instead.
I…
was supposed to protect her.
It was my duty.
[sniffs] I hate myself. I do.
[sniffs]
[Du-yeong] I also
can't ever forgive myself…
for what I've done.
I'll never forgive myself.
It's all my fault.
Yang-jung and Mr. Choi died.
I caused that.
[cries]
But you have a chance.
There's still time to save her.
So keep being strong.
I'll help you.
We can do it.
We'll rescue her.
[music fades]
Yes.
Guys, look at this.
BLOODHOUNDS: SEOUL
200 MILLION WON IF YOU SAVE MY COLLEAGUES
[sniffs]
What is this?
[somber music playing]
For the last four years…
to make ends meet,
I did things I'm not proud of.
I committed murder.
I killed good people,
and bad ones, many, for hire.
I…
became…
a bloodhound.
This chat is
how contract killers find jobs.
It's all anonymous and it's run by a host,
but I've never met him.
The host posts the job listing
and someone accepts it.
We get paid by Bitcoin.
The other day,
the host offered something different.
He said he'll pay whoever rescues
his coworkers, the ones who were arrested.
[inhales sharply] Is that Im Baek-jeong?
Du-yeong,
could you talk to the police officer
we worked with who's downstairs?
A policeman?
[music stops]
We can talk and figure this out together.
Du-yeong,
he's been helping us.
[exhales]
Do you know when the bloodhounds chat
first started by any chance?
I don't know for sure.
I, uh…
I joined four years ago.
A man who pretended to be a veterinarian,
Moon Dong-jo, is someone we arrested.
He's been involved in many crimes,
including drug manufacturing.
Have you heard of him?
Yes. I've heard his name often.
The host said,
if you get hurt, to go to him.
That's the vet you go to see to treat you.
Where is he now?
Was he arrested?
He was released
once his arrest was denied.
He might be at his house.
If you can say where his home is,
I'll go see him very covertly.
Woo-jeong,
trust him, he's with us.
Du-yeong, we'll join you.
- Gun-woo.
- Yes?
The blood won't show up on my hands.
- Even still.
- Don't worry.
I need to do this for you.
[suspenseful music playing]
But, Du-yeong, he could have others there.
[music intensifies]
It's okay.
[snores]
- [loud crack]
- [Dong-jo groans]
- [music fades]
- [water running]
[Du-yeong exhales]
[tense music playing]
I hate people
that open their mouths and say nothing.
It'd be better
if they don't bother at all.
So when you're ready
to tell me everything,
nod your head.
If you start talking, then stop…
I'll cut off your tongue.
[laughs]
[gasps]
- [slicing]
- [muffled moaning]
[muffled shrieking]
[whimpering]
[muffled pleading]
[muffled screaming]
[muffle yelping]
[tense music playing]
[Baek-jeong exhales]
What is it?
National Intelligence.
They're all over here.
Oh, this is fucked.
What are we gonna do now?
President Im, we might not--
- [wheezes]
- You shut your fucking mouth.
You said you would do it. Huh?
You fucking with me?
You gonna keep screwing around?
- [Baek-jeong exhales]
- You have to… get out of here now.
[exhales]
Just listen.
One more mistake you make…
and I'll kill your mom and dad, all right?
Understand?
- [choked] Yes.
- [Baek-jeong exhales]
[electronic voice] The phone is
turned off. Your call has been forwarded.
[music fades]
The phone is turned off.
Your call has been forwarded.
- You gave me the right numbers?
- [Gun-woo] I did.
They're from the phones
that Lee Man-bae used as burners.
Du-yeong got them from Moon Dong-jo.
- [Woo-jin] Min-beom.
- Hmm?
Could I…
join and fight alongside Gun-woo?
If you suggest a two-on-two match,
In-beom may also step up to fight
and go into the ring.
Then,
while Gun-woo and I are fighting…
you could get his mother.
[gentle music playing]
Please make this work
to rescue his mom.
I will.
Of course.
[Woo-jin] Thank you.
[breathes deeply]
[music fades]
[outbound call ringing]
[cell phone buzzing]
[cell phone buzzes]
[sighs]
[Min-beom] Lee Man-bae.
Who is this?
It's Hong Min-beom.
Put Im Baek-jeong on the phone.
Why would I bother?
Your mom's in a nursing home
in Chuncheon, right, Lee Dong-hyeon?
Don't think I won't hurt her.
[tense music playing]
President Im.
Hong Min-beom's on the phone.
- Did you call that guy?
- No. I wouldn't.
Speak.
Let's have another matchup round.
Gun-woo and Woo-jin against
you and Kang In-beom.
Why would I?
We'll bet 100 billion won each.
The winner will take it all.
[chuckles]
[whimpers] Let go of me!
[So-yeon screaming]
Give me the phone. Give me that shit!
[So-yeon] Let go!
[So-yeon breathes shakily]
100 billion won is gonna be exchanged
into Bitcoin and sent to me now,
or I'll cut off this lady's face
and send it over by courier.
You stupid fuck. You can't push me around.
- You think I'm weak or something? Huh?
- [So-yeon gasps]
Do you know why you're stuck in Korea?
The National Intelligence Service agents
are at the airport.
My uncle's the director
of the National Intelligence Service.
So, what, you want a fucking cookie?
Wire the funds.
[So-yeon gasps]
Or her face is gonna get fucked up.
Kill her!
Give me a reason to kill you.
You'll regret that.
Try me and see what'll happen, bastard.
[disconnection bleep]
[So-yeon whimpers]
[gasping]
Yeah. They're stupid enough
to think I won't kill you.
President Im, I'll fix this for you.
You little shit.
It's the National Intelligence Service.
We could get stuck in Korea forever.
If we stay, it'll only take a while
until we're caught by the police.
So, what are you gonna do?
I…
I'll get this figured out.
I'll also look into going to Thailand.
I need only a few more days.
And I'll make sure this match goes ahead,
and you won't put down any money.
[tense music swells]
[Baek-jeong sighs]
Ah, shit.
You have ten days.
Get this sorted out in ten days.
Or I'll be the one to kill you.
Yes, I understand.
[scissors clatter]
[music fades]
[Woo-jin] Min-beom,
what if they do something to Ms. Yoon?
What do we do then?
Let's wait a little longer.
[exhales]
[cell phone buzzing]
[Man-bae] President Hong Min-beom,
please excuse me for this,
but whether you meant to or not,
if you get Im Baek-jeong
worked up like that,
he'll do serious damage.
He's a loose cannon.
[tense music playing]
Now, here's what I can do for you,
and I hope you'll accept it.
Think it through.
We won't put any money down.
Instead, Kim Gun-woo's mom
will be escorted near the venue.
If we lose, we'll release her.
But if we win,
we'll take the entire pot,
and leave on the private jet
you have waiting for us you've prepped.
Once we've safely arrived
at our destination, we'll release her.
This is the best I can do,
and a promise I'll make with my life,
so trust me.
If there are any mix-ups,
even by chance,
and anything happens
that puts us in jeopardy,
say, others get involved…
You know I've got ears
inside the police, right?
If I hear anything slightly off,
Kim Gun-woo won't see his mom again.
She'll never be part of his life again.
You understand?
I trust that you do.
So I'll contact you
two hours before the start of the match,
which will be in two days.
Send us your wager in Bitcoin.
I'm turning off this phone
so it can't be tracked.
- Did you understand all that?
- [Min-beom] Yes.
I'll be back in touch.
Until the match,
Ms. Yoon will stay secure.
I'll outline a course of action.
I can gather some men we can trust.
Woo-jin and I
will come back much stronger.
I also got us a private plane to Thailand.
Fight Kim Gun-woo and Hong Woo-jin
in a two-on-two match in ten days.
I'll clash with Kim Gun-woo.
[In-beom exhales]
Kim Gun-woo
is mine to kill.
[somber music playing]
[Woo-jin] Oh, it's right here.
GUNSAN GYM
- [coach] Jab, then cross. Again.
- [man] Coach, someone's here to see you.
[Gun-woo and Woo-jin] Hello, sir.
- Do your drills over there.
- [man] Yes.
I guess you're Mr. Hong's son?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kim Gun-woo.
But you're the one
who fought Baek-jeong without gloves.
Yes.
[sighs]
I'm Heo Cheong-ho.
So, why have you come here?
We're fighting Im Baek-jeong.
Could you train us for the match?
We'd appreciate it if you could help us.
Are you looking for revenge?
Im Baek-jeong is the one
who kidnapped my mother.
[sighs] Hmm.
[inhales]
I don't know if I can be of any help,
but I'll train you.
I'll teach you what I know.
- Thanks very much.
Baek-jeong is quick.
He has a fast right hand
and a heavy left hand.
When he's in a southpaw stance,
watch for his jab. Got it?
He's similar to Thomas Hearns,
the Motor City Cobra.
Thomas Hearns?
No idea.
Chopping style. Well, uh…
Uh, never mind.
[suspenseful music playing]
Watch this. Call it a flicker jab.
You can't tell if it's gonna land
on your body or on your face.
It's surprising
because it comes in deep, quickly.
This jab requires the fighter
to have long arms.
The thing to know
is that his punches aren't that strong,
so if you're tough,
take his punches and get in close.
But also that's Baek-jeong's trap,
since he knows his strength.
If you try to get in too close
while taking his jab,
he might step back
and set up a quick hook like this.
[sighs] Mm.
[Cheong-ho] The real reason
why Baek-jeong's dangerous
is he knows good fighters
use speed, power, and their mind.
He reads his opponent's mind very fast
and downloads the info.
Uh, how is it possible to learn that?
Baek-jeong's home life wasn't good.
In middle school,
he ran away and stayed on the streets.
[somber music playing]
His father was a violent drunk.
His father got so drunk
he beat his mother until she died.
He had to read people in order to survive
and live such a rough life.
Now, come at me.
- Okay.
- I'll teach you how to block his punches.
Throw some jabs.
How's this? Huh?
- I can't use my lead hand.
- [Cheong-ho] Right.
If this happens,
Baek-jeong can't use his right hand
and will throw a straight left instead.
- Got it?
- [Gun-woo] Mm.
Now, try coming at me again.
Yeah. Harder. Go.
Not that way.
Stop dodging by turning it over fast.
Think what can be done here.
A counter.
That's it. A counter.
- Always the way to turn things around.
- A counter.
Now, come at me.
More. Again.
[exhales]
Good, yeah.
This is southpaw Baek-jeong's weapon,
and yours to keep and fight him with.
[tense electronic music playing]
Baek-jeong's professional record
is 18 fights, 17 wins.
Out of those 17 wins, 15 were KOs.
Thirteen were when
he was in the orthodox stance.
He likes his left foot forward.
Oh!
Watch out.
This move is the one
to anticipate the most.
Especially when Baek-jeong's
firmly like this.
If he gets you on this side, it's over.
How do I block
when he comes at me so fast?
Step faster. Boxing is
about where your feet are.
You just plant your feet
on the ground firmly,
then push up
with all the power you've got,
and then bam!
Big guys are slower. That's why
you have to fight with your quick steps.
If he turns, you turn with him.
Like this. Yeah, that's it.
Then he won't get in.
You got it.
[music fades]
I have very different ideas
from the director,
and I'm not sure
who I can trust in the department.
No one knows when Gang-yong will wake up.
This isn't a job
to be done alone, Myeong-hwan.
Woo-jeong, the Green Pine Club's perfect
for this kind of thing, so don't worry.
I'll notify them.
They'll get themselves ready.
[tense music playing]
We'll gather together
and follow your lead.
Thanks so much.
[cell phone buzzes]
BLOODHOUNDS: SEOUL
GYEONGGI-DO
20 GUARDS IN 2 DAYS
10 MIL UPFRONT, 15 MIL AFTER
I'M IN
When I searched the address
that Lee Man-bae gave Du-yeong,
this is what came up.
Originally, they were going to be
universities, but construction was halted.
Inside the building
could easily be over 100 rooms.
That might be why
they've chosen this place for the match.
It's a good place to hide Ms. Yoon.
They can have the match
in one of the three buildings,
while also hiding Ms. Yoon.
All three buildings are located on a hill
so they can see everything.
And so that means our chances
of finding Ms. Yoon before is very low.
It'll be extremely dangerous
to try rescuing her from the outside.
That's where I'll go inside.
Once Gun-woo and Woo-jin's match begins,
I'll look for Ms. Yoon.
Wouldn't it be too dangerous
for you to be alone?
If I'm alone,
it's the safest way to rescue her.
That's why I need to do this by myself.
Those men won't be concerned about me.
Most importantly,
her safety is the priority.
[chuckles softly]
Are the Bitcoins set up, President Hong?
Yes.
Tae-yeong, why don't you
come along with us?
The Green Pine Tree Club members
will all be waiting near the buildings.
- Once she's rescued, we'll go in.
- Yeah, sounds good.
I'll be there too.
I have to enter the password
for the transfer of the Bitcoin.
Okay, everyone.
Let's be strong.
Fighting for her.
One, two, three…
[all] Let's do it!
Give me the one. One. One. One. One.
Go faster. Go. Go faster.
- Go faster!
- [Gun-woo yells]
[grunts]
[In-beom grunts]
[yells]
[snarls]
- [grunts]
- Another!
- One more. You can do it!
[strains]
Yes! Go!
[Gun-woo pants]
You all right?
Yeah.
[both grunting]
[both grunt]
- Sixty-nine!
- [grunts]
- [strains]
- Seventy! Thirty more. Be faster!
- [grunts]
- Seventy-one!
- [Woo-jin] Seventy-two!
[strains]
[yells]
Use your core. Use your core strength!
[Gun-woo grunts]
- [Woo-jin] Use your core! Your core!
- [Gun-woo strains]
- [Woo-jin] Yes!
- [strains]
All right, go. Let's go!
That's good! Keep doing it. Okay!
- You good?
- [Woo-jin] Yeah.
[music fades]
I've been thinking about this
since last night.
Would Im Baek-jeong
have thought I would be fighting him?
Would he ever imagine that?
- Uh-uh. I would never imagine that.
- [eerie music playing]
- That's right.
- Hmm.
He's probably preparing to maul you
and will get thrown off
if I get in the ring.
[Gun-woo] Mm-hmm.
If I have to take 100 punches
from that bastard,
I won't let it end
until one of his eyes is cooked.
He'll lose his sense of distance,
and then I'll get the advantage.
Are you gonna be okay, Woo-jin?
This is what I've got to do.
And what should we do with Kang In-beom?
[sighs] That's a big concern.
Yes, you might have to fight them both.
[sighs]
[somber music playing]
Woo-jin.
In the IKFC, they wrap metal things
on their knuckles before the fight.
That's a weapon, isn't it?
I didn't use them
in the fight the last time.
I thought if I did,
no one would consider me a champion.
But now,
I'm gonna wear them this time.
I was wrong before.
I believed I could protect people
with a boxer's heart, but I can't.
Mr. Moon said so the other day.
The only way to grab a beast
is to become a scarier beast
without mercy.
Which means my heart is as tough as steel.
My fists will become a knife
once my heart is as tough as steel.
It's how I can stand
and shield my loved ones.
I need to make my heart as tough as steel.
Ack.
Ack!
[tense electronic music playing]
BLOODHOUNDS: IKFC 38
OLD JINAM CAMPUS, 12 P.M.
[cell phone chimes]
DU-YEONG
[tense music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
All right!
Face me and listen for a moment, please.
You all got a ticket
when you came in, right?
Now, take your spot based on your number.
Anyone who leaves their spot during
the match will be considered a traitor.
Please send me a text message
or kill them yourself.
There's an extra reward.
Fifty million won.
Whoa! So fucking awesome!
- [man 1] Yeah!
- Good. All of us, let's do it!
- Yeah!
- [cheering]
- [chuckles]
- [man 2] Let's go!
- [man 3] Yeah.
- [laughter]
[man 4] Yeah!
PRESIDENT HONG MIN-BEOM
OLD JINAM CAMPUS, 15:00
It's time.
[laughter]
[man] That 50 million won
is all mine, you bastards!
[laughter]
Fighters have arrived.
Get ready.
[exhales]
[snarls]
[tense music continues]
I'm Lee Man-bae.
Show me your wallet.
[Min-boom sighs]
[breathes shakily]
[gasps]
This is it.
I'm going in.
BLOODHOUNDS: IKFC 38
[cell phone buzzes]
THE FIGHT IS ON
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey,
do you have a cigarette?
And a light?
- [knife slices]
- [groans]
[knife slices]
[ominous music playing]
What the fuck are you doing here?
What the fuck do you think?
Today, it's you and me, Baek-jeong,
you fucking asshole fuckface.
You're gonna die.
"You're gonna die."
You scared?
[laughs]
Scared?
Scared? Huh, scared?
[dramatic music playing]
You motherfucker! [grunts]
[groans]
Who the hell
do you think you are? Get out!
[Woo-jin groans]
Scared?
Scared? Huh?
- [tense music playing]
- [Woo-jin groans]
[Woo-jin coughs]
[Woo-jin groans]
Hmm?
- [man 1 yells]
- [knife flies through air]
- [grunts]
- [man 2] Oh, fuck.
- [knife clatters]
- I fucking love this!
- [knives fly through air]
- [yells] Hya!
- [groans]
- [man 1] Where you going?
- [man 1 yells]
- [Du-yeong grunts]
Shitface!
Fuck around and find out, dumbass.
Scared?
Baek-jeong, scared?
Ah, fuck you!
[grunts]
You want this asshole to die?
Enter the ring!
[music fades]
[Woo-jin groans]
[groans]
[determined music playing]
Scared?
[bellows] Scared?!
[Baek-jeong yells]
[yells]
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
Ah, shit.
Stop the bleeding.
Stupid little bastard.
If the blood doesn't stop, I'll kill you.
[man] Understood.
[exhales]
[somber music playing]
[breathes shakily]
I got his eye.
Mm-hmm. You did.
[breathes heavily]
I'll finish this fight.
[Woo-jin] Mm.
[Gun-woo] Mm.
- [man 1 grunts]
- [knife slices]
[knife clatters]
- [Du-yeong groans]
[knives clattering]
- [knife stabs]
- [grunts]
- [man 2] I'll kill you! Die!
- [knife slices]
[man 2 groans]
- [man 2 groans]
[groans] Agh!
[thuds]
[Min-beom] Gun-woo.
Be careful.
Im Baek-jeong, come out!
- [tense music playing]
- [panting heavily]
You'll die.
[growls]
[both grunting]
[yells]
[Gun-woo yells]
- Oh!
- [In-beom yells]
[In-beom yells]
[punches thud]
[yelling continues]
[blows thudding]
[Gun-woo panting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathes deeply]
[snarls]
[dramatic music playing]
[In-beom yells]
[Min-beom] Get him! Come on!
Yeah, let's go! Let's go! There's more!
Gun-woo, go!
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
[bones crack]
[tense electronic music playing]
[huffs]
[both grunting]
[knives slicing through air]
- [knife slices]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[knife slicing]
[man groaning]
- [knife slices]
- [man groans]
[music fades]
[breathes heavily]
[tense music playing]
- [knife slices]
- [Du-yeong groans]
- [woman grunts]
- [screams in pain]
- [giggles]
- [woman groans]
- [Du-yeong grunts]
[gasping for air]
[cell phone buzzes]
Yes?
[Du-yeong gasping] Ms. Yoon
isn't here in the building.
She's got to be in the one next to it.
On the top floor is a room
with windows covered. Go there.
[Woo-jeong] Well done. Good work.
I'll head over there now.
[straining] Go, please,
and save her.
I'm depending on you.
Yes.
Hi, Myeong-hwan. Gun-woo's mom might be
on the third floor of the next building.
Okay. Got it. Be careful.
[dramatic music playing]
[both grunting]
[Baek-jeong groans]
[tense music playing]
[both yelling]
[grunting, panting]
Block it!
Yeah! Kill him! Go quickly!
[groaning]
[snarling]
[groans]
[yelling] Ah!
[both straining]
[Woo-jin] Get up!
Gun-woo, you gotta get up!
- Get yourself out of there!
- [Min-beom] Get up!
[groans] Agh!
- [crunches]
- [screams] Agh!
[growls]
[groaning]
Hit his leg!
[yelps]
[gasping]
[groans]
[somber music playing]
[Woo-jeong] Lee Man-bae, don't move!
[Man-bae] Drop the gun or I'll kill her.
- [So-yeon whimpers]
- [Man-bae] Drop the gun. I'm serious.
- Drop the gun, asshole!
- Drop the knife.
I'm gonna kill her. I said drop the gun!
Final warning. Got it?
Drop the knife.
[Man-bae] I'm giving you my final warning.
- [gun clicks]
- I'm really gonna kill her.
You hear? Drop the gun now.
Drop the fucking gun!
I will slash this lady if you don't!
Drop the gun!
- [Man-bae yelps]
- [So-yeon whimpering]
Did you get hurt anywhere?
[breathes deeply]
[yells in pain] Agh!
[groans]
[Min-beom] Yes! Get him!
Come at me.
[growls]
[tense music playing]
[yells]
[Baek-jeong screams in pain]
[Min-beom] Kill him!
[strains]
[groaning] Agh! Agh!
[both yelling]
[Woo-jin] You're doing good! Yes!
[Min-beom] Go back! Kill him!
[panting]
[dramatic music playing]
[Baek-jeong yells]
[groans, yells]
[yells]
[music fades]
[Baek-jeong groans] Agh!
[inaudible]
[groan echoes]
[Gun-woo gasping for air]
[panting]
[Min-beom and Woo-jin cheering] Yeah!
Yeah!
[tense music playing]
[Woo-jin] You did it.
Good job, Gun-woo. Well done.
That's good.
[Woo-jin grunts]
[man] Yeah!
- [Taser rattles]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[both straining]
You son of a bitch!
[dramatic music playing]
[man 1 groans]
[music fades]
[man 2] Everyone freeze!
[poignant music playing]
I've got Ms. Yoon.
She's safe. It's thanks to you. Great job.
Thanks very much.
Thanks for everything.
[sighs]
[exhales]
- [man 3] All right. This way.
- [man 4] Straight ahead.
[music fades]
Oh, Mom!
[gasps]
- [Woo-jin] Mom!
- [cries happily]
[So-yeon exhales]
[Woo-jin] You're okay.
I'm so sorry. I'm so, so sorry.
[Woo-jin cries]
It took me so long.
- I'll do better.
- It's okay. It's all right.
It's okay.
[So-yeon cries]
[Woo-jin cries]
- [Woo-jin] I'm so sorry, Mom.
- [exhales]
[sirens wailing]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [loud pop]
- [tires squealing]
What happened? Uh… Oh! [gasps]
[tires screech]
[device whirs, booms]
[loud click]
- [gas hissing]
- [sputtering]
[cell phone buzzes]
CHOI SIN-HYEONG
KANG TAE-YEONG
SIR, I ROUTED 860 BITCOIN
TO YOUR WALLET
[music fades]
[Gun-woo] Mom.
No, Mom! Woo-jin!
[Gun-woo breathing heavily]
No, Mom! [yells]
[breathes heavily]
- [Gun-woo exhales]
- You okay?
[Gun-woo sighs]
[sighs]
Do you need some water?
Woo-jin,
I'm hungry after that nightmare.
Let's go. I'll make ramyeon for you.
Deal.
[footsteps approach]
[gasps]
Oh.
[Woo-jin] Oh!
- Let's eat.
- [Gun-woo] Yes.
[gentle music playing]
[sighs]
- Woo-jin.
- Hmm?
Let's find another house.
I still feel anxious.
Like Im Baek-jeong's planning to return.
Let's go then.
And also,
we'll train for more battles to come.
We'll be ready for the next one.
What battles?
We'll train to fight the bloodhounds.
[quiet suspenseful music playing]
Then next time,
I promise I won't back down at all.
I'll also get stronger.
We will never lose.
- Ack.
[music builds]
Let's finish it.
[music fades]
[moans]
[tense music playing]
[Baek-jeong exhales]
This is our first meeting,
so we'll get to the point.
The person who is your contact
that helped you with the IKFC in Bangkok,
tell me his name.
I can kill you right now.
Ten, nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three--
All right.
[sighs]
Name.
Paichit Chaichana.
I've heard on the street
that bastard's bringing in one ton of meth
into Korea this fall.
It's worth about 300 billion won.
Yeah, so?
You scratch my back
and I'll scratch yours.
We're all someone else's bloodhounds.
Don't be upset about that.
Will you be a bloodhound?
- [gun clicks]
- Huh.
[grunts] Hmm.
[chuckles softly]
Ae-seo.
[suspenseful music playing]
I'll make it look nice.
[music fades]
[tense electronic music playing]
[somber music playing]
[music fades]