ACK
Don't worry.
You can count on me.
Woo-jin.
What?
Your mouth stinks of poo.
Hey, Gun-woo.
That's not something
you say in the morning to anyone.
Smell it. It's poo breath.
Are you sick or you caught a cold?
We'll go to the hospital after training.
Oh jeez, those boys.
- Ready! Ack!
- Ack!
Go!
- Let's eat the competition!
- Ack!
Number three!
Ack!
- Please enjoy these.
- Yes, ma'am, thanks.
- Gun-woo.
- Hi, Mom.
I've got a delivery!
Woo-jin, make me two espressos?
- Drive safely.
- I will.
Here, let's do this.
- See you soon.
- Okay.
MOVING ON FRIDAY, 2/14
THANK YOU FOR YOUR UNDERSTANDING
BUILDING 104
UNIT 1901
Jeong-gwon, how about
putting that over inside there?
- Yes, I ordered those.
- Here you are.
Whoa!
You're the boxer, Kim Gun-woo, right?
- Yes, hi.
- Could I maybe…
Shake? Sure.
You've got a strong hand.
Ah, sorry about making you use the stairs.
There's a lot of them.
No, that's okay.
I enjoy taking the stairs.
It's good. I end up working muscles
I don't normally use when I'm boxing
so it helps improve my balance.
Oh.
You're really amazing.
I'm an athlete too. In tae kwon do.
Oh, whoa, wow.
You fight too?
Uh, that's…
I'm not a talker.
I'm so sorry for being shy.
I'll root for you
in the championship match. Go win!
Yes, win!
Please enjoy!
- I will.
- Good.
Wow, this hand touched his.
Jeong-gwon, look!
Here.
Let's sit.
Thanks for the meal.
- Okay.
- Thanks for the meal.
Gun-woo, don't you
still have to lose some weight?
Hmm.
You think he's going to be okay?
Don't worry about his weight.
It'll quickly fall off him.
- Gun-woo, you'll make the weigh-in?
- Mm.
Hmm.
Gun-woo, keep listening to him.
Mm.
And you, look after him, Woo-jin.
Mm, mm.
Bring the fighters to the scale
for the WBC World Super-Middleweight
title match.
Yeah!
First for the weigh-in,
we have champion, Adik Belov!
Belov has stepped onto the scale
and he's made weight!
Yeah!
Next we have for the weigh-in,
his opponent, Kim Gun-woo.
Kim stands on the scale
and he's made weight.
In 26 hours, we'll have champion
Adik Belov against Kim Gun-woo
in an exciting match.
Fighters, come to the center of the stage
to face your opponent.
I'm gonna bust your face open!
I kill you!
You are dead tomorrow.
- Hey, are you crazy?!
- Break it up!
They're fighting.
We'd like to remind the staff
to calm the fighters down.
There's no need
for any of this to start now.
BLOODHOUNDS 2
We're moments away! I'm Hong Seok-hyeon.
And Kim Kwang-sun, the gold medalist
of the '88 Olympics, is here with me!
Thank you very much. Hello.
Tonight, we'll be watching the WBC
world super middleweight title match
between Adik Belov and Kim Gun-woo.
First, Kim Gun-woo
has made a remarkable rise
since he won the KBFC Rookie
of the Year Tournament five years ago.
Tonight, he's up for the championship
title. Do you think he'll win?
He's risen quickly in the boxing world.
I'm proud of him,
and I think he can do it.
The fighters have entered.
We're about to begin.
Adik Belov has refused to touch gloves.
This is a power move on Belov's part.
This shows that Belov
is engaging in a psychological war.
Who knows if that'll pay off?
Fans seem split.
Round one begins, and Adik Belov
again pushes away Kim Gun-woo's glove.
Kim jabs and Belov goes in for the attack.
He's coming on strong.
Kim punches back, but Belov
aggressively puts Kim into a corner.
Belov's taking control early,
using combinations with speed and power.
- Kim needs to start fighting.
- That's true.
Belov and Kim square off
as Kim steps forward and starts punching.
A combination of jabs and a right hook.
- Oh!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Belov's counter stunned Kim,
knocking him down.
It was as if Kim
was walking right into Belov's plan.
Six.
What happens if Adik wins?
He'll pay you. The prize money
will be used to pay off his debt.
Then why the fuck did I come
if I didn't have to be here?
I'll drag him in no matter what.
Get that bastard in the fucking cage.
Got it.
Win this! You can do it!
It's okay, it's fine.
Box!
Kim Gun-woo's going to be
cautious of Adik Belov's left hook now
because he got caught badly by it.
Kim's an all-around fighter
and he needs to start stepping it up.
- What a duck!
- Belov being aggressive.
Kim backs away.
He needs to show some combos.
Can Kim Gun-woo stop
Adik Belov's momentum and find his own?
He got hit in the face again as he ducks.
Belov backed Kim Gun-woo
into a corner again.
Belov keeps showing
his finesse in this first round.
The clinch tactic Kim just did
broke it up and was good.
Kim Gun-woo's
trying to stop Belov's momentum.
Kim's normally an aggressive fighter,
but he keeps getting pushed back.
Gun-woo steps back again.
This isn't going well.
It's clear
Kim's taken some damage already.
Belov hooks left and right,
driving Kim into the corner again.
And Kim backs up and babysits the corner.
Right jab, left jab. Adik keeps attacking!
Kim clinches Adik again.
Kim's tactic seems to be
to hold off Adik for as long as possible.
First round's over
and Adik Belov clearly dominated.
Yes.
And that's the end of the first round.
His punches are quick.
His infighting's good.
Catch your breath.
Focus.
Don't let him get to you.
Be in his face and don't back down.
You know there's no one alive
who can beat you.
Look at me, man.
Kim Gun-woo.
Trust your infighting.
Trust what we've built.
Eat the competition.
Number three's loading.
Calling in the order.
- Ack!
Ack!
Round two begins.
Kim looks more determined
at the start of this second round.
Kim's being more aggressive.
It's good to see him not back away.
It's great. Kim gives
well-landed body blows to Belov's side,
followed with quick combos.
It's a great series
of uppercuts and a hook.
Now, it's Belov retreating.
Kim's fighting
more like his usual style now.
Kim's displaying
his infighting technique and combos
in this second round.
His coach must've reminded him
who he is and what he's here to do.
He needed to be more aggressive
than he was in the first round.
Kim mixes up his striking
combos as he closes the distance
with a series to Belov's head and body.
Those punches land quickly
with force and precision.
- Belov into the corner.
- Things have turned!
- Number three!
- Kim's got the upper hand.
He delivers a barrage of blows to Belov.
Kim keeps pouring on the punches!
Those were fast and tight combos.
Kim lands a perfect straight punch!
It had power, speed and force.
What?
I can't believe this. He stopped.
That would've been the finishing blow.
He would've won. But he stopped.
That punch was going straight to the eye
and would've landed cleanly.
But Kim stopped.
- He stopped it just as the bell rang.
- Yeah.
The sportsmanship tonight.
It shows what kind of athlete Kim is.
In the second round,
Kim not only showed his commanding skills,
but also his sportsmanship to his fans.
Kim had a great momentum
in the second round.
His fans are on fire.
I'm looking forward to what
we'll see from him in the third round.
Kim Gun-woo! Kim Gun-woo!
- This one's yours.
- Yeah?
Belov's got a gash on his left eye.
Finish him off
with your right jab quickly.
Stop the blood! How's it looking?
- Woo-jin.
- Yeah?
Can't we go with number one?
We're almost finished. Why change?
- I gotta fight!
- I need you to focus.
- I need to win!
- Focus!
He'll need a dozen stitches to his face.
I can still win
by using number one instead.
No way. Too risky.
He's the champion.
You've got to stay the course and finish
it off when you have the chance.
We should trust the number one.
Trust what we've made and who we are.
It's just you and me.
He's gonna attack that left eye
with a right hook or a right straight.
Duck it, get in close,
and finish this thing.
- Yeah.
- Do that for me?
I understand.
So instead, punch him very quickly.
Mm-hmm. Fast.
Like the speed of light!
Lightening!
- Ack!
Ack!
Go!
You'll win this for Uzbekistan, Adik!
Round three begins.
Kim raises his guard, and he rushes
forward as Adik stays frozen.
Kim lands a left hook onto Adik's side!
It went clean
on the right side of Adik's body.
Wow, Belov quickly collapses.
Will he be able to get up?
- You can do it! Come on!
- Didn't take that punch well.
Belov's still down on the ground, in pain.
Belov took some heavy damage!
Is this the end?
- Nine.
- We're at the count of nine.
The match has been called!
It's over!
Kim gave a fight-ending KO.
Kim Gun-woo is the new
WBC super middleweight champion!
Kim Gun-woo! Kim Gun-woo!
Are you okay?
You're a good fighter. Forget what I said.
It's just business.
Thank you.
Gun-woo, see what I got. Look.
Gross. Why do people smoke this?
Throw it out.
- No way. This… …cost 100,000 won.
- It did?
But I'll throw it.
I'll throw it away.
Done. It was nice.
Having the cigar.
You just wasted money though.
Hey, we used to be so broke
we could barely afford the buffets.
Now, we throw cigars away.
And now you're the champion. The winner!
For real.
It feels like yesterday
we took down Kim Myeong-gil.
It's gone by so quickly.
What now?
Woo-jin,
should we go visit Mr. Choi's grave
with the championship belt?
Geez, you've grown up.
Not like your coach.
- I know.
- What?
I'm just playing!
You've grown so much now
you even know how to joke around.
I learned that from you.
Do you know why I'm grateful to you?
- Huh?
- Im, the loan shark.
When we went to borrow money
from that guy, he said he'd lend it
if we became bloodhounds.
That was his stipulation.
Here's a first-tier loan of 100 million.
In exchange, you'll do some work for me.
I would probably
be beating people up for money…
if you hadn't told me to leave
when he asked us.
It's thanks to you, Gun-woo,
that this belt's here, with us.
No, not at all.
You're the reason.
You're why we're here now.
Without you, we wouldn't have been able
to take down Kim Myeong-gil.
And also,
I wouldn't have been able to make it
this far. Not if I stayed with Coach Kim.
It's all because of you that we're here,
and as champions of the world.
Retiring as a boxer
and working as your coach
was the only decision
I could have done to change our lives.
But we're not stopping here.
We're going onwards.
Let's be the champions of the universe.
Until we die together,
we'll say, "Ack!" together.
- Ack!
Ack!
Time to turn them.
No, they got
30 more seconds of cooking left.
- Oh, just do it.
- No way.
It's time. Just try.
Huh?
Well, what's this?
I put more charcoal
when you weren't looking.
When did you do that?
- Thank you.
- Of course.
It's good.
- Grab two blue ones.
- Yes.
- Hmm.
- Mmm.
- Let's have the neck meat now.
- Mm.
- Oh my! Well, hello. Good to see you.
- Good evening, Ms. Yoon. Congratulations.
Hello, Ms. Yoon.
I'm sorry to bother you this evening.
Oh, no, no, you're always welcome.
Come in!
I was on a business trip.
I went to Taiwan and I thought of you,
so I got you a little gift.
- I hope you don't mind.
- Really? You shouldn't have.
Oh, it's so generous.
Thank you so much.
It's something small,
so accept it without obligation.
Oh, jeez.
You always make delicious food
when I come here.
Oh my, you're always welcome here.
Don't just stand there.
Thanks.
- Gun-woo, Woo-jin! Min-beom's here.
- Oh! Oh.
Congratulations!
Look what I have!
- Oh, the belt! Wow, nice.
- It's big.
I wanted to be there,
but my trip got extended.
- I'm sorry.
- I understand.
He clobbered his opponent in three rounds.
It finished quickly.
That fast?
I've got good news myself.
- Let's have a drink?
- Sounds good.
Great.
- Well done, you two.
- Cheers!
Drink all that at once?
Cheers!
Ha.
Mmm!
IIL SEOUL HOSPITAL
AERIAL RENDERING
Whoa.
My new approved project.
It's four floors underground,
ten floors above ground.
When our nonprofit grows more,
this is where I'll build
the pediatric hospital.
Once we build that,
we'll name the hospital
Tae-ho Pediatric Clinic, after Mr. Choi.
That's so freaking cool.
I know.
Min-beom, Gun-woo,
let's all raise our glasses
for those who aren't here.
Friends in heaven?
Let's say,
"Thanks for everything."
Yes. Mm.
Thanks for everything.
Yes, thank you.
Where are we going?
You will fight
to pay your debt.
Look at this.
Let's do it tomorrow.
Tomorrow, there will be
a million-dollar interest.
Ah, fuck!
Take Adik.
The fighter's here.
Hey.
Put them in.
For real?
I can kill someone.
It happens.
That's fucked up, man.
You losing over $3 million
in two hours in a poker game is fucked up.
We know where your daughter lives.
That's fucked up.
Pick that up.
Welcome to
the Iron Knuckle Fighting Championship.
Go in. You two, wait over there.
Okay, let's go, LOL.
At last, the undisputed
WBC super middleweight champion,
Adik Belov, just showed up at IKFC36.
The showdown between the Hunter
and Bulldozer's about to begin!
So better get the bets ready
'cause we're about to go down!
We've passed 300 million.
We've now gone past 400 million.
Our commission will be 12 million.
- How much is my amount?
- Well, more than if you were sleeping.
Say exactly how much, motherfucker.
At least, maybe,
three times more than before.
You motherfucker.
I needed to ask for more money.
'Cause you're too fucking easy!
Let's start this.
Let's fight!
Ah!
Destroying Adik now.
Oh, shit. Look at Adik's face!
He's bitching!
Cameras off.
Cameras off now.
How much did I make?
Twelve times more than before.
Bring me the one who beat the idiot.
Okay, will do.
Did you find anything useful there?
I'm able to hear a pulse.
I think I can get some things.
What about his heart?
His heartbeat sounds good.
It must be because he's a fighter.
How much can I get?
Fifty million won for the heart.
Double that for the kidneys.
That sounds very good.
Move over.
Hey.
How can I sell him if you kill him? Hey!
We're not gonna sell body parts this way.
It'll leave evidence.
He wants his next fighter.
It'll be Kim Gun-woo.
Two, three.
- Have you been exercising?
- Yes.
Okay, that's awesome.
Try it on your own without my help.
You're going to straighten your fingers.
A little bit more. Keep trying.
You're doing it.
Put more strength into it.
You're doing great. A bit more.
Keep trying. Very good.
- The kimchi's in there?
- Yeah. I put it right there.
Good, I see it. Yeah.
Try to straighten your fingers
all the way.
Good. A little bit more.
You're doing well.
Just a little bit more.
How about a little straighter?
Do it with two fingers
at a time, starting with these two.
Straighten them.
Let's see if you can do it all the way.
A little bit straighter.
Have a good rest of your day.
- She's coming.
- Thank you.
Hey. Congrats on winning the championship.
Thank you.
Today, we brought you… jangjorim.
Gun-woo's mom packed a lot.
Perfect, I finished up
all of my other food. I'll enjoy this.
Ready to go?
- Let's go to the supermarket now?
- Great.
- The button. For the elevator.
- Right, sorry.
President Hong
has been asking me to work for him.
He knows my hands
aren't as fast as before,
but I can still do the work.
Oh.
He said, next month, I can start on
the ninth floor of the Iil Group building.
- Oh.
Is the work similar
to what you did for the police?
I tracked for the
Cyber Investigation Unit. Cyber crimes.
My work at Iil Group is to protect
and secure their information network
from viruses
and potential computer crackers.
Oh, crackers.
What are crackers?
You get sick from them. It's bad.
Oh.
They're hackers with no good intent.
- Hmm.
- So bad hackers.
Hmm.
Oh, did we
go by the toilet paper aisle already?
- Looks like we did. I'll get it.
- See you soon.
Okay.
Woo-jin, could I talk to you
about something for a second?
I'm all ears.
So?
I really appreciate how you guys
help me like this every week.
It's just, well,
you really don't have to,
because there's no need
for you to feel guilty about me at all.
I was on duty as a police officer.
It wasn't anyone's fault I got this hurt.
I'm fine to do things on my own now.
Dear Tae-yeong,
we've never told you this before.
Gun-woo and I have a rule
we created together.
And what rule is that?
Once you become family,
you'll always be family.
We protect our family
with our lives to the end.
Together, for real.
It goes without saying,
Tae-yeong is
with us forever.
I… I'm sorry.
You can call us.
We're here for you always.
We're the Marine duo.
We're at your service.
- Dear Tae-yeong.
- I will.
Ack.
Tae-yeong.
Huggies.
They're dating!
Yes, who is it?
Good evening. We're friends of Gun-woo's.
I see. Well, Gun-woo isn't home
and he may return late.
Oh, we're supposed to see each other.
I might have come early.
Would it be okay if we waited inside?
We're friends because
we go to the same gym.
I see.
We were at the same match
where he won the title.
It's too bad we didn't say hi.
Is it okay if we wait inside?
Because it's cold?
Oh, well, sure.
Hold on while I let you in.
That was fun.
You're home.
- Mom, go upstairs.
- Why?
Please wait upstairs.
Don't bother being brave. Take a seat.
I said sit.
Sit down and let's talk.
Who are you?
I'm running a boxing corporation
called the IKFC.
I want you. You should join my league.
I know nothing about this league.
You wouldn't know
because it's very private.
Private and successful, with a membership
of four million worldwide.
You'd be a great addition to my roster.
Sounds like made-up nonsense.
IKFC?
It's a chicken place?
We don't do fights with chickens.
What did you make fighting Adik?
Hundred million?
Two hundred million won?
In IKFC, one match
will pay you ten billion.
Ten billion won.
A billion just to accept.
Gun-woo,
if you get hurt boxing,
you'll be a cripple for life.
I know too many guys who got fucked.
Make the dough while you can. Hmm?
Just fight one match. The upcoming event.
Your money worries will disappear.
With that much fucking money,
who in your family
would even have to work?
You would take care of everybody.
It's just one match.
For fuck's sake.
Hey,
an extra five billion if you win? Hmm?
Fifteen billion won?
Mom.
Who wants that much money?
They said they were your friends
from the gym. That's why I let them in.
What kind of people who lie so easily
have money that's clean?
Dirty money always comes
with a price, Gun-woo.
You have to go now and leave our house.
Hey, ma'am,
shut your fucking mouth.
You need to take your money and fuck off!
Sir.
Remember, we came here for a reason.
Let's go now.
Go fuck yourself.
Shut up.
Shut up and fucking stay still. Got it?
Everyone always gives me what I want.
You and I are gonna fight together.
See you around.
We're fine. It's okay.
You'll bring me his fucking mom.
If the payment's upfront.
They'll come back here for sure.
We'll be ready for them.
We'll be ready so we can destroy them
when they return.
Woo-jin… are you still in touch
with Yang Jae-myeong?
That asshole knew the world of boxing.
Let's ask Yang Jae-myeong.
Mm.
DIRT-DIGGER YANG
Well, well, well,
it's been too long, hasn't it?
Long time no see.
You ask and I give, again. I got you
all, all, all the information.
What? It's not there? Really?
No, it's not.
These come directly
from the Korean Boxing Association.
They fit the weight class and description
you gave, so that's that.
Could you check one weight class below?
Maybe his weight has changed.
Oh, you're right. That's the answer.
Give me a little longer
and that info's all yours.
Oh, and also, do you have information
on this group, IKFC?
I called the illegal fight clubs and
no one has heard anything about IKFC.
It might not be in Korea.
Maybe they're located abroad?
If you consider the name,
it sounds international.
Worldwide. They did say
they have four million members.
That many? Whoa, four million?
The stakes must be so big
with that many millions in the group.
Please explain what exactly that means.
Well, think about it.
That's four million people.
If they each put ten thousand won in,
how much will that be?
Forty billion won, that's how much.
Right? The fees must be outrageous too.
Thanks very much.
- Gun-woo.
- Yes?
We might need help.
We should ask the guys for it.
Like who?
Min-beom. Gang-yong.
Moon Gwang-mu. Everyone.
I don't want any of them to get hurt
because of me, Woo-jin.
Yeah, it hurts me, too, and I feel guilty.
Especially about Tae-yeong.
Then we'll do it together,
just the two of us.
We took Kim Myeong-gil down on our own.
We got him because we had help.
The other guys were there with us.
Mm. Yes, we had help then.
But
can't we just try
to do it on our own this time?
Hmm?
I've been thinking
about how we can kidnap Gun-woo's mother.
The four of them
are serving life sentences in prison.
They all would be good.
They've got a grudge against Kim Gun-woo
and his friend, Hong Woo-jin.
If we can get them out of prison,
we'll get relentless bloodhounds
that will never give up.
Can we control them?
I see why you're concerned.
They won't have any choice
but to rely on us
since they'll be wanted criminals.
And if they help us get the job done,
I'll throw a carrot and offer to help them
to escape to somewhere abroad.
How much does that cost?
100 million won. For each person.
Shitface. That's fucking expensive.
The profit's going to be
more than ten times the cost.
You're full of shit.
This one.
The one I would've picked.
There's a security company I always use
whenever I have VIPs visiting from abroad.
The founders are
former presidential security agents,
which means they're thorough.
But recently, their sales director
and their CEO had a falling out.
By default, their hired hands
haven't been paid for a very long time.
So what?
There's a small risk
of things not going our way.
Well, especially because gangsters
and ex-cons are rough.
So in case Ms. Yoon gets hurt,
things could get really messy,
which isn't what we want.
So I recommend we use them,
even if it costs a little more extra.
Shit, another way
to get extra funds? Just handle it.
During jobs like these there are
all sorts of variables that might happen.
That's why… you should
go with a bloodhound who has our back.
That's a golden rule when I'm working.
No mistakes.
Thanks for the payment.
Hmm.
Will you get these for me?
GASOLINE, DDNP, SALTPETER
NICHROME, DETONATOR, CELL PHONE
There's no reason
to go this far, Sergeant Yun.
I need to be ready, Mr. Lee.
Well,
trust what I do.
I still need to be ready and prepared.
TAO TE CHING
SWALLOW THIS AT 1 P.M. TWO DAYS FROM NOW
I'LL GET YOU OUT
With this last one,
you have eight in total.
It should be good.
- Thank you.
- Gun-woo!
- You outside?
- Yeah.
Adik's team is leaving today.
Yet, Adik has disappeared.
He's gone missing.
UZBEK BOXER MISSING AFTER TITLE FIGHT.
POLICE INVESTIGATING.
I have a bad feeling, Woo-jin.
I think those assholes are behind this.
Sir, this is the job?
It's just,
why do we have to stoop so low?
We're trained to protect.
How does it help to say this now?
We agreed to do it.
Don't you understand
we're about to go under?
We need to pay the other guys too.
Hey. They trusted us.
They worked hard and what did they get?
Broken bodies.
- Yes, I know that, of course, but--
- Jin-nam.
Stay in the car. We'll handle it.
Mr. Jang,
we can't finish the job with two.
Let's give it a go.
Bingo.
FRONT DOOR
Yes?
You can go in.
Let's do it.
Oh, Mom!
- Gun-woo!
- They're taking her.
- My mom!
- Mom!
- Don't fight. I will.
- It's my job.
Shit! You fucker!
- Woo-jin.
- What is it?
- I've gotta go.
- What?
Gun-woo, are you okay?
Ugh!
We've gotta go.
Agh!
Shit!
Oh, oh, oh!
You okay?
- It hurts a lot!
- Gun-woo!
Come on, let's go. Let's leave now.
You okay?
- Here. Can you get up?
- No, my… My mom's there!
Hold on, I've got you.
Come on, let's go!
Hey, stop!
Get up! Let's go! Come on!
Drive faster! Floor it!