I...
miss you.
You miss him that much?
Yeah.
Then call him.
I do not dare to call him, P?Hill.
I'm afraid that I might disturb him.
I miss you.
I miss you so much.
Having you by my side,
makes everything better.
Will you be my boyfriend?
P'Jo
Why do you like me?
There are many people who have a crush on you.
But why me?
I don't even see anything interesting in myself.
I like you since forever ago. Why?
Can you tell me more?
About what?
About since when did you start to like me.
You wanna hear it?
Come sit here.
Kiss me one time and I'll answer you one question.
No freaking way.
Why not?
Don't you want to know anymore?
I don't have to tell you then.
What do you want to know?
Well...
I want to know...
how long have you liked me?
Like since when?
It's been so long. Like since 3 years ago.
3 years!?
That means...
since I was in grade 10 then?
That's also another question.
You're cheating.
I had a big crush on you back then,
you know that?
-  But you rejected me.
- Huh!?
Me?
Rejecting you?
- I've gotta leave for school.
- You're late again today.
- You're so beautiful again today.
- Hmm. My grandson is such a player.
- Rong. Don't forget to buy Jo as usual.
- Yes ma'am.
Can I just skip it?
No, you cannot
cause you neve wake up in time for breakfast.
And come back for the dinner this evening too.
- Sure. Sure.
- There.
- I really have to go.
- Yeah.
Wow. How rich must I be to have a house this big?
Can't I just skip it?
You may not, sir.
Your grandma already ordered me.
Don't let that kid make it.
Cannot. We also cannot choose who to make.
Did you tell him not to make it sweet?
Yes, I normally do.
He always make it so sweet.
- Please make sure that he doesn't make it sweet.
- Sure.
All done. Thank you.
Oh uncle again.
- You want the usual?
- Yes, but don't make it sweet.
Sure sir.
How can I make it good If it's not sweet?
All set.
I also give you free fried dumplings cause you're my regular customer.
- Enjoy the food.
- Sure.
Here uncle.
There you go sir.
Ughh. So sweet.
That kid made this soy milk again?
Next time, don't let this kid make my soy milk please.
But we can't force other people to do or not to do, sir.
But he's such s sweet kid,
he gave me free fried dumplings.
He told me it's because I'm his regular customer.
Hey.
Why do you like this stall so much?
Eat it everyday.
I don't have a choice.
My grandma makes me.
Oh and do you remember the kid who sells?
He comes to my shop so often.
Who?
You drink his soy milk everyday,
but you don't remember him?
Do I need to memorize who he is?
Johan.
You should pay attention to your surroundings too.
Wanna read?
This?
Hey.
Why are you two dressing like this?
Your shirt is not tucked in, the ties are undone.
And you're not even wearing one.
For the hair,
why don't you guys get a nice hair cut?
Ugh miss. People do not care
or be conservative on how you dress anymore.
Stop talking!
Frank is also just like you guys. The three of you...
always bend the rules.
What are you looking for?
It's just the two of us sitting here.
Where's Frank?
Stop fooling around.
Come see me at my office.
Lucky us!
- Let's chill at the nice A/C room.
- Yeah. We don't have to be in the class too.
You guys!
What now?
Would you like us to be in your office or in the class?
Come see me at my office at noon, lunch break.
Now, go stand for the morning national flag.
- Get up! Why are you still sitting? Put these stuff away too.
- Go. Go.
You are always stay out of the line.
Don't let me see you two in these conditions again.
You're sure she's not gonna be pissed?
She wants to see you in her office, doesn't she?
- I'll do that some other days.
- Going to my cafe?
Let's play some chess.
7 rounds of chess.
- Huh?N- Come play  the chess with me. Just a min.
- You're at the internet cafe, Frank.
- But I wanna play chess.
- Hey but I wanna play games.
- Play with me first. Just for a minute. Play games later.
- You can't play games just yet!
- I'll hit you!
Dude!
You guys are playing chess?
- Ask him. I was playing video games,
- You're at an internet cafe, but you're playing chess?
Yeah.
I'll be back.
There we go.
Johan. Are you skipping class again?
The teacher called me.
Why do you ask since you already knew?
Why don't you be in class?
I'm lazy.
When are you gonna stop acting like this?
I'm okay if you're not gonna pay attention in class or whatever.
If you don't wanna study, then resign and come work with me.
Don't act like this.
What I do is my business, doesn't it?
Aren't you so sick of hearing people tell you
that don't know anything in life?
Always rely on your parents like this?
And how many times have you said this?
Aren't you so sick of saying it?
I am! I'm so sick of disciplining you.
Yeah then that's it.
Hey Frank!
- There.
- Here. Here. I'll capture all of them. I'm done playing.
You cheated!
- Your dad called?
- Um.
Hey.
Let's play some games to cool down your mood.
Shall we?
- I'll go with you guys.
- You just play your chess.
- You're done at 6.30pm, right?
- Yes.
- I'll come pick you up.
- See you.
Be have okay?
Bye bye.
She's blushing.
Oh you come so late today.
I got caught up a bit.
- As usual.
This one too.
Hello. What's up?
North, where are you? At home?
No, I'm at the internet cafe.
What do you want?
I need help with my homework. Have to hand in tomorrow.
Are you free?
I guess I am. Come see me here then.
Ok. I'll be there.
Okay okay.
Come on.
Let's play some games.
Help me. Help me.
Hey.
Let's do some homework for me, my friend.
Which subject?
The survey.
I need people to fill out the survey for me,
but hasn't reached the number yet.
So I think...
I'll just ask them myself.
What's the topic?
Their opinions towards rich or poor people.
Something like that.
- Damn. Your topic is actually interesting. Do you wanna know mine?
- What is it?
- Kibble food that dogs like.
- For real?
Yeah.
- Shit.
- It's for people who are new to owning a dog.
What do you wanna ask me?
What do you think of rich people?
What do other people say?
Mostly jealous.
They are born with golden and silver spoons.
They're good in life, yeah?
But some people also say that those who are rich by self-made,
those are more respectable than
who are rich because of their parents,
Those are not the real rich.
- Why?
- Hey.
Because those who are born in a rich family,
they're already living comfortably.
They don't have to study. Don't have to work.
Unlike you that you have to work your ass off for yourself.
What do you think?
Me?
To be honest, it depends.
If...
their parents are rich and they're happy with it...
it's their business.
Don't you think it's unfair?
Those who are rich,
they can be successful easily.
Loot at you.
You have to work so hard.
It's never fair in this world, isn't it?
It's not like you're born rich
and you'll be successful.
You need to use your ability
and your skills to make it happen to.
I actually think those people,
they might have a different kind of pressure
that we would never expect either.
Think about it, being rich...
you exist in the society.
You are being judged and compared...
Life like that is not easy.
But...
rich people might have a better start in lives than others.
Like if they wanna start a business,
even if they fall or fail,
they would never really hurt that much.
cause they have all the support to support them.
It's like they fall onto the their own bed.
And what do you think of those
who still ask their parents for money?
Umm..there's nothing wrong with that actually.
If their parents are okay,
and they are happy doing that,
it's their business.
But If I were them,
if I have the support and a good start,
I would wanna start doing something.
And if people look down on me,
I will do it and prove them.
That I have skills and I can do it.
- You're so cool!
- For sure.
- Quote me on that too.
- Of course.
- I need to quote you on that.
- Put a picture of me crossing my arm over my chest like a life coach.
- Isn't that too much?
- Hey do it.
I'm so cool, am I not?
Why are you standing there, Jo?
Don't you go inside and eat.
Hmm?
Grandma.
Do you think I'm useless?
Why do you think that way?
Cause...
I have never done anything.
Never studied.
Always fooling around.
People probably think I jsut use my parents' money everyday.
It's your father again, isn't it?
And do you think you're that kind of person?
You're never useless in my eyes.
You're my grandson. I would do anything for you.
I love you.
Yeah, grandma.
But if I were them,
f I have the support and a good start,
I would wanna start doing something.
And if people look down on me,
I will do it and prove them.
That I have skills and I can do it.
What are you reading?
Such a wimp.
You look stressed.
- Oh James.
- Hmm?
Do you remember that kid from soy milk stall?
Yeah why do you ask?
Tell me more about him.
- About North?
- The guy who always come play games at your cafe.
- Um.
- His name is North?
Um his name is North.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
t's just that I heard him talking to his friend yesterday.
Why?
It went right through your heart huh?
To be honest, he's actually the opposite of you.
From what I heard, his dad died.
he lives with his mom and his aunt.
Their family is not well off.
He has to do extra jobs.
Isn't he like in grade 10 only?
He's been working since junior high.
And what's he like?
He's a pretty chill guy.
People can be themselves around him.
- He's really like that?
- Yeah.
North is very lively.
- Follow me.
- On my way.
- Fire. Fire.
- I got one down.
Nice.
- I got it.
- Nice.
- Alright. Alright.
- Hey. Hey. Shh.
My mom. My mom.
Hello, mom?
Have you eaten, North?
I did.
What about you?
I also did.
Oh mom.
I will spend a night at my friend's today.
Why?
We will work on a group project.
Ok. Take care then.
Sure mom. Don't miss me though.
Sure~
Sure mom.
- Go in.
- North.
Are you sure lying to your mom like that?
Yeah I'm gonna work on my group project.
But our project is done.
Cause I wanna play games.
I can't stop playing here.
Up to you then.
- North.
- Why are you calling me? Just walk there.
- North!
- Oh mom!
You said you're working on a group project?
Tae. Ball.
Yes?
I already called your parents to come pick you guys up.
They will be here soon.
Thank you.
- And for you, come here.
- Ow. Mom.
- Come here.
- Mom. Mom.
You're lying to me now?
I'm fine with you addicted to playing games,
- But this is too much. Not going home. People do worry, you know?
- Ow. Mom.
Don't fool around like this.
Ow. Mom.
- You're embarrassing me.
- I'm not embarrassed.
You should be.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Don't say sorry now.
You're twisting my ears like this.
Are you hurt? i do care about you.
Let's go find something yummy to eat, shall we?
So you might be in a better mood.
Please mom.
Eat something yummy.
So you can be in a better mood, shall we?
Hey you're smiling now.
- Let's go eat.
- Um. Fine.
- Something yummy, okay? Let's go.
- Yeah.
Stop being mad at me, yeah?
- Wait mom.
- What?
I forgot my bag.
Hurry and go get it.
Ok mom.
I'll be right back.
Hey guys.
See you.
I will go deal my mom first.
Good luck.
- I'm back.
- Come on. Hurry up.
Let's go eat.
Which restaurant shall we go?
- The meatball is also good.
- is it?
- It is.
- Sure.
And what kind of a person is he?
He's a pretty chill guy.
People can be themselves around him.
Right. Right. Done!
There're so many ways dude.
Hey hey. I found one.
Oh.
Here. Here. Behind me. Go in.
Behind me.
Be careful. Behind you!
Hey.
Dude. I'm hungry.
I will go use the restroom. Be right back.
I'm back.
Whose snacks are these?
If no one claims it, it will be mine now.
I'm back. Wait a minute.
Yeah just like that. I got you.
I'm going in! There!
Sorry mate.
Come on.
Feels like someone is following behind me.
Hey how can you jump and shoot me?
What are you? A bird?
Thank you.
Please P'James.
I already gave you a few minutes.
A bit more please.
How long did you play just now?
- 2 hours.
- And you want more?
2 more.
What a way for me to make so much profits.
Please. I don't normally ask you this.
I just gave you some.
Fine. I'll give you 2 more.
- 2 hours?
- 2 minutes.
I cannot even log into the game just 2 mins.
What!?
Can I ask you something?
If...
What!?
Do you think...
is it weird if I like someone even that person has never done anything for me?
What are you actually asking?
And what do you think?
What do people do if they like someone?
Are they gonna take bullets for each other like the movies?
Bang. Bang.
I don't know.
It's not weird.
You can just see someone and fall for them too.
Why? Who are you having crush on?
Yeah...a person like you, Jo?
- Who is it?
- How am I supposed to know?
He's a Nong.
(Thais use Nong to call someone younger)
Nong?
North!?
Yeah.
I knew it!
You always check him out.
And you've been coming to my cafe a lot too.
You really like him for real? Why though?
I'm not sure why either.
That's why I ask whether it's possible for someone to like a person that has never done anything to you?
But it's not totally true that he's never done anything to me.
He's the reason why I wanna change myself.
I wanna see him smile.
I don't wanna see him being cute with anyone else.
I don't think you just like him, but you're obsessed with him.
Let me take care of this for you.
Are you gonna make it work or worse?
We're rooting for you.
What are you doing?
Trust me.
- What are you gonna do? Tell me first.
- Just stay still.
- North.
- Yes, P'?
- I have question.
- What is it?
My friend really likes you.
He actually wanna tell you himself,
but I think I should ask you first.
Whether you're dating someone?
I am actually.
Oh really?
Um.
How come I don't know?
Last time, you said you're not dating anyone.
I was trying to pursue her back then.
We just made it official a few days ago.
I'm sorry.
But...
my friend really likes you...like a lot.
Don't you wanna try talking? Just a little?
Ugh.
I told you. I'm already seeing someone.
If I agree to do that, that means I'll be cheating.
Um.
but my friend really likes you, North.
Wrong timing I guess.
- I'm sorry bro.
- Um.
- You'll find soon.
- Run. Run.
- You need to use your pinky.
- Pinky finger?
It looks more professional.
- Oh it's more professional?
- Yeah.
- Run. Run.
- Using your thumb doesn't look professional.
- This?
- Here. Found it.
- Go in.
- Okay. Oh.
Why?
Run. Run. Like that.
So?
He's always here playing games with his girl everyday.
You're sitting there like a sad dog.
I give you that.
Seeing him with his girlfriend everyday.
I wanna see him. Not his girlfriend.
You're always here looking at him for months.
Does he have any idea that...
there's someone
so obsessed with his smile like this?
He can do anything just to see his smile. Wow.
So romantic.
I thought I should be fine at first,
but how come it hurts a little.
When you love someone,
you need to spare your feelings.
It can be hurtful too, Jo.
But for a person who's never been in love with anyone,
I know...
that it must be difficult.
Damn.
I feel bad for you.
Even...
there's someone for you to love,
but...
you don't even have the chance to at least try.
He rejects you all the way,
But that's good.
At least you know that he's faithful to his partner.
Um.
What are you gonna do now?
Giving up?
I think...
it's less likely that he'll breakup with his girl soon.
I think so too.
I probably won't be able to see him again.
- I ask my dad to work too.
- Huh?
I get the not seeing him part.
But you're gonna work!?
Are you sure?
Um.
It's because of him.
I wanna try doing something meaningful too.
What was your dad reaction?
He was surprised.
But he said If I take it seriously,
he will let me live with my uncle in LA.
LA?
And...are you going?
Um.
I'll probably go there for a year.
Then come back for university here.
It's the only way that I can move on from him.
Go. Go.
Nice. Oh.
What?
P'James.
Hey who allow you to walk in?
The sign says staff only.
I'm not an outsider.
This is like my second home already.
What do you need?
Hey. You're playing guitar?
Um.
I'm actually practicing it.
Really?
- You wanna try?
- Sure.
What song do you wanna play?
Umm...
I'm into country songs about life lately.
You are?
Um.
Kinda tired and feeling hopeless.
So I need to listen to songs that inspire me.
Also, I have a problem with my girlfriend.
About what? Tell me.
I don't know.
I've been dating her for 2 months already.
But seems like she's never been happy being with me.
She's tired after class sometimes,
and she doesn't wanna see me.
I understand that she's tired,
but....
I wanna be someone who helps with her tiredness.
So you feel like...
you're useless to her?
I guess so.
If I date someone, I wanna be like a sanctuary for them.
Being together
and improving each other's lives.
Um.
I wanna help her no matter what happens,
But...
I can't help her with anything.
Even if...
I tried so hard already.
So I think...
It would be nice if you're with someone
who really wants you to be in their lives.
Hey.
Why am I telling you all those?
I actually wanted you to fix the computer.
The screen is blacked out.
- Um. You go wait outside. I'll be there in a sec.
- Hurry up please.
- Um.
- My hour is running.
Right. I'll do it.
- i'm losing my hour here.
- Go.
- Still not coming?
- You go ahead.
- Hurry up, P'.
- Yeah.
You heard that right?
Um.
You said you wanna move on.
But heard something like that...
are you sure you can?
Someone he wants to be with...
Someone who will improve each other's lives...
That's you.
But what can I do?
I can't do anything.
Should you just steal him from her?
- Why would I do that for?
- Hey.
If I do that,
he will be the one who disappoints the most.
I don't want to take his smiles away.
What a good guy.
You're leaving tomorrow?
Um.
Call us sometimes.
Maybe this is for the best,
taking time to heal yourself.
If you live here, you wouldn't be able to move on.
True.
I think this is enough already for this one.
I wanted you to wait for him actually,
but I don't think you should anymore.
I also don't wanna wait anymore.
It hurts.
James, please look after him.
Yeah.
I will.
- Oh. That was easy.
- Here. Here. There's one more.
- Same spot.
- Here?
So that was from someone who said he wants to move on.
Why isn't he running?
Jump.
Uncle.
- Hmm?
- The uncle doesn't come anymore?
Yeah, he doesn't come anymore.
You make it too sweet for him.
It's not. I always taste it first.
Or he switched to buy from some other places?
Yeah, just hurry, close up, and go to school already.
Come on. Hurry up.
There. There. Pack it all up over there.
- P'James.
- Um?
Same one for 2 hours.
Ok same table.
Thank you.
And how's everything with your girlfriend?
Good.
We're together for almost a year now.
Really?
Last time you said she doesn't wanna be with you?
Well...
now we're okay.
That's good.
- I have to go.
- Um.
- Oh, P'James.
- Hmm?
You know...
there's is this one guy who always gives me snacks.
Do you know who is this?
Does he....?
still come around?
Why do you ask?
I haven't seen him for so long already.
When I stay here really late,
he's always hang around with me.
Nothing...I just...
wanna give him back some snacks too.
Cause he's been giving me so often.
I will tell him for you if I see him.
- Sure. I'm really gonna go now.
- Um.
I brought you some snacks too.
That's mine though, but thanks.
All done.
Thank you.
Oh hey uncle!
I haven't seen you for so long.
My boss actually went to study abroad.
Boss?
You normally buy for someone else?
I thought you always buy it for yourself.
No, I always buy it for my young boss.
I can make less sweet soy milk now.
Yummy for sure.
I will give you free fried dumplings as usual.
Since you haven't been here for awhile.
It's fine. This time is on me.
Please tell your young boss 'Welcome home' for me.
Sure.
He told you that?
Yes.
You ran aways for a year,
but fall for him again because of a few fried dumplings?
I've been hearing the word 'wait' everyday.
'When is he gonna come?'
My friend is so into it.
Oh he was asking for you
when he came to my cafe too.
Why did you tell him that?
Hey.
You didn't see anyone when you were in LA?
I couldn't do it.
I tried to open my mind,
but I always miss him.
So...
you went away for a year...
but you cannot move on still?
If you're still like this...
you will stuck with him your whole life.
When I go to university and no longer see him,
will I be able move on from him?
You went to La, which is very far, you still cannot.
What do you think then?
Yeah.
Right.
Are you trying to kill me?
Oops. Sorry from the behind.
Shit!
There's no one left here.
Am I gonna meet any ghosts here?
I have to go.
Yeah see you.
Hey dude.
I can continue playing now.
There's someone just walked in.
Let's play until the sunrise.
Yeah do it.
Come behind me.
I heard. I heard.
What time is it now?
Huh!?
For real?
I have to go for real.
My mom will probably yell at me now.
Thanks for hanging around with me.
Gotta go.
You'll be here alone now.
Please hang with me at night like you used to do it.
I'm scared of ghosts.
It's like you're trying to mess with me,
when I'm trying to move on here.
At the end...
I still cannot do it.
But when I got into meds faculty,
I met Hill, Fah, and Arthit.
I decided not to see you again.
Just live my life.
Never care about anyone.
Acted like a player. Never approached anyone first.
I thought I could move on from you.
It's Trigonometry.
You asked me this during the class too. Memorize it.
Jo. Have you heard of  the new?
He got a scholarship to study in the US.
Hey Jo. Where are you going?
I know that you wanna move on from him.
But today is his last orientation.
Don't you wanna go see him a little?
To at least congratulate him.
After today, you might not get to see him ever again.
We should break up.
Good luck.
James.
He just got dumped.
What happened?
What should I do? I don't wanna see him cry.
Go comfort him.
He doesn't even know me.
Then buy something for him.
You can make him smile...maybe.
Do you have any other dolls?
No, I sold it all. This is the only one left.
- I'll take this one then.
- THB250.
I don't have any cash. Do you take credit card?
I don't know how it use that.
I will transfer to pay you then.
I take cash only.
I will pay with this then.
Oh. It's too much.
No, you can't do this. It's too expensive.
Also...do you have any pen and paper?
Yes.
Here.
Err...your watch is too expensive son.
Nong.
Can you give this to that guy?
Someone wants to give you this.
Smile please :)
Why do you look so silly, huh?
Hey North.
What did Jah talk to you about?
Oh...
- I just got dumped.
- Huh!?
- How!?
- Like broke up?
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
Forget it.
Are you sure you're okay?
You just got dumped.
Her look.
It's cute, isn't it?
Looking so silly.
- Someone gave you this?
- Yeah.
It's so damn cute.
Shit.
But it actually looks like you.
Suits you.
- You said I look liks this duck?
- No. No.
- Look at him.
- But it's cute.
Cute. Cute.
- Let's go.
- See you.
Yeah.
I am smiling. Thank you.
Where have you gone?
Where are you now?
At a bar.
Alone?
Um.
Where are you? I'll see you there.
What's going on?
Why are you so drunk like this?
I don't know, Hill.
I don't understand either.
Why?
- Why?
- Hey Jo.
Calm down.
I don't like the way I feel like this.
I don't like myself for being like this.
Hill.
Do you ever have someone you want to be in your life,
but you just can't?
You can give him everything,
literally anything...
just to see him smile.
But why...
why can't I have him by my side?
Dude...
What if I say I have someone like that...
are you gonna believe me?
Easter?
East means like where the sunrise.
That's nice.
North also means like in the north.
Yeah.
And he's going to America soon?
Too bad.
the fact that he's not seeing anyone anymore.
Um.
What about you?
He probably hates you now.
I think so.
Not surprising if that happens.
I even hate myself.
God is not on our sides, Hill.
What are you gonna do now?
What can I do?
But actually...
you've been waiting for him for so long too.
How did you do it?
It's nothing, Jo.
I just can't move on from him.
I'm stuck there.
Not that different from you.
Hill.
When tomorrow comes,
can you forget everything that happens today?
Like everything.
Including what I told you too.
Why?
I just don't wanna think about it anymore.
Wow.
Why are they this drunk?
I actually asked Hill to look after Jo.
- And why did he end up like this?
- I don't know.
I will go pay the bill.
Let's take them home.
Yeah.
Let's go. That's enough.
Hill.
Since that day, I cannot remember anything about Ter.
But Hill can remember everything.
At the end...
I couldn't move on from you.
And then you got into a fight...
because of the new boyfriend of your ex.
I'm sorry.
And thank you...
If I knew you're gonna end up crying like this...
I wouldn't tell you the whole story.
How can you not?
This is big.
Bigger than my story is you crying right now.
Why are you so good to me and love me this much?
It's been too long.
You must be in so much pain.
Not as bad as seeing you cry now.
Forget it.
Stop crying.
Ok. I will.
That's good...
that I didn't go to America.
If I went to America,
I don't know how everything's gonna turn out.
I'm just gonna go to the US more often.
That's all.
Thank you so so much.
Thank you for waiting for so long.
Thank you for never moving on from me.
I love you, P'
I love you so much,
I love you too, North.
North.
You don't have to call my name anymore.
If not by your name then what?
Babe?
Hey!
- Babe~
- No.
But I actually don't know what to do either...
I always take from you.
That's not true.
You make me want to change myself.
You are my inspiration.
and you are also my happiness.
Even you said so...
You don't have to do anything.
Just being here by my side...
forever like this, can you?
I promise...
...that I won't go anywhere.
I promise you everything.
Stop crying.
My mom invites you to visits my home.
Shall we go to my place too?
I have a present for you.
Give this to someone you love.
This is for you, Ter.
Both shooting stars and the moon.
Just only you by my side, no matter what’s gonna happen in the future.
Surprise!