When I said 'can I be with you?',
I didn't ask.
I just wanna inform.
That's not funny.
So you guys were holding hands?
I want someone
to take behind the scene pictures.
Do you know anyone?
I know a guy.
Or he's just pretending
to make me believe him?
If he doesn't take it serious with you,
he will stop eventually.
But maybe...
he might suddenly want to commit with you.
I made my mind.
- Made your mind about what?
- About what I told you.
I have moved on from him.
So I will no longer care about him.
Even if I meet him at the union or in campus,
I will just ignore him.
Like I cannot see him at all.
So he will finally stop talking to me.
How does that sound?
What?
Why are you poking me?
Dude!
How can you ignore him,
when he's picking you up like this.
Help me.
What are you doing here, P'Hill?
Picking you up.
I will go with my friend.
Hello P'Hill.
North!
Mother--
Seems like your friend is busy,
I guess.
Shall we?
I can walk myself.
- Be careful.
- Yes.
I can actually go there myself.
Ughhh. North.
Have you ever taken any photographer job?
For fun yes.
But I've never done a professional one.
Why?
The team that works on campus filming
needs a photographer.
Do you think you can do it for us?
Me?
Umm you take nice pictures.
But...
I'm not good at taking pictures of people.
You are.
There're some others
who do it better than me.
I don't want an outsider to do it.
But...
I'm also an outsider.
No, you're not.
I will be there with you.
Where do you want me to drop you off anyway?
At the library.
You still like going to the library huh?
- Hello teacher.
- Oh hey.
Can I help you with anything?
You can put these books away for me.
Anything else?
'Ratchakit Tanthikul'
Err...excuse me.
That guy he forgot this.
Can you give it back to him?
Oh sure.
That nong wants to give you this.
Nong.
Yes?
Thank you.
Oh yes.
No problem.
I found it at the library.
I always see you on that table.
I remember.
You remember me?
Yes, I do.
I'm a librarian.
I must remember things.
Then...
...can I buy you some drink to thank you?
Are you sure?
It's nothing.
I will have one with boba then.
Sure.
You're not getting any?
I don't like sweet stuff.
That's too bad.
My family owns a dessert cafe.
I thought of inviting you over.
Really?
I will stop by then.
But I thought you don't like dessert.
I wanna give it a try.
Sure, then you have to stop by!
Are you paying for me?
Yes, it will be on the house.
My mom pays.
Good.
You can taste the chocolate drink made by me.
It will be yummy. I guarantee.
You'll love it. Trust me.
Promise?
Do we have a deal?
Yayy~
Here. You have to do it like this.
Go get the car ready.
I'm leaving.
Aren't you gonna wait
and take him home too, sir?
Hello~
Please come on it.
Hello.
Any recommendation for me?
What shall you have?
Would you like to try the coconut cake?
My son said it's the best.
- I will take one please.
- Sure.
For here or to go?
- I will have it here.
- Sure. Please wait a moment.
Excuse me.
Is Ter here?
You know Ter?
I go to the same school with him.
Oh really?
He said that his family owns a dessert cafe.
So that's why I'm stopping by.
You're his senior?
He's upstairs.
I will go get him.
Make yourself comfortable.
Thank you.
I didn't think you would really come.
You invited me.
How can I not?
And...
have you ordered anything?
All done.
- What did you order?
- Here they are.
Wow~
These are like bestseller menus.
Please enjoy.
- It's on the house.
- Really?
Umm.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
You have a friend over,
I have to.
You should try.
These are made by my mom.
It's the most delicious things.
- Really?
- Why?
You don't believe me?
If you don't, then try it.
Here.
Eat. Open your mouth.
How is it?
Good?
Is it good?
Don't keep me waiting.
It's delicious.
I'm relieved.
Thought you're not gonna like it.
Good, right?
Then you need to finish all of it.
I love this cake from my cafe the most.
I've had it since I was a kid until today.
Never get bored.
So good~
Thank you so much for dropping me off.
About being the photographer,
please think about it.
I'm actually interested.
But it's just...
...I'm not that confident with myself.
Why not?
I'm afraid it might turn out bad.
Don't think too much.
You can do it.
Yes.
I will try then.
Attaboy.
I'm gonna go.
I'm so sick of you guys.
You're so disapointing.
Enough. Enough.
Are you going back with me?
Um. I will.
Really?
I thought P'Hill is gonna pick you up.
Hey.
My friend is grumpy again.
You left me with him.
I did not leave you.
I just didn't want to be a third wheel.
You left me.
Whatever.
Oh dude.
I need your advice.
- What?
- So…
P’Hill asked me to be university's photographer.
But..
I’m not so confident.
Why not?
I think your pictures are great.
They are?
Yes.
You should be confident with yourself
just like when others trust you.
Even with P’Hill,
he believes that you can do it.
That’s why he asked.
Damn…
What a line.
I must be very cool when I said that huh?
You're wasting my time.
Look again.
I’m so sick of you.
That side, bring up the limbo.
Up up.
Set the camera.
Bring the stuff over here.
Put it here.
Put it down.
Set up and make it ready.
Hey.
Who are you here to see, kiddo?
P’Hill asked me to come take pictures.
Oh the photographer.
I’m Mei Li.
I’m the production manager.
- Hello P’Mei Li.
- Hi~
I’m Easter or you can just call me Ter.
Ok nong Ter.
Anyways,
you brought your own camera?
You don’t have to next time.
We have one on set.
You can use it.
Come come.
I will introduce you to the others.
I will introduce all for you.
- Look.
- The watch is obvious.
Right.
What are you guys talking about?
Oh Mei Li is here.
- What’s up?
- It’s about Dr.Hill.
Ooh what is it about him?
Did you see his watch post?
The whole campus saw it.
Have you found out
who’s the owner of the watch?
He hasn’t told anyone at all.
He said he’s still trying.
Who would believe that?
Holding hands like that,
how can someone resist?
I would die since the taking care post.
- Right?
- I first thought it was Thunmild.
But if you look carefully it’s not her hand.
Dr.Hill is so difficult to read.
I have known him for years,
never seen him had an eye on anyone.
Yeah.
Not sure whether that person is still wearing the watch.
- If he does, people'd see it.
- Then start looking who's wearing the red watch.
- P’Mei Li.
- You tell me first thing.
Oh my gosh.
I lost track of time talking.
Guys this is Ter.
He'll be our behind the scene photographer.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I will catch up with you guys later.
Take care of it. Find it.
I will show him around the set.
Here come. I will introduce you.
There’s nothing much…wait.
Are you wearing any watch today?
- No.
- Ok never mind.
Hi kiddos.
P’Mei Li is here.
You’re here.
How long have you arrived?
Awhile ago.
How did you get here?
I took the purple bus.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I could have picked you up.
I can get here by myself.
Shall we start?
Oh yes. We can.
We will start with Hill first.
Come on doc.
Turn this way please.
Turn around. Okay.
There.
Shoot away.
Adjust the lighting for me too.
Make it soft.
Okay.
Hill, you can now post.
Go for it.
Smile.
Ready 1 2 3.
You’re finally my photographer.
Hill, please come over here
to do make up.
Go do your make up first,
then coma back and take some more.
Look after him for me please.
Sure thing.
I will take good care of him. No worries.
I will show you where they do the filming.
Great.
Ok so…
You will have to snap some of the shots
whatever you see like it will do.
It doesn’t matter.
It's behind the scene. For the rest, I will--
Ter.
Nong Ter.
Yes?
Why are you looking distracted?
I called you so many times.
You didn’t answer.
I’m sorry.
Or…
you were blushing with what Hill said?
Even I was feeling it as well.
It was nothing, P’Mei Li.
He was just kidding.
He did?
But I have never seen him
care anyone this much before.
Or you’re….
the guy from his posts?
No, I’m not. How can it be me?
Really?
But I’ve never seen him
talk like that to anyone either.
Are you guys close?
We went to the same high school.
Oh…nong from the same school.
Okay.
Let’s go.
I will have you waiting over there.
I will call you again.
Let me clear things over there first.
Do we have the camera ready?
Ok. We will start in a bit.
Hey Hill. You can sit down.
Thunmild please sit.
Listen up kids.
We'll film the combined one
and also each one for each faculty too.
Okay?
Prepared yourself.
I'll call out each faculty to come film.
Okay.
Ok Hill and Thunmild, you're next.
Others please stand by with people from your faculty.
Hill and Thunmild,
please give me some cute scenes.
You are the hope of Meds students.
They are so perfect together!
Hill is so handsome. Thunmild is also pretty.
What a perfect couple.
Awesome!
Hill, you have something in your hair.
It’s fine now.
Can you take a picture for me?
Can you?
Yeah. Sure.
Please relax.
1 2 3 go.
- Does it look okay?
- Hill!
- Let me adjust the lens.
- Dr.Hill.
Why are you looking so absent-minded?
Look at the camera.
Come on. We’re almost done.
You must be tired.
Thank you.
It's not that tiring.
I’m Junior.
Mei Li said…
your name is Ter, right?
Yes.
Hey what are you doing here?
I saw him sitting here alone.
So I hang with him.
Oh okay.
You looked for the photographer yourself?
It’s actually Hill who suggested him.
Hill did?
Why?
No no. nothing.
But...
he’s kinda cute, right?
Easy there, Junior. He’s all scared now.
Don’t be scared Ter.
I’m fine.
Can I please have your LINE ID?
I might ask you to go take some pictures with me.
Thought you were not gonna give me.
I want some model anyway.
What are you doing?
P’Hill.
- What are you looking at?
- The cat.
Like cat meow meow?
Cat burglar.
Dog in a manger.
Enough enough. What’s going on?
Hill.
They said they'd like to continue with meds faculty.
Um.
I will go wait over there.
Hello~ I’m Thunmild.
I’m Hill.
We are medical student ambassadors.
Ok thats great.
Hill and Thunmild can go rest now.
Next faculty, please come on in.
Ter.
Yes?
Can I have your phone?
Why do you want it?
Can I have it please?
Don’t be stubborn.
Mild.
- Hmm?
- You’re not going home yet?
I’m about to.
Why don’t you ask Hill to go with you?
Better not.
Why?
Or…
you haven’t told him that you like him?
Well...
what if he doesn’t like me back?
Why wouldn’t he?
The whole school…
thinks you and Hill are together anyway.
But…
it’s already great being friends like this.
Then you might have to keep it to yourself
for the rest of your life?
What if Hill found someone he likes?
Can you bear that feeling?
When that time really comes,
I probably won’t be able to bear it.
Wake up! Class has ended.
Get up.
You go first. I’m tired.
Ter.
Wake up.
Give me 5 mins.
Class is over.
My class needs to use this room.
If you’re not gonna wake up,
I will carry you out.
P’!
Now, you're up.
Since when you’re here?
Just arrived.
All your friends are gone.
Would you excuse me then?
When is this gonna be over dude?
Not yet, Ter.
You go ahead. I will catch you later.
You got punished again?
Yes.
We forgot to clean the classroom.
We have to run almost 10 laps.
The whole class.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
But you’re looking so pale.
I’m okay.
I will continue.
- Keep it up!
- Sure.
Hill.
The teacher told me
we'll be our class representatives to hold flower pedestal tray.
Um.
You’re not going home yet?
I’m waiting to play basketball.
I will go home then.
Let’s go get some drinks.
You go ahead.
Are you exhausted?
I am. Thank you.
I almost faint.
Thank you.
Hey Hill!
You’re not playing?
I have to take care of someone.
Who?
I’m not telling.
Come play later then.
I’m dizzy.
- Feeling better?
- I'm between life and death here.
Can I get a pic?
Sure.
Thanks dude.
You want me to pick you up?
It’s okay. I will go to the union.
I can find my own way.
Let P’Hill take you.
He’s probably not that available.
I think he would always be available for you.
Stop it, North.
You’re blushing!
I’m not.
I gotta go. Get home safely.
He’s always free. Just call him.
Wait a moment please.
Ughh my camera man is not here.
What am I gonna do?
P’Mei Li.
- Hey Ter.
- Hello.
Hi.
You need to help me again.
It’s alright. No problem at all.
What will you be filming today?
There’re actually interviews with each faculty.
It will be a long day.
Can you handle it?
I can. It’s all good.
But right now I have a favor ask you.
The usual photographer is not here yet.
Can you help us take some?
Could you please help me?
Sure. You’re more than welcome.
Okay you're awesome. This way.
Ok guys. Line up.
Come on. First one.
Smile with more confident.
Ok that's good.
Next please.
Oh...
Dr.Hill.
Shoot away.
Ready? 1 2 3.
That's great.
What a sweet smile!
The way you look at the camera
it's like you're looking at your lover.
Very strong emotion.
Ter.
- Ter.
- Yes?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Let's continue.
Let's do what you did just now.
Give us a sweet smile.
Sure.
If it's this photographer,
I will do anything for you.
Continue taking kiddo.
Okay.
Ok that's it.
All good since the first picture.
We're done.
You can go rest.
Next one, be prepared.
Why are you guys here?
Why?
We cannot be here or something?
We just wanna check you out.
And found something interesting.
"If it's this photographer,"
"I will do anything for you."
Is this the guy you were talking about?
Um.
Must be difficult.
Why?
Look.
Because the owner of 'my watch'
does not wear it anymore.
Ooh!
You're being mean.
Maybe he just forgot to wear it.
I'm really rooting for you my friend.
Umm.
Let's take a break.
Let the photographer get some drinks and rest.
Go rest near by.
Anyways...
I will just go get to know him a little.
No, you can't.
Hey Arthit!
Jo.
You should follow and check him out.
They might stir up some troubles.
Hello nong Ter.
Hello P'Johan.
I'm Arthit. A friend of Hill.
Right. P'Arthit.
What are you guys talking about?
Hi Easter.
My name is Tonfah. Nice to meet you.
Hello.
I'm Easter.
You can just call me Ter.
I'm a first year vet student.
First year vet student?
Your faculty must me close by to ours.
I remember the first years have to use our labs in meds building too.
We probably will see each toher often then.
You can go now. You already introduced yourself.
Hey don't be jealous.
We just got to introduce ourselves. Haven't really talked.
Nong Ter.
Please look after my friend.
Even if you don't like him, please have some mercy for him.
Because it seems like he is not the kind who loves anyone easily.
Go aways you guys.
Do not mind them.
Ter.
Yes?
I have something I wanna talk to you.
Yes.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I'm gotta go.
"Ter."
"I have something to talk to you."
You want to talk to me, P'Hill?
I don't know where to start.
I just want to start things over.
I think...
we've tried enough to run away from the past.
I think we should talk about it.
We shouldn't let it be like this.
Not good.
Do you have anything to ask me?
I can ask about anything?
I will answer every question you have.
How much can I trust you?
100%.
And...
how am I supposed to know that you're not lying?
I will prove it.
Then first question...
is....
You and P'Thunmild...
Why?
What are you guys to each other?
We're friends.
Oh.
You guys are not together?
I thought you guys have been dating.
I only see Thunmild as a friend.
Really?
And...
what about Christ?
She's a sister.
But...
But you and--
I thought you like Christ.
I've never thought in that way with Christ.
And...
what about me?
Hmm?
Why?
What about me?
It's obvious.
Obvious what?
If I want to be with someone,
there's only one reason, isn't it?
That only reason is...
"that feeling"...right?
If...
what you mean by that is 'I like you' then...
yes.
Huh?
Since when?
What do you mean?
since when that you like me?
Probably before you even know me.
Huh!?
You don't believe me?
How is that possible?
Cause I have had...
What did you say?
Cause I have had a crush on you for so long.
Not as long as I do.
Can you go see him for me?
You will see something nice.
Is this the guy you're trying to date?
Yeah.
I can totally beat him, why not?
When you're drunk, the whole vibes will lead you there.
So Hill doesn't need to waste his time to go out with you.
Waste his time?
I thought you were not gonna answer my call.