There's something happened on set today.
Someone said P'Hill shouldn't be with me. It's a waste fo time.
And P'Hill just burst and punched him.
Good. He deserved that.
But P'Hill got punched back.
Can you go see him for me?
Why me?
You will see something nice there.
Trust me.
How was it?
Good I guess.
I just want everything to be clear.
I don't know whether  the way I make it public is the right thing to do.
From now on, when I say 'it's fine',
the meaning will be, 'we're both fine'.
Cocoa drink here is good.
- Really?
- Umm.
You come here often?
Once in a while.
With who?
By myself.
I don’t believe you.
I really do come here alone.
Cause normally you never really liked dessert.
I’m not here for the dessert.
I come here because it reminds me of you.
What are you talking about?
It’s true.
We haven’t seen each other for so long.
That’s so irrelevant.
You love cocoa drinks.
I tried all the dessert cafes around here.
This one is the best.
I miss you…
but I couldn’t come see you…
So I had to distract myself by doing something to get my mind off you.
P’Hill.
I have always thought
of bringing you here.
I want to take you anywhere you wanna go.
So I did my research on so many good restaurants.
Or beautiful places.
In case we would meet each other again someday.
I thought we'd never see each other again.
I am here now.
Thank you…
for letting me see you.
Continue eating.
Sorry.
I’m sorry.
Thank you.
What are you looking at?
Stop looking.
I won’t.
I will charge you fee for looking.
- How much is it?
- THB100 each time.
Do you have a lump sum payment option?
Like I lay once and I can look at you the whole month.
It will be expensive though.
Is there any promotion, if I pay you cash?
What kind of promotion?
Like I can borrow you home to hug while I sleep?
For a few days?
I won’t allow that.
Please.
No.
You’re really doing this to me?
I will buy you cocoa drinks too.
Don’t try to convince me with the drink.
Coconut too.
It’s not working.
Thank you.
Ter.
Yes?
You forgot this.
Oh right.
Thank you.
Night night.
Bye bye.
Oh the thief is coming.
Go go. Go in.
Yes! I’m holding a sniper.
I’m home.
Where have you been?
I was with P’Hill.
I also brought you this.
Hey! It’s like you can read my mind.
I’m kinda hungry right now.
Thank you. How much do I owe you?
It’s fine. P’Hill paid.
Wow~
He also paid for my food. He’s so smooth.
Trying to win over through his friends.
So strategic.
What are you babbling about?
Oh Ter. Do you still want a part time job?
Sure.
It’s a Japanese restaurant.
Working from 6-10pm.
Are you interested?
Sure.
If you are, I will tell them.
Okay.
- Oh North.
- Hmm?
Do you know P’Johan?
The guy who dropped me off the other day.
No.
You really don’t know him? He’s so popular.
I know that he’s a friend of P Hill.
But I don’t know him personally.
Really?
Yeah. Why would I lie to you?
And what do you think?
Think of what?
Like what do you think of him and such?
Well…
I don’t know.
Why so many questions?
I have enemies on my front door.
I have to protect my land.
I’m sorry.
Do you know North from Crime Suppression Division?
- For the pride.
- Always play the game.
You're ruining my hair.
Do you know how long it took me to do this?
Half an hour.
- Hey. Your turn.
- Let me play too please.
Oh I have to start first?
Expert.
It’s a competition.
You’re so noob.
I can’t see.
I let you try again.
Not as good as mine anyway.
Let me decorate the car a min.
Wanna go for some food after?
North and I cannot join.
We have to work. Part time job.
So hard-working.
We need it for the tuition fee.
What time do you guys get off?
Either 10pm or midnight.
Woah. So late.
Be careful when you go home.
People have to be careful of me instead.
It'll be just me and Phoon again.
So lonely.
Having meal just the two of us.
Let’s do this.
We will have dinner at your work, shall we?
We’re free anyways.
Let’s do that.
Japanese right?
- Umm.
- We wanna have Japanese anyways Come with us, Daotok.
Sure.
Huh!? Can I!?
For real?
- Hey are you for real?
- Go. Let’s go.
Daotok is finally joining us.
We’ve been waiting for this moment.
- Shall we?
- Now?
- Let’s go. I’m hungry.
- Let's go.
Whose bag is this? Where’s my bag?
I guarantee you. This is good.
Please welcome.
Irashaimase.
What? Hurry.
Oh Ter. North. You're here.
Hello~
Why are you here so early today?
I brought my friends for dinner.
- Hello.
- Are these your friends?
- Yes.
Good.
Everything will be on the house today.
Ooh. Really, P'Yah?
Can I also join?
North.
It's okay. P'Yah. I feel bad.
If not, I won't let them come here anymore.
Ok fine. I won't pay.
I will give you guys lots of free stuff instead.
Thank you, P'Yah.
Please make yourself at home.
Come on.
I will take care of you like family.
North.
Why are you sitting down? Get up.
Go change.
What would you like for today?
What do you wanna eat?
Just order.
This waiter has no manner.
Can't you see that we're still deciding?
How can you rush?
Shall we report the manager?
Stop messing with him.
There're so many people already.
Fine. I will get this one.
And this set too.
Okay?
- I will be back.
- Okay.
Here are your drinks.
You don't have the butterfly pea lemon?
If you're so picky, please go dine somewhere else.
You can have mine. Here.
The food is here my friends.
- Ugh. Finally, I get to sit.
- Yeah.
So many people here today.
And you guys can sit out here like this?
P’Yah told me to take a break.
I’m hungry. So damn hungry.
What are you having? Let me try.
How is it? Good?
It’s good.
I guess we might come here more often.
Good, so we won’t be so bored working.
You should come hang with us often.
Sure thing.
Ter. Come here.
Yes.
Nong Ter.
Someone is here to see you. So handsome!
Your boyfriend?
P'Hill.
Why don't you tell me you have a part time job?
It's dangerous, going home so late.
I work with North though.
Even so. It's still dangerous.
I wanna do something by myself too.
I don't want to be a burden to my family.
And how is it?
Good. It's good.
Everyone is so kind.
You work here with North, right?
Yes.
Then I will come take you home from now on.
It's fine. I can come and go with North.
Please.
Fine.
That's good.
Then we will start today.
I will wait until you shift is over.
It's fine. I can go back by myself.
All my friends are also here.
Fine.
I will go back work now.
Yes, you go ahead.
I will make a call for a min.
Sure.
Are you free?
No.
I have something to talk to you.
I'm working. Can we talk later?
It's about North.
What is it?
- P'Yah.
- I'm not. I'm not peeking.
Yeah. I believe you.
So what's going on?
Are you guys a couple?
No, we're not.
He's waiting for you there like that.
I'm just gonna go.
Let's go.
You scared me.
Go home already.
Next time.
P'Hill.
I'm done.
Then let's go.
We will go now, P'
Sure. See you around.
- See you dude.
- Bye. See you.
Do you wanna leave your motorbike here?
Riding motorbike at night is too dangerous.
I'll take you home.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
- Be careful.
- Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Yes.
Thank you for dropping us off.
- Thank you, P'Hill.
- Sure.
Go go.
Oh Ter.
Hmm?
I think he takes care of you so well.
Why don't you guys make it official?
How can I?
Why can't you?
Cause I haven't told him that I like him.
Another thing.
What's another thing?
He has never asked me to be his boyfriend.
I think he's waiting for you.
Waiting for what?
Waiting for you to realized yourself.
Let's put it this way.
Have you told him how do you feel about him?
Not yet.
See?
Cause you're still scared, aren't you?
About when you were hurt before or something.
You're afraid that it will happen again, right?
Yeah.
I think he's waiting for you
to be honest with yourself.
It's up to you now, Ter.
Understood.
Just give me sometimes.
- I'm gonna go play games now.
- Umm.
Aren't you gonna shower first?
I like to be nasty.
If it's overthere...green right?
You can try.
You can end it with brown color too.
All I'm asking is to explain to me why you disappeared.
And just tell me you love me once again.
What's up, Mr.president? Everything's good?
Umm.
I thought we're not gonna be able to host this
before the term starts.
We also have very few members too.
Right.
Both booth and concert.
Are we making it too big for welcome back activity?
Last year, the seniors did it so well.
Hill.
Johan will be here to help.
Fah and Arthit also.
Those guys are gonna come help?
I don't know.
I will go check everything over there first.
Umm.
- Please handle this after me.
- Sure. Thank you.
Hill.
I heard that the guy that you're seeing...
...is here somewhere?
Lower your voice.
Many people here.
- Hmm?
- Keep it down.
Is it the same guy we met the other day?
Must be the same one.
It's Hill. Not Johan, who constantly changes.
What the f*ck?
Can I go talk to him?
Hey Arthit.
Hello Nong Ter.
Hello.
Hi.
President. Come here.
Come here.
If you need anything,
just let my friends help you.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Don't have to feel bad.
Damn. He said so nice things.
Our friend has changed guys.
- Right.
- I can't.
I also can't when you flirt with the girls.
Enough you guys.
We will help him, Hill.
Go do your thing.
Right. Take care of him.
I will be back.
Sure.
Dude.
How can we help you, Ter?
There is this
that you can put the flag on.
Do you think you can do it?
- It's just a simple out it on the rope.
- Hill really has changed.
Umm. It's so weird.
Ter. Your phone.
Yes?
Who's calling me?
Typhoon.
Oh Typhoon.
I will just give this to him.
- Nong Ter.
- Yes?
- Here.
- I'm sorry. My hands are a bit dirty.
- Can you answer it for me?
- Okay sure. I will put him on speaker.
Hello, Phoon. Where are you?
Ter. Help me. I'm lost. Foam took me out front of the campus. He said he wanted to take a detour.
We ended up around other people's houses.
Oh and which alley are you at?
What alley?
Dude. I think we need to stop and use the GPS.
No. Trust me, Phoon.
What the hell you guys!?
I'm busy here.
You can tell me the direction.
I can go get you.
Thank you.
P'?
Who's speaking?
My name is Tonfah.
Ter is kinda busy.
Just tell me the way and I will come pick you up.
Please help us.
Ok then. I left the campus
and turn left around the corner of that dress rental shop.
Oh ok I know where that is.
Wait there. I will pick you up.
See you dude. Bye.
- I will go now.
- Yes, please get them for me.
- It's not a big deal.
- Thank you.
- Jo, can I borrow your car?
-  Where are you going?
Ter's friends are lost somewhere in front of the campus.
I'm going to get them.
Do you want me to go instead? I'm free.
You are not normally this kind.
Please don't go.
You'll come back and complain.
He's right.
I think you should leave it to Dr.Fah,
who's so kind.
- Drive safe.
- Sure. Thank you.
You look like you're free.
I'm so damn bored.
What's going on boys?
You guys are here helping.
This seems weird.
Hey P'.
What kind of guys do you think we are?
You guys are probably here
to check out Hill's sweetheart, right?
How does she know?
- Hello~ P'Mei Li.
- Hi~
How come you're here?
Cause I miss you, kiddo.
You're too sweet.
Just kidding.
I have some work at the union,
so I stopped by to check.
Good.
We have so many things to do too.
Woah. He won't let anyone sit by his side at all.
Jealous type too.
Hello P'Mei Li.
I thought you were not gonna say hi to me.
Hello.
Are you hot?
Yes, a bit.
Wow...you guys are so sweet.
I was also in the sun while walking here.
Our friend has emphathy too?
I think he's probably has it for this guy only.
Hill is so Hill.
Oops.
Opps what
Opps.
You want some water?
Thank you.
Hey guys.
Come help me carry stuff from the union to here.
Let's go.
- I'll be back.
- Sure.
- Come on.
- Oh guys. I also bought you these.
-  I will have one.
- Please take it. I bought for you guys.
That's the coldest one we have.
Is this okay?
Easter.
We're here.
I can hear your voice since miles away.
Took forever to get here.
- Why don't you just punch me?
- Can I?
Just one time.
Without P'Fah, we would be in trouble.
Thank you so much for picking them up.
You're welcome.
By the way, where are all my friends?
Oh they went to get some stuff from the union.
Ok. I won't be in your way anymore. Excuse me.
- Oh and here's your phone.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Sure thing.
Why are you still standing?
Sit.
- I've been waiting for you to ask.
- Sit. Sit here.
These are your friends?
Oh yes. This if Foam and this is Typhoon.
Oh Typhoon. Hi. I'm Mei Li.
Mei Li.
I have heard of your name before.
I heard that you kinda always look after him.
Thank you.
It's not that much.
Now, I'm blushing.
P'Mei Li. Phoon is a photographer.
He takes great photos.
He does it even better than me.
- Really?
- Not really. I normally don't do portraits.
What?
Not portraits then what do you normally take?
Like sky and stuff.
Sky?
How?
Here.
Phoon's IG.
It's pretty.
But why do you only take pictures of the sky?
They're beautiful.
And I also like blue color stuff.
You're so weird.
You can post some other pictures too.
None of your business.
Oh.
Stop fighting you guys.
Since you are here,
come help me take all these to the stage.
Guys, can I go with you?
I don't have anything else to do today.
Sure, but it's kidna hot out?
Are you sure you wanna go?
I'm a fighter.
This is not right.
I think the president gives you guys too many hard work.
It's fine, P'Mei Li.
We're happy to help. The term almost starts too.
Very protective of him.
But it becomes a burden for us.
Oh I thought you're willing to help?
Come on.
P'Mei Li, are you okay?
I'm fine. Wait.
I think booth A looks okay already.
- Can you go check booth B for me?
- Okay, on it.
Oh hey P'Hill.
Hello.
I heard you guys were lost?
Fah came to get you, right?
Yes, he seems like an expert in directions.
Even I told him my guess.
I couldn't really remember thing.
He still managed to find us.
- Hey Phoon.
- Huh?
We still haven't thanked him.
Oh right.
It's okay.
It think he wanted to help.
Then could you excuse us?
Bye.
We worked so hard.
Are you alright, P'Mei Li?
Not really, but I still wanna help.
Hey do it.
- What?
- It's you!
- There's something goin on,
since the day P'Hill took you home
from P'Yah's restaurant.
There's something make me believe that
you and P'Hill are not just two normal people.
You're having secrets with friends?
Tell me now, Ter!
You can just asked me nicely.
I will let you talk.
I will pay good attention.
Even if you are secretly having a boyfriend
and won't tell us.
or when my feelings are hurt when you hide things from me.
Sure. I still can take it.
Listen to me first.
You're so overreacting.
Fine. I will tell you now.
P'Mei Li. Help me.
Ok have you seen P'Hill's posts?
#SugarDaddyDoctor and #WhostheOwneroftheWatch.
Oh I remember.
I saw many people reposted on Facebook.
That's it.
The one and only reason behind all those.
The owner of the watch
and also the owner of P'Hill's heart.
Or...
Why you never told me!?
There's no good time to tell you.
I couldn't tell you directly.
It's you!
"I'll go drinks with friends tonight."
"Are you okay?"
"A bit heart broken. If I got too drunk, come get me"
"Don't drink too much. I'm worried"
Oh.
Is he asking for something back?
- Yes?
- Come check the overall with me, will you?
Yes. Sure.
You see that?
How come you guys don't have any idea?
He just never told us.
- "I'll go drinks with friends tonight."
- "Are you okay?"
- "A bit heart broken. If I got too drunk, come get me"
- "Don't drink too much. I'm worried about you"
You need to talk to me?
I think...
we should break up.
I need you to understand, North.
We're grown ups.
We need to choose someone with the future.
We cannot just date for fun
like little kids anymore, right?
I really want to thank you.
For everything...
...that you have done for me.
But--
You already chose Temp, right?
Um.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I understand.
But please tell Temp for me.
Promise me that he will take care of you for me.
Good luck.
North.
Are you okay?
I am.
Let's go. Cheers.
Easy there.
I think you're somewhat drunk.
The drinks cannot do anything to him.
He's heart broken. Let him be.
Don't say that I'm heart broken.
We broke up long time ago.
But today she just updated relationship status
with her new guy.
If you're really okay,
we wouldn't have to be here, would we?
Why?
What's wrong with engineering?
She wants to be with someone with the future?
She doesn't want to date for fun?
I also didn't date for fun.
I did take care of her.
But he's a doctor. That's why.
So?
Engineer has no future?
This is offensive to all of us.
That's true.
Does Jah go to our university by the way?
But Temp, her new boyfriend, sure does.
I'm praying for you two,
to not run into each other.
You're such a hot-headed guy.
Ughh. I'm not like that.
To be honest,
I don't have a problem with him.
But just don't break her heart.
- Hey Q, you haven't drunk anything.
- This way!
You guys are not drinking
even though I pay.
The chance that I win lotteries
does not occur often too.
If you're all drunk,
who's gonna take care of y'all?
Look at each one of them.
You guys are drunk already?
Who's drunk? No one.
Are you coming back with me, North?
No, my dorm is in a different way from yours.
But I already informed Ter.
If I'm drunk, I wil lhave him pick me up.
Right. If I don't look well,
please call Ter for me.
Okay?
Yeah.
North.
Temp that you were talking about...
is that him?
Yes.
Yes what? Look!
- Shit.
I just said don't want them to run into each other.
Hey but the girl that he's with is not Jah, right?
- Follow him.
- Where are you going, North?
Hey! What are you doing?
North.
North?
I asked what the f*ck are you doing?
You've got a problem?
Why? You're a sore loser?
What a loser.
Temp!
North!
- What are you doing?
- Just go.
F*ck you.
Hey North!
North, are you alright?
My lips.
This sh*thead.
Why did you punch him, Nhow?
Cause he punched my friend.
You!
- Hey someone's calling. Pick up.
- Ter Ter. I'm Ikkyu. North is in trouble.
Hurry up.
Are you sure you want this?
What?
Let go of me!
I really don't wanna fight.
Fall again.
Don't hurt my friend.
Stop stop.
Hey that's enough.
Why don't you mind your own business?
Hey! Come at me!
- Hey.
- I said enough!
Let me go!
Why are you holding me?
Hey! Let me go!
Just let me know how much do we owe you.
I will handle it.
I'm sorry about tonight.
Let me know your hospital bills.
Sure.
- I helped, but you kept punching me.
- Next time, just leave it to me.
Oh sure. Next time, I'll leave it to you.
Can you take your friends home?
Yes.
But...
I will handle that.
Yes.
Oh P'
This is North's.
North.
- North.
North. North.
North.
Get up.
Come help me.
Ugh. My body is still hurt.
Take the bike home.
How is it?
I already handled it.
What about Nong?
He's sleeping here. Just drank too much.
I'm taking him home.
Can you bring Ter over tomorrow?
So he won't have a heart attack when he wakes up.
Good that he's okay.
I will bring Ter over tomorrow.
Um. I gotta go.
I told you to not break her heart.
Why are you doing this?
My heart hurts so much.
Who told you to drink so much?
- I can't.
- Huh?
- Shit.
- Mr.Johan.
Aunty Da.
Can you prepare some clothes for me?
Yes.
- Take care of him.
- Yes sir.
Oh my my.
How can you be this drunk?
Ugh I need to pee.
I need to pee.
Where's the restroom?
I have to pee.
Why is this so high up?
I need to pee.
Or the restroom is over there?
Hey or it's...
over there?
Or it's...
over here?
Or...
Where is it?
Hey what!?
Oh my god. Why are you so drunk?
Oh my. Mr.Johan is gonna like this.
Aunty. I'm sorry.
What am I gonna do?
Be careful!
Oh my!
Aunty.
- Go to the room.
- Where are we going?
- I told you to go back to the room.
- I need to pee.
Go to the room.
- I told you go back.
- Aunty~
- I need to pee.
- I told you to go back.
Aunty, I'm sorry.
Please come clean this up for me, Aunty.
Aunty. It's over there too.
Go to the room.
Oh my god.
Restroom.
Where's the restroom?
It's here.
It's so far.
Restroom.
I have arrived at the restroom.
I can pee now.
Shake it shake it.
North.
Ter.
- Easy dude.
- Why is it so hurtful?
- It's morning already?
- Not morning.
It's already evening.
I thought you were not gonna wake up.
Why is my whole body ache?
You deserved that.
Seeing you like this, I even wanna aggravate you even more.
But I don't know where to start.
Don't do that to me.
Thanks for picking me up last night.
It's not me.
Oh.
And where am I?
P'Hill's room?
North. I'm really mad at you.
Why did you do it?
Why were you in a fight with them?
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
When I called Ikkyu...
...and he said you were in trouble?
When will you stop being so hot-headed?
Right I'm sorry.
I will try to calm down next time.
You won't be in a fight next time.
I will...
try to calm down then.
Anyways, I think you probably wouldn't want to drink
for a very long time.
Why?
Where am I?
Can you tell me already?
This is a house of P'Hill's friend.
P'Johan's house.
Oh. P'Johan.
Huh!?
And how come I'm here?
When Ikkyu told me you were in trouble,
I didn't know what to do.
So I called P'Hill
and he said he will handle it.
I need to answer this.
Yes.
Dude...so what happened?
How did I get here
and where is he now?
He went out for work.
He probably will be back soon.
Hey let go of me!
I told you to not break her heart.
Shit...or I...
puked all over him last night?
You remember now?
He seems very upset with you too.
I only remember some parts.
Dude but...
I don't understand why it was him to pick me up?
Right? When he said he'll handle it,
I also didn't think it would be P'Johan to go get you.
You said you called Ikkyu, right?
Yes.
I will call him.
This is my phone?
Why is it in this condition?
I have no idea.
Dude. I can't turn it on.
When P'Johan gave it to me,
it's already like this.
He must be the one who did this.
Why would he do that?
You said he seems upset with me, didn't you?
Look. I cannot turn it on.
This is too much.
What did I do to him?
to make me deserve this?
You kinda did a lot though.
- What did I do?
- Um. Here.
This is why you probably
wouldn't want to drink for a very long time.
What is this?
Ter.
Yes, dad?
I will go back this weekend.
Yes. See you.
- You're done?
- Umm.
Is he awake?
Yes, he's talking to Ter inside.
Wait.
You're not thinking of
doing anything funny, right?
I'm sorry about last night.
And thank you so much.
Also..I'm sorry that...
you puked all over me.
Yes.
It's okay. You just pay me back.
Pay?
For the damage you caused.
You need to pay all of that.
Damage fee.
You have to pay all of that.
I cannot afford just the damage fee alone.
He's charging me interest also.
That's why I'm looking for more jobs.
Oh.
I won't charge you.
But will you do anything as I said?
You said you ave had a crush on you for so long, right?
Yes.
You know me before that?
Ter.
Can I start everything over with you?