The team that works on campus filming
needs a photographer.
Do you think you can do it for us?
You?re finally my photographer.
Can I please have your LINE ID?
Cat burglar.
Is this the guy you were talking about?
I will just go get to know him a little.
Hey Arthit!
I have something I wanna talk to you.
I think we've tried enough to run away from the past.
I just want to start things over.
Since when that you like me?
Probably before you even know me.
How is that possible?
Cause I have had a crush on you for so long.
Not as long as I do.
How much do you want?
What?
Is a hundred grand enough?
What are you talking about?
You're probably the one who's dating Hill.
No, I'm not.
- You're misunderstanding.
- Liar!
Stop seeing my grandson.
- I think--
- Just tell me how much do you want and get out of my grandson's life.
I don't want any.
Are you alright?
Why?
You're upsetting with me or something?
Would you like me to be honest with you?
Stupid kid!
You're being fooled by him,
you know that?
Hill!
Where are you going!?
What was that just now?
It's nothing.
It's just a little misunderstanding.
Was that your grandfather?
Yes.
I'm not trying to fool you.
I know.
It's fine.
I will try to make him understand.
Are you sure everything will be fine?
Don't worry.
Ok.
What is this?
My grandpa wants to give you this.
He understands now, Ter.
He's apologizing for that day with this.
That's a relief.
It was really a misunderstanding.
Don't worry about it, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
If what you mean by that is 'I like you'...
Then yes.
Since when?
Probably before you even know me.
Back then...
He liked Christ, wasn't he?
Is something wrong?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Well...
I have someone I love and really care about.
But I haven't talked to her for a year.
I don't know what to do.
Why don't you just talk?
We had a bit of a issue back then.
I thought turning back to each other
was the best way out.
So we wouldn't hurt each other any more.
Has it been successful?
Not at all.
I believe...
that time will heal something.
But...
it does not.
I cannot move on from the past
and start over.
I think the way for you to overcome this,
is to let go of the past.
Especially when it's the past that hurt you.
No matter how long it has been,
it can't be healed.
I think it's the kind of wound,
that you have to heal by yourself.
Um.
So are you really gonna sit there
and see me draw?
I'm just waiting for North to be back.
After he's done,
we will go find something to eat.
Do you wanna join us?
No.
I want to finish this drawing.
Are you sure? It's yummy.
I've never seen you eaten anything.
You always draw and draw.
You mean he likes you
even before you know him?
It's impossible, isn't it?
I still remember the day
he transferred to my school.
Or...
you guys probably met before that?
Really?
Love at first sight?
I don't think so.
Another thing is that
when he first transferred,
we've never even talked.
Are you saying that...
he's lying to you?
I don't think he's lying.
He might have something hidden.
Did he say anything else?
He actually wanted to tell me everything.
But it's me,
that didn't want to hear the whole truth.
So you're here
thinking it all in your head?
Fine fine.
Next time,
I will ask him everything I wanna know.
Including...
when he ghosted me.
You're lucky.
He came back to answer your questions.
Mine is long gone after we broke up.
Huh!?
You were in a relationship before!?
- Yeah.
- For real?
How come I didn't know?
She's from other university.
That's why I never told you.
But we already broke up.
It's okay.
Are you alright?
I have to be, even if I don't.
It's fine dude.
Go on.
Eat up.
Oh hey hey.
Why are you sad instead of me?
Just eat.
- I cannot stop thinking.
- You have to be on set soon.
- They are filming today, right?
- Yes.
Anyway,
you're gonna drop me off there, right?
You're such a burden.
Please. You cannot have me walking there.
I can't do it. The faculty is so far.
Please take me.
Fine.
- You're the best!
- What a burden.
Come on. Let's get started.
Go ahead and pose.
I want like twist yourself a little. Turn to each other.
Right.
Oh nong Ter.
- Hello. P'Mei Li.
- Hello~
We only need to take a few scenes today.
When you're done, you can leave whenever you'd like.
Sure.
Oh or...
you have to wait for someone
to take you home?
P'Mei Li!
What are you talking about?
Someone is blushing.
Hill. Someone here is blushing.
Stop it, P'Mei Li.
Oh he's coming.
Yes?
Have you eaten?
Yes, I did.
I already ate with my friend.
Do you wanna have something more?
I will take you.
It's fine.
Ok, fine.
I will leave him to you now.
Sure thing.
I will look after Easter as much as I can.
Oh and Mild won't be here today.
Has she called you?
She did.
It's okay. We just have pick up some of the scenes.
She doesn't have to be here.
Okay.
See you.
Sure.
What are you looking at?
No. Nothing.
That's a high pitch voice for nothing.
I don't know. Not sure.
Maybe someone would like to tell me something.
I just wanna know stuff.
What kind of stuff you would like to know?
Just tell me already.
The guy that Hill posted with is you, right!?
Right!?
Yes.
Yess!
Do not tell anyone please.
Oh why?
You don't want other people to know?
I don't.
So...
you are not ready or...
...something?
I'm not ready at all.
Umm...
But I finally know now that it's you.
Do you have any idea that
the whole campus are talking about this?
My mouth was so itchy from gossiping,
do you have idea?
- Itchy?
-I asked everyone from my faculty. I asked all of them.
Come on guys. Gather here please.
Before we take a break,
can I get a group photo?
Chop chop.
Good.
Junior!
We haven't taken anything.
Don't have to look at the camera.
Why are you smiling like that, Hill?
Look at the camera. Not your boyfriend.
All: Boyfriend?
Cause the photographer is cute.
I can't take my eyes off of him.
1 day 1,000 situations.
Everyone please be silent.
Right.
When people are in love,
you can't hide it from the world.
Oh.
Hill just looked at you,
now your hand is as cold as a corpse.
Is this the guy that you're trying to date?
Yeah.
He's a real deal.
I'm blushing for him.
Hill is all in.
What now, Junior?
Are you up for a fight?
You guys are ridiculous.
This is nothing.
I can totally beat him.
Nong Ter.
I also cannot take my eyes off of you.
This one is okay,
but I think it's a little too bright.
Or we can adjust it?
I will adjust it on my laptop.
Okay. The overall looks ok already.
So this one is the owner of the watch?
I can't say no now, can I?
No, you cannot.
Let's just be honest, my friend.
It depends.
Whether he's okay with it or not?
And are you guys officially together?
Not yet. I'm trying.
Even Dr.Hill still has to try?
Oh and why did previously,
you wouldn't tell us,
but you just suddenly told us today?
So unpredictable.
I just wanna let some cat burglar know.
That Ter is mine only.
So what now?
He's very public about it.
I don't know.
I'm so confused.
You don't have to rush.
I think he can wait.
Really?
He said
he can wait?
But he's out there letting the whole world know already.
Why did he do that?
Yeah right.
How jealous he must be.
That's why he announced his ownership like that.
P'Mei Li!
Please I'm begging you.
You're so adorable.
I'll stop giving you a hard time for a moment.
Yes, that's good.
Ok times up.
I will continue harassing you.
But I really am rooting for you.
Just think about it. Take your time.
You're Easter?
Yes.
Do you wanna go celebrate?
Celebrate?
Hey, celebrate you and Hill.
It's not just him,
we don't even know whether Hill is going?
He has to.
We have to celebrate such a good news.
You just wanna drink. Let' be honest.
We're also in.
If someone pays.
Right.
Let's go.
Good opportunity like this doesn't come often.
And anyways,
when you're drunk, the whole vibes will lead you there.
So Hill doesn't need to waste his time
to go out with you.
Hey.
That was a bit too much, wasn't it?
Too much what?
I was just teasing him.
And Ter doesn't mind.
Right?
Hey!
You don't have to be so serious.
It's not fun.
But it's true, isn't it?
You're playing hard to get,
when you're actually trembling with joy.
P'Hill!
What the hell is wrong with you?
I have to ask you that instead.
P'Hill.
Hill!
- Motherf*cker.
- Hey.
Calm down.
- Take Ton away.
- Why are you guys locking me?
I'm not wrong here.
He just barged in and punched me.
You're the wrong one, Ton.
Why are you on their side, Junior?
You're not the upper hand,
so now you're bowing to them?
This shit head.
I might just punch you too.
- Come at me!
- Ton, enough.
Let's go.
Go.
P'Hill.
You're bleeding.
Ton.
Apologize to Ter now.
What did I do?
Hill punched me first.
Hill was also wrong about being physical.
But you were also wrong.
Be careful with things that you say.
You're so bad.
Apologize now.
I'm sorry.
Hill.
I cannot hide this from the professor.
They might call you in to talk.
since you're also the union's president.
Yes.
Both of you,
don't let anything like this happen again.
Do you understand?
Would you excuse me?
So Hill doesn't need to waste his time
to go out with you.
Wasting his time?
(Christmas)
Christ!
P'
What's wrong, Christ?
Why are you crying?
I thought that...
you would never answered my call again.
I should have called you first.
P'.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
You're not mad at me anymore?
I've never been mad at you actually.
Really?
Yes, really.
What about you?
Are you done being mad at me?
I did long time ago.
Really? That's nice.
Thank you.
And how are you Christ?
Are you doing alright?
Well...
I'm fine.
But it's been really tough with my school stuff.
I have made my decision to become a nurse.
That's great.
You finally made a decision.
What about you?
Has the semester started?
Um.
Almost.
I've been busy myself too
with all the university stuff.
So many activities.
Oh Christ.
I'm also the photographer of the university production too.
That's nice.
Nobody takes pictures as good as my brother.
Woah. Nice saying.
And how are you doing up there?
Is it cold yet?
No, not yet.
How are things at home?
It's really hot over here.
Let's...
go to the beach together,
when you're back in town.
Sure.
And also...
I heard that...
P'Hill is also in meds school there.
Um yes.
And...
...have you guys met?
We did.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't mention him.
Hey it's fine, Christ.
I'm fine.
But..what about you?
Are you okay?
It's my fault.
Christ.
Really.
If it wasn't because of me,
you two were probably,
Huh?
You mean...
Me and Hill?
Yes.
Not you and Hill?
Huh?
Don't tell me...
that you have no idea?
Know about what?
About P'Hill, that he...
For this question, you will...
have to plug this equation here.
Then you take all of these,
minus from the this part.
- and all these, plug in another equation.
- P'Hill.
Yes?
P'Hill...
are you dating someone?
Why do you ask?
Well...
So...
- I kinda--
- I'm not.
-But...
-Yeah?
I already have a crush on someone.
Oh.
Really?
So you've always known?
Yes.
Everyone can tell.
It's just you that have no idea.
Know what?
P'Hill always take good care of you.
But P'Hill has always been nice like this to everyone.
But with you, it's more special.
And you're okay with that?
With all these?
I am.
I already moved on from him long time ago.
Are you sure?
I am.
The two persons that I love are happy.
Then I am happy for you.
Now, It's up to you two.
Christ.
You guys are ugh.
Anyways,
are you coming home any time soon?
I will.
I miss home so much.
But I still don't know when.
Dad's not mad at you anymore too.
Really? For real?
Um.
But he keep his lip tight.
I guess that's how old people are.
I'm so happy.
Okay okay.
I will visit you guys when the semester is over.
Yayy~ That's great.
I'm looking forward to it.
Why are you smiling with yourself?
Hey...so you cleared things up with your sister?
Um.
You and Hill are officially together?
Why not?
You can tell me everything.
Ughh North.
What am I gonna do? I'm stressed.
There's something happened on set today.
Someone said that
P'Hill shouldn't waste his time going out with me.
F*cker.
What a foul mouth.
Then P'Hill barged in and punched him.
Good.
That shithead deserves that.
But that guy punched him back too.
How is he feeling then?
Right. I'm also confused.
What should I do?
When I heard that,
I was mad so I just ran away.
I just left him there.
It's okay.
I think you have a lot going on lately.
It's okay dude.
Is he gonna be okay?
Is he gonna be alright?
How hurt is he?
- I'm afraid that he'll be mad at me too.
-It's okay. Calm down.
Easy for you to say!
Where is that d*ckhead?
He thinks he's cool huh?
He deserves more than just a punch.
Forget it.
I don't want to make a big deal.
You never thought of telling your friends
when you were in trouble?
I'd never found out,
if P'Mei Li didn't call.
You never thought of telling your friends
when you were in trouble?
I'd never found out,
if P'Mei Li didn't call.
I don't want to make a big deal as I said.
Please don't tell Arthit and Fah.
Fine fine fine.
Dr.Hill.
Professor is looking for you.
Are you gonna get punished?
Probably not.
Might be just a warning....I guess?
P'Mei Li said so.
It might be just a warning.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried about that.
Oh then what are you worrying about?
I'm worried about nong.
He didn't answer my call.
Don't know what's happening.
You should take care of your business first.
Jo. Can you go see him for me?
Why me?
Please. Just go check on him.
What if I said no?
You'll see something nice there.
Trust me.
Who are you here to see?
Is Ter here?
He is in the shower.
I will let him know.
Do you wanna come in?
No. Please tell him for me.
Sure.
Are you just gonna wait there?
- Ter.
- What's up?
- Someone is here to see you.
- Who is it?
I don't know.
Hurry and come out to see him.
Fine fine.
Bam. Ow. Ow.
- That's it.
- Who is it?
- Huh?
- Who came to see me?
I don't know. He's outside.
I told him to come in, but he wouldn't
Hey. Hey. I'm stuck.
Hey!
Do you wanna get slapped?
P'Johan. What's the matter?
Someone asked me
to come check on you.
You're alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
Is P'Hill alright?
Just bleeding on the lip.
And the professor called him in.
And where is he now?
Do you wanna go see him?
Let's go.
Wait wait. Give me a moment.
North, I'm going out, okay?
- Where're you going?
- I don't know. Bye.
What?
You can drive slower.
Am I a bad driver?
Is he gonna get punished?
No.
I called me and said it's just a warning.
That d*ckhead was wrong. Not him.
P'Hill.
I'm done here.
I will leave now.
Did you see him?
Yeah I did.
Face to face.
How was it?
Well...
Good. I guess.
Talks later. I'm gonna go.
- Wait P'.
- Talks later. Please talk to him.
About Ton,
I'm sorry.
You were not the one who said all those things.
I actually have to thank you instead for stopping him.
But you have to feel bad
because of me.
I just wanna be transparent with my commitment.
But when Ton did that...
I'm not sure anymore that the way I make it public
is the right thing to do.
But anyways...
I already did it.
I will try.
Try?
what?
With what about to happen.
You mean..?
Stuff like P'Ton?
That's part of it.
But something bigger might be coming too.
Don't worry.
It should be me who says that.
I don't want you to be in trouble like this.
Hang in there.
Okay, kiddo?
Don't act like I'm a kid.
I'm not a kid.
Look.
You're pouty like one.
I'm a grown up.
And...
does it hurt?
No.
When I said I like you,
I mean it.
About when you said that you like me,
even before you know me.
That means there are some other things
you haven't told me, right?
I will tell you everything,
when you become my boyfriend.
Okay?
You're forcing me.
Not exactly.
But if you really want to know,
you can say yes now.
What are you talking about?
Stop smiling.
Oh P'Hill.
How's your grandfather by the way?
He's good.
That's good.
And when you told me that he was misunderstanding,
it was not true, right?
Why are you asking that?
Come to think of it,
you might just told me that
to make it less stressful.
didn't you?
P'Hill.
What do you mean?
You guys are not dating?
No.
Are you telling me that...
you guys are like brothers?
Something like that.
But what I've heard,
is not that.
We're not together. Really.
Then why do you have to care him so much?
I love him.
How dare you...
to say such things!?
I'm telling you the truth.
Damn it!
All the kids in this house are gone mad.
Dad.
Calm down.
You guys are all the same.
Useless.
Don't worry, son.
He's always like this.
But this time, he went over line.
He just have high expectation
to the only grandson he has.
Just like when he did to you, right?
I guess so.
What should I do?
I believe that....
at the end...
you'll choose the best thing for yourself.
Right?
Yes.
May I come in?
Yes grandma.
Thay boy...
you love him that much?
You knew!?
Your grandpa was loud.
I heard everything.
But don't worry.
I will talk to him.
Thank you.
This is nice.
My grandson is capable...
...to love someone.
I thought that
my grandson doesn't know how.
Grandma!
Bring him over to see me sometime.
Sure grandma.
Your grandpa...
has always been tough.
He was worse back in the days.
I don't know how come I married a guy like this.
Grandma...
Let's buy some snacks for that boy, shall we?
To apologize to him.
Your grandpa caused a scene with him, didn't he?
Yes, he did.
Let's just tell him
the snacks are from grandpa.
I think your grandpa
must feel guilty more or less
about what he did based on his anger like that.
You're so understanding.
we've been together for 40 years.
That's why.
Under his kindness,
there's suspicious lie below.
Really?
But he's never be mean to me though.
So that's why I feel I'm special to him.
He's mean to the rest of the world,
but only nice to the only one person.
But I have an instinct,
that you might be like grandpa.
Grandma...no.
I don't want to.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you too, grandma.
I knew it!
It was actually your grandma.
My grandpa is difficult to understand.
I'm sorry.
Fine.
And how are you feeling?
It's fine.
You can't say that you're fine.
Why?
I don't care.
You cannot say that you're fine.
This is an order.
From now on it's a forbidden word for you.
Understand?
What are you talking about, Ter?
I'm talking about everything.
I meant for everything, about you, me, and us.
P'Hill.
Well...
you take such good care of me.
Always be nice to me.
But I've never known anything.
It's fine really.
I said you can't say that.
Okay.
From now on,
when I say 'it's fine',
the meaning will be, 'we're both fine'.
Okay?
Okay.
I think P'Hill take care of you very well.
Why you don't date him yet?
He didn't ask me yet.
I think he's waiting for you.
Thank you so much for taking them here.
My pleasure.
Do you know P'Johan?
Hello Easter! North is in trouble at the club!