Why did you walk in the rain?
If you catch a cold,
you’ll be in a lot of trouble.
Can I ask you something?
How’s it going with you and Johan?
You came here even with the rain?
What did you just say?
You're alone, aren't you?
I’m not a kid anymore, Suer.
When you said you like me,
why is that?
Hey.
Wait.
You’re New!?
You woke up so early.
You're up?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Hi.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm so happy.
Happy?
To have you here.
What are you talking about?
Can I see that?
Tutoring? That one out there?
Even my parents force me to do tutoring, I just ignore it.
Thinking about it already gives me goosebump.
You like coconut cake?
No, I saw it as a recommendation.
What's wrong with people recognizing you?
Do you wanna have cocoa drink?
Fine.
You remembered now?
Hey.
Wait.
You're New!?
Why didn't you tell me your real name back then?
I don't know how to tell.
I'm so glad.
I thought you wouldn't remember me.
Who's gonna remember?
I couldn't even see your face.
Then you were just gone.
And moved to Singapore.
I lived there for around 1 year.
Before moving back to Thailand.
When you moved and didn't keep in touch with me,
I thought that you probably forgot me already.
I will never foregt you.
I always missed you.
I always wanted...
to come back here as soon as I can.
So...
you moved back and transferred to the same school with me?
Yes.
That's why you said you have had a crush on my before.
So before is this?
Here we go.
Then...
What?
Yes?
Why are you moving closer to me?
What are you doing?
It's a morning kiss.
Now, I have all the strength to work.
Stop it.
Hey.
If you don't stop making cute face,
I'm gonna kiss you again.
I know. I know.
Scoot over there.
Are you hungry?
Not yet.
Are you?
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just so happy.
It's like I'm dreaming...
that we get to be boyfriends like this.
Me too.
It's like a dream.
Maybe...
we're both dreaming.
Yeah.
Then...
I would never want to wake up.
- Really.
- Um.
Me too.
- Ter.
- Yes?
Wanna travel when the semester is done?
Travelling?
Really!? Where?
Where do you wanna go?
I can take you anywhere.
Really!?
You're so generouse. Whose boyfriend is this?
Yours.
Where should we go?
Let me think about it.
I will let you know once I know where I wanna go.
I wanan go to so many places.
Oh tonight I'll be tutoring with my friends at Johan's cafe.
Do you wanna com with me?
Can I ask North to come too?
Sure.
Are they normally this stressed?
Um why?
You're worried about P'Jo?
Yeah.
A shipper like me, is probably losing my job huh?
Cause he's been so busy lately.
And he has to also go to Boston too.
Huh? P'Jo? Going to Boston?
Yeah for work.
Is my friend gonna be okay?
Oh.
I have something for you to see. Almost forgot.
Have you been on Instagram today?
Not yet.
You need to see it with your own eyes.
Makes me blush thinking aboout it.
What are you talking about?
Let me see.
What's the hurry?
Cute right?
Johan's little puppy.
Cute.
Look. Your picture is the only picture on his IG.
Right.
So cute.
Oh.
- When the semester is done, I'll travel with P'Hill.
- Hey!
Really!?
Can I go?
Don't forget.
I'm one of your boyfriend.
Ugh!
You wanna go but have you asked your owner?
Hmm?
Little puppy.
I'll bite you.
Now you're accepting that you're a puppy?
Cute.
I'll take a break.
Good.
Hey. I'll be back.
Where are you going?
I'll go downstairs for a bit.
Ok.
Are you stressed?
Um.
Here.
It's already late, so i mae you a not so strong one.
I think you might need it.
Thanks.
P'Johan.
If you think you're carrying everything on your shoulder alone,
I...
will always be here...by your side.
When I go to Boston,
are you gonna miss me?
Of course. I will.
I'm sorry.
Let's go inside. It's chilly out here.
You might get sick standing here in the wind.
You seem fine.
I'm fine. I don't get sick easily.
Cause I'm strong.
But you just sneezed.
Lots of dust.
Don't let me see you get sick.
Go inside.
Hey hey.
North.
What's the matter?
You look a little pale.
Just a bit dizzy.
Hey.
Why are you still drinking cold drink then?
You might get a fever.
Hey North.
You're on fire.
Dude.
I think you should tell P'Johan to take you back.
You're having a fever.
No. He's studying with his friends,
I don't wanna bug him.
North!
- I'll tell him myself then.
- Hey Ter. No.
- Ter!
- What!?
Hey North.
I'm cold.
What are you doing?
P'Johan. Hug me.
You're so--
P'Jo.
Is your arm tired?
No.
You're cold, aren't you?
Are you feeling better?
A bit.
You said you're not gonna get sick, huh?
I'm sorry.
How shou;d I punich a stubborn kid?
Hmm?
That's it?
I don't know.
I don't know how.
You...
start first then.
Start what?
Kissing.
Ask me nicely.
P'.
Can you please kiss me?
I have an exam, so I had to leave early.
P'Prang will come see you.
Don't go anywhere. i'll be back.
Johan told me to look after a patient.
Here. I bought you some food too.
Let's eat, so you can take your meds.
Thank you.
Here.
Thank you~
You're still having a fever.
Better now.
Okay.
Eat up then. After this you can take some rest.
Oh Jo also wants me to give you the key card.
Normally, he's very protective of his place.
You're extraordinary.
Are you guys like together now?
Not yet.
Why?
You don't like him?
I do.
Hey if you like him
why aren't you guys officially together then?
The timing is not right yet.
He seems so busy lately.
Both school and also work.
You understand him too well.
Have you ever told him that you like him?
Never.
Err...
P'Prang.
Can you tell me more about P'Jo?
You probably know a lot already.
Ohh!
He's the only son of his father.
So he's kinda a hope of the family.
His mother told me that Jo used to be such a naughty kid..
..until he got into university.
Now, he's better.
Really?
Um.
And also...
normally Jo doesn't live here.
He has another house with his grandparents.
A provinc nearby here.
He lived there during high school.
Oh wait wait.
Ahh.
North are you done? Come down here.
I'm done. I'm done.
Come on.
I'm leaving.
- Bye bye.
- And you're not gonna eat first?
It's fine. I'll just eat from uncle's.
Soy milk and some deep friend dough.
It's free.
- Again?
- I'm gonna go now.
Kiss first.
Gotta go. Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Wow.
How rich they must be in order to have a house this big.
Really?
You drove pass everyday?
Yes, it's on the way back to my home.
Ahh...that means Jo must have seen you before then.
If not, he wouldn't be this obsessed wih you.
But I'm not familiar with him at all.
Hey.
You might bumped into each other somewhere else.
Hey. I have to go back to work.
You will be okay alone right?
- Sure. I'm fine.
- Okay.
Get lots of sleep.
- Yes.
- Gotta go.
Thank you.
She didn't tell me it's hot.
Hello?
Are you going?
To where?
We have the Gear ceremony today.
Can I not join?
I'm still stick.
And I'm at P'Jo's too.
I didn't tell him in advance that I will go out.
I don't want him to be mad.
I'm also sick.
Tell him you'll go get something for him to take with while he's gone.
He's going to Boston soon.
Give him your gear. That's it. He won't be mad.
Are you coming or not?
Fine. I'll go.
Okay. See you.
Oh North.
Oh P'James.
You said you're gonna study in America.
You're lying.
I was gonna go P'.
But I'm worried abut my mom.
I don't wanna leave her behind.
I didn't know that you're my faculty freshman.
We need to catch up.
What's your ID?
212.
North.
224.
North!
Be serious.
- 249.
- Yeah.
Go there. Behind all your friends.
Hey! My name is gone.
Flip it!
- Go!
- I'm going.
Yeah.
This row stand up please.
P'.
I actually have some errand to do.
Can I please take the gear and leave first?
No, you have to wait until all your friends finish too.
Why are you in a hurry?
You wanna go see P'Jo?
I actually sneaked out.
- He's gonna be upset then?
- No doubt.
He just really care about you I guess.
P'. Can't I just take it and leave first?
No, you have to wait for everyone.
Next, this row please stand up.
Ok. You all received your gears, right?
Okay? All good?
Here.
Just give him your gear, he won't be mad.
Or you're gonna ask him to be your boyfriend with the gear?
Why are you talking about that?
You came this far.
Or you're waiting for him to ask you instead?
I've never told him that I like him.
What!?
Huh?
Nothing.
Trust me. There's no better chance than this.
Trust me.
You should stop talking.
Like I said earlier about the rules,
You need to follow the rules.
Any questions?
Anyone with the ID starts with 249?
Is it you? 249? She's looking for you.
Anyone with 249 ID, please raise your hand.
What's going on?
The one with 249 ID, please go.
Someone is here to pick you up.
This is the chance.
Go!
How come you're here?
Why do you think I do all these?
I went back home and didn't see you there.
Do you how worried I am?
Can you don't leave
or be out of my sight like this ever again?
I'm sorry.
Today we have a Gear ceremony.
I didn't mean to worry you.
Can you please don't be mad at me?
Are you're not sick anymore?
You're still warm.
Since you're done, go get some rest.
Well...
can you come with me first?
What's the matter?
You probably know the meaning of this already?
I'm sorry for not listening to you so often.
But you're still with me.
I've actually...
never had anyone taking care of me
or do things like what you've done to me.
So that's why I think...
my life is already good in a way
but since the day I have you in my life
everything has suddenly been better.
P'Johan...
I like you.
How can I possibly leave you?
We'll take the exam in a few minutes.
Why are you reading it now?
- Do you think it's enough?
- I'll do whatever I can do.
Don't stop it.
If he could eat the worksheet, he probably would.
If you're this desperate,
I think you should just pray.
Yeah.
I was kidding, but he's really doing it.
Long prayers too.
Amen.
Yeah...
Can you memorize everything?
No.
I was shocked since the first question.
- Yeah.
- What did you answer?
I couldn't even remember.
You want a full score or something?
You too.
So?
No full score. I couldn't do it.
What? Then why sitting there for so long?
Oh tomorrow we have Physic exam.
- Do you wanna study together?
- Sure.
Sure. Let's find a place.
- Go. Find a play to study.
Wow! Smiling to the screen like this,
you're so madly in love.
You're falling for him.
Let us see.
We'll go study after. Are you joining us?
Probably not.
- Sorry gotta go.
- Hey.
- What?
- Hey Kyu, give me the bag.
- Gotta go. See you.
- Yeah.
Bye bye.
Just like that.
- Why is he in a hurry?
- We waited for him.
- He wants to leave. He just leaaves?
- Someone is in love.
And why did we wait for him then?
- No, why did we wait for him?
- I'm going crazy, we waited for him.
You're nuts.
Go go. Let's finda a place to study.
How was your exam?
It was okay.
You?
A student like me?
Probably didn't make it.
How can I pass the test?
And when you said that you're tutor me, are you for real?
Um.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah but we will do it at my place,
I have to buy some food for the boys first.
- Shall we?ss
- Sure.
Have you ever tried this place?
Not yet, but I think it's good.
You need to try.
They're here.
You're here.
- What did you order?
- Salmon.
This is mine.
Here.
P'Jo. The change from the store.
You keep ti.
Wow. You always keep a thousand bill huh?
There'll be too many.
You also have too many thousand bills anyway?
I don't want to go to the ATM so many times.
Some store still only take cash too.
Why don't they make ten thousand bil?
You're so annoying Jo.
Shit.
PJo. Did you bring my gear?
I bought you the bracelet.
Jo? Wearing gear?
Why? What's wrong with me?
Nothing. That's good.
Before this happened,
how many times do you have to scold him?
Right?
But from now on, you don't have to do that.
Cause I'm committed now.
-  Cannot believe it.
- My potato suddenly becomes so sweet.
Oh P'Jo. I have something to tell you.
He likes to snuggle.
Snuggle what?
Cause you always sleep walking and snug on my bed.
And he always like snug and hug me.
And what do you do?
- I have to hug him, if not he'll keep moving.
- Ter.
It's true,
- For real?
- Yeah.
Jo.
I don't think this is right.
Um.
Wait until I come back from Boston.
What do you mean?
Here the fork. Take another one.
You like this one.
Um.
He's jealous.
I give this one for you.
You like vegetables?
North. I'm sorry.
I washed it. Bathed your stupid duck.
Don't forget to put some powder on.
Sure 5555
Okay.
If everything is done, please send me the details.
Sure.
Why are you smiling?
Ter sent me something funny.
Shall we study?
Sure.
You try to solve this question first.
It can be on the exam.
Sure.
This one?
Um.
Are you tired?
Aren't you gonna be more tired
when you go to Boston?
Um.
But after Boston, there's probably nothing much.
Tomorrow I have an exam.
I can't send you off at the airport.
It's okay.
Just get ready for the exam.
Hmm?
Look at you.
What's wrong?
Why are you making that face?
I wanna be at the airport.
Yes, P'Prang?
I'm on my way.
Yes.
Gotta go.
Don't you have an exam?
Yes.
But I still have some time.
I think it would be bad...
if I can't say good bye to you.
Never thought, going to Boston would be this difficult.
Don't drunk just the coffee.
Eat some food 3 meals a day too.
I will miss you a lot.
Come back as soon as I can.
Should I stay?
You can't!
Have a safe trip.
I will go take my exam now.
Good luck with the exam.
Hm?
Sure.
Go.
North.
What!? You scared me.
You're gone after the exam. I've been looking for you.
You're wearing a gear?
Yeah. It's Nao's.
Hey. Really? You guys swap each other's?
- No.
- Oh.
I...
did it behind his back.
How can you do that?
And why were you looking for me?
Yeah.
You led me off the topic.
So what do you need?
I need your help with something.
About what?
About Nao.
Guys. After this, there'll be my friend joining us too.
Do not leave yet.
Thank you for sending me stars.
Do not leave please.
See.
He's broadcasting his game, right?
But then there're so many people sending him stars to flirt.
Can you stop him?
Are you crazy? We can't stop them.
He always wanted to do broadcasting.
I know....at first....
it looks fun and everything.
But lately...it's not okay.
- You're jealous.
-  Yeah I am.
- You don't understand me.
- What do you want me to do?
North.
- HuH?
- Come here.
Come on.
- Handle this.
- Come on.
I'm about to lose.
Nao. What are you doing there?
I can't get out. I'm surrounded by them.
Just get whatever guns.
I went there. It doesn't have.
North....
I told you to help me.
Ended up playing with him.
North.
Read the comments. I'm playing. Can't read properly.
I miss you P'Suer.
P'Suer is not joining?
Ger played with you before?
Yeah used to.
Suer. People wanna see you.
Do you wanna join us?
No.
Is P'Suer seeing anyone?
I'm willing to do anything for him. I love you, P'Suer.
He's single now.
I want my friend to date someone too.
You can try.
Why are you online so early? You just finished your class.
Thank you 1,000 stars from P'Guitar.
Thank you 1,000 starts from...
What's the name? I can't read.
Why the hell you need to read it out loud?
Thank you P'Gun.
You know that person?
Of course. Send me stars so often.
Been following me since day 1.
I asked for the name.
But he told me to call him...
P'Gun.
He called me P'! So cute~
It's you!?
And why the name Gun?
It came from my first name, Gunnatee.
Today's class is so tiring.
But you heel me a lot. All the tireness is gone.
What's wrong with him?
Why do you need to mind other's people business?
Nao.
Look.
Hey thank you all of you,
but please don't fight.
Love each other.
What are you doing?
Stop him.
Hello P'?
Are you busy?
Does North normally play games? Come play with Duennao.
So cute. 2 guys playing games.
I normally play with Nao too.
These stars are for you, North. You're so cute. Can I flirt with you?
Thank you for the starts, but you can't flirt with me.
I'm gone not long ago, now you're naughty?
- Nao. I'll be back in a bit.
- Yeah yeah.
So...now you're not in the mood?
It was you, right?
I asked you to help me.
You ended up playing with him.
What are you doing?
Just playing games with my friend.
I also earn some money too.
You want money?
Send me your video clip. I will pay you THB100 a second.
Come on. I'm gonna go work soon.
Ger.
And what do I have to do in te video clip?
Why do I have to do this?
He wants to see your face. That's why.
He's always working. Rarely have the time.
He can see this video whenever he's free.
- What should I say?
- Anything. Just talk.
THB100 per second. 1 minute, you'll earn THB6,000.
Write me a script, will you?
- Just say whatever. He will like all of it.
- Are we starting?
I'm recording.
Err...
P'Johan.
Err...enjoy your work there.
I will always be here to support you.
Take care of yourself cause it's cold overthere.
Don't forget to eat some food too.
Don't drink just the coffee.
And also...
I...
...miss you.
I'm waiting for you to come back.
What’s the matter? Why are you looking so stressed?
It’s won’t be long. Only 2 weeks. He'll be back soon.
P’Hill. Have you been talking to P’Jo lately?
You can call him.
If he’s busy, he just won’t answer.
Gear event is for you to come with your couple.
But his probably won’t be back in time.
Ughh. I don’t even have one.
You guys are not boyfriends yet?
Or he hasn’t asked you?