I told you that I understand why you have to work hard.
But please.
You have to take care yourself too.
I just want to do it for you.
You have to promise that you will not overwork yourself.
Also have a proper meal.
Then I won't stop mad at you.
I promise.
Nice. Nice.
Go in. Almost done.
This is the last fort.
Yeah. Like that.
Like that.
Done!
1 day before North's birthday.
What is he doing now?
Happy birthday, North.
Hello, P'Jo?
You just got off work?
Um...are you asleep?
Not yet.
Don't tell me you're waiting for me.
- Err--
- I told you to go straight to sleep.
Hey. I just want to talk to you.
Stubborn.
And...are you arrived at your room?
Not yet. I just left the office.
Woah. Just finished?
Um.
North.
Happy birthday.
Yes.
Thank you.
Am I the first one?
Actually....
there's Ter who called me earlier.
But he called before midnight.
So...that doesn't count.
But after midnight,
you're the first one, P'Jo.
Should I wish you something?
It's fine.
I bet you're not very good at wishing for people.
I'm sorry I couldn't be there with you today.
You're here now.
In a call like this?
Just hearing your voice...
I'm already happy with that.
P'Jo.
Hmm?
I miss you.
And don't drive so fast.
Even if it's already late at night and there're less cars,
but you still need to drive carefully.
Understood.
And can you talk on the phone while driving?
If I can't do it why would I call you?
And...how's your work today?
Well...
It was not good.
Are you okay?
Not really.
Do you mind telling me?
About what?
About your work today.
Oh it's nothing.
But I would love to hear it.
Please, P'Jo.
Please. Tell me.
Well...
there were some changes within the team.
And they didn't update each other.
So when there's a mistake,
they also didn't tell me.
But at the end,
sI'm the one who solves all the problems.
It's your birthday.
Why do you wanna hear about my work?
It's fine.
I would love to hear anything about you.
But everything is settled now, right?
Not yet.
Even I don't really know much about your work,
but I will always be by your side, P'Jo.
Let's hug to charge our battery.
Come on.
I'm sorry I couldn't be there for you either.
That's fine.
Hearing your voice already makes me feel better.
Wow. You make me wanna squeeze through the phone and be with you there.
Clingy?
Yes, I wanna be clingy.
Can I see your clingy face?
Ugh. P'Jo.
You're such a cheator.
You're not gonna turn on your camera?
No.
Why not? Turn it on.
I wanna see your face.
Please.
Please turn it on.
Woah. You're wearing a suit?
Um. I had a meeting earlier this morning.
I actually have never seen you in a suit before.
It's to hot to wear it.
And you're still continue working?
Um...a little.
This reminds me of that time.
What are you talking about?
When we first talked.
When we called...
...and I just fell asleep
while I waited for you to work.
Oh.
And...
do I have to be quiet? Not to disturb you this time?
No need.
Hey then why did I have to do it back then?
Cause I was not used to your voice.
I can talk now then?
I'm not stopping you.
I have...
a question for you, P'Jo.
What is it?
When you met me for the first time...
can you tell me what it felt like for you?
The firs time we met?
At the bar?
Yes.
I'm so mad, of course.
I understand why.
- You didn't have to be so cruel to me though.
- But you deserved it, didn't you?
- I did.
- Um.
I could scold you with literally everything you did.
Got in a fight in a bar?
Working behind my back
and put yourself in danger?
You worried me everyday.
I shouldn't have asked
to get myself scolded at.
P'Jo.
My mom asked...
that you're not going to visit her during the break?
Oh sure...but...
when my work is done.
Okay. Just let me know when.
I will have everything prepared nicely.
Oh and how's your birthday?
Just like any other year. Nothing special.
I didn't have a party or anything.
But my mom bought me a gift.
What is it?
She got me a pair shoes.
And do you want anything else?
I haven't bought you anything.
Woah. You already gave me so many things.
Then...
can I ask you for something else?
What is it?
P'Jo...
can you tell me that you love me?
- That's it?
- Woah...it's not 'That's it'.
Please. Tell me that you love me.
I love you, North.
I love you too, P'Jo.
- If I was there, you're not gonna get away from me.
- Huh!? What do you mean?
Nothing. I just wanna tell you that please be less cute.
Go to sleep.
But I wanna talk to you.
Go to sleep. I will be here.
Okay.
I wanna be with you.
You're probably so tired recently.
You want me to leave work behind
and come see you?
No.
Then don't be so cute like this.
If not, then I might need to leave my work.
I'm sleepy now.
Go to sleep then. I will be here.
No. I will be the one who stays up.
You're still working.
- Go to sleep. I will be here with you.
- No, I can't.
I will be the one who stays up for you.
You're stubborn.
I got it from you.
You're really good at arguing lately.
Ter.
Enjoy your trip.
P'Hill.
Johan.
Hello?
You're still up?
Yes, why did you answer me so quickly?
You said you're sleepy.
I just wokee up.
Probably cause I miss you too much.
You're done working now?
- Yes.
- Really?
Why finished early?
You said you have so many things to do.
But it's done now.
You're so good.
You're the most talented person in the entire world.
Are you gonna go back to sleep?
Yeah I think I will.
Really?
Yes, I'm still on the bed. Didn't get up or anything.
If you're gonna go back to sleep,
and why the lights are still on?
How do you know?
Open your window.
A delivery for you sir.
Special delivery just for my boyfriend.
Sure. I'm coming down.
Be careful.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I thought you said 'it's fine.'
I really am. It's fine if you cannot be here.
But it's definitely better if you're here.
Better than from the phone?
Yes, so much better.
You're probably exhausted.
You worked so hard, and still come see me.
Exhaustion is all gone.
What's this?
It's--. Err...
It's...
It probably caught my hand when I packed my things.
I didn't mean to bring this with me when I packed.
I swear.
Really.
I remember it was in the closet, wasn't it?
Or I have bad memory?
Yes.
I took it with me.
Why?
Cause I cannot sleep.
Cannot sleep?
Cause I'm not used to this.
I normally go to bed hugging you everyday.
When you're not around, I couldn't sleep.
At least...
I still have your smell.
Please do not...
Do not tease me. I'm begging you.
Ok I won't.
Then...
you don't need this shirt anymore.
Stop it.
You need to rest.
Sweet dream.
Sweet dream, baby.
I love you so much.
Did you know that?
Where are you going?
I will go cook.
And prepare stuff for my birthday merit making.
Are you coming with me?
Sure.
Then...
you can continue your sleep.
I will go prep things.
Um.
North. I already prepared food for you and P'Jo.
Don't forget to go make some merits.
I have some errands to do today. Will be back later tonight.
Woah.
My mom...
sneaked out again?
P'Jo.
P'Johan.
Thank you.
P'Jo.
We'll go make birthday merits
and can I stop by to visit my dad a bit?
Of course.
I never asked you this...
...but are you a buddhist?
Can you go to the temple then?
I can. It's okay.
P'Jo.
This is my dad.
His name is Ko.
Dad.
This is P'Jo.
He's my precious boyfriend.
You might not look as hot as him...
but that's okay. You don't have to be jealous.
At least mom...
also doesn't think that you're hot.
Hello North's dad.
I'm here to visit you already.
I miss you so much.
You were close to him?
Yes, I was really close to him.
I still want him to be around until these days.
Cause it was fun when he was here with me.
Can you tell me more about him?
My dad?
He's the kind of father who hang his 3 years old underwear
to the ceiling fan.
And I just stood there, looking at it and cried
cause I didn't have anything to wear.
There's another one.
When he fell off his motorcycle,
instead of going to the hospital.
He rode the motorcycle back to me.
then smiled and showed me he lost 2 teeth.
When I saw blood all over his mouth,
I was shocked and started crying.
Then my mom hit him and I cried even more.
Something like that.
That's why I grew up and become like this.
Not surprising at all.
And...
what happened to him? Do you mind?
Not at all.
He...
passed due to an accident.
During that time,
my family was kinda lost too.
But my mom said...
don't feel bad for those who passed.
Feel bad for the one who lives.
So that's why we tried to be strong.
And...
tried not to be so sad.
Cause we believed that
dad also doesn't wanna see me and my mom sad too.
Both of you are so strong.
Yeah.
Shall we go?
Hey don't you wanna do something on your birthday?
Right.
I don't know where to go.
But...
I want you to rest more.
Cause you've been working very hard too.
Get very little sleep. Last night also.
Had to drive all the way here too.
So I will let you rest first.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
Well...
I will let you rest first.
And we can discuss later.
Sure.
Anything you said.
Yup. That's it.
Are you sure you can drive, P'Jo?
Yeah.
I already got some rest.
Woo!
What a nice weather.
Oh P'Johan.
Can you teach me how to drive?
Or take me to the driving school?
Why?
Well...
so I can drive for you sometimes
and you can rest.
Thank you so much P'Jo.
For bringing me here.
Even if I asked you last minute.
It's okay.
This is your day.
I'm so excited.
I haven't done camping before.
Have you?
Never.
Oh and..
are we gonna survive tonight?
If we do not survive,
we can find a hotel to stay.
Okay.
And why camping?
I just want you to try things that are not so comfortable.
I'm kidding.
I just wanna change scenery
and be with the nature. That's all.
And I just thought camping
sounds really nice.
What about resort and well-prepared camping? Like glamping?
We can't do that.
If we wanna do camping, we have to try putting up a tent
and start a fire ourselves.
Let's just give it a try first.
If it doesn't work for us,
we don't have to do it again.
Adventurous things like this remind me of P'Arthit.
Why do you suddenly think of him?
The thought just came to my mind.
The person who likes adventurous things.
- You like that kind of person?
- Huh!?
Cause I don't know how to put up a tent?
That's all?
Are you seriously jealous of me and P'Arthit?
You're close to him too latele.
He asked you to grill steak and made a sauce, you also did it for him.
I charged him THB500 for doing that.
What's so good about him?
Why did you do all those for him?
Oh...nothing.
You're the best, P'Jo.
I love you the most.
P'Arthit is just...
another dog to me.
You're being so cute.
You're jealous.
This way, P'Johan.
Here. Take a seat.
Please sit.
You must be exhausted from driving.
- I will take care of the rest.
- Are you sure you don't need my help?
Yeah. Sit first.
Please.
Trust me. I will handle it.
You drove so far. Trust me.
You've never done this before, haven't you?
I can just look at the manual.ß
Fine. Fine.
I will rest here for a bit.
Thought you know how to do it?
I was kidding.
Here. Poke here.
Everyone knows.
Right?
I need to loosen the soil first.
Poke through here, right?
Just kidding.
I know.
This one goes through here, right?
The weather is getting chilly.
P'Jo, do you agree that cold weather...
and...
snuggling in a blanket
and watch a movie like this...
is really heart warming, you know?
Do you wanna watch this one?
Reviews are really good.
Really?
Um sure.
Okay. I will put it on.
"Go!"
"I will handle it from here."
"Then..."
"pelase take care of my friend."
- "Please take care of my friend."
- He's very chill.
P'Jo.
Hmm?
"Hia."
Thank you so much, P'Jo...
...for coming into my life.
Why suddenly you wanna thank me?
Well...
I'm just so happy.
When I have you with me,
it makes my birthday even more special.
Thank you so much. Really.
Actually--
I...
...don't have anything.
And I'm still the same North.
But everything becomes special because...
you're here with me.
You always pay attention to me.
And that makes me realize that...
you really love me.
and you will never leave me.
Did you know?
That you make me feel like
the most special person in the world.
So...
can you be with me for the rest of your life?
Whether it's this life,
next life or any life...
I will follow to see you in every life.
Am I too selfish?
You can be selfish as much as you want.
Cause I am too.
I don't want you to meet anyone else.
Thank you too for taking such good care of me.
And like you said...
we will be together in every life.
No matter in hell or in heaven.
I will follow you down.
I love you, North.
I love you too, P'Jo.
North.
Why are you up so early?
Well...
Since we're up here,
we need to see the sunrise.
That's right.
Fine. I'm up.
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
Watch out.
Wow. Such a nice weather.
Wow.
It's really beautiful, P'Jo.
Thank you...
for waking me up to see the sunrise.
Wow~
Really nice weather too.
North.
Yes?
This might seem to be too early...
but for me it feels so long already...
since the first day the I fell in love with you...
and waiting for you for many years.
I used to be such a disappointment.
Unreliable.
Unlike you.
I'm trying to be a better person,
so I can be someone you can rely on.
You are every reason...
that I don't need anything else.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
I will marry you.
Why are you such a crybaby?
It's because of you.
You know why.
If you're the one who asked, I only have one answer.
This is to engage you.
After graduation,
let's get married.
Sure, P'Jo.
I will hurry and graduate for you.
Let's get married.
That's very cute.
When are you getting married?
Not anytime soon.
We just wanna take pictures.
Congratulations in advance.
Thank you.
All done.
You're so handsome.
And whose husband-to-be though?
Mine.
Are you...
feeling hot?
A bit. But I'm still okay.
What about you? Are you hot?
I'm fine.
We will take separately first.
Who wanna go first?
I will go first.
This way please.
See. I think it was a great idea to take pictures first.
Look. They are so cute.
Do you wanna do it again?
I'm down with whatever.
And since we're here, don't you wanna go somewhere?
It's Christmas in LA.
There're probably a lot of people everywhere.
Shall we...
stay at home to celebrate?
Or...
do you wanna go out somewhere?
No, I'm up to you.
If it's up to me,
then can we stay in?
It's cold outside too.
Look. It's snowing.
It's too cold.
You're really acting.
Just a little.
Look. I was so rigid.
So embarrassing.
I never did things like that before.
Oh. I will check it for you.
It might be the delivery guy.
P'Jo.
They're delivering the Christmas tree.
Can you help me carry it?
You're really into Christmas huh?
Even bought a Christmas tree.
But I already ask for your permission.
I didn't say anything.
But isn't this too much work?
I think we should go out.
Or hire someone to do this for you.
No. I wanna do it myself.
Then let me help.
What do we have to do next?
Decorate the tree.
I have so many ornaments.
I bought so many.
Do you think my new earrings are pretty?
So dang cute.
You really complimented me.
I will put it here.
Where do you think I should put this?
It should be here,
cause we already have something big there.
Here?
No.
- Not so pretty.
- Too low?
- Here then.
- Here.
Where are you taking me?
I have a present for you.
What present?
Is it a new game?
But there's nothing coming out though.
Hey. Or is it gold?
I really love gold, P'Jo.
No, it's not.
- Hey.
- I'm about to open your eyes.
The claw machine?
Um.
Cause someone said 'he wants a gift'
when we were boyfriends.
So I got him a claw machine.
Cute, right?
I totally thought it was gold I'm getting.
P'Jo. I'm kidding.
This is cute.
But why...
there's only one turtle in there?
They probably forgot to take it out.
Let me complain them.
Hey. That's okay.
I think it's cute.
I will try to catch it tonight.
I'm gonna go for it.
Here we go.
Hey.
Hey. P'Jo.
I got it.
With your first attempt?
Hey.
P'Jo. It's so cute.
It even looks uglier than that one.
Hey.
How come?
He's such a cutie.
Come on, P'Jo.
You promised me that you're gonna do it.
Come on.
Let me tie it for you.
That'a not it.
You still need this.
Cute!
Why are you smiling?
Hey cause...
you're wearing an apron and looks so cute.
Let me see.
Let me see what you're filming.
Do not delete it.
You're pretty good at filming too.
Thank you.
Shall we start?
- Here.
- And...
where do I begin?
You mix the eggs first.
Crack the eggs and mix it all up.
Cookies are not that expensive, aren't they?
What did you just say?
Oh nothing.
- Mix the eggs right? Crack it first?
- Yes. Yes.
P'Jo. You should do it here.
The shell is in the bowl now.
P'Jo. You need to mix it like this.
Look how I do it. 1 2 3.
Swirl it like this.
Again.
Do it.
You're teasing me again.
Guys look. This guy is teasing me.
I'm not.
It was really yummy,
the cookies that made by you.
I didn't do anything.
I just mix everything together.
Really? It's really good.
Um.
Just a blink of an eye,
we've been together for a year already.
Let's do a quick recap...
of what...
we went through this year.
What about you?
How was yours?
You came to my life this year,
it's been the best year so far.
What about you?
Me too.
It was one hell of a year.
So many things happened.
Since...
the moment I woke up...
...and had a debt.
But at the end,
...plot twist.
My creditor has become my boyfriend.
Haaaa.
I have a question to ask you today as well.
What?
If you could wish for 3 things,
what would your wishes be?
3 wishes, right?
I'll give all the wishes to you.
Then I'll have 6 wishes?
Um.
What should I wish for?
I will ask my favorite game company
to produce a lot of new games.
And...
I'd wish for myself to have more money to buy their games.
I would wish to have time to play those games.
And I wish for myself, you, mom,
and eveyone around us to be so happy.
And lastly...
I'd wish for myself to win a lottery.
Even at least the last 3 digits.
You really wanna win a lottery that bad?
- Do you want the 2st prize? I will transfer for you.
- Wow.
You don't get me.
What I'm wishing for...
...is to make money for our household.
But if you give it to me,
the money is the same amount.
Yeah. I don't get it.
And anything else you would like to ask me?
I wanna ask you...
whether you have anything
that you wish I could change?
Or anything that you don't like about me?
Nothing. You?
For me?
If I'd have to change...
I would like to be more discrete.
Cause I think I'm too funny and immature.
I meant anything that you would like me to change?
See. I'm being funny again.
For you?
I think...
you don't need to change anything.
Cause you're already perfect.
Last question.
Do you have any questions that you wouldn't dare to ask me?
Every time I look at you,
I always have one question in mind.
What is it?
Who is this kid?
Where is he from?
How can he make me so in love with him?
Me too.
I also have a question.
Like who is this guy?
Who send him to me to make me happy in everyday?
Please be with me like this every year, okay?
Christmas and start a new year together.
Be together forever.
Sure.
I will be with you forever.
Whch one do you like better?
i like them both equally.
And you gave both of them to me.
And...
why don't you like this stupid ducky?
It is even the first gift you gave me.
Even though we didn't know each other
when we first met.
Because it was the first gift,
and I wanted to buy something nicer for you.
And...
what's wrong with this stupid ducky?
Look at his face.
Even you call him stupid ducky.
He looks stupid but he's still cute though.
Only his own mother would say he's cute.
Poor thing. Let me see.
What?
Your daddy doesn't love you?
What!?
Cause daddy can only love mommy.
P'Jo.
What are you doing? Playing house?
I better sleep.
Kiss me agiain?
All day long.