North.
I gotta go to the class.
You don't have any class today, right?
No, I don't.
Drive safe, P'Johan.
I'm going to class now.
Hey.
He had only coffee again?
Didn't eat any food.
Why didn't you eat something?
Only coffee again?
So stubborn.
We're have spaghetti for dinner.
North. I'm sorry. I have an urgent work.
Gotta go.
Don't wait up for me.
North.
I told you not to wait up.
I couldn't sleep when you're not around.
- Go where?
- To the bed.
This one has veggies.
I have to go to class.
What?
Wait. You said you have a class at 10?
You're not gonna eat first?
I remembered the wrong time.
And Hill called to wake me up.
I don't think I have time.
Sorry.
Hey. Is this mine?
Yes.
What about my food?
North.
You want me to carry you?
It's okay.
P'Jo.
Why are you still working?
You should go to bed already.
It's only a bit left.
Why are you out of bed?
I told you to go to sleep, didn't I?
I also told you before.
I cannot sleep when you're not around.
And why are you working so much?
As if you're in debt.
Are we in debt?
What if I said yes?
How much?
Umm...
Probably a billion.
A billion!?
Kidney is worth 4 million each.
If I sold 2 of mine, we'll have 8 million.
But it would not be enough still.
What did you do?
Why are we in such debt?
I don't think we should pay.
We should just flee the country.
Umm...
But are you gonna help me?
How am I going to help you?
Even if I sold my lungs too, still not enough.
Let's resign.
So you don't have to work
and I don't have to study.
But I will probably still need to work,
so I can take care of you.
Even I might get paid very little.
Cannot afford to eat..
...but we would still have each other.
Would you like to starve with me?
I'm not a high maintenance person.
Not picky about food either.
Very chill. Nothing serious.
What's the living condition gonna be like?
We'll probably need to sell your car.
Also your house and your condominium as well.
Then we will leave.
We might need to rent a small apartment.
I need a leader for the family.
Hand-to-mouth lifestyle.
Why?
You're in debt. You need to pay it off.
And what's gonna be your job?
What's the salary?
Just a normal job. THB15,000 salary.
15,000?
That's half day expense for me only.
Woah.
You need to live more frugally.
I don't like that word 'frugal'.
But I like it.
Like the word 'frugal'?
No. I like you. Haa!
I love you too.
I'm feeling sleepy already, P'Jo.
Shall we go to bed?
Let's go to bed.
Like really sleep.
Not like you trick me to go to sleep,
then you sneak out to work again.
I will really go to bed with you.
Let's go to bed.
Yeah.
Let's got to sleep.
- Haa!
- Again?
I will be home late today.
North.
What's the matter?
Eat.
I already heated up for you.
Why are you mad at me?
North. North. North.
Baby.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
North.
Babe.
You're that mad at me?
I will let you hit me.
- Hit me.
- No.
No, I won't.
You only care about work lately.
You don't take care of yourself.
You don't eat proper food.
Only drink coffee.
And you never rest.
I asked you to come to bed with me,
but you sneaked out to continue your work.
If I did all those things too,
wouldn't you be worried too?
I would.
Cause I care about you
that's why I work really hard,
so you don't have to work so hard.
And you're not going to think about how I feel?
I woke up early to cook your favorite food.
I wait up for you and you just never come home.
And when you do, you always work.
But..
I told you before...I understand that you need to work hard.
But please...
you need to take care of yourself too.
But I do all these for us.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I will improve myself.
But can you please stop being mad at me?
Please stop being mad at me.
No.
If I stop being mad easily, you'll never remember.
I'm serious this time.
- I'm really mad at you.
- North.
Don't do this.
What do I have to do,
so you'll stop being mad at me?
Hmm?
I will stop eventually.
You should take a shower first.
Okay.
P'Jo.
I'm still mad at you.
Then how am I supposed to sleep?
When you work, I also have to sleep by myself.
I told you before.
I cannot sleep without you by my side.
Even I told you that,
you still don't come to bed with me.
P'Jo.
If you are not gonna stop,
I'll go sleep on the couch.
Go in. Yeah.
You're mad at me still?
Food is on the table.
If you don't wanna eat, you can toss it.
North.
Why do you have to be sarcastic?
Can't we just talk nicely?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to be so mean.
I won't be sarcastic then.
But if you're not gonna eat,
it's fine.
North.
When will you stop being mad at me?
I couldn't sleep last night.
You're not
gonna let your guard down a little?
Why are you so cruel?
I have to be firm with myself too.
Cause if I don't,
you will never remember.
I do now.
North. I won't be like that anymore.
Forgive me please.
Please.
I will do anything. Really.
Not yet.
Can I have a hug before I go to work?
Oh.
Woah. That's a lot.
Go. Go. Go.
Come on. Come.
Hey.
I have to go.
Stop being mad at me already.
Yeah.
You will be late.
I'm going to work.
I will be back as soon as possible.
Call me if you need anything.
Sure.
Dad.
When Jeen is mad at you,
what do you do?
Take her shopping.
What if he doesn't want to go?
Then find another excuse to go.
When he got something, he'll be in a better mood.
What if he doesn't want anything?
Just buy him everything he looks at.
Bring him there, grab the stuff and put it in his hand.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
Yeah, I've been doing this for the past 20 years.
Works every time.
North.
Talk to me first. This is urgent.
What urgent?
Jeen asked me to do an errand for her.
Come with me.
- What errand?
- You should go change first. Come on.
P'Jo.
What kind of errands at the mall?
Hello.
Err...can I see the shirt from the front?
- Which size?
- Medium.
Let's do both medium and large.
You want new clothes?
Large is better. Looks more comfortable.
I will take Large.
This one too.
This one.
And this one.
Please, this way.
P'Jo. You need to chill.
You want the bag from the front
or some other ones?
Err....I just--
If you are not gonna choose,
I'll choose it for you.
Fine. This one.
This one?
Isn't it a bit too cheap?
It's fine.
One is enough.
We might not be able to carry all of it home.
They do have delivery.
Would you like anything else?
It's fine.
Why are you doing this?
Are you pressuring me to stop being mad at you?
No, it's not like that.
I remember when Jeen is mad at my dad,
he'll buy her everything that she looks at and things will get better.
So...I thought I could try this
and you might stop being mad at me.
And when you said you had to do an errand today--
P'Jo.
This is not working.
That's okay. I can keep buying.
I will take all of them. One each.
You can do home delivery, right?
- Please wait a moment.
- Sure.
Now, you'll have multiple bags
for your class everyday.
I don't wanna switch everyday.
Could you please come to the cashier?
All set.
Products'll be delivered to you
within 3 working days.
Thank you so much.
I will buy everything that you look at today.
As a way of saying sorry. Okay?
P'Jo.
I think what you're doing is too much.
All these are so expensive.
This is not the right thing to do.
Even though I'm mad at you,
but I don't want you
to ask for forgiveness like this.
And how would you like me to do it?
I begged already.
Even talked nice and soft.
You're still not letting your guard down.
And...
this is the only way I can think of.
You looked at the shoes?
You want some shoes?
No. No. P'Jo.
When did I say I want it?
P'Jo.
- I will help you carry.
- It's fine. Let me carry it.
You need to stop buying.
Now, I have plenty of shoes.
I didn't look at anything either.
Anything else you want?
I didn't want anything in the first place.
So does this mean...you're no longer mad at me?
I'm even more mad now.
Hey. My dad told me he uses this trick with Jeen for 20 years.
It always works.
But it does not work with me.
Or I need to buy more?
P'Jo.
Let's do this way.
If you can catch one of these dolls for me,
I will stop being mad at you.
If I caught it,
you will completely stop?
Yes.
You will talk to me like usual?
But...
You need to promise me
that you're not gonna over-working again.
And you need to eat proper food too.
Not just coffee.
If not,
I won't forgive you ever again.
I promise.
I will catch a doll for you.
P'Jo.
This duck looks exactly
like the one in our room.
Oh...do you want some other ones then?
You already have this one.
It's fine.
I can have another one.
One more thing, that ducky...
you gave it to me as a gift
since when did you know each other.
This one you can give it to me as gift from a boyfriend.
It's totally okay,
if you cannot catch it.
I'll catch this one for you.
Almost get it, P'Jo.
It's okay if you cannot.
I'm actually not that mad at you.
I just wanted to act cool and all.
I'm worried and care about you, P'Jo.
I really want you to take care of yourself.
But now I'm okay.
North. I almost got it.
Wait a min.
I think it's okay for people
to have things that they can't do.
Nobody's perfect with everything.
I'm perfect with everything.
P'Jo.
I really appreciate it.
Really...you're doing all these for me.
I know that you love me the most.
Nobody loves me like you do.
So....
...i'm hungry now.
P'Jo...shall we go eat something?
I can do anything for you.
I love you the most.
But you just need to wait a bit more.
Let's go, P'Jo.
I'm hungry.
North. Just a moment.
I almost got it.
- Let's go.
- North. North. North..
How much does this machine cost?
North.
North. Can I try again?
Stop it, P'Joham. Eat first.
Eat first.
You know that I don't really use all these stuff.
But...
thank you anyway. I will try to use all of them.
I know that you're not gonna use it,
but I want you to have it.
Thank you.
Oh there's another thing I want to buy for you.
And you need to take it.
But I don't want anything anymore.
My computer still working just fine.
Oh I heard you complained that it's over heating and it's lagging.
Just a little sometimes.
You're not gonna have a look?
New edition of Neon Horizon will be coming out soon.
What about Marvel Rival?
Naraka...we're talking about.
- Fine. We won't have a look.
- Fine. We can have a look just for a min.
Just a little bit.
Go check it out.
P'.
Do you have 5090 GPU available?
We do, but the price has gone up quite high.
How much is it?
THB140,000.
What are you currently using?
I'm using...
2060.
P'Jo.
Er...I just talked to the guy.
The price has increased so much,
If we're talking about the latest one.
It's THB140,000.
but if we're looking at one step down,
it's around THB70,000.
Which one do you want?
To be frank,
I kinda want the newest one of course.
But I can't afford with that price.
It's too high.
It's probably because there are so much demand
and they have little stock.
Price might go down in awhile.
It's fine.
Thing is...do you want it?
Err...
I think it's too expensive.
If I upgrad my GPU,
I'll need to upgrade my CPU too.
If I upgraded my CPU,
I'll need to upgrade my mainboard.
So with the upgraded mainboard, they'll draw a lot more power.
Then I need a new power supply.
So with all that,
there's only the case that I can keep.
Then we will change all of that.
Ughh. I can't.
Replace all of those, I cannot.
But my computer still working okay. Might be lagged a little.
Or maybe not so little.
It's quite lagging.
But I can bear with it.
But If you play open world games, and the graphic is not nice. It's lagging.
It's not gonna be fun, isn't it?
That's true.
But I think it's too expensive.
Really.
Do they have everything you just mentioned?
From what I talked to him, they do.
- Yeah I will take all those.
- Sure.
I already informed him.
If you'd like to upgrade anything,
I can recommend you.
What are you currently using?
I'm using 20.
Power supply too.
P'Jo.
All in all, it will be THB200,000.
Let's do it.
I think it's too expensive.
No, it's not.
Only THB200,000.
You have always wanted a good computer, right?
You also plays game everyday.
But I still think the price is too high.
It's true that I have always wanted a nice computer.
But it's too expensive.
Just take it as a gift from me.
Can you please accept it?
Or...you don't want it?
I do.
I have always wanted it.
Then shall I transfer to pay now?
Sure. You may transfer 50% deposit first.
Another 50%, you can pay when you come pick it up.
Then I will transfer now.
Here's the QR code.
Thank you very much.
Here's your receipt.
Use this on the day you come pick it up.
Thank you.
Let's go.
New computer. New computer.
Yayy. New computer.
I got a new computer, P'Jo!
- You're in such a good mood.
- Hey. Of course.
I got a brand new computer.
Thank you, P'Jo.
I love you so much.
Go.
That's it.
North's life.
Born to play games, love P'Jo, and just die.
New computer.
I didn't kiss you for the whole day.
I almost couldn't survive.
Me too.
No more being mad, yeah?
But you need to behave like a good boy too, understand?
Understood.
Heyyy. New computer.
Hmm the spec.
What are you doing, P'Jo?
I better go shower.
Can I join?
- No.
- Yes. I will join.
No.
- Let me join.
- No!
Soft lather.
That's tickling.
P'Jo.
You hands are so pretty.
What makes it pretty?
It's just beautiful.
Here. If you compared with my hand...
Look.
My hands are so chubby.
They are cute.
Looks like ginger root.
Umm...actually...
I've never asked you about  your tattoos.
What's the meaning behind?
I'm a realist dreaming.
The impossible.
I am...
The person who accepts a situation as it is.
Dreaming of thins that can't happen?
- Like that?
- Um.
Something like that.
I think I am a realist, who lives with the present.
But many times...
I do think about the impossibles as well.
Like what?
You.
When I got these tattoos,
I thought of you.
I did these in LA.
When I wanted to forget you.
So that's the story behind.
Umm...but there are some other stuff too.
There are things in life that's impossible too.
But 80% of the meaning behind is you.
Then...should I get some tattoos about you too?
What tattoos?
Like your name on my forehead.
Or you face on my chest.
Not a good idea?
Not at all.
I was just kidding, P'Jo.
I actually wanted to get a tattoo once.
But I didn't know what to get.
Then don't.
You don't think I should?
Um.
If you said so...
then I won't do it.
Dad.
This is P'Jo.
My precious boyfriend.
Hello dad.
There's anything you want to do in your birthday?
Having you makes my birthday becomes the best day in my life.
Will you marry me?