When I go to Boston,
are you gonna miss me?
Of course. I will.
What's the matter?
You look a little pale.
You said you're not gonna get sick, huh?
How should I punish a stubborn kid?
P'Johan...
I like you.
You want money?
Send me your video clip. I will pay you THB100 a second.
I miss you.
I'm waiting for you to come back.
Why don't you talk more?
It's only 20 secs.
That's equivalent to THB2,000.
I don't know what else to say.
Hey.
Damn!
- 700,000.
Why 700,000?
Oh.
I think...
it's not a THB100 per second.
But it's actually $100 per second.
That's a lot of money.
Wow..
Are you buying our lunch?
What's wrong?
Why are you looking so stressed?
Physic's exam result is out.
I did so bad.
Huh!?
Since when do you care about school?
P'Jo kinda tutored me for this subject.
Even he was very busy.
It's fine.
You did your best, right?
Come on.
And how long has it been that he's gone to Boston?
4 days.
Do you miss him?
- Enough with the teasing.
- Hey.
I'm seriously asking you.
What would you say?
If it was P'Hill who went to Boston?
Awww...it's alright. It won't be that long.
Only 2 weeks and he'll be back.
I really wanna fast forward the time.
Why are you looking distracted?
Here.
- You're home?
- Yeah.
Hey.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm gonna turn off the light, okay?
Um.
Don't think too much.
Smile.
Yeah.
Good night.
You should go to bed too.
- The truck only delivered the ice out front. We have to carry it so far.
- So damn heavy.
You're looking like a sad dog there.
You're missing him that much?
Yeah.
I texted him but he hasn't replied me.
If you're worried, why don't you just call him?
I don't wanna disturb him.
Hey.
If you can't do anything,
then why don't you come help us?
Can't you see what we are doing?
He probably doesn't want to do it.
The gear event.
I's for you to come with your lovers.
But his boyfriend won't be here.
Oh.
My poor friend.
It's okay.
Ughh. I don't have a boyfriend.
Hey wait.
You guys are not boyfriends yet?
Why?
Or...
he hasn't asked you yet?
He's in a real bad shape.
With his conditions,
he needs to see the doctor.
What kind of doctor?
Doctor Johan.
You guys are so funny huh?
I'm gonna go.
- Where are you going?
- Go see Ter.
Hey don't be mad.
Aren't you gonna come back and help us?
No.
What's the matter with him?
What are you drawing?
Here.
There.
P'Hill. P'Fah. Hello!
- Oh hi.
- Hi.
What about me?
Why do I have to say hi to you?
- You guys are working?
- Um.
We also have to do for Jo's.
P'Hill.
Have you been talking to P'Jo?
Why?
You miss him?
Well...
...yes.
Then call him.
I do not dare to call him.
I'm afraid I might some how disturb him
You can call him.
If he's busy, then he just won't answer.
Don't be afraid.
I'll call for you.
Why are you such a chicken?
What's up?
Are you drowning with work to death?
Are you cursing me or something?
I'm just worried about you.
I'm still alive.
What about him? How is he?
He's good.
If you're worried, why don't you give him a call?
Don't you wanna talk to him?
It's not like that.
If I talk to him, I even wanna go home more.
Just hearing his voice,
I can just leave all my work here behind.
But he misses you.
Really? As much as I miss him?
Oh tell him this for me, about the exam result.
he doesn't have to think too much.
He's done well.
I will tell him for you.
You can go back to work now.
I will call you when necessary.
I told you. See!? It's nothing.
You don't have to be overthinking.
It's alright. He will be back in a few days.
Oh.
Can you give this to him when he's back?
What is it?
His midterm score.
You can open it.
- P'Fah.
- Hmm?
What's the red mark here?
It means 'Failed'.
- English?
- Um.
P'Jo failed English test?
Here's the thing, he doesn't attend any of the classes.
He said the professor teaches stuff that's too easy.
Like we're in college, but still teaches grammar.
I know that it's easy, but he has to attend some classes.
And where is he gonna get the grade?
It's not like he got TOEIC score 900,
- and he doesn't have to attend any class.
- He got 900?
If I were you, I call him 3 times and he doesn't pick up,
I probably won't call anymore.
What are you doing? He doesn't get it!
(TOEIC  in Thai sounds like 'Call some one 900 times')
I will give it to P'Jo myself.
- Once is enough. I'm begging you.
- Call again? (TOEIC)
- No more.
- I'm still hurt.
Good, so you will remember. You embarrassed me.
I used TOEIC pun,
you need to play along with me sometimes.
Then you go use that pun alone.
Hey North. Are you done?
The even will start soon.
Don't rush me.
I squeeze until my hands are burning.
Don't complain, North.
Look at me here.
Whose idea was this to make healthy drinks?
Hey cause people are now interested to take care of their health more.
Just like me.
You're the root cause, Get.
If it's not because of your name on paper,
all of us wouldn't have to be here.
I probably be wandering around the fair already.
Damn it.
What are you complaining?
Nao. I bought you lunch.
Wow.
We could've been starving, if you didn't buy.
It's raining heavily.
- Thank you dude.
- Yeah.
Hey guys. Here.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
So wet.
Absent minded again.
You're missing him again?
No.
But I have always been missing him.
Woww.
You got me curious.
How? Like how are you missing him?
Well...
I just miss him.
Wanna talk.
Wanna see his face.
I don't know what he's doing right now.
Is he gonna eat 3 times a day? Or will he just drink only coffee?
Don't know how much is his workload.
i'm just worried about him
I want him to be here with me.
You miss him so much huh?
Yeah. Why do you ask?
- Can you hear me!?
- Huh?
P'.
You heard all of it?
Yeah.
You're free now?
I'll have to hang up soon.
Hey now he's down again.
I have to go.
He hung up.
Why didn't you tell me you were calling him?
If I told you, were you gonna say all those things?
That you miss him?
You let it all out my friend.
You're so---
Let's eat.
What?
Nothing.
'Drawing club'
Oh Ter.
North is not coming?
I haven't seen him here lately.
Um His faculty has a gear event.
He's helping them prep.
Bu the event is today right?
Shall we go guys?
There's a concert and so many food at the fair.
Shall we?
- Gear event?
- Um.
Sure. I'm in.
Dao, join us.
Um sure.
Really!?
Foam. Are you joining?
- Sure.
- Then...
I will ask P'Hill to come with us, is that okay?
So you just wanna hang out with your boyfriend?
No, it's not like that. I wanna go with you guys.
But the fair does not occur everyday right?
And it's not easy to have all of our friends here.
What would you like to drink?
Orange juice please.
For how many?
2 glasses.
- Get me some ice.
- Sure. Sure.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Can I have Tiger's LINE ID?
Tiger's LINE ID.
Suer.
She's asking for your LINE ID.
No.
Suer! She's cute. Are you sure?
I said no.
I'm sorry.
Yelling to let customers walk in.
Want some healthy drinks?
- Healthy juice for your health.
- Can I get one orange juice?
One orange juice.
Nao.
- Huh?
- Come here.
What?
How's the broadcasting?
It's been okay. Why?
Are those 2 people who donates you still around?
Yeah they are.
They are always watch me almost all of lives.
Why?
I think they like you.
Especially the one named Gun.
He donates A LOT to you.
Sending you so many stars.
Really?
I think he just likes...
my broadcast. That's all.
No, I think he's like really into you.
Don't you feel it?
I only see him on screen yeah?
I don't even know him in real life.
I'm not special or anything in real life too.
Why do you think that way?
It's true.
He only sees me online.
He doesn't know the real me.
What if...
there's someone who likes you for who you are?
- Why are you asking me that?
- Hey.
I'm your friend, right?
I just wanna know if there's someone who likes you for who you really are,
what are you gonna do?
- If there's someone who likes me for who I really am?
- Um.
I think that would be nice.
But I don't think there's one.
You do your work. I'm gonna continue mine now.
You can scan to pay.
Have you been waiting for long?
Not really. Just arrived too.
Where's Foam?
That one is picking up a girl.
He probably wants to walk around the fair with his lover for sure.
I will walk around with my lover too.
P'Hill.
Where are you guys going?
He's inviting me to go to gear event.
You should join us.
Come join us P'Fah. Come together with many people.
It should be fun.
I actually...
have some errands to do.
I don't think I can join.
Would you excuse me?
Hey.
Bye then.
North.
Hmm?
Dude.
I wanna be at the concert with Nao.
Only just the 2 of us.
What!? Why are you doing this to me again?
Please. Help me.
When we go inside,
can you just leave us?
Fine. This is for the sake
of the effort that you've been trying though.
If not, I wouldn't help.
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing.
- Let's go. Concert is about to start.
- Yeah.
And now it is time, that you guys have been waiting.
This is our highlight for today.
Dude. Let's go in the front.
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Hey I will leave you guys from here then.
- Thank you, dude.
- See you.
And to not waste anymore time, please meet our first band!
Let's go, P'Hill.
- This one?
- I like this one.
- I like the blue one.
- Try it.
See. It suits you.
Yeah right.
(If you pay attention,)
(you'll see love that is not too far from you...)
If there's someone who likes me for who I really am?
I think that would be nice.
- (Two people. Just to meet...)
- Nao.
- When North asked you about if there's someone who likes you for who you are.
- (what kind of attraction is that?)
What?
I just wanna tell you...
that I...
Hey where is North?
Where did he go?
He went to buy some food.
Oh.
And what were you saying?
(My heart beats fast only when I'm with you)
- I said the song is nice.
- Yeah.
I really like this song.
Can you make some noise?
Why are you looking so sad?
You miss me that much?
Why are you...
What's wrong?
You miss me, didn't you?
I do.
I miss you so much.
I'm here now.
Don't have to cry anymore.
Make some noise!
P'Jo. I wanna eat that.
2 sausages please.
Hey P'Jo.
Are you leaving?
No.
Then where are you going?
We haven't checked out all of the booths.
Um. Do you wanna go for some ride?
Ride?
Sure.
Sounds fun.
Let's go.
You like it?
I do.
It's so beautiful.
Oh I wanted to ask you this.
Why are you back early?
Aren't there just a few more days until your flight back?
Cause someone said he misses me.
He wants to see me.
Wanna talk to me.
Being together is better, isn't it?
Yes.
And...
did you drink coffee instead of actual food over there?
I told you to eat some food too.
Was there a lot of work in Boston?
I was worried about you.
You know what...
the work at Boston was not difficult or heavy at all,
but whenever I turned to my side and I didn't see you,
it's more difficult for me.
What I'm trying to say is...
having you by my side,
it's way better that way.
So...
can you stay by my side forever?
Will you be my boyfriend?
Yes.
You're so mean!
I miss you so much.
When I wanted to talk to you, you hung up on me.
Do you have any idea how much I miss you?
I'm responsible for that.
I will be there for you to hug every night, okay?
You're so clingy.
Stop it.
Thank you.
It's me.
That needs to thank you.
That kiss.
I have to charge you.
I can pay.
Hey. I will go talk to the professor first.
You can wait for me at the cafe.
I think Ter is there.
Sure.
What do you wanna eat today?
Think about it.
Where have you been?
I've got a question.
Why?
Are you guys boyfriends already?
Hey. How do you know?
Here.
Are you?
So cute!
A shipper like me can die peacefully now.
Oh dude.
The movie that you wanna see is now in the theater.
It's in?
Um.
I might go see it with P'Hill. You should ask P'Jo.
- Let's go.
- Really?
Deal!
Help me eat this cake.
- Oh hi.
- Hello.
Those 2 went to talk to the professor, right?
Yes.
North.
so...
you're officially with Jo, right?
Yes.
I'm so happy for you and...
hope you guys stay together for a very long time.
If you need any help, please let me know.
You're my friend's boyfriend now.
- Thank you, P'Fah.
- Um.
Good luck.
- What's up with you?
- I'm just so happy. That's all.
- Dancing like a crazy person.
- P'Fah.
Has P'Arthit been back?
Nope.
- Oh you guys are back.
- Um.
You didn't wait for me?
North kinda stole some bite.
- Is it good?
- It is good.
How was the talk with professor?
- Went well.
- Oh Hill.
Ter was asking why Arthit has not been back yet?
i think same reason.
- Um.
- He's into the native local lifestyle again?
Um.
He's been like that before?
Yes.
He gets bored easily.
He likes to try new things.
So when he goes away, it's difficult to come back.
But I think if he doesn't come back,
- He might get a suspension.
- Have you tried calling him?
I did. He didn't answer my call.
I will call him myself.
What' s up dude?
Where are you?
Manaus.
What's that sound so loud?
Manaus? In Brazil?
Thought you said you're in Miami.
I wanna fish some piranhas.
Fishing? Piranha?
Yeah. I'm kinda busy. Can we talk later?
Come back already.
You might get a suspension.
- Who's that? Fah?
- Yeah.
I know, but I have to go. The nurse is calling me.
Huh? Nurse? What are you doing?
I got bitten by piranhas.
Oh Jo. Can you transfer me some money?.
I don't have enough to go back.
Why do I have to do that?
Don't forget to do that.
I'll have my wound cleaned first.
See.
He's your friend.
He's also your friend.
So the movie.
Yeah what should we do?
Ask P'Jo.
We have to go together anyway, right?
Ask him.
Don't mess ti up.
Shall we?
I gotta go.
P'Johan.
What's up?
So...
Ter and P'Hill are going for a movie.
do you wanna go with me?
You wanna see it?
Yes, I do.
Sure then.
Really?
But...
you know what you have to do right?
When you're asking me for something,
what do you have to do?
P'!
Then I won't go then.
Up to you.
I should have charged you interest in the first place.
Let's go for a movie.
I haven't had dinner with you for so long.s
And who ask you to work that hard?
You haven't stopped eating.
Cause it's yummy.
Thank you.
Thank you, P'Hill.
You always buy me food.
You thank the wrong person.
All the money I used to buy you food came from Jo.
Why do you have to!?
I was not comfortable too,
but the owner of the credit card
asked me to use all of the money.
Thank you.
Keep eating.
I'm full.
So full.
Why are you smiling?
What do you wanna see?
The horror movie.
Aren't you scared of ghosts?
What about you, Ter? What would you like to see?
Shall we see the horror movie with North?
Are you sure that you won't get scared?
I will,
but I wanna see it.
Let's go buy the tickets.
Do you normally watch movies?
I haven't been to the theater for so long.
Because of work?
Um.
He's ruining the mood.
I thought I was gonna have a heart attack.
You screamed so loud, North.
I was terrifying.
You didn't see anything.
You close your eyes the whole time.
Do you wanna stop by somewhere first?
I think I will just leave.
Err...where are we going?
Back to the dorm.
Hey.
Are you guys going up too?
Let's go.
Hey hey.
What's going on?
P'.
I want you to move in with me.
Huh!?
How?
- Go go.
- What the hell?
I also don't know.
Their room is so small.
You've been here before, haven't you?
I didn't pay attention back then.
- You have anything to do with this, right?
- I don't. I just found out with you.
Excuse me. Would you like to pack your personal belongings yourself,
or you'd like me to do it?
I will do it by myself.
- You should have told me.
- I told you I just found out about it now.
Anything else?
P'Hill. Pull it more.
More.
Are you being sarcastic?
Hey. How can I forget this?
This stupid duck?
- Throw it away. You cannot bring it with you.
- No.
This duck is very important to me.
He's so cute.
He's so cute. Here.
You need to give him a chance.
Important?
It is.
It is a last orientation gift.
He saved my life.
I think we should break up.
Someone wants to give you this.
Smile please :).
Can I....
keep it?
you like it that much?
Yes.
Fine.
I bought you so many things,
but you like this duck so much.
Cute. Cute.
You get to live~
How long have you had a crush on me?
Quite long. 3 years already.
3 years!?
Do you think it's weird
if I like someone that has never done anything for me?
I knew it.
You always check him out.
Jo. Have you heard of his news?
He got a scholarship to study in the USA.
After today,
you might not get to see him anymore.