P'Hill has contacted you?
I heard that there was am emergency at his family.
No one had been able to contact him.
Hill.
Cover your boyfriend's eyes.
I'm going to Boston.
Are you going to Boston?
I'm so tired.
Are you feeling better yet?
Not yet.
Hello, P’Hill?
Is Jo there?
Yeah, but he’s still sleeping.
Do you want me to wake him up?
Wake him.
Sure. I will wake him for you.
P’Jo.
P’Hill wants to talk to you.
He doesn’t wake up.
Can you put me on speaker? I will talk to him myself.
Sure.
You’re on speaker now.
Jo.
What?
You’re so attached to North.
What do you want?
Come to class.
No.
Are you gonna cuddle with him all day? Come to the class.
I won’t keep the work sheet for you this time.
Fine. I will be there. Hang up now.
P’Jo.
You said you’re gonna go to class.
I just wanna sleep a little bit more.
Wait. We're late. Come on.
I’ll wait inside. See you.
What?
is it okay that you skip the cheer room like this?
It’s fine. I wanna be here for the tryout.
Black tee faster! Faster!
Be steady. Come on.
- Oh North.
- Hello P’Arthit.
Hi. Hi.
What are you doing here?
- You’re here for the tryout?
- No actually.
- I’m here with my friends.
- Oh ok.
I’m just gonna go.
I’ll follow you later.
P’Arthit.
- Meds students also do tryouts today?
-Um.
I’m waiting for the first year. Don’t know when are they gonna come.
- North.
- Yes?
Can I take a picture with you?
One pic.
Yes.
- Can I post it?
- Sure.
Can I have your IG?
I will tag you.
Why did you take a picture with me though?
Come on.
I just wanna tease someone.
Okay.
North. Come here.
Would you excuse me?
Go go.
Hello~ What's up?
Delete the picture.
So now you're quick.
Thit.
I won't. Why do I have to delete it?
Are you messing with me?
Where are you?
At the football field. Are you coming?
I can't.
But you need to delete the picture.
If you want me to delete, transfer me money.
You're that poor to begging me for money?
No, I just want your money. That's all.
Just transfer me.
How much?
Err around....
2,000 then.
No no actually. 20,000.
No no.
I think that's too little.
Can I have 200,000?
More suitable for Mr.Johan.
What the f*ck?
Stop messing with me.
What are you guys doing?
I'm not asking about you.
Don't think for yourself.
Well....
he's with his friends.
Watching people trying out.
Send me a picture.
And not your picture. Don't you dare.
Sure~
So how much are you gonna pay me?
How much for each picture?
How much do you want? Just tell me.
Let's do this. 2,000 per picture.
I will send you the full album.
Okay? Do we have a deal?
Fine. Just take some good pictures.
Okay. Deal.
Stretch. Stretch.
Football?
but they are stretching their arms?
Oh Nao.
- What?
- Your brother is in Boston, right?
Nuea? Yes, he is.
Why?
Well...
P'Johan is going to work there.
What's the time difference between here and Boston?
Umm...11 hours.
Like our daytime would be their night time.
Really? You don't miss your brother at all?
I do.
I wanna visit him. Saving up for that now.
But I've never been abroad before.
Am I gonna make it?
Ask Ger to go with you.
I did.
He said no. He's busy.
- A person like Ger says no?
- Yeah.
Try asking him again.
He might thought that you asked for the sake of politeness.
I will try and ask him again.
- Let's go to the field.
- So hard-working.
Look at how they run.
Are they alright?
They're gonna fall.
Hello, P'Prang?
Hello, North where are you?
I'm at the football field.
Why?
So...
Jo asked me to pick you up.
Pick me up?
To where?
To see him.
I gotta go. I'm almost there.
Where are you going?
Well...
To see the doctor.
Huh? Are you sick?
Are you okay?
Are you having a fever?
- Or stomachache?
- What are you doing?
Or back pain? What's wrong?
You're not having a fever.
I don't know. That's why i'm going to see a doctor.
See you.
Why don't you tell me?
Hey.
- North.
- Hello P'Prang.
Hello
You drove all the way here?
I had some errands nearby anyway.
And Jo called me. Asked me to come pick you up.
He's probably at the tryout.
- Yes.
- Oh.
You know that he will be going to Boston, right?
P'Jo already told me that.
This trip is a big customer.
Wow.
He's such a hard working person.
Umm..previously was not this much.
But his father said he's gonna let him take over the company
after he graduates.
I actually think it's too early for him.
But Jo insists to do it.
Give him the company?
Yes.
Jo was not an easily frustrated person like this.
He's more cheerful than this.
But lately,
he's stressed and rarely hangout with anyone.
I don't know how someone this age can handle all these.
But...
Jo is really good.
He's studying and working at the same time.
I told you all these..
cause I actually wanna tell you...
that it's good that it's you.
Jo told me...
I don't know...but...
he's better when he's with you.
Really?
Let's go. I will drop you off.
Sure.
Ugh...it's raining like this.
I don't have an umbrella too.
Umm.
It's okay. I will just run over there.
It won't take long.
Are you sure?
Do you want my jacket?
No, it's fine.
Thank you for picking me up, P'Prang.
I'm gonna go then.
Thank you.
P'Hill. Hi.
Oh you're here to see Jo?
Hi P'Tonfah.
You were out in the rain?
You're soaking wet.
Jo looks tired.
Probably didn't get enough sleep.
You can wake him up.
It's fine.
Okay.
Hey Fah.
Oh you're here.
Yeah it's raining outside.
Now, I can't even do my tryout.
Oh I see you again.
You should have come with me.
No, I would be all wet if I came with you.
Wake him up.
No, why do you want him to wake up.
I'm gonna ask him for my money.
He owes me 15,000.
He owes you money?
Jo owes you?
Yeah.
For the pictures.
What pictures?
I can't.
It's a secret.
Why? Tell me.
Just wake him up.
Hey. Wake Jo up.
It's time for the tryout.
P'Jo.
P'Johan.
It's raining?
Yeah. It's raining outside.
Who let you walk in the rain?
What if you catch a cold?
You can die!
I'm not gonna get a cold easily.
Yeah we will see.
Wear this.
Thank you
Hey.
Hey Jo.
My money?
What for?
Hey. For the pictures.
You took like you used your feet to take.
Still dare to ask for my money?
Hey.
You asked me to take those pics.
Fine. You're so annoying.
That's it.
You transfer me in the first place and it's done.
Happy?
Are we done?
Go. Hill is asking for you.
I'm so lazy.
You go do it for me, Arthit.
Wait. Can't you see my condition?
It won't be long.
Fine.
Bye.
Wait. Where's Jo?
It's fine. You do it for him then.
Let's go.
We're ready.
Thank you.
Oh you're going to Boston after the midterm right?
Um.
I heard that Arthit is also going to America.
But just a few days for holiday.
- Going to America?
- Um.
Miami.
Not surprising.
Come here.
Jo. There're lots of people here.
I don't mind.
So...are you taking him to Boston too?
No.
Or you wanna go?
I have class.
But if I really wanna go, you can take me?
Um.
Wherever you want, I will take you there.
Hey. You should go down now.
Hill is calling you.
This is your club.
Go.
This is already worn.
Yeah.
I did help with the tryout instead of you.
Come on Jo.
Do I really have to wear this after you wore it?
What's up?
Jerk! Where are you?
I'm at the basketball court.
Why're you calling me a jerk?
My bike key is with you.
How am I supposed to go back? I'm all wet.
Why do you have to be hot headed when the weather is so cooling? Ask Ger to come get you.
It's not cooling. What if my scooter got stolen?
You can come get it later. Just park there.
You're at the basketball court right?
I'll see you there.
Hey.
- North.
- Yes?
Can I ask you something?
How's it going with Johan?
How's it going?
He seems stressed lately.
But when he's around others,
he doesn't show.
That's why I wanna know how is he when he's with you.
- When he's with me?
- Um.
He looks tired.
Doesn't talk much.
But he talks a lot when he's around you guys.
Then it's probably how he is himself lately then.
How he is himself?
Like how?
Like a person doesn't have only one side.
When we're really stressed,
sometimes they just don't wanna talk to anyone.
And Jo is probably like that.
But he...
rarely shows that side to anyone.
With other people, he talks normally, right?
But with you, he doesn't talk much, correct?
Then that means...
he's willing to show you that side of him.
Without having to pretend or force himself.
Because with some people, he has to pretend
to show everyone that he's okay.
When in reality deep down...
he might feel really bad inside.
And do you think...
which one is better?
I think...
whatever how he feels or think,
let him be.
If he's stressed, he can say he's stressed.
He doesn't have to pretend at all.
I understand.
When people say Jo is better because of you,
it's true.
- Better?
- Um.
Because of me?
Um...how?
Let me ask you.
Have you ever thought?
With this kinda situation,
it's like he puts stressed on you.
Not really.
He's really stressed.
And there're so many things for him to do.
There.
It's good that it's you.
I'm not thinking too much.
No matter what it is.
You don't have to be pretend to be okay.
You can just show...
how you feel.
If possible,
I want you to
stay by his side like this.
If...
P'Johan is better when he's with me,
then I won't go anywhere.
You make me wet.
Hello, Suer?
Where are you?
Why?
Can you come pick me up?
My key is with North.
I'm at the side of the football field.
Who are you with right now?
I'm alone. Ikkyu and Get left me.
I'm just telling you.
You can come pick me up when the rain stops.
I'm just giving you a heads up that--
Um. You just wait there.
Hey.
What the hell? Hey.
You're still gonna come pick me up right?
You're done?
Not yet. Too many people.
I need do continue some other days.
What are you guys talking about so much?
I saw that.
Why?
Are you jealous?
I will tell you later.
It's all about you.
What about Hill?
He's gone. Probably went and pick Ter up.
I should go too the.
If we wait for the rain to stops, it will be a long time.
Are you also going back?
Sure.
- Riding a bike in the rain is not a problem.
- Bye.
Bye. See you.
What about you?
I can.
The problem is not that.
I should have asked him to take him too.
You take the big bike today?
Umm.
Actually....
I can be out in the rain as well.
- I'm very good at that.
- Stop acting like you're so strong.
- I really can.
- Just be quiet.
Arthit, you've got a raincoat?
If I have one,
I wouldn't be in this condition, would I?
I will just wait until it stops.
I'm gonna go then.
See you.
He likes to  flex his muscle yeah?
Are you tired?
Doing tryout with the 1st year?
Just in general.
About working and studying at the same time?
Umm..
And you are going to Boston for busines talk?
P'Prang told you?
Yes.
She told me so many things.
And...
will it be a tough for this Boston trip?
It's probably one of the hardest that I've done.
You can do it.
Um.
You drove in the rain?
Why did you do that?
I told you to wait until the rain stops.
You said you're alone, didn't you?
I'm not a kid anymore, Suer.
Now, you're stuck in the rain with me.
How's the tryout?
What do you think? With my skills?
- You're weak.
- F*ck you.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Nothing.
You're awake.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I saw you were exhausted.
Has the rain stopped?
Probably yes.
Shall we go?
Sure.
Go take a shower.
You go first.
You shower first.
Or....
do you wanna do it together?
Er...I will go shower first then.
Hello? What's up?
Where are you?
I came to see you at the basketball court. You're not here.
I'm...
I'm at P'Jo's.
Great.
Why are you doing this to me, North?
I told you I'm gonna be here.
I'm sorry. I didn't think you would actually come.
What am I gonna do now?
Come get the key here.
Or...
Can you wait? I will bring it to you tomorrow.
My scooter will probably got tolled.
Send me the location. I will go get it.
Yeah.
Wow.
You're so bad.
That's his clothes yeah?
Fine fine. I won't be mad at you.
For the sake of the ship that I'm rooting for.
Rooting your ass!
Where is my key?
You got a lot of people in trouble, you know?
I'm sorry. Here.
Fine.
Why..
are you blushing?
Shit what are you doing?
Hey are you having a cold?
Yeah probably.
It's your fault, North.
I didn't mean to.
Fine.
I'll inform the professor for you tomorrow.
Go get some rest.
Ger. Take good care of him.
Um.
Oh wait..
you normally you take care of each other really well.
What?
-What?s
-Let's just go.
I wanna shower so badly.
- Take care of each other.
- Go.
- Drive safe.
- Yeah.
What is up with him?
What are you doing?
Checking some work for P'Prang.
Have you ever been to Boston?
- Yeah, of course.
- Really? What is it like?
Is it beautiful?
I always want to go there.
But to be honest,
I've never really been out of the country.
You wanna go?
I would love to.
But it's gonna be awhile until I can.
I need to save up more.
When the semester is over then.
Semester is over?
Where would you like to go? I will take you.
Really!?
Thank you!
Are you gonna thank me for everything?
Yes.
Everything that others do it for me.
I got this habit from my family.
If someone give me somethings or if I see elders and do not wai them,
my mom is very strict.
I've seen that.
You've seen it?
You mean..
See my mom being strict?
- Come here. Come.
- Come here now. You lie to me now?
- Ugh. Mom.
You're glued to your games. I'm fine.
But you don't go home like this worries people at home.
- Don't be like this.
- Ugh mom.
You embarrass me in front for my friends.
I'm not.
Please be.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Don't apologize to me now.
You twisted my ears with your hands.
Does your wrist hurst?
I'm worried about that.
Shall we go find some yummy food to eat?
So you'll be in a better mood.
Please mom.
Just eat something good.
So you're in a better mood, shall we?
Oh look. You're smiling.
- Let's go eat please.
- Fine.
It'll be so yummy, yeah?
Let's go.
When you said you've seen it...
how?
I have something I wanna ask you too.
When you said you had a crush on me,
why?
Tell me more about that.
Please~
Tell me.
You wanna know that bad?
Yeah I wanna know.
I won't tell you.
Hey.
Look at your face.
It's almost campus sport day already.
I'm so excited.
For what?
Well...
I don't have to be in class that's why.
Don't have to study. So chill.
When is this gonna start?
Almost.
Foam. Why do you have to fan so much. It's cold.
It's so damn hot.
I'm so sticky right now.
Why are you so frustrated?
Or it's because you're not with girls?
Don't be Mr.Know it all. I'm done here. Bye.
Hey.
Where is he going?
Probably go see his girls. Forget him.
Let's go to the stage, shall we?
Sure.
Now, it is medicine faculty turn.
Here we go.
Too bad I didn't bring the camera.
I wanna take pictures.
Huh?
You wanna take pictures? Besides sky picture?
Taking pictures of the sky at night with some lights from the stage...
probably turn out beautifully.
Do you think it's gonna rain?
Probably. Always rain around this time of year.
But...
it should be fun, if it rains.
Yeah sounds fun.
How is it?
Yeah. I'm having fun.
When you were on the stage just now,
Ter couldn't not take his eyes off you.
Phoon!
Um. I saw.
I didn't.
I'm happy enough with you not looking at the others.
I will go se Foam.
- You stay here.
- Why do you have to go?
You just stay here.
- I'll leave Ter to you then.
- Sure.
Hey.
Your legs are probably tired standing.
Let's find somewhere to sit.
Sure.
You're bringing him out officially huh?
Can't underestimate my friend.
Guys. Look at Hill's boyfriend.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
i just thought...
that I would do absolutely anything....
to not lose your smile like that.
That's enough, P'Hill.
I won't let you see anymore.
Stop teasing me.
It always rain like this every year?
Yes. It was also like this during my year.
It's part of the sport day already.
Shal we go?
Let's go.
What are you doing, P'Hill?
Let me hug you.
P'Hill.
It's tickling.
You're not used to it yet?
- No.
- Not yet?
P'Hill.
Is it good?
It is.
- You give me all of it?
- Yes all.
Good?
- Too sweet.
- Why?
You don't like it?
- Then spit it out. I'll eat it myself.
- I like it.
I was kidding.
Show me your cute face.
Smile.
Pouty.
Duck face.
Go go.
You're such a cheater.
That rain has stopped.
Grey clouds are gone.
We can see the stars clearly.
So beautiful.
Yeah.
Then...
Are you interested to see this view everyday?
You mean you want me to move in with you?
Um.
Are you crazy? No.
Why not?
Please.
I cannot afford this place.
Hey.
I won't let you pay. Okay?
You will let me live here for free?
Sure.
But that's okay.
I feel bad.
It's fine.
People'd want to take good care of their lovers, right?
Right?
I can't. I'm worried about North.
He cannot live by himself.
North?
I will handle that.
Handle? Handle how?
What are you gonna do to him?
- I'm not okay with that.
- Hey.
If you do anything to him, I'll be so mad.
I won't do anything to North.
You think I'm that mean?
Hmm?
Who knows?
I think...
North might move to live somewhere else too.
How do you know?
Just my guess.
North? Moving where?
He never told me.
He doesn't tell me.
P'Hill. What are you doing?
P'Hill.
Stop it. P'Hill, No.
- A few more.
- No
Let me see.
That's cute.
Delete it. Delete it.
Come here. I will show you.
Smile.
Let me see.
Let's see.
- Looks good?
- That's cute.
You took it really good.
Can I post it?
I didn't smile for the camera. I smiled for the photographer.
What are you doing?
Are you being shy?
No, i'm not.
You're not?
- Um.
- Are you sure?
No.
Really?
- No.
- Let me see when one is shy.
What?
Where?
Cute though.
P'Hill.
- Are you blushing now?
- No, I'm not.
P'Hill.
- You're not blushing?
- No.
Don't do this to me. No.
- Are you sure you're not blushing?
- P'Hill.
Stop it.
Are you sure?
P'Hill. That's enough.
The person who gets the highest score in this round is...
Ratchakit got 60 points. Full score.
Everyone please him a round of applause.
Hill you're so damn good.
Only half of the class passes the test,
but you got full score.
Ratchakit, please come see me after class.
Sure.
You did really well.
You're the only one who got full score
out of the whole class.
This time. The test is really difficult.
Well done.
Keep it up.
I will send your score to your grandpa.
You must be under a lot of pressure, right?
Have you ever done anything that makes me proud?
It's not relevant at all dad.
How is it not relevant?
I'm planning a future for my nephew.
So he won't stay out of the line.
But it's his future.
You need to let him choose.
But what?
You're forcing him to get extra tutoring?
Isn't this too much?
If I do as you asked,
will you two stop fighting?
No no.
It's not like that son.
I just...
don't want you to have a life that I had.
I want you to live normally and have fun like other kids.
I'm fine.
Hey.
Wait.
Why are you standing there alone in the dark?
Waiting for your parents to pick you up?
You can go wait inside.
It's so dark here. Dangerous.
Come on in. D
on't have to be afraid. Let's go.
Let's go wait inside. Come.
Let' go sit inside.
There're lots of mosquito outside in the evening.
Let's sit inside and make yourself at home.
Are you hungry?
I have some dessert here at my cafe.
Do you wanna eat something?
Here. Take a look.
Whether you wanna order something.
Coconut cake?
Hmm...i'm not sure whether I have some left.
Wait a minute.
Ter.
Ter, can you check whether there's any coconut cake
left in the fridge?
Yes. There's 1 left.
Good. Bring it down please.
Ok. There's one left.
Go sit there and I will bring it over.
Make yourself comfortable. Don't have to feel bad.
Here.
Stay and hand out with him first.
He's waiting for his parents to pick him up.
I think he's around your age.
I'll clean up the cafe.
So..hi.
Um.
What's your name?
I'm Easter or you can just call me Ter.
Are you sick?
Why are you wearing a mask?
You have a sore throat that's why you can't speak, right?
Can you write then?
I will bring you some pens and papers.
Wait a minute.
Here.
Where do you go to school though?
Poranusorn school.
Wow. That's a big school, right?
You guys have a swimming pool too.
So nice.
I've only got to swim in the pool a few times only.
By the way...
you have a nice handwriting.
How can I write like this?
Teach me.
My handwriting...
is so bad.
Sometimes I can't even read my own handwriting.
And why are you going home so late at night?
Tutoring.
Tutoring? That one out there?
You're so hard working.
Even my parents force me to do tutoring, I just ignore it.
Thinking about it already gives me goosebump.
Even it's not that far from my home.
You like coconut cake?
No, I saw it as a recommended.
Recommended?
Do you try my cocoa drink?
On me.
Normally, my mom wouldn't let me make for customers.
It will be so good I guarantee.
Don't make that face. You're the first lucky person.
Wait a moment.
Here it is.
Here.
Try it.
How is it?
Why is your face like that?
Oh I forgot that you're having a sore throat.
Then you don't have to drink anymore.
It's not so good, right?
It would be better if you put more milk.
Oh add more milk.
Um sure. I will try that next time.
Come back and by lab rat for—
Err…
I mean come back and try it again for me.
Please come try it again for me.
Wait until your throat is better. It should be better.
Get well soon then.
Ter. Dad is calling you.
Yes?
I’ll be back.
What do you need, dad?
- Hill! You’re here!
- Mom!
How do you know that I’m here?
People from the tutor said they saw you walked here, so I just followed what they said.
You came here to pick me up?
Oh cause I’m free today.
I wanna pick my son up too sometimes.
Let's go back with me.
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Oh this is your mom?
Yes. Not sure if my son disturbs you or anything?
No. Not at all.
I always welcome all customers.
- Do you want anything else?
- Oh no more. We will go now.
- Oh okay. I will walk you out.
- Sure.
Let's go.
- Please come back.
- Sure.
Come son.
Would you excuse us? We'll leave now.
See you around kid. You can always hangout here.
Sure.
Oh by the way, what's your name?
Hill-- Oops. Sorry. My car blocks you.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Next time you can sit here.
It's better than sitting at the tutoring place.
I tell tell the driver for you.
- Mom.
- Hmm? What?
That aunty, the owner we met just now...
- he has a son around my age.
- Really?
You met his son?
He came and talked to me.
Did he talk to you badly?
No.
And he was he?
He talks a lot.
Even I didn't really answer anything.
Kinda weird.
But he seems nice.
Cheerful.
and...
smile a lot too.
Hill...I think...
I haven't seen you smile like this for a very long time.
Really?
I'm glad. I think he can become your friend.
Let's do this. Next time, you can stop by that cafe again before I pick you up.
Do you think that's a good idea?
It's fine.
Go wait for the driver there.
And I will find the time,
to pick you up more ofthen, should I?
Sure.
But...
what is his name? That kid.
Easter.
Easter. That's a cute name.
I kinda want to meet him now.
What kind of kid is he to make my son smile like this?
Oh he's back?
Um. They're gone. His mom came and picked him up just now.
Too bad he's already gone.
I haven't said goodbye to him.
But his mom is so beautiful.
If she didn't say, I would thought that she's the sister,
Don't know how old is she. Her face is so young.
I think if you don't complain so much, you might look younger ad well.
- There. Come help me clean up.
- Sure~
Oh did he say that he will come back?
Not sure.
But I told them they're always welcome to come back.
They said sure.
I think he's a bit weird.
I haven't see his whole face.
I don't even know his name.
Seems so mysterious.
- But I know his name.
- Really!?
- He told me.
- What's his name?
If I hear it correctly, it was...
New...I think.
New?
What did dad call you to do just now?
To wax his shoes.
- I wax until it's so shiny. He can see his refelx on the shoes.
- Really?
- What about Christ?
- Doing her homework.
Whose sister is that? So hard-working.
I'm so proud of her.
- Don't know when her brother is gonna be like that too?
- Yeah right?
Mom!
Put this away and wash it.
Sure. I will let them sit in the water.
- Ugh. Just wash it right away.
- I'm too lazy.
- Do it now.
- Fine.
Oh hi welome.
Make yourself comfortable.
Oh New!
I thought you are not gonna come back anymore.
Mom. Please take this.
Sure.
We have coconut cake to day too.
Do you want some?
That's good. I will leave some coconut cake for you everyday from now on.
If you don't come, I will just eat it myself.
Let's go sit.
You're still sick?
Yeah all good.
If you're are better, why don't you speak?
I don't wanna speak.
I get it cause sometimes I also don't wanna talk.
But when I get to speak, I can't stop talking.
And...
you're wearing a mask
because you don't wanna speak?
I just don't want people to recognize.
What?
What's wrong with people recognizing you?
When people recognize me, they will approach to take advantage of me.
Yeah right.
There're something like that out there huh.
- Do you wanna have cocoa drink?
- No.
What do you mean?
it's not that good?
Fine.
What?
Fine fine.
Because you wanna have it, I will make one for you.
I don't normally make drinks for anyone.
Wait a minute. I will make one for you.
Singapore?
Yeah. My family has to work there for awhile,
We have to take my son to attend the school there too.
Oh my. Then we won't be seeing each other for a very long time then.
That's why he's here to day good bye to his friend.
Oh...too bad.
Ter went to school already. He will be home in the evening.
Umm...can you wait for awhile?
We have to go to the airport actually.
Then can you say goodbye to him for my son?
Sure. Have a safe flight.
Let's go.
- Good bye.
- Yes.
Good luck, son.
I'm home.
Do you need any help?
Umm...not yet. Are you hungry?
Oh New and his mom stopped by in the afternoon.
They came to day goodbye before they fly to Singapore.
Singapore?
Too bad when they were here. You weren't here.
New's mom said...
they have urgent business there. And seems like they'll be there for a long time too.
You go put your stuff away upstairs and come help me.
Go.
- Sure.
- Hurry up.
Sure~
- You woke up so early.
- You're up?
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
Hi.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm so happy.
Happy?
To have you here.
What are you talking about?
Can I see that?
You remembered now?
Hey.
Wait.
You're New!?
Are they usually this stressed out when studying?
Are you worried about P'Johan?
Because he's been working a lot lately
and has to go to Boston.
Is P'Johan going to Boston?
Yes, for working.
If you think you're carrying everything by yourself,
I'll be by your side.