Have you seen P'Hill's posts?
Who's the owner of the watch?
Or...it's you?
- I said enough.
- Let me go.
Hey let go.
Go to the room.
I told you to go to your room.
What is this?
Damage fee.
You have to pay all of that.
But this is a few hundred thousands.
I was just in a fight there.
Why do I have to pay this much?
What is this? Wine?
I don't even drink wine.
You did not drink.
But you broke it.
- How?
- It was probably close to your hands.
And what's this?
What's the medical fee is for?
Those guys wanted to claim with you.
And this? Clothing?
That have your vomit.
Almost a 100k.
Ughh I'm going crazy. Clothes for almost a 100k.
And why do I have to pay alone?
For the damage fee at the bar?
Litigant also has to pay. Not just me.
Those people already paid.
And the rest are for the damage you made at my home.
Me?
Here...my phone.
All broken. Cannot touch the screen.
It's broken.
You broke it. You're responsible.
I'm not gonna let this go.
Here.
This is not included with what you owe me.
Actually...
you can just give me some money to fix it.
Too much work.
And for all the damage fee,
can I do installment payment?
Yes.
But there'll be interest.
- How much?
- 20%.
I cannot afford just the damage fee alone.
If you charge me interest too, how can I pay you back?
I don't even have the money to pay for the dorm either.
What am I gonna do, tell me?
I know!
Dude.
You can think about it later.
Customer is calling,
I have to go.
Again?
Yeah. Take care of this for me.
Yes?
He has work thing.
- Shall we go?
- Yes, I will.
You're so hurry.
If you were me,
you'd be in a hurry too.
You wake up then you have hundreds of thousands.
If I crashed something again,
- what are you gonna do? Can you afford it?
- What are you talking about?
Let's go home!
Fine. Let's go.
There's something on your face,
let me see.
You're not hurt there anymore?
Why the hell did you poke me?
You're such a troublemaker.
Aunty Da. I'm gonna get going now.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Check your belongings too.
- All good.
- You sure?
Don't be sad.
Thank you so much, P'Hill.
And I'm sorry for troubling you.
It's okay.
Then could you excuse us?
Go.
Don't be sad, my friend.
You can make more money.
Just make some more.
Right?
What do you think of P'Johan?
Why?
You're interested in him, aren't you?
He's my creditor.
I should know a few things about him.
But from what I've seen...
he's a quiet person.
But he can also talk to people.
Eventhought he has...
some intimidating vibes sometimes.
Oh and P'Hill told me he gets mad easily.
You just don't do anything to make him mad.
- He's easily get mad?
- Yes.
And...
...when and how's he gonna be mad?
Hey how am I supposed to know everything?
I think only his friends...P'Hill, P'Fah, and P'Arthit....
that knows when to and whne not to talk to him.
- Very unpredictable, right?
- Yes.
You hang in there then.
Come on.
- Why don't you push the button?
- Why didn't you?
It's here.
Hey North.
What are you gonna do now?
It's a a big amount of money.
I think I will just do installment.
Maybe THB1,000 a week?
Huh!?
A THB1,000 a week?
You'll probably be paying until you graduate.
What do you want me to do?
I cannot afford just the damage fee alone.
He's charging me interest also.
What?
Or should I just sell the phone?
Hey.
Or should I sell me shirt?
It's probably cost a lot.
What the hell?
Are you for real?
- I'm kidding.
- Huh!?
You think I'm that pathetic?
Who knows?
To be honest,
I'm still wondering
why was it P'Johan that come get me?
I also don't know.
But If you let me guess,
I think he just probably wants to take care of you.
Think about it.
Even the medical bill, he also paid for you.
I think P'Hill knows, so he asked P'Johan to help.
Then add his LINE and thank him.
- Why would I do that?
- Hey.
You owe him.
You don't have much of a choice.
Do it.
Add him. Give me your phone.
- Come on. Add him.
- Fine.
Added.
Text him too.
- Text him?
- Yes.
Do it.
I did.
Good.
But is he...
gonna reply you?
Cause you use cute yellow ducky as a profile picture.
Why?
What's wrong with my duck?
- He's cute. Do not bully my duck.
- Right. Right.
You're the cutest.
Can't stop hugging huh.
Who's this? What a shitty profile pic.
It's North. Thank you again.
Umm. I had to spend a few 100k.
I will pay you back slowly.
I don't have much.
I will charge you interest.
Can you only charge me 2%?
...?
Can we do 3%?
If not I'll have to pay almost THB10,000.
How is it? Are you guys talking?
Yes.
I'm asking him to reduce the interest.
He read, but doesn't reply me.
Damn it.
He's overcharging so much.
So greedy.
Come on.
You make a lot in a month.
You will pay up pretty soon.
I don't even earn THB10,000.
I cannot pay just for the interest alone.
Not to mention food, rent, and stuff.
Ter. I'm gonna die.
Don't die on me yet.
I think you just need to talk to him again.
Get up.
I think I'll come up with some sort of begging phrases
for him to reduce me the interest.
Ter.
Do you wanna go get some food?
We will have to work later.
Huh?
Huh? For real?
You look like this and wanna go to work?
Don't go. Just stay here.
I can't.
P'Yah will scold me.
Um. Let's go get some food then.
I will just go and hang with you. I already ate.
It's fine then. I'll ask Ket and Q instead.
I need to talk to them anyway.
I will just see you at P'Yah's then.
Are you sure?
Yes, I will just go change.
Okay. Okay.
Oh where's Sket?
I already asked him,
but he said he wated to rest.
Why?
That bad?
A bit.
What about you? How are you?
Look at my face.
With those little punches won't hurt me.
Sorry.
Really?
Here. Wanna get hurt some more?
You can't do that.
If my face has more bruises,
all the girls won't fall for me.
By the way...
I'm sorry about last night.
Whatever.
I intentionally fought with them too.
You didn't force me.
Just look snf Nhao.
Damn. He just went straight in.
More hot-headed than you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Is he alright?
He is the most alright one.
He's probably out playing footbal already.
Huh? Playing football?
Yes.
Oh.
And what else happened last night?
I couldn't remember anything.
Here's what happened.
North!
Ter called, so I told him that you were in trouble.
Did you know who came?
P'Johan.
I was so damn confused.
He just walked in. Cleared everything for you.
Pulled you away from Temp and just carried you out.
Let me go.
Let go of me!
- Carry me?
- Yeah.
When he walked in,
people stepped back for him.
It was like he was giving some intimidating vibes.
- Are you crazy?
- I'm telling you the truth.
You don't believe me?
I'm telling you the truth.
It's possible.
If he's that mad until he could break my phone like that.
He probably looked intimidating.
Wait.
Just now...
you said who broke your phone?
P'Johan.
He broke my phone.
Look.
Looks like someone freaking stomped on my phone.
I cannot even turn it on.
Look.
Who told you that?
Shit.
And why didn't you tell me?
I was yelling at him like a lot.
Who's gonna have any idea
that you cannot remember anything?
Damn it.
Oh you're here.
What's the matter?
Hey North.
What happened to your face?
I was in a bit of a trouble.
Oh my gosh.
Your pretty face now has many bruises.
This is not you, North.
Does it hurt? Let me see.
It was not hurt,
but when you pressed like that...
- it is.
- Sorry.
So what did you do to make these happened?
Can you work today?
I can. I'm all fine.
Don't let this happen again, okay?
Go go. Go change.
Yes.
Go go.
North. How are you?
Temp told me everything.
So what really happened? Can you tell me?
About the guy who helped you last night, he was a senior from his faculty. So he didn't want to cause more scene.
I will be waiting for your reply.
I'm worried about you. We're still friends.
What was happened last night?
Temp told me you suddenly just went straight in, but I know you better than that.
Or Temp has someone else?
You knew?
It's maybe not.
I just started 'dating Temp not so long ago
If this is true, I don't think I can be with him as well.
It could be just a misunderstading
I wish it was.
North. Can I text you again? As a friend?
I can be myself when I talk to you.
Sure, if I'm free I'll reply.
- North.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
You said you're not gonna talk to her again?
She texted me about the fight with her boyfriend.
Are you sure?
Don't let me find out that you have feelings for her again.
If you have to drink because of her again,
I'll kill you.
No more. I'm done.
But I still don't understand.
Why does she act like nothing happened? She's the one who dumped me.
Cause she sees you as a friend.
She can be herself when she talks to you.
Why are you repeating that to me?
You promise me that you won't go back to her?
I don't wanna see you like last night again.
Yeah, I won't go back for sure.
Umm.
I will wait outside.
Sure babe.
Don't say that. I miss you.
The beef is here.
- North. North.
- Yes?
Can you give this order outside?
- Yes, P'Yah.
- Thank you.
Ok, I will see you.
Okay?
Oh.
What are you doing here, P'Johan?
Er...
About the phone...
I'm sorry.
- I didn't know that...
- About the interest.
Can you please reduce the interest rate for me?
I will slowly pay you back.
I won't charge you interest rate.
But will you do everything I ask instead?
Are you really not gonna charge me any interest?
Are you willing to do anything I say or not?
What do you want me to do?
Yes?
Let's talk later.
Oh wait P'Johan. About my interest--
Thank you.
Why were you out for so long?
It's P'Johan.
P'Johan? What did he do?
He said he won't charge me interest anymore.
Hey really?
It's good. I know. It helps me a lot.
But he said...
I have to do everything that he says.
- Everything?
- Yeah.
Everything as in what?
Right.
I also have no clue.
He just answered his phone and left.
If he wants me to be his assistant,
is not so bad.
He said you need to do everthing thought.
What if he asked you to do illegal stuff?
You might be in more trouble though.
It won't be that bad.
Or will it?
Or will it be that bad?
No it won't.
Maybe.
I think so.
Are you guys not working?
No, we are.
- Customers are here. Seat them. Hello~
- Please come in.
Inside please.
Come on in.
P'Yah, you're not working?
Why are you standing here?
This boy...go.
We're gonna go home now, P'Yah.
- Bye.
- Yes. Thank you for today.
And how are you going back?
Of Hill will come pick you guys up like usual?
Yes.
I'm really jealous of you, Ter.
I wanna have someone come pick me up like this too.
To be honest, I'm actually annoyed.
When it's the three of us together,
I feel like I'm the air.
But it's fine,
I also get the benefits from their relationship.
- I can bear it.
- Enough North!
- I'm gonna go. See you, P'Yah.
- Always tease each other.
- Go go.
- Always like this when you're blushing.
- North.
- Sigh. Someone is in love.
I get it.
You're teasing us...
but I saw you were talking to a guy earlier.
What guy?
I talked to a girl kub.
(Kub is a polite particle used by men to end sentences in formal or respectful way)
Kub you said?
- Bye.
Are you exhausted?
Not at all.
- Hello North.
- Hello P'Hill.
Do you wana go have dinner?
Yes.
Do you want anything else, North?
No more.
Here.
Oh P'Hill.
Today P'Johan went to see North at work too.
Johan?
And he said he won't charge North any interest anymore.
But under one condition.
North has to do everything that he says.
He said that?
Yes.
What does he want me to do?
I also don't know.
And did you ask him? What does he want?
I did.
But someone called him.
He just answered the phone and left.
He's a bit busy lately.
Try texting him.
I already gave you his LINE.
I will.
Thank you.
Shall we go?
- Sure.
- Yes.
- Are you full?
- I am.
Dude you're full and don't have to pay.
Dude. What does he do for wokr?
Huh.
What? I'm just asking.
Oh.
Probably his family business.
Working for his family business?
You don't think it's true?
Just lookt at him.
If you told me, he's just fooling around everyday.
I would believe that.
What should I do?
Do what?
Just text him.
Ask him what does he want you to do.
That's it.
You owe him.
You don't want to b charged with interest.
Just do it.
It's true.
But what if he wanted me to do bad things like you said?
But if you don't text him,
you'll never find out.
What should I do, Ter?
When you said 'do anything that you say',
what do you mean by this?
If it's not too much for me, I think I can do it.
Or you can reduce interest rate just a little.
He read!
Dude.
He read but doesn't reply.
Should I text him another one?
Sure. You can.
If you're not worried that
he'll be annoyed.
Don't sasy that.
I just wanna know.
What if he changed his mind?
It's THB10,000,
we're talking about.
Up to you.
Are you working now?
I don't want to bother you,
but can you give me a bit of your time?
I just wanna know when you said you won't charge me interest,
did you really mean it?
He read but doesn't reply again.
He's probably annoyed now. I think.
Hey.
He's replying.
Answer in 5 seconds.
Hello?
Are you working?
Yes, I'm too lazy to text.
What's up?
I wanted to ask you about the interest.
Do we have a deal or not?
Well...
when you said 'Everything that you say'...
what kind of things do I have to do?
If it's not too much,
I think I can do it.
And what is too much for you?
Like...make me do illegal stuff.
Deal some drugs.
Stealing people's purses.
Rob the gold shop.
Or hurt other people.
I can't do those thing bro.
You're not gonna make me do those weird things, right?
And do you think
you're capable of doinf those things?
No.
It's not gonna be things
that out of your capabilty.
Cool.
I'm not capable of doing that many things too.
Good.
Then cancel the offer.
You're useless.
Er...let's just say...
I will do everything that you ask then.
You need to cancel the interest rate for me.
Umm.
But...
if you upset me,
I'll charge you daily interest rate.
Hey how so?
You're not happy?
Yes, I am.
And...
what makes you upset?
Think.
Hey. How am I supposed to know?
Just be quiet.
Don't fall asleep.
And don't mke any noise.
You mean you just want to be here?
Do you want me to talk to you?
Hey you want me to be here,
so I need to talk.
When my ex, Jah, wanted to hang,
she wanted me to talk to her.
I'm not your ex.
Fine.
I'll be quiet.
P'Johan.
I'm sleepy.
How long left?
For awhile more.
You work late like this everyday?
No, just somedays.
Can you talk to me?
I want you to just hang around.
Do I need to talk to you too?
Ugh.. I'm just sleepy.
Then you tell me your stories.
Hey...about me?
I have many stories though.
Which one would you like to hear?
Hello. I'm North.
North. Natchanan.
First year engineering student.
Woah~
Just the opening already makes me so cool, huh?
My roommate is Easter.
I'm an easy goin person. Pretty chill.
Not too serious about lfe.
I'm pretty joyful, delighted,
cute and also easy to feed.
I'm always humble with elders and a good friend to all.
I also respect everyone.
You can say that for yourself?
Not me who says that.
It's on my report card to my parents.
But...
The cute and easy to feed part,
I added on just now.
Can you tell me about yourself too?
- Why medical school?
- Just stay quiet.
But I'm sleepy.
I'm not a coffee persn like you.
How do you know?
I just guess.
You always work so late,
you must be addicted to coffee.
Hey.
I'm about to take a course how to make coffee.
I will let you try mine when I make one.
Learn how to make coffee?
Yes.
I actually work at a coffee shop you know?
Which shop?
Nearby the campus.
Work with Easter there.
You wanns make more money?
For sure.
I have so much debt like this.
To be honest,
I actually want to find a few more jobs.
But I'm not charging you interest anymore.
Hey who knows?
What if you want to charge all of a sudden?
You're unpredictable too.
Can I ask you something?
Does the person who hangs with you here
complain anything?
No.
No?
I never let anyone hung with me.
Don't ask too many question, can you?
Fine.
North.
If you're tire, just go lay down properly.
Stop working part time jobs, understood?
North.
I'm rooting for you dude.
About P'Jo. I saw you guys talking to each other. So cute.
I'm your shipper.
More like ship-hai.
(Means f*cked in Thai)
Wait.
How do you know?
Oops.
- You were eavesdropping?
- I did not.
I just overheard.
But I didn't hear you say clearly.
Just some cute sound parts.
- It was cute.
- Cute your ass!
Stop it.
Too bad..I'm already a JohanNorth shipper.
Stop babbling and go to your class.
I'm gonna go now~
Yeah.
My friend won't be lonely,
cause he always have someone to talk to all day.
- Bye bye~
- Yeah.
What?
- Everything's all good today?
- Yes, Mr.President.
Then please take care of the rest.
P'Hill.
Today seniors are gathering with all the first years,
can I join them?
Sure thing.
You already took many pictures today.
Thank you.
Do you have any class today?
Yes in the afternoon.
- I will take you there.
- It's fine, P'Hill.
You should be here. I will go there myself.
That's lovely.
Do you like it?
I do.
I do too.
We probably have everyone, right?
I'm announcing that you have exactly 1 week to find your code senior.
(Seniors who have corresponding student code)
You will be given with clues abut your code senior.
I will see you at the same activity area tomorrow.
So from what you told...
you basically have to pay him back?
Yeah that's why I'm looking for more jobs here.
Dude.
Let me know if you need any help.
I feel guilty.
You didn't think like this when you got in a fight.
You were the most hot-headed one.
They punched my friend.
I cannot just stand there.
You were the most hot-headed one.
They punched my friend.
I cannot just stand there.
- So you had to punched them back?
- Yeah.
They punched my friend.
I cannot just stand there.
- So you had to punched them back?
- Yeah.
Ughh enough. No need to argue.
My debt is not actually caused by the bar.
It's actually from myself.
I caused all that myself.
Anyway...
just let us know if you need our help.
Hello North. I'm Prang, Johan's assistant.
I will be handling his accounting.
If you'd like to Johan back,
please inform me.
But if Johan would like to deduct the amount,
I will also let you know.
Wait.
You said you need to make money to pay him back.
But how come you have the new phone?
- P'Johan bought it for me.
- Damn.
You blamed him for breaking your phone,
but he still bought you a new one?
So?
I think there's something's going on.
That night P'Johan came to get you.
He also bought you a new phone.
I was also wondering why did he come get you.
There's no something.
There's nothing going on.
Don't think for yourself.
I heard that Ter in your shipper.
Can I also join the ship?
I will help paddle.
Go paddle at your own place.
I will just sink all of your ships.
Now you're suddenly all on the same page.
We haven't started paddling
but the ship is already sunk.
Why? Are you shy?
- Are you blushing?
- I'm gonna go to class. It's time.
- You're suddenly wanna go to the class?
- I always want to go to the class.
Do you even have any idea
what's the topic?
You're babbling.
Look.
The girls wll be swooning.
What a guy.
Clothes are undone.
The hair is not set, but still manage to look so good.
Are you gonna be swooning too?
You should meet him in the version that I met.
You might not be swooning after all.
Are you trying flaunt or what?
You're not interested?
He's both handsome and rich.
He also gave me debt.
I think if you become his boyfriend,
you will be given 100% remission.
Nonsense. Just pay attention to the class.
Hey.
I passed.
Wanna go back to sleep already.
The term has just started.
Don’t complain yet.
I’m sleepy.
What? You guys!
So what, Foam? Are you gonna skip the class?
Can I?
Can you check attendance for me tomorrow?
Easy there.
Foam…you cannot just fool around
like you did in high school anymore.
It’s a big thing, if you failed in university.
You two are so whiny.
My parents do not even complain to me this much.
Cause you do not pay attention in the class.
It’s not like you pay much attention.
Cause you always talk to me.
Stop it. Why are you guys arguing?
The professor might scold at you.
Just be focused.
I already wanna leave.
That’s it for today guys. Class dismissed.
Thank you.
- Are you done with the class?
- Umm.
As you wished.
Are you guys going home right away?
We have club thing today. You forgot?
Right.
- Are you guys going?
- Yes.
North and I already promised Daotok
to be there.
I think I’m gonna stop by the club
before going home.
What about you Phoon?
If Ter goes, I’ll go.
I will go too.
Let’s go.
You’re suddenly determined
when it’s not related to the class.
Dude.
Why there’s no one
signing up for our club?
When is Ter gonna be here?
He said he has arrived.
But he took Foam to check out some other clubs.
Are you gonna apply for other clubs too, North?
I don’t know.
But maybe more.
I will just check out later.
Do you know anyone
who’s looking for a club to join?
Maybe you can ask them to join ours?
Why? The less people, the better.
So we won’t have too many fuss.
I’m afraid that we might got cut down the budget.
So…
I'll ask my engineering friends to join first then.
We might gain several.
Here. I did.
Hey.
I will have Ter ask his medical senior.
He has so many friends.
Medical senior?
Umm. It’s P’Hill.
If P’Hill joins, many people will be interested in our club more.
For sure.
I will tell Ter first.
Daotok said if we have a few people in our club,
we might have to shut down.
You better start finding more people to join.
You can ask anyone. Could be P’Hill and his friends.
Just hurry. Daotok is crying.
Hey Ter!
- Hey P’Arthit.
- Hello.
Are you in any club?
Yes, I am.
Hmm? Which club?
Drawing.
Oh I thought you’re joining Basketball club with Hill.
Probably not for me.
You’re in Football club?
I am the club president.
So cool.
So? Are we in this club or what?
Sure. I wanna join some sport clubs anyway.
Deal.
Okay.
So I will have Hill coming around to my club more often then?
A jealous type like him,
he won’t let you out of his sight easily.
And…
which club are P’Johan and Tonfah joining?
Fah is in tennis’s.
For Johan and Hill, they are in Basketball’s.
There…
speaking of the devil.
What’s up Fah? How’s your club doing?
Mine is already full.
- What about yours?
- Also full.
You?
Is there anyone joining a club
with a president like you?
At least Ter is joining mine.
You want to join Football club?
- Yes.
- I feel like I wanna join Football club.
So? Are you in Fah? Jo?
Are you in any club yet, Ter?
I’m actually in Drawing club at the moment.
- Drawing club?
- Yes.
Do you wanna go check out my club?
We need more people.
Let’s go.
Go. Let’s go.
Fah, come join Football with me.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Not convenient for me.
- Go.
This club gathers every Friday
at the old Fine Arts building.
You go in at 4pm and you’ll be out no later by 6pm.
Interesting.
If P’Hill joins, many people will be interested in our club more for sure.
It’s true.
You said Daotok is  earlier huh?
Really? I said that?
You lied to me.
Help.
Can I sign up for my friends now then?
Yes.
That’s great P’Hill.
Write a lot of names down please. The more. The merrier.
What’s your plan after this? Where are you going next?
No plan.
Do you wanna go eat something?
Umm.
What would you like to eat?
Anything. Up to you.
Do you wanna go to the market?
Let’s go.
- See you.
- Bye, P’Hill.
- Are we leaving now?
- Let’s go.
Do you call that Mauhom shirt?
Yes.
You want one?
It’s okay.
It’s beautiful.
That elephant pants are also cute
Looks so comfortable to wear.
You want one?
Sure.
Do we need to hold hands?
You might get lost.
Why?
You don’t want other people to see?
No.
Just feel a bit weird.
How?
I’m just not used to it. I guess.
Then I will have to hold your hands more, so you can get used to.
Hi. This is my favorite longan drink.
I will have one please.
Not so sweet.
Drinkable?
Would you like to try?
Good?
Sorry.
Here.
Thank you.
Can I help you pay? I don’t want you to always be the one who pays.
Then I will be something else in exchange then.
What is it?
I’m not telling you yet.
Do you want anything else?
I don’t know. I will just walk around some more.
Sure. Let’s walk.
Does this look good?
You’re not eating?
I am.
Feed me.
No.
Please.
Here.
How was it? Is it good?
It’s so good.
Whatever you feed me are always good.
- Really.
- I don’t believe you.
Does this look good?
It does.
- Ter.
- Yes?
Tell me.
Tell you what?
Since when did you like me?
You’re asking me directly like this, I’m too shy to answer.
Please tell me.
Please.
Really wanna know.
Why would you want to know?
Cause if my crush likes me back, I would like to know how.
Anyone would like to know.
Then think of it as a way to thank me
for buying you snacks today.
Sounds good?
You already planned this.
But…
I still don’t understand.
You told me you have had a crush on me
for so long already, right?
Yes.
Then…
you have had a crush on me since high school?
Yes.
That means you know be even before then?
You have had a crush on me
since when I returned your notebook?
Yes.
I had no idea.
That’s not surprising.
We didn’t get to know each other properly back then.
You never told me anything.
I can be shy too you know.
What about you?
I…
have had a crush on you since the beginning.
Beginning?
Yeah right in the start.
When we got to know each other.
I remember that so well.
You transferred to our school
in the middle of the term.
You liked to play basketball with your friends
and teachers always scolded at you guys when you played.
That’s when I met you.
But I think around that time, you didn’t know me yet.
I did.
Really?
Really.
Ter
That’s not the first time though.
Hey.
How?
So you are interested in me since then?
Yes.
I was very impressed by you.
You were really good in school.
Great in sport as well.
And when we got to know each other more.
I know that you’re a very kind person.
- So I just...
- You just started to like me?
That’s nice.
If I knew that you have liked me since then would be great.
Stop talking already.
Can I start everything over with you again?
I love you, Ter.
I love you too.
Oh North.
When you said you need to find more part time jobs,
are you sure you can handle it?
Yes, I can. My creditor is so unpredictable.
What are you doing after?
I have to go work for my new job.
At a bar?
If you go,
P’Johan will be very angry at you.
But he works his ass off to pay your debt, right?
That’s right,
but bar is also full of risky situations.
This is North.
It’s his first day here.
You don’t have a boyfriend?
Can I ask you out then?
Excuse me.