I heard the president is a med student, right?
I know right. So talented.
You have to also work at the Student union, right?
You might meet him there
Excuse me.
Do you remember that person I told you?
He's in the union as well.
Hill. You have someone you want to be serious with?
See you soon.
Hey!
Ter!
What?
Come check this out.
Hurry!
Isn't that...?
Isn't that your hand?
Right?
You know P'Hill,
med student?
You also know him?
Yes, he's famous.
Really?
"If I can take care of you..."
"...will I pass the test?"
He's a bit cringe.
But still cool.
Has he been flirting with you?
I don't think so.
Don't think so?
He's posting it.
Ughh. I don't know!
But to be honest...
I think he's already dating someone.
Right? I think so.
And how come you know him?
So...?
Hmm?
Fine. That's the guy.
Who's the guy?
Which guy?
The guy I told you about.
Oh...the guy you told me that story.
Yeah.
- Huh!?
That guy you said you hate him so much?
- That's right.
- Shit!
How come?
So you hate him
because he's trying to flirt with you?
- It's not like that.
- Then why?
I don't know anymore.
I'll tell you about it later.
- Hey come back and tell me first.
- No.
This is for sure.
How are you, Ter?
I'm good, mom.
You?
I'm also good
Is it cold over there?
Not so much right now.
Take care of yourself too.
Don't get sick.
Sure mom.
You'll be alright overthere, right?
Yes. All good.
There're only mountains here.
I miss the beach back home.
Then come visit us sometimes.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I can't face other people now.
Aren't you embarrassed of yourself?
Sure. If you're so embarassed
having me as your son,
- I will leave.
- Ter!
Ter! Son!
Let him be.
If he wants to leave, let him leave.
- But he's your son!
- Don't follow him.
Ter!
What about Chris?
How is she?
She's fine.
Just finished her exams.
You haven't talked to her?
No.
I need to hang up now.
Gotta go mom.
Ok. I miss you, son.
I miss you too mom.
Damn it, Song!
You should go play retro snake.
I will download it for you.
Look at that.
Hill.
Hmm?
Why do you look distracted?
Not studying anymore?
Yeah...always on your phone.
You also haven't read, Jo.
You also, Arthit.
I'm too lazy. Damn it.
I'm just gonna quit med school.
That's good. You should quit.
Always increase class average.
Me? Increase the bar?
It's more like him.
Sitting there looking distracted.
I almost got an F last final
'cause of him.
Had to do my best, hadn't I?
Just make it good enough.
Damn, if it's norm referenced, we're gonna fail.
You got what? 98?
Tonfah got 90. He got a B.
I got 84...almost down to D grade.
What? Hmm?
You seem off lately, Hill.
Do you have something to tell us?
Distracted...
always on your phone...
Like he's in love, isn't he?
Hill.
You can talk to me about everything.
Nope.
That means he's really falling in love.
Who is it?
I will introduce to you guys soon.
Like are you currently dating?
Why are you so nosy?
What?
Don't act like
you don't wanna know.
I don't know...
A guy like you?
Make the first move?
Why?
What's wrong?
Thought you are dead inside.
If you're a player like Johan,
that's another story.
Why am I mentioned?
Cause you're a player.
- What are you talking about?
- Hey guys.
Stop fighting.
Each one of you...
So our friend,
Hill, is about to be married.
So it's just us left
...Jo...Ton.
It's probably not just me.
Right?
- What?
- You too?
He's babbling.
Hey.
Just keep studying.
I gotta go.
Oh.
Where are you going, Jo?
I have to be somewhere.
Three?
Do you need my help?
It's fine.
P'Hill.
Let me help you carry.
Don't be stubborn.
Anything else you need?
No more.
Thank you.
Can I have my books?
I'm going home now.
Just these two then.
I'll take you home.
Ter!
Let me take you home.
Let go of me.
I can go back myself.
If you don't let me take you home,
I'm not gonna let you go.
Let me go, P'Hill.
Don't be like this please.
Please~
Please.
Fine.
Good boy.
Let's go.
Let me go then.
Thank you.
Your welcome.
By the way...
did you have the answer?
What answer?
About my post.
So...
Do I pass the test?
Would you excuse me?
Hey dude.
Why are you making that face?
You met the person you hate?
So what now?
About you and P'Hill?
I'm only telling you
because it's you.
Really?
Come on.
Tell me.
So?
Well...
We went to the same school.
11 syllables poem
has the following characteristics.
1 verse has 2 lines.
Why are they playing so loundly?
Don't pay attention to them.
Focus on the class.
Each line has 2 verses.
There you go.
Any one of you
are good like my friend here?
Ok. They do not respect us at all.
You guys!
Can't you play quietly?
Oh...miss.
How can we play basketball quietly?
Just play some other times.
Can't you see that
they are studying?
Are you arguing with me?
No, we're not at all.
These kids. I swear...
Go! Go!
Put it away. Play some other days.
Yes ma'am~
So you knew each other before?
I never thought
we'd meet each other again.
Kinda surprising.
Let me guess.
You ended things badly, right?
Were you two super close?
Ever talked to each other?
A bit.
And...did he show any interest
or giving you any hint?
No.
Then why do you hate him?
He posted a picture like that.
If it's not flirting,
then what do you call it?
It's up to you now.
What's your feelings towards him?
My feelings?
Why don't you just give it a try?
It's Hill, we're talking about.
He might just fooling around.
Probably not.
You like to think for yourself.
How can I know for sure?
He also works at the union, right?
It must be very awkward.
That's why I'm stressed here.
I don't know
what exactly happened between you two.
But I'd suggest you to be honest with yourself.
If you don't like him,
then tell him you don't like him.
Please.
Understood?
Yes.
Fine.
Go back and play your games.
Forget it.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You scared me.
You don't understand.
(Drawing club)
Ter.
Are you bringing me to the right place?
Yes, I am.
There's only one drawing club, right?
Why is the vibes so spooky?
Cause the term hasn't started yet.
Nobody's here.
I think we should go, Ter.
Why are you so scared?
I'm scared of that thing.
Terrr~
Stop hanging on to my arms.
- Ter.
- What!?
Stop calling me.
Or the reason why
there's no one sign up for this club 'cause...
there're...
Hello!
Let's pray.
I will lead...Namo Tassa.
Repeat after me.
North.
Calm down.
North! Calm down.
That's a human. Not ghost.
Open your eyes, North!
Look at that.
Here.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
- He's scared of ghosts.
- Just tiny bit. Not much.
North?
Is this another friend,
you said he'd like to join?
Um. Yes yes. This guy.
It's me.
Anyways...nobody's here at all?
Um...
all the seniors are busy with the orientation.
So they don't have time to be here.
Then you're probably here alone?
Umm
I'm not participating in the Welcome Back camp.
I like to be alone here.
Must be real lonely.
You guys are here to sign up, right?
- Err--
- Yes yes.
We're here to sign up
cause we don't want to find any other to join.
Dude. Should we reconsider
and think it through again?
What?
We agreed to join this one.
I didn't know it's gonna be this quiet.
If I knew, I wouldn't agree with you in the first place.
I think we should check
whether there's any history here.
There's gotta be something 100%.
Believe me. I have a feelin'
What kind of sense is that?
You're talking nonsense.
What about the other 2 guys?
Phoon and Foam?
They'll come later.
They will join too.
- They will come later.
- Good.
Don't be scared, North.
There's no ghost here.
You can rest assured.
I'm not gonna rest assured 'cause of him instead.
More scary than a ghost.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
See, North?
I told you there's no ghost here.
You're scared of no such things.
Huh.
You were screaming with me just now.
Cause you made me!
Pleased to be here.
My pleasure.
Let's go.
I will give you a tour of the club.
Um sure.
Come on.
Let's go.
You're stiff like a rock!
Here?
Why is it so eerie here?
Is there anybody here?
I think you can go check out yourself.
Hey...but Ter said...
he will be waiting here.
Really?
Just go in.
- You come with me.
- Go together.
Or you just go alone?
These motherf*ckers!
What the hell are you doing?
- His idea.
- Don't look at me like that.
Here.
It's Ter. His idea.
- You're blaming me now?
- It's both of you!
Yeah both of you.
Dao.
Can we be done for today?
Yeah sure.
I'm hungry.
Daotok...aren't you joinig us for some food?
No, I'll have to close the club.
You want me to stay with you?
It's fine.
I can stay by myself.
I believe you.
What about you?
Are you joining?
I have to be at the faculty.
But I'll drop Ter
behind the campus first.
Okay.
-  Shall we go? I'm hungry.
- Let's go.
Let's go
- I'm gonna go now, Dao.
- Ok see you.
Bye bye~
Get home safely.
See you later.
- Are you sure you can stay?
- I can.
Don't scare the ghost.
- Just kidding~
- Dude!
Pull over here.
Thank you.
Find something to eat too.
- See you.
Bye bye~
What's up?
Hello?
Where are you now?
I'm at the back of the campus.
Where are you guys?
I don’t know. Phoon is kinda lost.
Huh? Again?
You go ahead and choose the restro. We’ll be there.
Alright. Okay.
Just come on down.
Left! I said left! That’s the right, Phoon!
I gotta go, Ter.
Right. Drive safe.
Oh Ter!
Hello P'Thunmild.
Never thought I would see you here.
Thought you'd be studying in Bangkok.
Never thought
I would meet you here either.
Haven't seen you for so long.
Yeah.
Which faculty are you in?
Oh.
I'm a vet student.
What about you, P'Mild?
Med school.
Ah~
And...how long have you been here?
Just a few days ago.
Are you adjusting okay?
You can get lost easily here.
I was confusing too
when I first arrived.
Lost here
and there all the time.
I'm not used to all of it yet.
Get lost quiet often too.
Hill is also here.
Really?
Yeah same university.
You might bump into him somedays.
Yeah.
Well...
I'm gonna get going.
If you need anything,
text me anytime.
Sure. Thank you.
See you around.
How do you pronounce that?
Gene.
is the basic unit of heredity.
If our grandparents have it...
That was one hell of a ride.
What?
You told me the wrong direction.
So daring. I told you to go left, you went right.
Told you to go right, you turned left.
i won't let you drive next time.
Good.
I'll tell you the direction instead.
That's worse.
You should just sit quietly and let me drive.
Enough enough.
Why are you guys arguing so much?
All day. Everyday.
Did you order?
Umm. Also ordered for you guys.
Why are you making that face?
Hmm?
Nothing.
Like we're buying that.
I just met a person
I didn't wanna see.
Thank you.
Who is it?
Is it the union guy,
that you're trying to avoid?
You can tell!?
It's obvious.
Am I that obvious?
Yes.
But I just don't know who it is.
Is it the same person?
No no.
Then who is it?
You know him before?
Umm. Kinda.
Haven't seen each other
for a year though.
Let's just eat.
P'Peem,
can I be excused from the union tomorrow?
Why?
Are you okay?
I'm just not feeling well.
Nothing serious, right?
No, I will just get some rest.
Oops.
Is something wrong?
Last night, Easter texted me.
Seems like he's taking leave today.
Probably sick.
What's the matter?
How am I supposed to know?
Give me his number.
So....
Hmm?
The picture that you posted.
You took it
at the restaurant the other day, didn't you?
Umm.
Is this why
he doesn't want to be here today?
Are you saying that....
it's because of me?
Isn't it?
I will talk to him myself.
Do you like Easter?
So?
I'm not giving this back to you, if you don't tell me.
Or should I delete his number?
Fine.
Just don't tell anyone.
I don't want him to be uncomfortable.
I knew it!
Bua and I have been suspecting you since that day.
I'm such a psychic.
Gotta go.
Be nice.
Our president is in love~
Bua!
You need to know this.
Hello?
Are you sick?
I will take you to the hospital.
I'm fine.
I actually have errands to run anyway.
But if you're not well,
you should rest at home.
I gotta go. Got many things to do.
I'm hanging up now.
Are you lying
that you're sick?
I'm not.
If you don't show up at the union,
your points will be deducted. You know that right?
Will I?
Um.
So...are you really sick or not?
I am.
Then I will come get you.
No.
Why not?
Gotta go.
What's up, sick boy?
You don't seem to be sick.
That's good.
- Let's go. I will take you.
- No, I'm not going.
Don't be stubborn.
I'm not going.
Fine.
Fine fine.
Where are you taking me?
- You'll let me now?
- You still haven't told me, where are you taking me?
You'll find out.
You're so devious.
With stubborn kid only.
Let's go.
I can walk myself.
Is that hurt?
Yes it is.
Why did you ask?
Stubborn kid deserves that.
P'Hill!
I should have gone my own way.
Where are we going?
Where would you like to go?
I didn't want to go anywhere.
I thought you want to go take some pics.
I know a place.
Really beautiful.
That beautiful?
Umm yes.
You never changed.
Still love taking pictures
Have you been here before?
Never.
I will be your guide for today.
This is an old temple.
It used to be a forest here.
That's why this temple is very big.
And it's also very close to the nature.
All these are Lanna Architecture.
The walls are made from mostly bricks.
Rarely renovated or built anything new.
They still remain Lanna style.
I think it's fasinating.
Wait up!
Then catch up with me.
That's beautiful.
Hey don't look.
Can you be a photographer for me?
No.
You'll waste my SD card space.
Please~
Please.
I never let anyone
take a picture of me.
Really?
I never let anyone
take a picture of me.
Really?
I saw many took pictures of you.
You check out my photos?
Nice!
I do not.
People share it.
I just see it on my timeline.
But at least you see it?
Right?
What are you talking about?
Do you wanna go pray?
Ter.
You might get sick.
Thank you.
Your welcome.
Ter.
Can you do me a favor?
No.
Please.
Please~
What is it?
Can I hold your hands?
Can I ask for one more thing?
What?
Can I be with you?
Who is this?
- He's my nong.
- Oh.
(Nong is used to call someone younger in Thai.)
Nong that I'm dating.
That's not funny.
I'm serious.
Shit!!
-Look!
- So what now?
- Try to be opened.
- Be opened is not easy to do.
Cause I've been hurt so much before.