P’Johan.
I really wanna talk to you.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Because I like you.
Then I don’t want your money.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
Why? I can’t hug you?
From now on, there’ll be only good things happening.
- Come on.
- What?
We're late. We're late.
Ter! Are you awake? We're late.
Ter!
Ter. We're running late. Are you up?
- Still asleep?
- Why are you shouting? I'm sleeping.
This is not the time to sleep.
Get up.
Wake up.
- No.
- You're late.
- Give me 10 more mins.
- 10 mins your ass. Get up!
Come on.
Get up and go shower.
Still asleep?
Do not slow down. Go.
Dude.
I wanna sleep.
Why are you waking me up?
Come on. You're late.
Don't continue to sleep in there.
Here.
Thank you.
Enough with that sleepy face.
Um.
- I know.
- Go to your class.
- Go go.
- I'm gonna go now.
- Drive safe.
- See you.
You should eat more.
I already eat a lot nowadays.
Hey Ter.
Why are you looking so pouty here?
I'm sleepy.
Where's Foam?
Dropping a girl off at Science faculty.
Instead of picking me up.
- And how did you get here?
- By myself.
Let's go to class.
That's it for today. Class dismissed.
Hey dude.
This is the video of our meds student, right?
Who is it?
You cannot tell, right?
Maybe I will tell, when I'm successful.
Do you think that person is watching this right now?
Probably.
Would you like to say something to that person?
I miss you.
Which faculty is that person studying?
Can you tell us?
Do you wanna guess?
Meds students have to be with nurses for sure.
No.
Then management?
Engineering?
No, I'll give you one more try.
I'll just randomly guess.
Vet student?
Correct.
We finally got a clue guys!
Last question
before I let you continue your study.
If you made it with this relationship,
what would you like to tell this person?
I'll do my best to take care of you.
Why am I not that person?
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Hey Ter.
Are you still here?
Is your soul out of your body?
Shit.
I'm blushing for you.
What a hot doctor he is.
Yeah I'm going crazy here.
And why did you just breath out like that?
Guys.
What if people find out that it was me?
What am I gonna do?
Why do you  have to do anything?
You don't have to do anything.
Don't have to be stressed.
Are you done with your class?
Yes, I am.
I'm watching your interview clip right now.
Ahh. You saw it.
Yes, I did.
Who allowed you to say that to the camera?
Are you blushing?
No, I'm not.
Really?
I bet your face must be so red right now.
I wanna see.
No, it's not.
Even though I already said it on the video clip,
but let me say it again.
Say what?
I miss you.
Um.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
Are you done with your class?
Shall we go find something to eat?
My class is done.
Then let's go for some food.
Umm.
Hello.
Can I get one Americano
and a cocoa drink please?
And also one banoffee please.
Sure. Wait a moment.
- Thank you.
- Look at that guy.
He's so hot like a model.
Lower your voice. He already has a boyfriend.
You're not my boyfriend?
No, I'm not.
And when will you be?
Keep trying until you're successful.
Later.
Is it good?
It is.
Is it as good as my mom's?
Why does it taking so long to think?
Just kidding.
Mom's is the best.
Mom?
I kinda miss that time too.
When I liked to hang out at your cafe after tutoring.
Tutoring?
Um.
You were tutored too?
Even before that.
Before that?
You've been to my cafe
before you even know me?
Oh umm.
Here.
Here. I give you the banana.
Sir.
What's going on?
Your grandpa is asking to see you immediately.
Oh...I'm drowning.
Over.
Ter. Why are you standing there?
You might get a cold.
It's getting colder outside.
Come inside.
Shut the door when you come in too.
If not, we all will have a cold.
Um.
I'm gonna go shower.
What happened?
You're suddenly gone.
Is everything okay?
Call me when you're free please.
Ter.
You're not going anywhere today?
No. I don't have any class today.
I will be at the faculty today.
Might come home late.
Are you okay?
You don't seem to be okay since yesterday.
I'm not really okay like you said.
About P'Hill?
He's just gone.
I texted him, but he hasn't replied.
I called. He also didn't answer.
You're worried about him, huh?
Yeah that too.
And also...
you're afraid that he'll leave you again, right?
Is it so bad that I think that way?
Not really.
You've been through this before.
It's not wrong to be traumatized.
Come on.
It'll be okay. Don't overthink.
If you cannot get in touch of P'Hill,
then contact his friends.
It's not good that you're overthinking like this.
- You should go.
- I'm gonna go now.
- Yeah.
- Don't think too much.
Do not miss me.
You can only miss P'Hill.
- P'Jo.
- Oh Ter.
Have you heard from P'Hill?
Heard there's an emergency at home
but nobody can get a hold of him since then.
I was gonna ask you too
whether you hear anything from him?
I also have no clue.
The other day his family just came to get him.
He just said don't worry.
He'll be back as soon as possible.
He told you that?
Yes.
But he just disappeared like this.
How can I not be worried?
Don't overthink.
If he said he'll be back, he will be back.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey. Answer me.
Why can't I contact you?
Are you okay?
P'Jo also cannot contact you.
You should keep me updated too.
Do you have any idea that P'Jo, P'Fah, and P'Arthit are worried about you?
And I am too.
I'm worried.
And now I'm almost mad at you if you don't text me back in 2 hrs.
Okay. Now, I'm mad and do not ask me to forgive you.
I've been calling you and now my fingers are numb.
You're not there?
And when will you be back?
P'Jo told me he came to see you and you're not there.
You're having a getaway trip?
If you are,
I will never forget you.
When you're back, I'll squeeze every single details out of you.
You'll have to buy me snacks too.
You grandpa scolds at you or something?
Next time, bring me to meet him.
Jo. I wanna see him.
Come get him for me. I cannot drive.
You're calling me,
but not gonna try to explain anything at all?
Help me.
P'Hill?
This is not Hill.
P'Johan?
I'm in front of your dorm.
Is your roommate here?
North is not back yet.
He will be home late today.
Oh and...
where are you going?
There's a sudden call...
from the number
that we've been trying to contact.
He just called and ordered me around.
Damn him.
He's gone for 2 days
and doesn't explain anything.
The first word he said in the call
was so annoying.
What was the word?
'I wanna see him~'
Let's go. Get in the car.
Sure.
He asked me to do this,
I wanna make sure
that I deliver you to his hands myself.
Knock.
I also wanna see a person
who said he cannot drive.
Try again.
P'Hill
That's a little too much.
I'm still here.
Hello?
Hill. Hello?
Can you see me?
P'Hill. You can let me go.
Thank you.
No problem.
You are okay now?
Fah and Arthit are also worried about you.
I'm okay now.
Let's talk later.
I should've taken some pictures.
Never thought I'd see this side of yours.
I'm gonna leave now.
Wait P'Jo. Are you leaving?
Yeah.
Why didn't you call me when you're back?
I was worried sick.
I wanted to surprise you.
You're too close.
I miss you.
I wanna see you up close.
You want me to dry your hair?
Sure.
Then first of all,
you should put some clothes on.
Please.
P'Hill.
Done.
Thank you.
Sure. You're welcome.
I dry North's hair everyday.
Can I be jealous of him?
No, you can't.
What are you doing?
I wanna hug you.
I miss you.
That's enough.
I can hear your heart beat just fine
without having to use stethoscope.
And why is that?
Are you blushing?
That's cute.
Let me go, P'Hill.
Can I have 10 more minutes?
This is nice.
I can see you whenever I want.
How are you?
I miss you.
I didn't ask about me.
I mean what happened when you were gone?
There's a little situation.
Was it good or bad?
It went very well.
My grandma is back.
Back?
- She has woken up.
- Really?
Umm.
I'm so happy for you. That's good.
Thank you.
When I arrived at the hospital,
- Mom!
- Hill.
- What happened?
- Grandma is awake.
- Really?
- Um.
Doctor is now examining her right now.
Grandpa and dad are in front of her room.
Let's go see her.
Let's go.
I was so happy.
I was busy at the hospital.
- so I didn't get to check my phone.
- Ok.
That's great that she's awake.
Right?
But you look so tired.
Cause I haven't slept.
As soon as I'm back here,
I called Johan to take you here.
That's good.
That P'Jo came to get me instead of you.
But to be honest,
you don't have to rush to see me.
- Just calling to let me know is more than enough.
- But I wanna see you.
I don't want you to wait too long.
Here. You're seeing me now.
Now it's time for you to sleep.
But I have so many things I wanna talk to you.
- We can talk later.
- No.
- Yes.
Fine. Fine.
What would you like to talk?
Do you wanna ask me anything?
Can you tell me?
When you first moved here...how was it for you?
Bad.
Everyday goes by with the feeling of missing,
guilt...
...and also sadness.
Everyday,
I always read books in my room.
Grandpa's aim is for me
to enroll meds school with the 1st rank.
It was not easy.
And you didn't go out anywhere?
Um.
Because of what happened between us,
my grandpa grounded me until I go to university.
I rarely met anyone.
That's why...
...you disappeared from me.
- I'm sorry.
- It's fine. Really. It's fine.
You don't have to apologize.
But I really thought that way...
...that you dumped me.
But as soon as I got into meds school,
I tried to contact you.
But I couldn't.
Why did you change your number?
Oh...cause I also fought with my family.
That bad?
Umm...yeah kind of.
Actually...
since the day my dad came to pick me up from your place,
we had a very big fight.
And I always fought with him everyday since then.
That's why I decided to left my home
and changed my phone number.
But I actually stayed with a relative.
I think my dad knew.
My mom called me from time to time.
But when I got into this university,
I just moved here right away.
Since that day...
I still haven't gone home.
Oh P'Hill. I also talked to Christ already.
She said my dad is no longer mad at me.
That's good.
So does this mean we are all clear?
Understand everything?
Um.
Then I will continue with my attempt then?
10 mins is over. Let go of me.
A bit more please.
- Can I?
- You quota is gone.
Stop with the clinginess.
What are you doing?
Come sit here.
I already replied your text.
You replied to me now? I will unfriend you.
- I thought you wanted me to reply you?
- Previously yes.
Not now.
You were worried about me.
You're not now?
Really? You're not?
You sent so many messages.
You said you were gonna squeeze my neck for information.
So?
And do you have anything else to tell me?
You haven't squeeze my neck though.
I'm not telling then.
Come on.
There's no come on.
Let me go.
Do you still want me to buy you dessert?
If you don't let me go, I will have you buy me more dessert,
until your bank account is empty.
I guess I will be buying for you in the next 10 years.
Can you be with me for another 10 years?
Stop talking and let me go.
You like to talk nonsense.
Ter.
Yes?
I love you.
I love you too.
Having you by my side like this is like a dream.
I used to think...
if one day I have you by my side,
if one day I get to meet you again...
just once...
I will do anything in my power for you.
Give me one more chance
to take care of you once again please.
Will you be my boyfriend?
Yes.
You were gone the whole night.
Left me here alone.
How was it?
Are you guys boyfriends?
You're looking like this...
you guys did it, right?
What?
So?
Are you ready to make it official?
Make what official, North?
About you and P'Hill.
Believe me.
Not long until the whole campus finds out.
Let's not talk about my business.
Let's talk our business.
I just met aunty, the owner.
She was asking for our rental payment.
Aunty again?
Always asking for the payment.
I can't be a few days behind at all.
But you can't do that every month, can you?
But I am never not paying her.
I just don't have the money at the moment.
Cause look at the way you spend your money.
Computer. Games.
Models the whole shelf.
If you sell all those,
you'll have a lot of money.
I think those are cool.
Stop with the ignoring.
What about you?
About me what?
Pretending not to know?
I'm talking about you and P'Johan.
Are you guys together?
P'Jo asked me about you last night too.
So sweet.
Ugh. So Sleepy.
- Why are you sleepy?
- I'm gonna go to bed.
Where're you going? You cannot sleep.
Today is Saturday, you need to work at P'Thun's
I played games all night.
Let me get some sleep.
I'm gonna nap a bit.
North. You're making excuses.
Answer me first!
I know that you guys are actually together now.
Stop pretending.
Answer me first.
Here are your cake and coffee.
Be careful.
Please take this.
You're still stressed?
If you were me,
you would be stressed too.
What's going on these two?
Er...so...
P'Thun.
Yeah?
Can I borrow you twenty or thirty thousands Baht?
Huh!?
- Twenty or thirty thousands?
- Yes.
Who would lend you that kind of money?
But...
why do you need that much money?
I need to pay for tuition and also for my drorm.
I forgot to pay.
Forgot?
I already used the money to pay for my computer.
- What!? For computer?
- Yes.
Whatever.
You used the money for your gaming computer.
But you forgot to pay for where you sleep.
If the aunty cuts the utilities, I'll kill you.
- Why didn't you remind me?
- I told you to talk to P'Johan about this, but you wouldn't do it.
No.
I don't wanna discuss money with P'Jo.
- No way.
- I'm going crazy.
Er....P'Thun also...
when will I get paid?
Your salary?
Yeah I was gonna talk to you about that.
Someone wants to buy my cafe.
Buy this cafe?
Why are you guys surprising?
I actually didn't wanna sell it.
But...
the offer is really good.
I'm preparing all the documents at the moment. It will be done soon.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Who is it? The buyer?
I also don't know
cause he sends someone to deal with this on his behalf.
Don't be paranoid.
You still have your job. Just change the owner. That's it.
I'm gonna go check on customers.
Dude.
Why is this happening to me when I have a problem?
- Right.
- Are we gonna get paid or not?
Oh hey.
I heard you talked to Ter about Johan.
Are you two like really close?
Not exactly, but yeah we kinda are. I guess.
He's been flirting with you, right?
How many times have I warned you about Johan?
Everyone knows that he's a player.
I warn you because I care about you,
you know that right?
I'm sorry,
but I heard that P'Johan stops talking to many people already.
Being a player is not easily stopped overnight.
I told you all these
because I hope the best for you, you know?
I care about you a lot.
You know?
- P'Jo!
- Hey.
Wait.
Where are you taking my staff?
- He's not.
- Not what?
Not yours.
Can I order some drink and dessert?
Er...sure.
How come you're here?
P'Johan.
I'm tired.
Let me take some rest.
Hello, P'Hill.
Hi P'Jo.
You have class today?
Yeah had an appointment with the professor.
Your study is so intense.
P'Jo. North has something he wants to discuss with you.
Ter!
What is it?
Nothing.
- Ter was just babbling.
- Tell me.
Nothing.
Hill. Close your boyfriend's eyes.
Jo...you're too much.
Really?
Er...I'll just go help P'Thun downstairs.
Ter, I will go with you.
So what do you wanna discuss with me?
You haven't told me.
I will tell you after work.
But right now, I need to go back to work.
P'Hill. I will be back.
What?
Hey Ter.
Don't be quiet.
I'm not. I just don't know what to say.
P'Johan is so--
Even I'm your friend,
I still have never seen you like this before.
You guys are making me blush.
I can't get that off my head.
You should delete it from your head.
How much did you see?
A bit.
P'Johan is so daring.
I was like some air to you guys.
Thinking about it makes me blush again.
Stop it.
So what...?
Or do I have to be used to it?
Cause I might be seeing those more often?
Ughhh stop it.
You're so annoying.
North.
Why did you have to followed him like that?
I helped you.
Did you see the way he looked at me?
It was like he wants to kill me.
He just shook my hands off like this.
No manner at all.
Does he have to be that rude if he wants to be with you?
We can tell from these thst he's not trustworthy.
Does he force you to do anything else?
No.
Why don't you just reject him
if he keeps bugging you?
You mean P'Johan?
Yeah of course.
Why do you have to do whatever he tells you to do?
Actually...
he does not force me or anything.
Are you saying that...
you actually have feelings for him?
Wel...
I guess.
North. How many times have I told you?
Well...
I'm not saying that you're lying...
about P'Johan's rumor.
I know that too.
Not that I'm not aware.
But at the end...no matter how bad the rumors are,
I don't really care.
Cause he is nice to me.
It's the truth.
So I'm the losing one here.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I'm sorry too.
I was...
too hot headed.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back.
What actually just happened?
It's my fault.
for never really saying no to him.
Are you okay?
This is a big cafe.
- Hi P'Arthit.
- Hey.
Hello.
You're working?
Yes.
P'Jo and P'Hill are upstairs.
Is this your friend?
Oh this is North.
Hello.
Hi.
North..?
This is the one?
Yeah this ond I told you about.
Oh.
Hi. I'm Tolfah and this is Arthit.
Yeah I'm North.
Can we order here?
Yes you can order here.
We will serve you when it's done.
Ok.
Please.
Oh there're customers?
Yes.
This is P'Khim, the new manager.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I'm sorry for showing up unannounced.
Prang told me the sooner I'm here that better.
Prang?
What's the matter?
I just thought Prang is the same name
with P'Johan's assistant.
But it's probably just a coincident.
Does he really doing this?
Ms.Khim...let's just go talk overthere.
Sure.
P'Prang...has P'Jo bought any coffee shop lately?
Yes, the one thart you work at.
Don't know why. There are so much work.
Wait...for real!?
Yeah for real. Not just that one.
He asked me to buy the bar too. Don't know why he wants it.
Bar?
Umm SoulOut bar.
He also said he wants to buy a Japanese restaurant too.
Hey.
Come on.
There're so many Japanese restaurants out there.
Probably not P'Yha's.
Will I get to actually work?
It's fine.
P'Johan does this to me again.
I'm going to serve these.
You guys are not going to study?
Here are your coffees.
- North.
- Yes.
You made this Americano?
Yes why?
It's so bitter, North.
I think...
there's only Jo who can drink this.
If you're complaining, you don't have to drink.
Yeah I'm not gonna drink it.
You drink it then.
Yeah It will be just me drinking.
I'm so sick.
Sick of Arthit's face?
Why me!?
P'Jo.
Let go of me.
Oh Jo.
Why don't you tell us that you bought this coffee shop?
Hey. Give me back all the money I spend here.
Why do I have to do that?
Hey.
You're not gonna buy your friends coffee sometimes?
You can't pay for your own coffee?
You spend all the money on girls?
Get out of my cafe.
Stop arguing.
P'Jo.
I have something I wanna talk to you.
Can we talk outside?
Um.
I'll be back.
P'.
You bought this cafe?
So?
I got fired from SoulOut.
It was you right?
I know that you have a lot of money.
But don't you think this is too much?
I told you to stop working.
But you never listened to me.
So now you work for me.
I will be going to Boston by the way.
P'.
You're going to Boston?
For work?
For how long?
Around 2 weeks.
So you have to take leaves from school?
Um.
And...
you will be okay right?
Well..
why am I not gonna be?
Just in case you miss me?
And what does Ter mean when he said...
you have something to tell me?
Well...
I don't have the money to pay for my tuition and dorm.
So...
I would like to borrow--
Borrow you.
From now on, if you wanna ask me for something...
just follow my conditions.
You want me to kiss you?
No.
I don't wanna borrow you anymore.
This is just a deposit.
Thanks P'.
What's up?
So...
if you wanna be committed to him,
don't treat him like any other people.
I know.
You're acting just like Hill.
But that's good that it's him.
He's cute.
Don't have to be jealous.
I didn't mean it that way.
Hill told me...
that he's a chill guy.
Never stressed.
And also a very strong person.
If he's not like this, he can't be with you.
Not like that.
It's not good because of him that I'm with.
But because it's him...that's why everything is so special.
I never thought I'd get to see this side of yours.
You will go back with me today.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Have I ever refused?
I probably won't be at the company for awhile.
What's up?
I wanna ask whether have you seen my lab worksheet?
The one I brought to study with Hill today.
I couldn't find it.
Yes.
You have it?
Arthit has it.
Why does he have it?
And you didn't tell me he has it?
Cause he's not done.
Even if I asked, he's not gonna give it to me.
Tell him to give it to me tomorrow.
Don't forget. I don't wanna talk to him.
Why me?
Come on.
Fine. Fine.
Another thing.
You look stressed lately.
Like you're easily frustrated. Like more irritated.
Hill said you have so much work?
Um just like what Hill said.
You have to work that hard?
I have to.
He said he'll hand over everything to me
before I graduate in a few years.
Alright.
Don't work too hard then.
I gotta go.
Don't forget to tell Arthit for me.
Um.
North.
Yes?
Come here.
I'm exhausted.
Does this make you feel better?
Not yet.
When you said that you like me before we met.
What is the reason?
Can you tell me about it?
Will you bring him to Boston with you?
I will take you to wherever you want.
I'm glad that it was you.
He seems better when being with you.
Go to take a shower.
Or we should take together?