How about you and Johan?
It's good, I guess.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yes?
Did you feel something to P'Johan?
At that moment, when you were disappeared.
Can you tell me about it?
I have something to talk with Ter.
Ter don't want to see you.
- Hey Ter!
- Oh hey, Duennao.
- You're here for lunch?
- Actually to buy one.
Oh Ter.
I saw Jah came to see North today.
JhaJah? North's ex-girlfriend?
Yes.
I think you should check on him.
I saw him looking so distracted walking out.
Um. Sure.
- I'm gonna go now.
- Um.
If not, Tiger might be starving and eat me alive.
- See you.
- See you. Bye.
Is North gonna be okay?
North?
He'll be fine.
Right?
A person like him is not gonna die easily.
Let's go.
Jah came to see you?
Duennao told me.
Why did she come?
What did you guys discuss?
Nothing. Just talked a little.
What did you guys talk about?
Don't hide it from me.
Tell me.
Are you so free?
I just wanna know what did you guys talk about.
She came to see you at the facullty?
What did she say?
Tiger. Are you free? Please answer me.
I don't have time for you.
Tiger. I suddenly feel uncomfortable.
It's like I keep someone's secret with me for so long.
But like I can't keep it to myself any longer.
Why? It's not even your business.
What's the matter?
Can I call?
Yeah.
What's up?
I wanna ask you something.
I went to see Jah today, my ex-girlfriend.
She mentioned about Temp.
Did you do anything to him?
Why did he transfer?
So now you're pinning it on me?
Cause out of the people around me,
there's only you who's capable of doing this.
When he provoked Duennao,
I was so pissed.
I wanted get the footage from cctv,
but your Johan already took it first.
When I asked him,
he said he already handled it.
How? You tell me so vaguely.
I talked to him.
After that day, he did not stop.
He kept provoking Duennao.
So me and P'Jo just kinda made him expelled.
He already has bad history too.
So it was not difficult.
Are you done?
Why are you asking me so damn much?
So that happened?
Yeah cause he provoked my Duennao.
My love is great alright?
You're always so protective of him.
Does he have any idea?
What about you?
If you ex didn't show up,
you'll never know right?
How am I supposed to know?
Have you realized that you like him?
What?
Hey.
It's about your P'Jo.
What?
- I'm not...
- Fine. Fine. Okay.
Maybe you're not...
But for him...
you're driving him crazy.
You're not stupid, North.
I'm being serious.
You tell me all those stories...
are you telling me that he doesn't like you?
So?
-I...
- don't like him?
Right?
Yeah I never really think that way.
We just got to know each other.
He never said he liked or wanted to go out with me.
How can he like a person like me?
That's another thing to think about.
I...
don't wanna keep thinking too much.
Especially about love.
Fine fine.
You never thought of anything.
But...
But what if he does...
he does not think all day.
How?
I don't know.
I'm just babbling.
Bye. I don't wanna talk to you anymore.
Right. Right.
Ugh. Ter.
Why do you wanna know so much?
Jah wanted to get back together.
Happy?
You're back?
Umm.
Why didn't you text me back? Hmm?
- I did.
-  No, you haven't.
Look. Here. Here.
See. I already replied you recent messages.
See?
- Check this out.
- Umm. Where?
Shit!
- Shit?
- I replied the wrong chat.
Huh!? And who did you text?
P'Johan's.
When you throwing me a bunch of texts,
he kinda texted me too.
And what did you text him?
- Jah wanted to get back together.
- Huh!?
Jah wanted to get back together.
Did you reject her?
I did.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I no longer have feelings for her.
You should help me think
what am I gonna do with P'Johan.
Why? It's fine.
Or it's not?
a little?
I don't want him to know.
I'm afraid that
he might add more debt to my account.
Really?
More like you're afraid that he misunderstands?
Or...
To be honest, you just don't want him to find out cause you started to care huh?
Right?
Answer me, North!
Answer me now.
I...
I'm scared.
Scared of what?
Not sure that I can tell...
You can. I'm ready to listen.
Yeah something like that.
Shit!
I know that he took care of the damage from the bar.
But I didn't know that he took care of Temp issue too.
Dude! Ughh he's so into you.
He likes you!
Finally! My ship has sailed.
You're focusing on the wrong point.
Dude.
From now  on, it's up to you.
I'm not feeling anything.
You're destroying my dream.
North.
Be honest with me.
Don't you feel nice,
when there's someone to protect you.
Who woud not
when there's someone to protect you?
I'm blushing.
- I'm not gonna talk to you anymore. Gonna go work.
- Hey wait wait.
I'm not done.
What about that guy from the bar
you told me about?
How is it?
P'Day?
Yeah how is it?
Does he mess with you again?
Same.
I'm worried about you.
To be honest,
I really don't want you to work there.
Yeah.
I will be careful.
I'm gonna go get ready.
Yeah.
Oh you're here.
Hello.
Haven't seen you for so long.
I miss you.
Hey.
I'm not a dog.
What?
I cannot even touch you?
Why don't you let me flirt with you?
I already told you. I don't like this.
Oh North. Day.
Hello P'Paan.
Just wait until I have the chance.
I'm gonna go work now.
What's the matter?
Nothing. It's nothing.
I'm gonna go work too.
Where are you?
Jah wanted to get back together.
Happy?
I asked...where are you?
Forget it.
Explain.
Are you gonna tell me here
or you want me to open your mouth and tell me myself?
I'm telling you now. She's my ex.
Hello?
What about your ex?
She wants to get back together.
But I already rejected her.
The girl that got you in trouble?
What did she say?
She just broke up with her boyfriend
and she wanna get back together with me.
But I rejected her already.
I know. You told me. What else?
Nothing else.
That's it.
Anything else?
About Temp.
I got in a fight with him til he had to transfer.
Jah asked me
whether I have anything to do with it?
I said I did not.
So she suspects you and Ger instead.
Then I asked Ger.
Umm.
That shithead already told you huh.
Yes.
He said...
Hey.
What?
I haven't told anything.
You still send me even if it's blurry?
Cute. I won't show you the clear one. I'd be jealous.
I just wanna show you his cuteness.
Right. Whatever.
But good that you're texting me.
I need your advice.
No. I'm gone.
Hear me out. I've been so uncomfortable.
There's a guy from my work, wanted to go out with me.
I already rejected him.
But he keeps trying.
Lately, been so touchy too.
I already told him that I don't like it, but he wouldn't stop.
What should I do?
That's easy.
Just tell P'Jo.
Funny.
What can you do?
Hey North. Come help us.
Customers are here.
Sure.
Where's my phone?
Where is it?
Are you looking for this?
You do not take care of your stuff.
I dropped it?
Thank you.
Should I give it back to you or not?
Can I have my phone back please?
I'm about to go home.
Come get it.
I'm not playing wih you.
I'm also not.
- P'
- I told you already...don't let me have the chance.
Hey what are you doing!?
P' stop.
Stop, P'.
Why are you playing hard to get?
No. Stop.
Stop.
Hey!
- You think you can get away from me?
- Let go of me. What are you doing?
Are you scared?
But you were acting so cool,
arguing with me earlier.
It would be done easily
if you didn't play hard to get.
Now, I have to be physical with you.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
What am I doing?
I'm gonna make you mine.
Let's see whether you can argue with me further?
Hey.
What?
Step back.
Turn around. Hands on the wall.
P'Jo.
Take care of the rest.
I told you not to work here anymore.
I can get up myself.
North.
Don't be stubborn with me.
Here it is, Mr.Johan.
Do you want me to take care of him?
So you can rest.
It's okay.
I will do it. You can go rest.
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
Still hurt?
Not anymore.
And...
Mr.Johan just left.
The moment he saw you woke up,
he just left.
Even he was with you all night.
He was here with me all night?
Yes.
I wanted to take care of you myself,
but he wouldn't let me.
He wanted to be with you himself.
Did he say anything else?
Oh.
Not really.
But his facial expression was not so good.
I've never seen him this angry before.
He can be frustrated sometimes,
But angry lilke this,
I've never seen before.
Really?
He left
because he probably don't wanna see you right now.
He's probably too angry to see you.
But also...
too worried...
to leave.
I will go prepare you some food.
Oh and these medicines, he prepared it for you.
Take it before the meal please.
- I will leave it here.
- Sure. Thank you.
I...
...don't know.
I don't even know myself.
But if one day I really fall in love with someone,
you know that I am not a complicated person.
I will do my best to show them.
I think..
I also don't see P'Johan with anyone either.
He might really like you one day.
Why don't you try to open your heart for him?
Please try.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Where are you going sir?
I'm about to bring you your food.
Er...
can you take me to P'Johan please?
I think...
you better not see him right now.
No one's dare to see him when he's angry.
But...
I really need to talk to him.
P'Johan.
I have something I need to talk to you.
Are you in there?
Aunty Da.
Yes, Mr.Johan?
Can you take him back to his room?
- Let's go. We should go.
- Wait a minute.
P'Johan.
I really wanna talk to you.
I'm sorry. I know you're angry with me.
But I really wanna talk to you.
Please hear me out.
You know that I'm mad at you right?
I know.
I...
I'm sorry for not listening to you in the first place.
And also...
thank you.
Without you, I'd probably--
Why...
are you so nice to me like this?
Because I like you!
If you tell me to stop,
I will stop.
Can I kiss you?
About me working at the bar behind your back...
I'm sorry and...
thank you for rescuing me.
You know what's gonna happen right?
If I didn't go there?
I know.
- I didn't mean to lie to you.
- But you never told me.
You also never told me
why you don't want me to work there.
Cause I'm worried.
You don't have any common sense?
But from now on,
I will no longer let you work anywhere.
No more.
I was not gonna go work at the bar anymore.
But let me work in some other places.
I need to earn to pay you back.
Not to mention my personal spending.
Dorms and etc. So many expenses.
Then I won't take your money anymore.
What do you mean?
If you let me hug you like this.
I will give you 500.
If you let me kiss you, I will give you a 1,000.
But if you give more than that,
I will give you 5,000 each time.
How?
It'll be like I use my body to pay you back.
No, it's not.
Cause I like you.
No.
Are you even listening to me?
So that was a 1,000, right?
Yes.
What about earlier?
That doesn't count.
Why not!?
- Cause I haven't told you the rules.
- What?
You're mean.
Go to sleep.
I already called Duennao
that you won't attend the class.
But seems like you have to attend the afternoon one.
Good. I'm still sleepy.
I will go to sleep then.
Where are you going?
Go to sleep.
Sleep here.
Sleep in your room?
Um.
How can I sleep when you stare at me like that?
Go!
Hey! What are you doing?
Why? Can't I hug you?
We're not boyfriends.
Can we do this?
Why?
- You wanna be my boyfriend?
- It's not like that.
It feels weird doing this
when we're not even boyfriends.
Then we should be.
You're talking nonsense.
You already opened your heart for me, yeah?
If not,
then you wouldn't let me kiss you.
I'm not gonna talk to you anymore.
Mr.Johan. May I come in?
Yes.
I don't know which size do you normally wear, so...
so I brought all for you to choose.
This one is fine.
Thank you.
For the shoes,
I already have it ready downstairs.
Would you like me to bring your food up here?
Are you hungry?
Not yet.
Then you go shower and change.
I have a class in the afternoon too.
I will drive you.
Sure.
Please.
Mr.Johan never brought anyone home at all.
Same goes to the condo.
Really?
Yes.
You're the first boyfriend
that I get to meet.
Oh so...
Am I saying anything wrong?
No.
I was worried that he is a player type.
Never committed to a serious relationship with anyone.
But that's good that he stops now.
Even though he's really smart and hard-working,
but he still needs someone
to support him.
Right?
Yes.
- Would you excuse me? I'm gonna go shower.
- Sure.
If you need anything else,
please let me know.
- Sure. Thank you.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna shower now.
Hello? What's going on my best friend, Tiger?
Asshole.
What's up?
Can you buy some snacks for Duennao?
He didn't have breakfast.
Neither for lunch.
Transfer me the money.
It's just a few Baht. You still need me to transfer?
Why don't you buy it yourself
if it's just a few Baht.
I can't.
Hahaa. You cannot? With just this kinda stuff?
And you call yourself tiger?
I will be worse when it's my turn.
I already transferred you. Bye.
I will take care of it.
Tiger?
Yes.
He wants me to buy some snacks for his crush.
- Is his name Duennao?
- Hey.
How do you know?
He told me when he came to see me.
That's a relief.
I thought I slipped it.
Thank you.
Hey...what are you doing?
Don't forget...
how you're gonna pay me back.
Go to you class and pay attention.
The new ice scream shop, that recently opened.
- I already tried it.
- Why didn't you invite me?
For real!?
Is the world ending? You bought us snacks?
- Or you don't want it?
- That's crazy.
What do we have?
I heard that...
P'Johan drove you here?
So?
Why does he do that?
- Were you with him this morning?
- Nao!
My nosy habit is already kicking in. Come on.
I called him this morning whether he's coming to class or not.
- Do you know what happened?
- What?
P'Jo answered.
He said North couldn't make it.
- Why? What did you do?
- Let's do it this way.
Why were you guys together?
Or...
- Or...
- Are you guys officially boyfriends?
Answer us please. What's the story?
Nosy. Nosy. Nosy.
- You don't get to eat these anymore.
- Hey!
Go to your class.
You know which class you have to be?
See. He's pouty.
Now, he's back.
The class that you told me not ot miss
is Home Economics?
Yeah. We have a group project.
It's a free elective
and why do you have to choose this one?
Blame on Ikkyu.
He signed up for us.
Why? When you're done with Calculus,
you can bake something. Pretty chill.
- Like I know how to make it?
- You know how to cook, right?
But I don't know how to bake.
If I got an F, you guys are responsible for this.
What? Why us?
I'm not involved in this.
Here we go students.
I would like you to find your pairs.
Today, we will make an easy cake.
-  An easy one.
- Easy one.
Not difficult one. We're good.
What are you doing?
Who do I have to be your pair?
Cause you and Ikkyu have some skills.
If I were to be with him, we would fail.
I think this is for the best.
Do we pour this in?
You need to sift first.
You didn't here the instruction just now?
Sift what? How to do it? Like this?
Funny.
Here. Pour it.
- Pour here?
- I will sift it myself.
Wait wait. Hold this.
What?
- You continue. I'll be back.
- Yeah.
Keep sifting.
Hello, P'Paan? What's up?
North. I'm calling to tell you about the bar.
The new owner fired you.
Fired me?
Umm. I don't know why.
But are you okay?
I'm okay. I was gonna resign anyway.
Really?
Yes. Thank you though, P'Paan for telling me.
Okay. Bye then.
Yeah.
How's it going?
North. When I cracked the eggs,
the yolk was broken.
It's fine. We will have to mix it anyway.
But we've got some shell in it too.
I already tried,
but I probably didn't take all of the shell out.
And why didn't you do it before?
Let me see...woah.
Calcium.
You think you're funny?
Take it out.
Why is your face like that?
You're still asking?
The professor face when she talked still cracks me up.
'Students. Are you gonna poison me or something?'
Stop talking. It's because of Nao.
Cracked the eggs but he didn't take all the shell out. Why though?
Why? You get some texture. Crunchy.
Crunchy your ass!
People make mistakes too.
Yeah. Whatever.
- Are you going straight home?
- Yes, I'm so sleepy.
Me too.
Except some people, they might go cuddle with their boyfriends.
Teasing me huh!
Right right. Let's go.
Did you bring your ride?
- I didn't.
- I will drop you off.
Let's go.
Why did you bring me here?
I wanted to talk to you.
About what?
Is it important?
Why do you look so serious?
It kinda is.
I've been thinking for awhile.
Think about what?
Shit. I'm getting nervous.
Can you just tell me what is it about?
About Tiger.
Why?
I...
I just...
- I think he likes you.
- Huh!?
He always acts like he's seeing someone.
When people approaches him, he always rejects.
When I ask him to give it a try, he always says he doesn't wanna talk to anyone.
So I think he already has someone that he likes.
Which is you.
And why me?
He always mentions about you too.
He always calls you when he's at the dorm.
Not like that.
He doesn't have a crush on me. Trust me.
Um.
I know that you already opened your heart for P'Johan.
But...
Tiger is a nice guy.
I don't want him to be disappointed.
Oh god.
If he finds out, he'll be so heart broken.
Trust me. He doesn't have a crush on me.
So am I misunderstanding?
Yeah like big time.
What were you thinking?
Really?
What are you looking at?
What happened to your lips?
Why does it look swollen?
- A wasp stung me.
- When?
Just now.
Be honest, wasp or bee?
Or P'Jo kissed you?
Shit. I was just kidding.
Am I right?
You guys kissed?
Are you guys boyfriends yet?
Not yet.
But you let him kiss you?
Or you wanted to?
Yeah. I didn't feel bad or anything.
Oh so now you have feelings for him?
He's probably not fooling around with you.
He actually...
- said he likes me.
- Shit! For real?
I'm blushing for you man.
And do you like him too?
I already tried to open my heart for him.
Like a lot.
And why you open now?
He's been so nice to me.
Like real nice.
But isn't it normal?
when people are nice to you, you must feel good, right?
Yeah that's good that he's nice to you.
But you probably have feelings for him too.
if not, you wouldn't let him do all these to you.
I like it!
He kissed until your lips are swollen.
Don't you think he's cruel?
He can't do it in a normal way, yeah?
Why not?
Cause a guy like you, when there's someone likes you, and you don't like them back.
you'll push them away from your life.
You won't keep them in your empty head.
But when P'Jo does it this way,
it stucks in your head like this.
You call all those flirting?
Yeah they are.
North.
- Come here.
- What is it?
No matter how bad I'd like to know
about the guy from the bar,
but I wanna know about P'Jo more.
Spill the tea.
What are you doing?
About last night, P'Hill told me already.
He saved you last time.
This time he also did again.
Let's be honest with me,
you don't have any feelings for him at all?
I already told you I'm not a complicated person.
That means you're now opening your heart to P'Jo?
Um.
And...
do you know how does he feel about you?
He sends someone to look after you like this,
it's impossible not to have feelings for you, right?
He actually...
- told me he likes me.
- Really!?
That hurts. You hit me too hard.
I'm so happy!
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I was too happy.
A shipper like me has been rooting for you for so long.
Let me have my moment.
Oh and what re you gonna do about P'Day?
To be honest,
I didn't think he is such a scum bag.
But forget it.
- P'Hill told me he got fired.
- I'm also fired.
Oh why?
Someone took over the bar, new owner just fired me.
But whatever. I was gonna resign anyway.
I should've listened to you.
I shouldn't have worked there.
It's okay dude.
It's already in the past.
Here. From now on, there'll be only good things coming to your life.
Come on.
You look happier than me.
That's good.
I saw you're happy. I'm also happy.
I just met the owner aunty, she's asking for the rental payment.
Pay.
I already spent the money on my computer.
Huh!? Computer?
I don't have the money for my tuition fee and dorm rent.
Just follow my conditions.
These are just the deposit.
Give me one more chance to take care of you.
Will you be my boyfriend?