And how come you know him?
Fine. That's the guy.
That guy you said you hate him so much?
That's right.
So our friend,
Hill, is about to be married.
So it's just us left
...Jo...Ton.
It's probably not just me.
I thought you want to go take some pics.
I know a place.
Really beautiful.
Can I ask for one more thing?
What?
Can I be with you?
- What are we gonna do?
- Ter.
Ter. Calm down.
It's okay.
It's fine, Ter.
Don't worry.
Are we gonna be able
to see each other again?
We will.
Don't worry.
Wait for me, okay?
Yes.
I will wait.
Welcome.
Thank you.
P'Hill.
(Block Contact)
Can I be with you?
No.
Why are you smiling?
I didn't actually ask.
When I said 'can I be with you?',
I didn't ask.
I just wanna inform.
That's not funny.
Yes.
Not funny.
I'm serious.
I'm not taking that.
But I already took it.
P'!
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
Ok. Sure.
But I already called dibs on you.
Are you hungry?
Let's go grab a bite.
You're not hungry?
Hmm?
Well...I am.
Good. This meal is on me.
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Are we going now?
It's still raining.
I will build an elevator here myself.
Where are you?
Oh Thunmild!
Have you seen, Hill?
He's probably at the union.
What a waste of time.
Is there something you need, P'Mei Li?
I need a little bit of help from Hill.
It's about the shoot to promote our university.
Is it the same one
that I will have to shoot as well?
Yes yes. That one.
Don't know what's wrong with him.
He hasn't answered my call.
I'm about to go see him at the union anyway.
I will tell him for you.
Please tell him for me, my dear
Tell him it's urgent.
Please. Thank you so much.
You're awesome!
You are the most awesome, girl!
See you.
(Student Union)
Here, P'Peem.
Thank you.
More work.
This gives me a headache.
Hi Peem.
Oh hey, Mild.
Hill is not here?
He just left awhile ago.
- Where did he go?
- I don't know.
But seems like he's probably having so much fun now.
Fun?
He went out by himself?
No, with a nong.
He's one of the guys from the union.
Who is he?
Not sure you will know him,
if I tell you.
Is it the guy Hill posted a picture with?
Hey you know him!?
Is he gonna come back?
Probably not.
If he does,
I'll tell him you stopped by.
It's fine, I will call him myself.
I'm just stopping by to see him.
That's all.
I will just go then.
Oh mild.
You and Hill went to the same high school right?
Umm.
Do you know someone named 'Easter' then?
Yes, we also went to the same school.
I knew it!
That's why those two always act so weird.
What do you mean?
It's nothing...it's just...
Seems like those two know each other before.
Oh.
I gotta go.
Bye bye.
I knew it that they had something goin' on.
My instinct was right.
The rain has stopped.
You can let me go now.
What's up, Mild?
Where are you, Hill?
What's up?
I came to see you at the union,
but you were't there.
What do you need?
P'Mei Li was asking for you.
She said she needs to talk to you.
But you didn't answer her calls.
Oh...I probably didn't have any signals earlier.
Seems like something urgent too.
It's something about
the shoot to promote our university.
Are you...
...going, Hill?
So I can tell her.
I can't be there today.
She didn't told me in advance.
You're busy?
Umm.
I am.
You guys met?
Hmm?
Nothing.
Today, you won't be at the faculty, right?
No.
I will see you tomorrow then.
Umm.
That's not nice.
Eavesdropping like that.
I did not.
Let's go eat.
Wait.
If you have some work to do,
we can leave.
But I rather spend time with you
and take you out for dinner.
There are some yummy cocoa and cakes too.
Ok fine. Let's go.
You're so cute
when you're not stubborn.
Let's go in.
Hello.
Did you book the table?
I did. A table for 2.
Under which name sir?
Ratchakit.
This way please.
Do you like the atmosphere here?
It's good.
Do you like me?
I do.
You said it.
I mean I like the restaurant.
Yeah I also meant the restaurant.
Do you want me to help you order?
What would like to eat?
The cake.
Hey.
You should eat something
before the dessert.
What!?
There's no need to scold.
Are you okay?
It's the picture.
Yes.
The picture you posted.
It's...
Forget it.
I'm serious.
About the picture I posted,
and also when I said I will be with you.
So...trust me.
Let's continue ordering.
I will eat now~
Careful! It's hot.
I will blow to cool it first.
Why are you looking like that
when you see your friend?
Why are you here?
Why?
Can't I be hungry too?
Are you the only one
that can be in this restaurant?
Who is this?
He's my nong.
Oh...nong.
Nong that I'm dating.
Cute too.
Jo!
Don't mind him.
Why?
Can I just get to know him like a brother?
No, you cannot.
Fine. Cannot it is.
I'm gonna go then.
I have to go.
I guess I have to eat somewhere else today.
Bye bye then.
Is he your friend?
Umm. His name is Johan.
Oh.
This is the guy.
You know him?
Yes for sure.
He's so popular.
A lot of people talk about him.
Talk about what?
Well...he's handsome.
What is he like in person?
Still handsome.
What about me?
Just eat.
It's getting cold.
Looks so good.
Wait a bit, I will eat you~
How was the cocoa and the cake?
Yummy?
It was.
I like it.
You seem to be in a better mood
after eating your favorites.
Yes, I am.
You remember?
What is my favorite food?
I remember everything about you, Ter.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Ter.
See you at the union.
And don't avoid me again.
Sure.
Can I be with you?
Shit.
Go! I gotta get away.
Hey, you're back.
Where have you been?
Dinner.
You had dinner with P'doctor, huh?
Wowww~
Wow your ass!
Hey for real?
You really went with P'Hill?
Was it a date?
How was it?
It was not a damn date.
So how was it?
What are you talking about?
About P'Hill.
I don't know.
He's dating you now?
I guess so.
If other people found out
that he's dating you,
they would cry their eyes out.
Right.
There're many people out there,
why me?
Dude.
Or he's just messing with me?
Why would he do that?
Like make you fall in love and leave you?
Who knows?
That would be too much.
It's possible.
If you don't like him,
then just tell him directly.
I already did that.
and he didn't stop?
I'm just gonna go shower.
- Hey don't leave!
- You’re not making any sense.
I still haven't got the answer.
Just play your games.
Play all day all night.
Play until you're blind.
I can play, but you--
...didn't tell the whole story.
Hi son. Arrived home already?
Yes, dad.
Where are you, dad?
I'm with grandma.
How is she?
Same same.
She will wake up eventually.
Are you guys doing okay?
We're fine.
We takes turn to be with her.
Don't worry.
How are you? Are you tired?
What about grandpa?
Like usual
If you have time,
go visit him sometimes.
You're not mad at him at all?
Hill.
I have to go.
You guys take care of yourself too,
You too, son.
What's up?
You were gone all day yesterday.
What are you doing?
Nosy.
Hey.
I will get back to you later.
Hill.
Have you talked to P'Mei Li?
I will go see her today.
Don't forget please.
It seems urgent.
Where were you yesterday?
I took nong to take some pictures.
I will go now.
So you took someone out to take pictures?
It's none of your business.
Mild, do you know whose was it
that P'Hill posted a picture with?
- What picture?
- Here
- (The owner of my watch)
- Who is that?
I don't know.
I don't know who to find anymore.
What are we gonna do?
Oh hey.
Hill, what are you doing here?
Heyyy golden boy.
Come here. Sit here.
Please sit.
Where were you all day yesterday?
I had an appointment.
Appointment?
You're sure it's not a date?
You have something to talk to me?
Oh.
It's about the promoting video we discussed.
Is there a problem?
I basically want representatives
from each faculty to shoot.
For med students,
can you help me out?
Thunmild will also be there.
Err....it's pretty busy at the union lately.
It's just a day or two.
Please. Help me out.
If you don't help me,
I don't know what to do anymore.
Have you tried Jo, Ton, or Arthit?
Those guys you're asking?
Please just help me, Jo.
You'll be your faculty's representative.
Sure.
Are you serious?
If you can shoot this in the hoop,
I will do it.
Too bad.
I just wasted my time, didn't I?
- Lately..
- I'm busy lately.
Ughh. Hear me out first.
What's up?
- So next week--
- I'm also not free next week.
Why are you so busy?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. You don't have to apologize.
I will just ask some other people.
Thank you.
Sure.
I don't know what to do,
if you're not helping me.
I would be in so much trouble.
Just a bit of shooting.
I know you can do it, Arthit.
Just following the script.
A short interview.
I know you can do it Arthit.
Not long. I'm not---
I spoke for so long.
Are you seriously asleep?
Just like that.
There's only you, Hill.
Please help me.
You are my last hope.
Fine.
You're the best!
Thank you.
Oh...do you also know anyone that can take pictures?
I want someone
to take behind the scene pictures.
Someone to take pictures?
Do you know anyone?
I know a guy.
- I will handle it.
- Right?
I will let you handle that.
- Yes.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you. Really.
You're the best!
Girls.
Isn't he so cute?
Ayy~
Shit.
What's going on?
Calm down.
Are you okay?
Dude. I can't.
Look.
It's just a picture.
Um.
Holding hands.
Then what?
We can see a watch.
But that's your watch, isn't it?
Yes.
Whatever.
People can't see your face,
P'Hill. P'Hill.
Enough.
Stop looking at it.
Hey Ter.
You don't seem to be mad though.
It's like you're blushing.
Really?
You're not denying too.
- What?
- So?
It's nothing.
So you guys were holding hands?
He asked for my hand.
And you let him?
Um.
And...
why are you not okay?
It just seems weird.
How?
I don't know.
This is why...
...he hasn't posted a picture with your face.
Why?
Cause you, yourself,
still don't know how you feel.
He's probably waiting for you
to recognize your own feeling first.
And when things are settled,
he will make it public.
Making it public?
No way.
No way? We'll see.
Dude. You have to be on my side.
I'm always on your side.
But you're always overthinking.
Dude.
Or he's just pretending
to make me believe him?
You're so pessimistic.
Try to be open-minded.
There's nothing wrong with that.
You...
Being open-minded is not easy to do.
Cause I've been hurt so much before.
You've been hurt before?
Well...
when I was in high school,
I had a crush on him.
Huh?
I told you before.
I went to the same school with him.
I met him quite often.
And I just fell for him.
But...
But what?
He liked my sister.
You helped out at my shop so often,
my mom should pay for your wages already.
Can I get free coconut cakes
for a lifetime then?
That's not a problem at all.
P'Hill.
Just coconut cake is not enough.
I'll also give you cocoa.
Please. Try it.
I've been practicing.
But cannot make it as good as my mom does.
How is it?
Good?
You've improved actually.
Really?
Er...but have I
ever made one for you to try?
P'Ter.
Come help me with my homework.
P'Hill.
Hello.
Oh.
Here. Let P'Hill help you.
He's so much smarter.
Can you help Christ with her homework?
Do you mind?
Not at all.
- You're not troubling me.
- Really?
You're the kindest person.
And my sister also likes him a lot.
What can I do?
Except keeping it to myself for the past 2 years.
And you...
helped your sister out?
Don't tell me
you were the matchmaker for your sister and P'Hill?
And did they end up dating?
Dude.
If they were actually together,
it'd be easier for me to move on.
So if they liked each other,
why didn't they end up dating?
Okay.
Just tell me when you're ready.
Now, I kinda understand
why you're not opening up your mind.
And has he ever brought up your sister
when you guys talk?
No. Nothing. Like nothing happened.
What about your sister?
Oh.
I haven't talked to her for so long as well.
And when you were in high school,
did he give you any signs or hints?
To let you know that he likes you?
Not really.
He's always nice...
and kind to everyone.
Everyone?
And can you move on?
I think I can...
Then...
just forget it.
You don't have to care.
If he doesn't take it serious with you,
he will stop eventually.
But maybe...
he might suddenly want to commit with you.
There's no commiting or anything.
No way.
I think you need the time to tell you.
If you can move on from him,
then you don't have to care.
Right.
Christmas.
Ter.
Let's go.
- Hey.
- I'm coming.
Let's just go down.
Come on.
You're talking too much.
I made my mind.
- Made your mind about what?
- About what I told you.
I have moved on from him.
So I will no longer care about him.
Even if I meet him at the union or in campus,
I will just ignore him.
Like I cannot see him at all.
And now he will stop talking to me.
So how does that sound?
What?
Why are you poking me?
Dude!
P’Hil lasked me to be the photographer for our university,
but I’m not confident at all
But he thinks you can do it.
That’s why he asked.
Please look after him.
I’ve never seen you care anyone this much before.
The owner of my watch is no longer wearing i
Oh can I have your LINE?
Are you P’Thunmild together or something?