If there's nothing else,
I'll go to bed now.
Sleep here.
Your friend is about to quit being a player.
You know that I have a crush on Hill, right?
If you made it with this relationship,
what would you like to tell this person?
I'll do my best to take care of you.
he's not like this with the others,
But why this one?
What time do you get off work?
Normally around 10pm.
But it depends on when P'Yha wants to close too.
P'Yha?
She's the owner of the restaurant.
You can go back with Hill.
He's gonna come take Ter home anyway.
Sure.
Call me if you need anything.
Thank you for dropping me off.
I gotta go.
Oh my word.
Ughh. I just missed it. Too bad.
What's going on, P'Yha?
The guy just now.
I came out to see your boyfriend.
I know that he's hot only just one look from behind.
My boyfriend?
And who's that?
It's P'Johan.
He's a friend of P'Hill.
Really?
Is he single?
I'm not sure about that.
Oh cause if he's single, then I can flirt with him, right?
Can I?
- I guess you can. Just flirting a little.
- Just kidding!
Anyways, but you do you have a picture of him?
I wanna see his face.
- I don't.
- Don't keep it to yourself. Come on.
I know just from the behind.
If I get to see his front--
What are you guys talking about?
The guy named Johan.
He dropped North off just now.
So handsome. I only got to see him from behind.
Oh...North's boyfriend?
Boyfriend!? So what's the truth?
Oh...not yet.
But in the future maybe?
For real!?
Do you have a picture?
I wanna see his face clearly.
- Yeah. There're so many on the page.
- Really? Let me see.
So hot!
Oh my gosh. Why is he so hot?
I told you. North is deepdown a badass.
I'm gonna go change.
Are you blushing?
- No.
- Haa!
He's so handsome.
- Here.
- Yeah?
- Can you save it for me?
- Sure.
- All of them?
Jhaja: How are you, North?
I'm good. What's up, Jah?
I'm about to work.
I have something I wanna talk to you.
Are you free tomorrow?
Let me see.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Are you sure?
Sure.
I better go sweet the floor.
- Sweet the floor.
- What sweet?
I'm gonna go get some plates.
There's no plate here.
No plates there. The plates are over there.
Over there.
These guys...
..are so weird.
Hi. I'm going home.
Bye bye.
You have something you haven't told me, right?
What?
You and P'Yha hide something from me.
Don't you think that I also know?
What? Nothing.
You're so smooth, huh?
You're a bad liar. You know that?
Alright. Fine.
Promise me that if I tell you,
you're not gonna be upset?
What is it?
Promise me first.
Promise. Fine. I promise.
Can you tell me now?
Hot news! Someone spotted P'Johan's rode a big bike to campus.
He's so hot, but there's also a mysterious guy with him.
Anyone know who he is?
Ugh. I wanna see P'Johan on a big bike with my own eyes.
Don't tell me that there were together last night
that's why they're there together?
Above comment is so harsh. I can't.
Hey hey. Today Tiger, our faculty's moon, also rode a big bike.
I wanna be on a bike with him too.
But you guys notice someone on the bike with him too? Weird...right?
Same jacket with the guy who was with P'Johan.
He's dating two guys? I really wanna know who is this guy?
Enough. Don't read further.
These are just comments on the internet.
Don't overthink about it please.
When have I ever overthought?
Who knows?
I'm afraid that you might be.
I shouldn't have let you read it.
I'm not really.
I'm not like what people say.
There's nothing between me and P'Johan.
Ger is also my friend.
Really?
Yeah.
Don't let me find you crying in the bathroom alone later.
You're the one who might be, not me.
Cause I'm worried. I don't want you to feel bad.
You're worried about me?
Stop being so pouty.
Forget about my stuff. What about you?
Are you alright?
I saw you were absent-minded today.
I kinda misunderstod P'Hill a bit.
About what?
Well...
about when I thought he left me.
What? Left you? There.
He's here. Left you how?
Go.
- Are you sure you'll be okay?
- Yeah.
Hi P'Hill.
P'Hill.
You need to talk to P'Jo for my friend.
Ter.
What did he do?
- Well--
- It's nothing.
Ter is just babbling.
Cause in Cute Boy and Girl page...
posted a picture of P'Johan.
And the comments are not so good.
Are you overthinking about it?
No not at all, P'Hill.
I will handle it.
If P'Jo makes my friend regret,
I won't let he dates him anymore.
Sure~
Let's go.
Are you sure you're okay?
- Are you crazy?
- I'm just curious.
Why can't I worry about you?
Dude look.
The page has apologized.
About the picture we posted earlier,
we have to apologize to everyone in the pictures.
Apologize for the misunderstanding.
Also for posting your pictures without asking for permission.
From now on, we will stop posting.
Thank you for supporting us.
Shit. They shut down their page.
That's good.
Yeah.
Good.
They post shitty thing
and made the whole internet talks bad about my friend.
Shut down for good.
Do you guys wanna stop by somewhere to buy stuff?
Don't feel bad.
I'm also ordered by someone to do this.
I'm fine. Up to North.
It's okay. I don't want any.
Umm..and how are you guys...
North and Johan?
Good.
But I haven't paid him anything.
Don't rush.
I think he doesn't even remember...
how much does North owe him.
He doesn't?
But he keeps adding more debt for me.
Just pay him back when you can.
He's adding more everyday.
Right?
Why are you calling me here?
Did you drop him off?
Yeah.
Don't tell me
you want me here just to ask that?
When are you gonna use all the money?
Stop transferring me.
Are you buying him a car or something?
Do you think he has a driver license?
I was being sarcastic.
I already asked him.
He doesn't want anything.
You're very good at spending money.
But please be nice to him too.
I'm trying.
I'm doing my best right now.
And shuting down that page was you, right?
Umm.
It's so nonsense.
I've seen they do it so many times.
Ter said if you break North's heart,
he won't let his friend date you anymore.
North is upset?
No.
He's not overthinking
and not even thinking about you either.
F*ck you.
You also send someone to check up on him at the bar, right?
But seems like he's hiding you.
Cause Ter also never told me anything.
Um.
Yeah I have someone there.
Why don't you just tell him that you know?
He doesn't want me to know, so I won't.
You're suddenly so behaved.
What about girls in your stock?
Have you talked to them?
Ter said he won't allow that,
if you're still talking to other people.
I'm taking care of it.
You chose North?
Um.
Since long time ago, yeah?
- Oh Jo.
- What?
He knows about my grandma, right?
He's really worried about you.
And when are you gonna tell him?
When we talk about my family,
I'm getting scared suddenly.
You mean...
He just disappeared
when his grandma got into an accident?
Um something like that.
But he just disappeared without telling you?
I think it's a little weird.
I also don't know.
I will just wait until he's ready to tell.
Oh North.
- Let me ask you something.
- What?
Do you...
have feelings for P'Johan?
You're in the mood to ask me that?
Cause normally you're my adviser.
I wanna be a good adviser to you too.
More like...
you're just wanna be nosy?
Yeah I kinda am.
But I saw you guys talk a lot.
Always out and about together.
Pick you up. Drop you off.
Also spent a night together.
Also borrow each other's clothes.
Hmm?
and why do you suddenly ask me this?
You normally only ship us.
Cause from what happened today, I'm not okay.
You're bad mouthed by people
when you actually did nothing.
Don't think too much.
And when I ship, I never told anyone.
I just wanna tease you that's all.
Just wanna get back at you.
Right. I'm not overthinking or anything,
Stop with that pouty face.
And...
Do you think he has feelings for you?
How am I supposed to know?
What kind of question is that?
Cause I see you guys are together a lot.
Cause you also notice
for P'Thun case.
It's not the same.
But there're times when I kinda doubt too.
What kind of a person is he?
If he likes me, but do all these to me?
It's not right.
Come on.
Maybe it's his style of flirting.
Dude.
What if he really likes you?
What are you gonna do?
What can I do?
I cannot do anything.
You really don't have any feelings for him?
I just...
...don't know.
I don't even know myself.
But if one day I really fall in love with someone,
you know that I am not a complicated person.
I will do my best to show them.
I think..
I also don't see P'Johan with anyone either.
He might really like you one day.
He lends you money
and always take you to places.
He does a lot for you though.
Why don't you try to open your heart for him?
There's nothing wrong with that.
Drawing club.
See you this evening, North.
- Hey North!
- Ghost. Ghost.
What are you doing here alone?
Ter and phoon are in class.
I don't wanna be at my dorm.
What about you?
Drawing again?
Do you think drawing will hlelp ease my mind?
Forget it.
It actually does help.
It will help you concentrate.
You have something on your mind?
Yeah a bit.
Do you wanna borrow my tools?
I've never seen you drawn anything
since you joined the club
Better not.
I think I will just eat something
and that will ease my mind.
I should just watch you draw.
You are pretty good at it.
I will continue my drawing then.
Umm.
I shouldn't compliment you huh.
Cause now you're drawing.
Hey, I'm gonna get going now.
You have a class?
Um.
I will go buy some drink first. I still have time.
Okay.
- See you.
- Bye.
Don't scare the ghost here.
Just kidding.
- You're gonna be okay alone?
- Um.
What are you doing there?
Filming a music video?
Where's Nao?
He's buying some drink out front.
I have something to show you.
So damn cute.
What do you mean cute?
He looks like he's gonn eat you alive.
Cute like a kitty showing their claws.
Let me ask you something.
What?
When you like someone?
What does it feel like?
You sound like...
you've never liked anyone before?
I have.
I just don't understand.
What makes someone like someone so much?
Like what you have now.
You just like them.
Like who they are.
Their characters.
Their look, their behavior and all the stuff.
It's...
he's born to make me fall for it.,
You ever heard of...
'it's more than just a type' concept.?
You're madly in love too.
Why? Do you like someone?
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hey what?
North!
Let's go to the class.
Let's go.
Where?
To class.
We don't have the combine section.
Why can't I go to your class?
- No, you can't.
- Yes.
- Let me go.
- Sure.
- Let me come with you.
- Ow.
- Let me go with you, Nao.
- Don't follow me.
That's it for today.
Don't forget to go home and study.
Especially you. Please pay attention.
You might fail.
Yes sir.
I'm here.
I will wait for you at the cafe in front of your faculty.
Hey I gotta go. Jah is waiting for me.
Wait what did you say?
Jah is waiting for me.
Wait for what?
She came to see me.
She needs to talk to me about something.
Talk about what?
I don't think you need to talk to her.
No, I have to.
She came all the way for me.
She's probably wanna get back together with you.
I think she knows that at the end, there's only you who treats her well.
Probably not.
What if she really asks you to go back to her?
You can't go back to her.
Don't you remember what she did to you?
Right. I'm not going back to her.
I know you won't, but your heart maybe not?
Right. I won't.
I will just go talk to her and go home. See you.
Gotta go.
You guys think he's okay?
I don't think so.
Do you wanna order anything?
No, I won't be here long.
I never saw you in a uniform like this before.
So unfamiliar.
Um. Probably.
You cut your hair?
Um. I did cut it a little.
Does it look weird?
No, it suits you.
Thank you.
You need to talk to me with something?
Well...
I already broke up with Temp.
He cheated on me like you said.
You punched him because of this reason, right?
It's already in the past.
Let's not talk about it.
I'm sorry
for not believing you in the first place.
There's only you who wish the best for me.
Um... Never mind.
I heard that Temp also transferred to other university.
What did you do to him?
A person like me?
How can I do anything to anyone?
Most that I can do is to punch him.
If it's not you, then who did?
North...
I know that this is bad to say it...
but...
do you...
wanna start thing over again between us?
Can you give me another chance?
Please don't.
It's better this way.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect you to be this cold to me.
I get it.
If you don't have anything else to talk, I'll go.
Oh hey how come you're here?
I followed you.
So what..?
She wants to get back together with you?
Are you going to?
I understand.
Eventhough we don't want you to do that,
but it's your life.
I'm not gonna do that.
Oh.
So what's the matter then?
I...
just feel weird.
Previously...
I couldn't bear just to think about her...
but when she asked to get back together,
I actually rejected her.
I don't think it's weird.
That means
you don't have feelings for her anymore.
Or...
there's someone who you have more feelings for.
Sit sit.
It's time to reveal your student mentor.
If you already know your mentors,
please get up and go see them.
Do you know yours?
Not yet.
Me neither.
Me too.
Shit. What are we gonna do?
Please, those who got punished, move to the side.
Yeah.
What the hell is that, Ter?
Eggplant devil?
Yeah. It's so itchy because of these leaves.
The eggplant. Can I take a picture with you?
- Me?
- Yes.
Sure.
- Both of you also.
- Oh ok.
- Thank you.
- Ter.
- Huh?
- Your doctor is here.
How come you’re here?
Can I take a picture with you?
Sure.
3 2 1
He’s so handsome.
You’re not jealous at all?
Having a hot boyfriend like that?
No! We’re not boyfriends yet.
If I were you, I would be so damn jealous.
Thank you.
P’Hill.
I’m hungry already. Let’s go eat.
Sure. I will take you.
Yeah.
Let’s go.
What?
What about us?
He’s gone. You’ll be his substitute.
- Stand there. Let them take pictures.
- I might outshine him.
No.
Nong eggplant is so cute.
Stop teasing me.
I’m not.
I’m telling you the truth.
You have so many rashes.
Really?
I'll put some medicine on for you.
Sure.
Do not scratch.
It will get worse if you do.
This reminds me of that time…
When?
Well…
you used to clean the wound for me just like this.
Be careful.
Are you alright?
- I’m sorry.
- Are you okay? Are you hurt?
- I’m fine.
- Are you sure?
Yeah.
I will go talk to that motorcycle first.
Yes.
I’m sorry. Are you okay?
- Are you hurt somewhere?
- I’m fine.
What about Ter?
I’m fine.
But you’re bleeding.
Oh it’s just a little. I’m fine.
Do you wanna go clean the wound first?
Sure. I will clean it at home.
Where are we going?
Sit here. I will clean it for you.
Sure.
Does it hurt?
A little.
I’m so sorry.
And thank you so much for saving me.
You’re welcome.
Were you about to go home?
Yes, I am.
You go home so late.
I have to work at the library.
That’s why I go home a little late.
And you also. Why do you go home so late?
I have to study with my friends.
Wow.
That’s nice.
You are so hard-working.
Which class are you in?
Class 7.
Class 7...
You’re also a science student too?
Yes.
Is it difficult?
Kinda.
Especially those subjects that I’m not good at.
It’s even more difficult for me.
Which one that you're not good at?
There are…
Physics, Chemistry, Biology,
and also Math.
Aren’t those main science subjects?
They are.
What about you?
Any subjects that you like in particular?
Me?
Nothing in particular.
How's your senior year?
Is it tough?
Yes when it’s close to the exams.
Oh.
That must be real tough for you.
And…
do you have any faculty in mind?
Which one that you would like to study?
I…
am not sure either.
Which one do you think suits me?
I don’t know.
Depends on what you’re good at.
Oh.
I think I know which one suits you.
I think...
you should become a doctor.
Really?
You know what you're doing.
Also very good at small talk.
Come on. Almost done.
Yes.
You're right.
And now you really become a doctor.
Doesn't matter it's back then or today...
you still make me worry as usual.
You're such a complaining doctor.
See.
You need to let me look after you forever.
Sure.
P'Hill.
Yes?
I need to ask you something.
Sure.
So...
about back then...
when you disappeared from me.
Can you tell me what happened?
I don't know where to start.
About...
your grandmother, right?
How do you know?
My friends told you?
Please don't be mad at them.
They're so worried about you.
Please don't be mad at them. Please please.
I'm not.
That day was when everything started.
Ter.
Yes? What's up?
Me and my friends will have a little party at my place.
Come join us.
Can I?
Yes, of course.
Ahh.
But I will have to pick up Christ first.
Can I take her with me?
Sure.
Okay.
Just a blink of an eye,
you're now graduating.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're here.
Hello, P'Hill.
Hi Christmas.
Here. This is my present.
Don't forget me when you're in university.
Thank you.
What about you?
Anything for me?
Yes actually.
But I will give it to you later.
Umm okay. Come on in.
Cheers.
Yayy~
Christ. Would you like to try?
I will drink for her.
Let's take pictures.
Come on.
So cute. Here.
So cute.
I'm gonna use the restroom.
I'll be back.
P'Hill.
Yes?
A present for you.
Thank you.
I will keep it really well.
Yeah.
P'Hill. Please don't forget me.
I won't.
I promise.
Promise.
P'.
I...
I actually...
have had a crush on you for a very long time.
You're mine now.
Ter.
- Dad.
- Shut up!
Just discuss this at home.
Sir.
It's my fault.
Really?
Dad don't.
- Stop!
- Go. Go home.
P'Hill.
Let's go.
Where is that boy?
His dad took him home.
It was you, right?
What did I do?
Are you saying that
his father just dropped by out of the blue?
I thought you said...
you're gonna have a graduation party
with your friends?
- How come that boy was here?
- Why can't I invite a junior friend?
A junior friend?
You brought him here
to do some nasty stuff under this roof.
How dare you say that?
You said you're gonna apply for medical school
and get in with the 1st rank?
Why are you wasting your time...
- with that boy?
- They're not relevant.
I will get in with the 1st rank score for you anyway.
We will see.
But to punish you,
you're now grounded.
Cannot go out without someone with you.
You're not allowed to use your phone.
Cannot contact that boy or go see him ever again.
Grandpa!
But if you resisted,
I cannot promise you...
...that the boy is gonna live his life peacfully.
Sir.
Misses got hit by a car.
She's now at the hospital.
Grandma...
She'll be okay.
She'll wake up soon.
Oh mom already finished her work in Singapore.
I guess she'll arrive this evening.
What about grandpa?
He won't eat. He cannot sleep.
He's with grandma all day.
He won't go anywhere either.
Oh and I talked to grandpa already.
We might have to take grandma back to Chiang Mai.
Can you live here alone?
I will go with you guys.
What about university?
I'll just go to university there.
About the promise that you made with him
regarding the 1st class score,
just forget it.
Don't think about it too much.
No.
I will make it happen.
I'll talk to grandpa for you.
About the grounding,
he's probably busy with grandma.
He won't have the time to pay attention to you.
Uncle.
Yes?
Can you please take me to this one place?
But he already ordered me to take you straight home.
Please help me for once.
Sure.
Ter.
Sir.
Is Ter home?
Why are you  here?
Go back.
But...
I need to talk to him.
He doesn't wanna see you.
Sir but...
Just go.
Remember this...
you're not welcomed here.
Don't let me see your face again.
Go!
Sir!
Let's just go.
If your grandpa doesn't see you at home,
we'll be in trouble.
Dad never told me you came to see me.
I tried to contact you so many times,
but you didn't answer me.
Until I thought you really don't wanna see me anymore.
Cause before that...
you just disappeared.
I thought you dumped me.
I would never leave you, Ter.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for misunderstanding.
I never knoew that you were gone cause...
you were grounded.
and you grandma too.
What about you?
Your dad looked so angry that day.
Well...
Yes.
We got into a big fight after we got home.
After that, I rarely speak to my dad.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's not your fault entirely.
It's me...
that I had no idea what you had to go through.
I actually never really told you the truth.
I just left things unclear until today.
But from now on...
I won't let go of your hands anymore.
Me too.
Where is my phone?
Where is it?
Are you looking for this?
You never took care of your stuff.
I dropped it?
Thank you.
Shoul I give it back to you or not?
Can I have my phone back?
I'm going home.
Give it to me.
I'm not fooling around.
I'm not also
- P'!
- I told you already. Don't let me have the chance.
What are you doing!?
Stop!
Why are you playing hard to get?
Hey!
- You think you can get away from me?
- Hey! Let go of me! What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I'm gonna make you mine.
Let see...
whether you will have a smart mouth again this time?
Hey!
What!?
Step back.
Turn around.
Put your hands on the wall.
P'Jo.
Take care of the rest.
I told you not to work here anymore.
I can get up myself.
North.
Don't be stubborn with me.
Why you're so nice to me?
Because I like you.
Can I kiss you?
I won't let you work anymore.
Please let me. I still have a lot to pay you back .
If you kiss me I give you 1,000 Baht.
But if you give me more than that...
Sir, your grandpa needs to meet you now.