I'll leave from here then.
- P' Hi.
- Hi.
- See you.
- Yeah see you.
Come here.
- I was gossipping about you.
- How come you're here?
Did you wait for long?
The professor just released me too.
He's here now. Shall we go?
Let's go.
Hey wait wait.
Where are we going?
What? To drink.
To celebrate for the two of you.
Did you know that I almost cried
when I heard that the two of you are together?
How can we not celebrate?
Do you wanna go?
We haven't seen each other for awhile,
so we wanna hang out.
I'm fine with everything.
But it's fine, if you wanna hangout among friends.
Hey.
How can we go without you?
We're celebrating for the two of you.
How can you let Jo go alone?
Yeah right. Let's go drink.
Go go. Let's get some drinks.
You two are finally together.
North...did you know that Frank and I
are one of your first shippers?
You're exaggerating.
Hey, I'm telling the truth.
You know how it was back then.
- I was so sad like it was my own story.
- You liked him.
When he had a girlfriend...
and was soooo in love with her~
You made my friend really heart broken.
So drink this!
Hey don't pressure him.
Yeah do it for the sake of what you did to Jo.
Yeah.
What about you, Jo?
You're not gonna drink?
I have to drive.
Then North can.
Cheers.
Just drink a little.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
Bottom ups.
Give me that.
You're so rushed.
Finish that first.
And follow with this.
Yeah.
Cheers.
Hey. You almost spill it.
Cheers then.
You're so drunk already.
No, I'm not.
Oh Jo, you're out tonight!?
Wow. You're acting so cold.
Unlike when you were with me back then.
I miss you, Jo.
So he's just gonna do that.
Sitting on him now.
Just like that.
Why...
are you so hot?
You are mine only.
Yes.
I'm all yours.
Jo!
- P'. I think you should go.
- What's going on?
You better go.
Let's go.
Let's just go home first. See you. Bye bye.
Why do you have someone else?
Are you normally like this when you're drunk?
Cause I'm jealous.
Why are you...
so cute like this when you're drunk?
North.
I think he's falling asleep.
Um. I know. Long ago.
- I will go home first then.
- Um.
Drive safe, my friend.
- See you.
- Good luck.
Bye bye.
P'Johan.
I'm not the jealous type.
But when it's you...
I don't anyone to look at you at all.
Can you just don't have anyone else?
Can you?
You don't want me too?
You have me only.
You can't have an eye on other people, just on me.
You know what to do right?
if you wanna ask me for something?
You're mine only. Only mine.
Nobody can mess with what's mine.
Do you realize that you're drunk?
I'm not drunk.
This way.
Answer my question!
Are you mine only?
Yes.
I'm yours only.
Why? Are you shy?
I didn't initiate this last night.
It was P'James. He forced me to drink.
So you just...
Stop talking.
Oh P'Johan.
Are you free this coming break?
So...
My mom actually invites you to visit my home.
Yeah sure.
Well then...
do you wanna visit my home as well?
Can I?
You can.
But I don't want you to see my mom.
Why? Is she strict?
No.
And...are we gonna spend the night there?
Probably.
Are you gonna spend the night at your place or mine?
Yours.
Why are you blushing?
Enough.
That's enough.
It's been so many semesters,
I still cannot draw properly.
If I'm not better,
I swear I will switch to other clubs.
You need to practice.
And when am I gonna excel?
- Hey Ter.
- Amen.
- What are you guys doing?
- Eating maybe.
Where? Is there anything for me to eat?
What do you think we're doing?
We're drawing while waiting for you.
What? But you said eating.
Oh I haven't seen Foam around lately.
How dare he sign up
but rarely be at the club?
I think that one is with a girl.
- Hmm?
- Oh North.
Come here.
Sit down.
You and P'Johan are official?
- Um.
- Heyyy~
I wish your relationship to last very long.
Awww.
Another one sold.
You're jealous huh?
- Ter.
- Hmm?
- The cat is jealous.
- Wow.
Woww. The cat is jealous.
The cat is so jealous. Wow.
What cat? Why the cat?
Cause your face looks like a cat.
A sleepy one too.
Let me ask you. Really.
How many hours do you sleep in a day?
- Do you ever rest?
- I do sleep, North. This is my normal face.
- This is your normal face?
- Yeah.
Then you'll be forever looking sleepy.
Hey Dao. Did you bring the cards?
I wanna see my fortune.
Huh? Again!?
Again what? I haven't done it for a very long time.
I wanna check my faith
...like how's it going to be this time around?
I might win the lottery.
Ohh...did you win the last time?
You are talking too much.
Please Dao~
Do fortune telling for me.
Please. Please.
North. You'll have some luck with money lately.
Hey I'm gonna be rich. I'm gonna win the lottery.
But if you said lottery, I'm not gonna believe you
cause you only win once in your life.
You always burst my bubble.
Cat.
You try it.
Cat. Open a card.
- Open a card.
- Do it.
Fine.
Do it. Do it.
- ***
You should make some merit now.
Hey why? His fortune is that bad?
No. Just kidding.
Dao! You scared me.
Your love game looks good.
Hey! The cat is gonna be in love.
He's gonna have a partner.
He's gonna be a cat in love.
How?
How what? It's nothing.
You're making this up.
- Are you lying?
- So am I gonna be rich or not?
Oh Dao.
Why is your name Dao even you are a male?
Oh that's because my parents used to make a wish
from shooting stars that if they conceives a child,
they're gonna name the baby 'Daotok'  regardless of the baby's gender.
(Daotok = shooting stars in Thai)
Why did they make a wish from shooting stars?
What if your parents make a wish froma shrine,
your name is not gonna be 'Phraphum'?
You're asking such a stupid question.
Yeah just like that.
- But shooting stars are a bunch of dirty rocks on fire?
- You cannot name a baby with that, can you North?
You can do it English. Mete...
Meteor, right?
Southern ghost or whatever.
(It's a Thai myth name for shooting stars)
Who's gonna have that kind of name?
And why is your name 'North'?
Cause my mom said North means north region in Thai
I'm also confused why didn't she just named me Nuer.
(Nuer = north in Thai)
She probably wanted to sound international.
What about you Ter and Phoon?
Easter is from Easter holiday.
My mom loves it when she was traveling.
For my sister too, Christmas as in the holiday.
For me...
they just made it goes with my sister's name.
Hey you've got a sister?
What's her name?
Torfhun.
Torfhun?
How does that go together?
Well...
Phoon and Fhun.
Sounds similar.
Phoon and Fhun?
How are these two similar?
It is. Just go with it.
- Oh yeah it is. I think it is.
- Um.
Oh I'm hungry.
- Shall we go find some food to eat?
- Hey.
- You're just hungry out of the blue.
- Yeah.
We opened 2 cards only.
Cause you guys kept talking too much.
I'm hungry now. Shall we?
You're gonna be rich soon,
then you should pay.
Rich your ass.
I'll be poor again after I pay for my meal.
The card says you're gonna be rich.
Then you should pay.
- Yeah. Let's go.
- Yayy~
- You pay. Come on. You're gonna be rich soon.
- No.
Dude. Ask him.
Oh...
I will do it myself.
We will be tutoring tonight.
North is also coming. Wanna join us?
- Wanna join?
- Where though?
At P'Jo's coffee shop.
Do you wanna come with us?
Umm sure. I will join you guys.
Good. Do you want me to pick you up?
It's fine. I will go there myself.
Just send me the location.
Are you sure?
Cat.
Are you leaving?
I have to go.
What is up with him?
How long have you been here?
For a while already.
I'm sorry. We just got off work.
It's fine. We can wait.
Do you wanna have anything else?
You guys go ahead. We're full already.
- Do you want something?
- No.
Jeen.
It was good. So full.
If it's good, then why didn't you finish it?
You need to eat more vegetables,
you're still young.
Another bite. Come on.
Please.
Come with me.
It doesn't taste good.
Good?
Where are they going?
Why are you staring like that?
Can't I just look?
Jeen.
Ok fine. I'll stop.
I just wanna look at how cute he is.
You make him obsessed with you.
He's so cute.
Hey! I also cannot touch him?
No.
Fine~
He's protective of you. I guess.
He waited for 3 years
And why are you here exactly?
I drove past, so I just wanna stop by.
Oh...
I should introduce myself first.
I'm Johan's mom.
Hello ma'am.
You're North, right?
Yes.
You two are dating, right?
I was so happy when I found out.
He used to come home
looking sad and depressed everyday.
But nowadays...
I'm so relieved.
Hey North.
Did you also know...
that he's been working hard for you?
Huh..yes?
He said...
he wanted to be someone who you can rely on.
When he accepted his father's proposal,
I was shocked.
Cause I have someone
I need to look after.
Oh.
On my. Too bad.
I have to go. I'm so sorry.
No worries.
Let's have a meal together sometimes, okay?
Can I have a hug?
No.
Hey. I'm just so happy.
- Can I get a hug from him?
- No.
Fine. No hug.
I will see you later, son.
I have to go.
- Sure.
- Bye bye.
You're always like this.
That's why I don't want you to see him.
Yeah~.
I know that you're protective of him.
Hey.
Phoon will be here soon.
- North.
- Hmm?
I need your advice.
About what?
About P'Fah and Phoon.
What about them?
I don't know whether I just overthink or not.
But I feel like there's something up between them..
..from what I've observed.
What do you think?
To be honest,
- I think there's something weird going on too.
- Right!?
Nothing.
Right?
I didn't just think for myself.
Or you and I are overthinking?
Why don't we just ask cat?
I wouldn't dare to ask.
Why not?
Phoon always look sad when he sees P'Fah.
But it's not only when he looks at P'Fah though.
I think Phoon is a kind of person...
that he likes to keep everything to himself.
Umm..
Or he has something in his mind
that he can't tell anyone?
But if he doesn't wanna tell,
then we shouldn't ask him.
Yeah I know.
But I'm just worried about my friend.
- Yeah.
- What should we do?
- Oh he's calling me.
-Speaking of the devil.
Hello? What's up?
Ter. I don't know where I am.
What? You're lost again?
I just sent you the location.
Just look at the map. Where are you on the map?
North is also there?
North. Help me.
How are you getting here? Motorcycle?
Yeah I borrowed from a friend.
Ughh. Cat is riding a motorcycle?
That's way too dangerous.
Ter. What should I do?
Hey guys. It's raining. Help.
Raining!?
Yeah just give me a min.
I'm trying to figure it out.
What should we do?
Is something wrong?
It's Phoon.
He's lost and riding a motorcycle.
It's raining heavily too.
Ask him to send the location.
We can pick him up.
Who's picking me up?
Err....
Fah.
I will pick him up.
Ter. Come with me.
Yes. Yes.
I will go pick you up.
- Hurry and come back.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Fah.
What?
I'm one who needs to ask you
what's going on?
Yeah.
I just don't wanna be ignored anymore.
North.
Dude.
Hey you're soaking wet.
Like a kitten fell in the water.
- Hey are you cold?
- Here here. I will take care of you.
Sit. Sit.
Thank you, P'Hill.
Sit down first.
Do I have to put so much effort to tutor here?
I told you to pullover, and wait until the rain stops.
I was afraid of getting lost.
It's really dark there too.
Life is tough on you, huh?
The nature is punishing you.
Hey what's that, cat?
Stop going through my stuff.
Hey. Meds book?
Huh!?
Are you gonna re-applying for meds school?
Um.
Huh!?
If you got in, then you'll become our freshman then?
I guess so.
- Hey~
- If I got in.
So you're not gonna be with us anymore then?
Hey.
But this is cool, cat.
I think you can do it. Keep going man!
Thanks.
- Let's go home.
- Sure.
P'Hill.
Hmm?
When you said,
you'll take me out of town during the break...
I know now...
where I'd like to go.
Where would you like to go?
Home.
I wanna go back home when exams are over.
Can I go with you?
Of course.
I would like to you see my grandma as well.
After visiting your home, let's visit my grandma too.
But if you don't wanna go, it's fine.
It's not like that, P'Hill.
But...
are you sure I can go there?
I'm sure.
My grandma really wants to see you.
Really?
Err what about...
your grandpa?
Sure.
I will go.
Thank you for dropping me off.
This is your last exam,
stay focused okay?
Don't stress. Understand?
Sure.
I have to go.
Bye.
We're done with the exams!!
Woohoo~
Where are you guys going during the break?
I wanna travel, but still don't know where.
What about you, North?
Do you have any plans with P'Johan?
Me? I'm going back home.
What? You're not gonna ask him to travel somewhere?
Hey why not?
You don't wanna be on a honeymoon?
Heyyy.
There's no such thing.
I wanna travel. Do you wanna join me Sket?
Huh!? You and me again?
- You two again?
- Always.
Dude, I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Let's go.
Hey you guys go ahead.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- See you.
Nao. Wait up.
Hey.
What's up?
Ter, are you done with your exam?
Um. I am.
What's going on?
The break is about to begin,
don't you wanna come have a meal with me before leaving?
I'm sorry. I'm already out with P'Hill.
Umm~ Understood.
- My love for you is an old love.
- What?
The break is so short, I will see you again soon.
Stop being pouty.
Right. Have fun on your break.
I'm so sick of someone being in love.
Stop being sarcastic.
You should go see your Johan.
Oh right. I have P'Johan.
Then I better go see him.
- See you dude. Enjoy your break.
- Yeah. Bye.
Okay. Bye.
You're still working?
Um. It's urgent.
You can go to bed first.
No.
I wanna be here.
You're stubborn.
You're so attached to me now.
Do you realize that?
I know. I'm so attached.
Oh P'Jo.
Can we travel during the break?
You wanna travel?
But if you have work to do,
then it's fine.
Where do you wanna go?
I will take you.
Are you sure?
Then...
after we visit our homes,
let's go to the beach.
Sure.
Really!?
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Nothing.
P'!!
I've been waiting for you!
- Hello, P'Hill.
- Hi.
You looks so much more handsome
since I last saw you.
If I didn't know you before, I would think that you're a celebrity.
By the way...
are you guys officially dating?
By the way you react, I guess you are.
For how long?
Nobody tells me this.
I'm so jealous.
I wanna have a handsome boyfriend like this.
That's enough, Christ.
You're being shy again. That's so annoying.
Let's go inside.
Mom and dad are waiting.
When she found out that you're coming,
she went to the market since 5am.
My son.
- I miss you.
- If you miss me, why haven't you been visiting?
Cause I've been busy.
University is so tough and tiring.
Really?
Has my son been paying attention to all the classes?
I have. My grades are also great.
If you don't believe me, ask P'Hill.
Hello ma'am.
Hi. I haven't seen you for so long, Hill.
You're more handsome everyday.
You must have a lot of people
wanting to date you, right?
They can't. He's taken.
His boyfriend is right here.
Huh!?
Are you guys together?
Yes.
What? These two?
Am I missing something?
Yeah right.
Or when he came to help around here often...
was because he wanted to date P'Ter?
Right. He was here every weekend.
Oh yeah.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Um.
You two are dating?
Er...
Yes.
Um.
I hate your facial expression and your gaze...
like you're never afraid of anything
...since back then.
Why do you have so many issues with Hill?
I don't have any issue with him.
Stop acting so cool, apologize to our son.
Babe. Fine. Fine.
I'm sorry, son.
What!?
You're still acting like a child
even when you're a grown man.
I'm not a grown man. I'm still a kid.
Then you can't date anymore, right?
Fine. I'm a grown man.
These two...
You guys used to be so tight-lipped.
Suddenly, very understanding of each other.
I'm not.
Really?
Carry on. I will go prep dinner.
Sure.
- I will go help mom.
- Sure.
He stopped being mad at you long time ago.
He said he shouldn't have said harsh words to you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I have been worried.
From now on, you don't have to worry anymore.
Yeah.
I've been worried for so long.
I'm afraid he won't accept me.
I'm afraid he would still be mad at me.
This is nice.
I think your parents are so nice.
Really?
Er...
I think I better go help mom.
I don't wanna be a thirdwheel here.
Christ.
I think mom doesn't recognize that you're P'New.
Yeah right.
Let's go.
Let's go sit.
I will make you cocoa drink.
It's here.
The best cocoa drink in the world.
I haven't had your cocoa for a long time.
I miss it.
Try it.
But...
I'm not making it for P'New, my old friend anymore.
I made...
for P'Hill...my boyfriend.
Is it good?
P'Hill!
Is it 1good?
Hey where are you going?
What are you writing?
Let me see.
It's so good.
That's nice to hear.
I will make you this drink everyday from now on.
Okay?
Forever me, okay?
Yes.
Forever you.
Thank you.
I think you're too skinny.
Everything looks so good.
- I miss home cooking so much.
- If you miss it, then eat up.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- P'Ter.
- Hmm?
You're here only a few days only.
Please stay longer next time you're home.
Um sure.
Yayy~
How's your school?
It's good, dad.
I'm taking all the basic subjects right now.
Luckily, I have P'Hill to help tutoring me.
That's nice. Someone tutors for you.
And also takes good care of you.
- Yeah right.
- Christ.
- Enough.
- Why don't you give P'Hill some of those?
I will. Of course.
Thank you.
Wow.
Can you tell us?
Who confessed the love first?
- Christ.
- Wow~
- Yeah right!
- We also wanna know, right?
I also want to know.
Can I be the one who tells?
- Oh! That's good.
- Good.
I'm all ears.
- Err...back then...
- Here~
Hey. I wanna hear him talk.
Is it yummy?
Food at my home is the best.
Bye bye.
I haven't had enough time with you.
I know. Me neither.
I don't wanna leave.
I have to say goodbye now.
Yeah.
Please look after him for us.
He' a bit cray cray.
- Don't take it seriously.
- Dad!
Don't worry. I will do my best.
Um.
Don't be stubborn with him too.
Sure.
- Please, look after him.
- It's my pleasure.
No worries, mom.
- We have to go.
- Yeah.
- Can I have a hug?
- Come here,
Take care of yourself, son.
Sure. You too.
Gotta go.
Bye bye.
I don't wanna go.
- I have to go.
- Bye bye, son.
- Safe trip.
- Sure. Thank you.
Bye.
- I don't wanna go.
- Have a safe trip.
Sure.
P'Ter.
Hmm?
Send me lots of pictures, okay?
Um sure.
Be good in school.
Ok, I will.
Bye bye. I really have to go.
- I'm leaving.
- Bye bye.
-  See you.
I'm still missing him.
Bye bye, Ter.
When will I get to see him again?
Mom, I wanna have some cake.
- Let's go.
- What cake?
- Coconut cake.
- Okay. Let's go.
- You want some cocoa too?
- Sure.
Are you nervous?
Yeah. Why I wouldn't be?
Seeing your grandpa again.
It's alright. I will be with you.
Yeah.
Hello.
This is your boyfriend?
Let me see. Come closer.
Yes.
What's your name?
Easter.
Sounds familiar.
Is this the kid?
I was rooting for you.
You know me?
I know.
He used to tell me so many of your stories.
That he had a crush on a kid.
But he couldn't approach or talk to you.
I didn't know what to do either.
Grandma.
You don't have to be shy anymore.
- Is this true?
- Yes.
He was so shy back then.
I didn't know how am I gonna help him.
He always said that you're cute here and there.
When you eat, you're cute.
When you laugh, you're also cute.
He couldn't approach you.
I was so hopeless.
But congratulations.
Thank you.
How are you, grandma?
I'm better, but I still cannot walk properly.
But it's fine, grandpa is taking care of me.
I stopped working now.
That's good, so you won't stress and put it on the kids.
Hill has a issue because of you.
You shouldn't bring that up again.
Now, you're regretting what you did.
I have to apologize on behalf of grandpa.
It's fine.
You don't have to apologize.
I'm also old. I wanna see my only nephew be happy.
Hill has grown up differently from other kids.
I would never ask for anything else, except for him to never be like the old days.
If grandpa does anything to you again, tell me.
I will handle him.
Hill.
- Yes, grandma?
- Come in fornt of me please.
Here. I have a gift for you.
I don't have anything much for you.
I also gave your dad a necklace like this.
Here.
Give it to someone you love.
That's why your mom has it.
You mean...
I think this necklace suits him.
And don't take it back from him.
Grandma!
Thank you.
Grandma. P'Hill.
Why are you running? You could fall.
Grandpa wants me to bring you guys this.
I was wondering where were you.
You went for some snacks.
No, I did not.
Grandpa wants me to prepare this for grandma.
Let me see.
Let me try whether it's good or not.
Try it.
Good?
You try it.
Thank you.
Here...your turn.
Good?
So you can answer it yourself.
A bit too sweet.
Then you need to tell grandpa. Don't tell me.
This is your room?
I actually never liked this room.
When I first moved here,
my grandma was still in a coma.
I was always grounded in this room.
I had to study for the exam...
in this room.
Didn't go anywhere.
I was always in this room.
But now that I have you here with me,
I feel like...
it's feels so much better in here.
It would be nice
if I could be here with you back then.
So you didn't have to face that alone.
Buti it's all good now.
Seeing you here with me,
already fulfills how much I've missed you in the past.
But if we have to be apart again,
I don't think I can handle that.
P'Hill.
Me either.
You can't run away from me again.
I promise.
You still have it?
What is it?
The wishing bottle
I gave you at the last orientation.
I do. It's important for me.
This is nice. It took a lot of time to do this.
You did all the foldings?
Yes..
It took forever.
Had to practice for awhile.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
Hey Jo.
You actually brought him.
- Hello.
Let's go inside.
Everyone is waiting in the living room.
Let's go.
Are you nervous?
To be honest, yes. I'm super nervous.
You'll be fine.
If you said so.
Hello.
This is the one?
Don't stare at him for too long.
Our son is very protective.
Come. Come sit with me.
I cannot see you clearly.
This is the kid that you told me about?
Yes, mom.
You live nearby?
Yes.
He's got you under control, huh?
It's good that you have someone to monitor.
I'm tired of tracking you.
I told you.
If you're tired to do, then stop tracking me.
You're still arrogant like usual.
That's not the only thing that I'm good at.
Again. These two.
Never stayed true to yourself.
You are actually..
glad about this, right?
I have to go.
What!?
You only get to talk to him for only a few mins.
Too bad  we have urgenet work.
So we didn't get to talk much.
Please come visit us again.
Sure, ma'am.
Let's go babe.
Yes.
Come give me a hug.
Jeen.
Just one hug.
See you later.
I have to go.
See you, son.
Bye.
Your family is so adorable.
I'm getting nervous to meet your family now.
Why do you have to be?
My family is nice.
Woah.
I still remember clearly
when your mom dragged your ears out of the internet cafe.
Let's go inside. Your grandma is waiting.
To be honest,
I used to drive pass your house a lot.
Never thought I would get to see the inside.
And it's actually more beautiful than
what I had imagined.
Mom.
You're here! I miss you so much.
Wait wait. I miss you.
Miss you so much!
- Have you eaten?
- Not yet. I'm waiting for you.
Hello ma'am.
Hi.
My mom wants me to give you these.
Thank you.
You guys actually didn't have to do this.
Miss you so much.
Let's go inside. It's too hot out here.
Let's go inside. It's cooler in there.
You're Johan, right?
- Can I just call you Jo?
- Yes.
You're a second year? Then you're his senior.
Is he stubborn?
He is.
Like really stubborn.
Hey! Me? Stubborn?
You're making that up. Here.
He's always been stubborn since he was a little kid.
You need to scold him a lot.
If you don't,
he's not gonna listen to you.
Sure.
He's always been stubborn, huh?
Yeah, since he was young. Always got in a fight.
Others wanted to fight him.
Sometimes he started the fight.
Always been like that when he was young.
That's why..
How did you two meet?
- He actually got into a fight at a bar.
- Hey P'!
Don't be a snitch.
You did something again!?
You always hide it from me.
Never told me anything.
It's a long time ago, mom.
Mom. I wanna eat now.
You always do like this
when I caught that you got in trouble.
Let's go. I'm hungry.
I miss your cooking. Go. Go.
Yeah. You're always like this.
-  Please. I want to eat your Pak kad jor.
- You never told me anything.
Cook for me first, mom.
When he was young,
he was the leader of the gang around here.
Used to cause trouble for me to solve everyday.
People around here know.
Oh and this is not it.
I almost forgot to tell you.
North is someone who likes to shows off his partner.
Ugh. That's enough mom.
Really? And what did he tell you?
He said
'My boyfriend is so handsome, mom'
Really?
- That's not it. There're more.
- Mom!
He called me and said
'he's so nice to me like this and that.'
'What should I do?'
'North loves him. North likes him a lot'
'Did you know that he's the first person
that makes me wanna change and be a better person?'
'And I will also do better in studying.'
Mom. I won't tell you anything anymore.
Ughh. Just let me.
Why have you never told me that?
Yeah why not?
So he knows how you feel.
Let's eat. Let's eat.
Ughh. Why are you so shy?
Your face and your ears are all red.
I'm being honest. I didn't lie.
I'm telling P'Jo the truth
You're like that.
- Not done yet.
- You're the one who called me and told me all those.
What did you talk to my mom after the meal?
Gossiping about you.
It's nothing. I just asked for her permission to take you out of town.
Oh.
And are you okay with my family?
Of course.
But my mom seems to love you.
Probably more than she loves me.
What am I gonna do if she loves you more?
What about you?
Hmm?
Do you love me?
Why are you suddenly asking me that?
I do love you.
That's more than enough for me.
Why is Tiger calling me?
Put him on speaker.
What's up dude?
It's Nao. Nao.
What's wrong with Nao? Are you drunk?
No, I'm not.
What's going on?
Nao...
It's Nao.
- He's--
- Duennao. What the hell are you talking about?
Am I gonna find out today what do you want?
I don't wanna be like this.
I'm--
- What do you need?
- Oh hey P'.
You're also there?
That's nice. You two are together.
- What you actually need just tell me?
- Forget it.
Oh P'Jo.
North...
actually owes me money.
He blackmailed me for a hundred thousand.
Hundred thousand.
He threatened me.
Always threaten me about Nao. Same topic.
That's funny.
You're talking nonsense when you're drunk.
Nonsense what?
- What!?
- Hello? Sorry. Ger is too drunk.
Over Nao?
I guess so. He's wasted.
But I think it's nothing.
He probably just misunderstood.
Misunderstanding what?
Yeah I need to hang up.
Sorry to bug you man.
Yeah.
You borrowed his money?
You got me curious.
How scary were you when you threatened him..
..and got a hundred thousand?
Show me.
I didn't threaten him or anything.
I just asked him to buy me some drinks.
And why you've never asked me?
I won't ask you.
I will just steal..
...when you're asleep.
I will steal your wallet and disappear without any trace.
- Disappear?
- Yeah gone.
You won't be able to find me.
If you want my wallet, then take it.
I can give you anything.
But I won't let you go anywhere.
Er...
Have you ever...
seen me play a guitar before?
You play guitar?
I play a little.
But I'm not a professional or anything.
Come to think of it...
we never had a flirty moment at all, did we?
I will play the guitar to flirt with you then.
I will make you blush so hard.
Not forgetting anything?
- Probably not.
- No, you always forget.
- You know me too well.
- Have a safe trip, son. Have fun.
Sure.
Jo.
If he's stubborn to you, come tell me.
Ugh mom. I've never been stubborn.
Really?
Ma'am. Would you excuse us?
We have to go.
Sure. Good luck.
Come here.
Let me kiss you.
I'm leaving.
- Safe trip son.
- I'll travel for you too.
Sure.
Drive safe.
Hey!
Wow~
It's so beautiful, P'Jo.
Come take a look.
Look.
There's a boat too.
Do you come to the beach often?
I don't know what to do here.
Well...
Right...maybe cause you have to work.
So you don't have much time to travel often.
Then let's take this opportunity to do it.
Over there.
Surprise!!
- How did you guys get here?
- Beause of P'Johan...
so we got a free trip.
I was gonna invite everyone,
but these are all the people who can.
Thank you.
Come on. Let's eat.
I'm hungry.
Sure. Sure.
Being at the beach like this is so nice.
Um.
Oh Nao.
- Hm?
- About the Boston trip to see your brother...
Why? You changed your mind?
- Really!?
- Yeah.
But...
I still need to save more money. A long way to go.
It probably wont't be anytime soon.
Actually...
you can borrow me first
and pay me back later.
What?
- For real?
- Yeah.
- Wait. Wait.
- Hmm?
- What are you doing?
- To record as a proof.
In case you changed your mind.
What am I gonna do?
Here. I'm about to record.
- Say it again.
- What do you want me to say?
Just say umm...
Suer will lend Nao some money to go see his brother in Boston.
Here we go.
Come on. I'm recording.
Suer will lend Nao some money to go see his brother in Boston.
Happy now?
I am.
Thank you.
Here. Take a bite. It's dripping.
Do you like it?
I do.
Smile. Come on.
You like to take pictures of me.
So I wanna take pictures of you too.
Really?
Can you take when I'm over there too?
Please.
P'Jo.
Now, I understand...
why Ter likes to take pictures of P'Hill everyday.
I have always wondered that.
Even though P'Hill looks the same everyday.
But it's because he wants to keep and see the pictures for himself.
And it never gets old.
You're so sweet.
- Do you like it
-What?
Do you like it here?
I do.
I like it a lot.
Thank you, P'Jo.
For everything you have ever done for me.
P'Jo.
Do you have any idea...
that everything right here right now is really good.
It's too good and it makes me scared.
Scared of what?
Scared that you might be bored of me someday.
I cannot imagine.
I felt like this once
when someone warned me about you.
I thought I can handle it.
No matter what I have to face.
I will love you like I'm not afraid of anything.
But at the end...
I still feel afraid.
Um.
Have you ever thought about your future?
I have.
I wanna have a family. Have a house.
I want my mom to live comfortably.
And...
what about your dreams?
It's you.
You've always been my dream.
I never wanted to be someone or do something.
If I didn't meet you,
I would have probably just live my life day by day.
And...
live without life goal.
P'Jo.
I just wanna have you by my side...
no matter what's gonna happen in the future.
Wherever you would like to go, I'll take you.
Whatever you wanna do, I will support you.
If it's not you...
I probably couldn't love anyone anymore.
So...
can you be with me forever?
Yes.
Forever.
I love you, North.
I love you too.
The stars are so beautiful tonight.
Yeah.
Are there gonna be any meteors?
I don't know.
Why?
I just thought...
it would be so pretty if we get to see meteors.
If we don't get to see it tonight...
then...
let's make a wish from the moon instead, shall we?
The moon is so pretty tonight.
What kind of wish would you like to ask for?
I would wish for smartness,
diligence, and prosperity.
or I can eat as much and never gained weight.
Oh...
and maybe a bit taller in terms of height.
What about you?
What would you like to wish for?
Me?
I don't wanna wish for anything else.
Just for me having you by my side like this...
and won't go anywhere.
I'm more than happy with these.
The moon says...
the person right here...
won't leave or go anywhere ever.
Really?
Then...
can I change my wish?
Change to what?
I'd like to wish for....
both of us to see the moon...
like this every year.
Sure.
The moon is so kind.
I took them for you.
Both meteors,
and the moon.
You're a liar. That's not possible.
They're so beautiful.
My grandma gave me this necklace.
She told me to give it to a person
who's really important to me.
P'Hill.
I love you.
I love you too, Ter.
But I love you more.
I do more.
How much?
Like as much as the stars in the sky right now.
Stars in the sky?
Then I love you more.
Not true.
I love you more. No more arguing.
Why not?
Do you know...
who I am?
You're my boyfriend, right?
Yes.
Hence, you can't argue with your boyfriend.
Fine. I surrender.