Hey…
Actually…
I...
have had a crush on you for so long.
You are mine now.
Ter. Ter. Ter.
What’s going on?
Is there a robbery or a ghost?
Nothing.
If it's nothing,
then why did you just scream?
I just had a bad dream.
What kind of dream?
- Well…
- Well?
It was really terrifying.
Thinking about it,
gives me goosebumps.
Look!
Ter...or...
we actually have a ghost in our room?
What the hell!
You’re being nonsense.
What’s wrong with you?
Just go to bed.
There's no ghost.
- Are you sure there's nothing?
- Yeah.
Nothing.
Just go to sleep.
I’m begging you.
If you don't go, you'll be late tomorrow.
Go go.
Please do not haunt us.
Ter.
You should pray before sleeping too.
If not, they'll haunt you.
Yeah I know.
Hey!
Did you hear that?
What?
It’s my voice.
Oh.
Shit!
What are you doing?
I'm already late!
Come on.
It takes you forever in there.
Don’t be so dramatic!
I’ve been waiting for so long already.
Almost done.
Stop rushing me.
I AM LATE ALREADY.
Come on!
Yeah give me a min.
Get out here now, Ter!
Damn it. Get out!
F*ck you!
Just go in.
F*ck you~
Hurry up.
You’ve been in there for too long.
Come on, North!
You've been in there forever.
I’m shitting.
We’re late~
First year,
come register here please.
Are you a freshman?
Um…yes.
Do we have to register?
Yes,
she said first years register here.
I’m Phoon.
And you are...?
Oh…I’m Ter.
Is this your first day?
I’ve never seen you before.
Yes yes.
Oh I actually have another friend.
Met him during the orientation.
He should be here by now.
If you don’t have any friends,
you can hang with us.
Thank you, Phoon.
I don’t know anyone here.
When I first joined,
I also didn’t know anyone but Foam.
You’re here early today.
Oh you’re here.
Speaking of the devil.
You’ve got a problem with me?
What?
Better watch your back.
Also a freshman?
Um…yes.
Yeah
I met him at the registration just now.
Oh and this is Foam.
This is Ter.
Hi Foam.
Hi Ter.
Ter?
Why?
Is it short for something?
It’s from Easter.
I was born around Easter.
Oh that’s why.
Easter...
I also have a sibling,
named Christmas.
Born on Christmas day.
Hey that’s cool.
But…it's a sister, right?
Does she have a boyfriend?
Stop it.
If I were him,
I wouldn’t let my sister date a guy like you.
Why?
What’s wrong with me?
Can I say it?
Hey.
You are no better than me.
You two calm down.
Where are you goin'?
Those who just arrived,
please queue at the back.
This should be all, yeah?
First of all, I'll introduce myself.
My name is Bua. I’m a representative from Student Union.
I'd like to invite you guys,
Vet students to join our union.
Quiet. All quiet.
Let’s put it this way.
Apart from work experience, you’ll also get extra credits.
Is anyone here a student
from Lady Rattana’s scholarship?
Anyone?
Ok wait…there’s one…
Ok since you’re scholarship students,
you have to help out the union anyways.
Anyone who wants to voluntarily join?
If you do,
please go fill out you name over here.
Those scholarship students too.
Come sign up here.
I heard the president is a med student, right?
How do they manage the time?
I know right. So talented.
Good with both extra curricular and studies.
Top of the faculty too.
Ter.
You’re a scholarship student?
That means you have to join the union?
That must be tiring.
Classes haven't started,
already complaining?
Don't let me hear you complain.
Why?
I’m not going to complain anyway.
Oh I also heard that
we have to join some clubs too.
Which club are you interested in, Ter?
No idea.
What about you, Phoon?
I don’t know.
Haven’t thought about it.
Way to go...all my friends.
Like you already have something on your mind?
Me?
I wanna join Basketball club.
I heard the seniors there are very tough.
Especially the club’s president.
He’s also the president of Student Union.
That’s cool. Multitasking.
Doing many things.
You have to also work at the Student union, right?
You might meet him there.
Right.
Probably.
You can do it.
Girls!
Look at those med students
They're so handsome.
Who’s that?
What?
Don’t tell me you don’t know who they are?
That one…
that’s reading.
His name is Tonfha.
Sir.
Can I have more paper?
Thank you.
He’s smart.
Guys, if you don’t understand anything,
please ask me.
Nice, kind, warm and gentle too.
Oh myy~
what about that one?
His name is Arthit.
Even he looks a bit like a bad boy,
but he’s good with music instruments.
And so does sports.
What about the one that’s napping?
That one is Johan.
He’s hot and also rich.
The whole place...on me.
It’s like he just comes out of a fairly tale.
You asked me to come study,
didn’t you?
Fine. I’m up.
What about the other one?
That one?
That’s Hill.
He’s super smart.
Always the 1st class honor.
He’s the president of the union too.
Like you're aware,
work at the Student union is pretty detailed.
If you have any questions,
please ask me.
Yes, president.
He's also the president of Basketball club.
He's so hot.
Look.
They're so perfect.
Don't know
whether they're dating someone?
How's the union this morning?
Busy.
About to start new semester.
I'll have to be at the union after this.
(Panupong Jittangkul)
(Veterinary Medicine)
Finally home.
The orientation alone is already exhausting
Ter.
What?
If you sleep now,
the ghost will come haunt you.
Whatever. Just let me be.
Go play your games.
And go easy with the keyboard sound.
Getting my nerves?
Come on!
Oh yeah.
Come at me.
- Hey!
- What....hey!!
Ter!
What's the matter?
I told you not to nap during the dusk,
when the ghost is around.
That's why you have bad dreams.
How was it?
Did the ghost gave you lotto numbers?
I'm just gonna go shower.
You should go to bed too.
Playing games all damn night.
Just one round.
It's been so many damn rounds.
What the...
Why are you up so early?
I haven't slept actually.
Huh? Really?
Because of those bad dreams?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
Ter. What are those dream?
You can tell me.
It's nothing. Forget it.
We have a ghost...in our room, right?
You cannot sleep cause all those bad dreams.
There's no other way.
Please leave me alone,
I will make merit for you.
Just kidding.
It's not funny.
Ohh it's fine.
And..are you really okay?
Um...I think so.
You can always tell me everything, yeah?
Dude.
Let me ask you something.
What?
Let's say...hypothetically...
If there's someone that you really hate,
and you don't wanna see his face.
What would you do?
Then don't go see.
It's not that simple.
Sometimes you just walk into each other.
Just pretend that you didn't see.
Don't talk. Don't pay attention.
But I think if he hates you,
I don't think
he'd want to show his face to you either.
Unless he wants a fight.
There're many types of hatred though.
Hate because you just don't like his face.
Or you've done something bad to him.
Or...
You hate him because you used to love him.
If that's the case,
not seeing at all is for the best.
Hey.
Or you...
have a love problem?
Nonsense.
It's all hatred.
Stop it.
You're not going anywhere today?
I will hang out with a senior.
What about you?
I will go out in the evening.
Might take a nap a bit more.
Then go ahead.
So tired.
I'm gonna go shower.
You just woke up.
I haven't slept. How can you be tired?
I didn't get enough sleep.
Hello?
"Hey you picked up so fast!
You already got up?"
Umm...I just took a nap
...not so long ago.
"What?
Why didn't you sleep last night?"
"Is something wrong?"
Umm...nothing.
Never mind.
"Phoon and I will go to a coffee shop."
"Just wanna ask you to join us."
"You can nap there."
I can actually nap there?
"Sure"
"It's a coffee shop for students"
"I've seen so many take a nap there"
Okay okay.
I'll go.
"Good."
"Leave now, okay?"
"I'm at the front of your dorm already."
Huh?
Okay.
Let me shower first.
Okay okay.
I will wait here~
How long have you been waiting?
Since before I called you.
I was thinking,
if you refused to go,
I'd drag you out of your room myself.
That's forcing.
Stop babbling.
Hop on.
Here.
Fine.
Where's Phoon?
He's at the coffee shop
to get a table already.
Let's go.
Just drive safely.
Hang on tight sir~
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hi Phoon.
Oh.
You wanna order something?
You already did.
I'm gonna continue my nap.
What' wrong with him?
Why is he like that?
He couldn't sleep last night.
Why?
Whatever...let him be.
I'm gonna go pee.
Hey.
I'll go with you.
When did he get up and order?
Wake him up.
- Ter.
- Hmm?
Why don't you eat what you ordered?
You guys ordered this?
We just got back from the restroom.
You didn't order this?
No, I didn't.
Hey!
This is yummy.
You try it.
It's good.
It's probably someone else's order.
Whatever.
We can pay them later.
The food is here.
Er...excuse me.
Are you serving the wrong table?
We didn't order these.
Neither the chocolate nor this cake.
Table 15.
2 orders. It's correct.
Already paid too.
Enjoy.
Sure.
- I think she remembered the wrong table.
- Yeah.
It's okay. Let's just eat.
You guys are so...
but let me have a bite.
Umm...
About the club,
which club are you guys joining?
Anything in mind?
Not really.
I'll join whatever you'll join.
Thing is...
we still don't know what to join.
What are the clubs do we have here?
Err...well...
You guys are looking for a club to join?
Yes yes. Why?
I'm from a Drawing club.
We're looking for more members too.
We only get a few members each year.
If you're interested, you can join us.
But I cannot draw.
Am I allowed to join?
Why not?
It's not that serious.
Or you can just sign up your names.
Then decide again later
when the semester begins.
In case you have no idea what to join, then you'll have mine as a backup.
Sure.
That sounds good.
Oh hey..
can I sign up for my friend too?
My friend also needs one to join.
Umm sure.
Which friend?
It's North.
He's not gonna join his engineering friends?
He said all his friends already signed up.
Mostly sports.
He doesn't want to use so much energy.
Good.
By the way...what's your name?
I'm....Daotok.
I'm Foam.
I'm Easter.
You can just call me Ter.
I'm Typhoon.
Hill.
Hill!
What's wrong with you?
You're smiling to the book.
Just thinkin' about something.
What thing?
You know what's it about.
About that person?
Um.
I'm so wanna meet that person.
Who is it that makes my friend like this?
(Student Union)
Come on.
Follow me.
Come come.
Put it here.
- Hello.
That's it for now.
We'll talk later.
You're a Vet student, aren't you?
Yes.
What's your name again?
Easter.
You can just call me Ter.
Oh ok...Ter.
Wait a min.
Peem!
Peem.
Come here.
This is Ter.
This is Peem. He's a coordinator of the union.
Peem,
you will delegate some work for him to do.
Sure. Follow me.
- Right.
- We'll have a Welcome Back to the campus thingy.
It's usually busy around this time.
We'll have to organize a concert too.
Well...will you help me paint all these wood?
Make it all white.
Sure.
Thank you.
Peem. Peem.
Do we have to carry all these to the stage?
Or there'll be someone do it for us?
Right...I haven't asked the president.
And where is he now?
I think he's taking a nap in there.
He just finished his exam.
- I'll have a freshman go get him.
- Sure.
- Ter. Ter.
- Yes?
Can you go wake up the president?
He's in the break room.
Tell him Peem needs your help.
Sure.
- You want me to go now?
- Yes.
- He knows right?
P'...
Peem wants me to wake you up.
Excuse me.
Ter.
Hey.
Hey...Ter.
What's the matter with him?
Here we go.
Don't tell me the president scolded at him
so he ran away?
Right...
he doesn't like when people wake him up too.
Why didn't you go do it by yourself.
I didn't know
that he's gonna be this upset.
Hill!
What did you do?
I told him to wake you up.
I didn't think you would be this upset.
He's probably crying now.
This is bad.
What should we do?
Yeah.
This is bad.
What should I do?
Why are you here?
Don't you have to be at the union?
Phoon.
What's wrong?
I don't wanna work at the union anymore.
You're being funny.
I'm serious.
You can't.
You're a scholarship student. You need those hours.
That's true...
If I don't go,
would I get my credits deducted?
What's the matter with you?
What's going on really?
Dude.
Help me.
What's going on?
Fine fine. Calm down.
Shall we go?
Take the drink with you.
Oh.
Don't you have to be at the union?
What's the matter?
Foam...let me hang with you guys here please.
(Memorable moment...
before we won't see each other again)
(I no longer want to see this post.)
What's up dude?
Did you have fun working at the union?
Not at all.
I wanna quit.
Why?
Too many tasks?
Hey.
Do you remember that person I told you?
He's in the union as well.
And he's also...
also what?
He's also the president of the union.
Shit.
For real?
Yes.
What a coincidence.
You probably met him face to face, yeah?
Yes.
What are you gonna do now?
If you don't participate,
you might lose your schorlarship.
Losing the scholarship?
What should I do?
Weird.
What weird?
Why?
Why don't you wanna see his face?
I hate him.
Hate like hate hate?
Not exactly.
Weird...see!?
You're really weird.
Nonsense.
You keep bugging me.
Are you sure that you hate him?
Or....
Enough, North!
What are you talking about?
See.
You're always like this.
Whenever you're blushing or upset
...it's all the same.
No!
(Student Union)
That's right.
Great. Great.
Hello.
Please come on down.
The freshmen are here, Mr.president.
You should go work now perhaps?
The kid you scolded yesterday
is also here.
Or at least apologize to him.
I don't want any uncomfortable situation here.
I didn't scold.
Didn't scold?
Didn't do it?
Then why did he ran away like that?
And where are you going?
To apologize.
He said he's gonna go apologize,
then why is he standing there?
That's odd.
What happened yesterday?
I think we need to help our president.
What's up kids?
Hi.
Ter.
I'm so sorry about yesterday.
I shouldn't have asked you to wake him.
He probably gave you a mean face.
That's why you ran out like that, right?
No not at all.
Oh...then what happened to you?
I thought he was being mean to you
that's why you cried.
I DIDN'T CRY.
I didn't cry.
But still..I fell guilty.
I will buy you dinner after this...how's that?
It's fine. Really.
It's actually not big a deal.
I"m the one who needs to apologize for running away like that.
But we're still guilty.
Let's have dinner with us.
Please Ter.
I feel bad.
I understand...
that you're not comfortable to have dinner with us, right?
It's not like that.
Fine. I will go.
- I'll go.
- Yes!
Then I will go help the president first.
- Sure.
- See you, Ter.
Keep up y'all.
I'm going with you.
Is this enough cloth?
Yes.
- Dude.
- Hmm?
Is that the union's president?
Yes. That's P'Hill.
Why is he looking this way?
I don't know. Ask him.
Are you crazy?
Look at him.
Looks so scary with his resting bitch face.
I wouldn't ask.
What are you guys whispering about?
It's the president, P'Bua.
He always looks this way.
Did we do something wrong?
Nothing. Keep working.
Oh P' by the way...
is he seeing someone?
I don't know.
How come you don't know?
You've never asked him?
I have.
Do you know what did he answer me?
What is it?
He said...
'Now, I already have someone
I wanna commit myself to.'
So charming the way he said it.
Come here.
You told me that you have someone you want to be committed to, right?
Um.
I'm going to the restroom.
Ter.
I have something that I need to talk to you.
Let me go.
Ter.
I said let me go.
Let me help.
Holding a needle like that is really dangerous.
You need to hold it like this
And hold the cloth like this.
Be careful.
Don't poke yourself.
Let's have dinner~
So exhausted today.
Not at all.
- Isn't that right, Ter?
- Let's go eat, Ter.
Let' go.
Sure.
And today Thunmild is not joining?
No.
Let's go eat.
Come on, Ter.
Let's go eat something.
I will get this one please.
Sure.
And err...
Do you wanna try this?
Ter.
Order whatever you'd like. On us.
Please order.
Sure.
Make that 2 for Ter.
I will get a big set of salmon sashimi please.
Okay.
Anything else?
No.
- That'll be all for now.
- Okay.
Okay so--
Hill.
You have someone you want to be serious with?
Um.
Who's that?
Ughh can you just tell me?
I'm dying to know.
Right.
I can't.
Please give me a clue.
You guys will find out soon.
Eat up please.
Are you full, Ter?
I am.
Good.
Next time I will have Hill buy for you.
Hill,
you can drop me and Bua at the faculty.
Then you go drop him at his dorm.
That's fine. I can go back by myself.
Hey you're not a burden.
Let Hill take you home.
- But--
- You don't want me to take you home?
Let him take you home.
Don't have to feel bad.
Fine.
Thank you.
Thanks for dropping us off.
Please drop him off for us, will you?
Take good care of him, okay?
- Bye. See you.
- Good bye.
You can come sit in the front.
I'm fine back here.
Then it's gonna look like I'm your driver.
Fine.
I will fasten by myself.
Did you like the food?
I did.
Then I will take you there again.
It's fine. I rather not.
See you soon.
Thank you.
Ughh.
Too many things happened in one day.
I'm so tired.
Ter!
What?
Come check this out.
Hurry!
What is it?
Isn't that your hand?