They say the more you mess around with spirits,
the easier it is for them to get to you.
Is there any guarantee you’ll be safe every time?
What if that ghost at the cemetery just now tried to hurt you? What would happen?
I could even die.
And if one day you realize you can’t back out anymore,
then you’d better move forward.
Before it’s too late.
Thank you for the ride, P'Arthit.
Thank you for the ride.
P'Arthit.
Hey, Daotok.
You’re taking this class too, North?
Yeah. I still haven’t completed my elective credits.
I thought I’d be lonely at first. Good thing I ran into you.
Yeah.
So how’s P'Arthit doing?
After I hung up on you, I just let him sleep on the floor like before.
Hey!
He didn’t do anything weird, right?
Like what?
Oh, well...
As long as he didn’t do anything weird, that’s good.
Did you bring your motorcycle?
Yeah, why?
Can I get a ride back?
Huh?
You didn’t bring Patcharamon today?
Then how did you get here?
The guy next door gave me a ride.
Why did he give you a ride?
He saw that I wasn’t feeling well, so he was worried I couldn’t drive.
Ohhh.
I see.
So, are you giving me a ride or not?
Sure. I’ll take you home myself.
You don’t have to pick me up.
I’ll head back with North.
Damn it, North.
Do you want a flat tire or what?
Well, look who’s trying to move on.
Are you just dropping him off and waiting to pick him up?
So what’s your deal with me?
How so?
You’re so damn nosy.
Do you like my friend?
Yeah, I do.
Satisfied?
So what, P'? Are you going to court him?
Hey, Daotok.
I’ve got something to tell you.
My rear tire’s a bit low on air.
So if you’re going to ride on the back, it might be dangerous.
Then it’s fine.
I think you should have P'Arthit pick you up.
Hmm... I kind of want to take a chill walk around campus.
Oh come on, don’t get all artsy. It’s dangerous.
Walking alone is pretty deserted.
Heeey!
How did you get here, P'Arthit? Wow.
I had no idea. What a coincidence.
Wow, such a coincidence.
Man, what a coincidence.
- How did you get here?
- Damn it, North.
- At least make it subtle, asshole.
- Wasn’t I subtle?
How did you get here?
I told you I’d come pick you up.
Here.
Hurry up.
Thanks.
You’re unbelievable.
What?
I knew this would happen.
You won’t be able to move on.
It’s not that easy, P'.
If you’re going to court Daotok.
What’s so hard about that?
So what are you going to do?
I’ll be myself.
Be sincere. Be natural.
I don’t think you should be yourself.
- Just try being a better person.
- Hey, North!
Hey, hey.
But don’t rush things.
He’s closed off right now.
Damn.
Too late.
I already slept hugging him.
That’s good, isn’t it?
How is that good, P'Jo?
Well, I’ve done it before.
Oh, that’s enough, both of you.
Daotok isn’t me.
If it were you, I wouldn’t want you either.
Why don’t you try me?
Asshole.
North, what breed of dog are you raising? It’s freaking vicious.
Damn it.
You jerk.
Seriously, P'.
Daotok doesn’t really need anything anymore.
He has a stable job.
He’s happy being on his own.
Exactly.
And I’m freaking useless too.
But...
At the very least, having me around is better.
It makes him feel secure.
That’s it?
Shit, what else is there, Jo?
I... I can protect him.
I can take care of him. I can look after him.
- I can be someone he can rely on.
- Someone he can rely on?
Yeah.
You? Someone he can rely on? You can’t even handle your own life.
Then let me be his burden instead.
Maybe his life’s just too perfect.
Well, that could work.
Yeah.
I’ve got it.
I think I’m handsome.
Right?
Isn’t being handsome enough?
You’re not wrong.
About taking care of him—you probably could.
And protecting him? Yeah, you definitely can.
But...
Won’t you cheat on him?
No way.
And how can you be so sure?
If it would hurt him,
then I won’t do it.
Damn.
You’re actually pretty nice to look at.
Are you afraid he might like you, Michael?
If he really does like you,
what will you do?
I’d probably tell him honestly
that I’m not ready to be with anyone yet.
Your heart’s completely closed off.
Once I'm done handling things about his mom,
we probably won’t see each other much anymore.
He’ll forget about me eventually.
You think so?
What is it?
Well...
I just want to be with you.
Hey, wait.
If you don’t let me in,
I’ll really break the door down.
North.
The guy next door came into my room.
Well...
Why the hell did he came into your room?
He said he wanted to stay with me or something.
Seriously?
Wow.
Damn, isn’t that a bit much, bro?
What should I do to make him leave my room?
Wait—
Don’t you want him there?
Why would I want that?
Come on, it’s obvious.
Can’t you tell
why he’s doing all this?
Honestly, I kind of can.
Oh?
Really?
Then I can openly root for him now.
North.
I didn’t call so you could root for him.
Come on.
I’ve interrogated him. He passes.
That’s it for now, North.
What are you doing out here?
When are you going back to your room?
I don’t know.
Whenever I feel like it, I guess.
You’re unbelievable.
Let go.
Or I’ll step on your foot.
Wow, you even gave me a warning.
Then step on it.
You’re so tiny. How much could it hurt?
See? You can stay still.
That’s much better. See?
Satisfied?
Not yet.
Fine. I’ll let go.
Are you mad?
Yeah.
And you need to let go of my hand.
I have to go to work.
Hey.
Aren’t you even going to ask why I held your hand?
Why I hugged you?
I don’t really want to know.
You sound so damn fierce.
Do you dislike it that much?
I do.
That answer suits you perfectly.
Can you let go now?
What if I say no?
Fine.
Hey, wait.
Are you really going to ignore the hand I’m holding like this?
Yes.
If you don’t stop me like this,
it’s going to get bad.
If I get carried away and do something more than this,
you’ll be the one in trouble.
Don’t.
I don’t like it.
You don’t like me holding your hand?
I don’t like you.
That paid off.
That’s enough.
This is pointless.
You mean what I’m doing right now?
How is it pointless?
It’s fucking great being with you.
I like you.
I really like you.
I don’t even know how or why, but I like you.
I’m sorry.
But I don’t feel that way about you.
So please give up.
I figured you’d say something like that.
But sorry,
that doesn’t work on someone like me.
You’re making this hard for me.
Then deal with it.
Guess you didn’t earn enough merit in your past life.
That’s why someone like me likes you.
Just accept it.
Because I’m not backing off that easily.
Then I’ll go make more merit.
I’ll take you with me.
Let me tell you.
I’ve never had
any of that damn love stuff.
If I hadn’t met you,
I’d probably stay alone until I die.
As for you,
how you feel about me is up to you.
What I want right now
is to be with you.
Just let me stay by your side.
Then you’ll be the one who gets hurt.
Are you saying
you’ll never like me?
What if I say yes?
That’s your business.
I’m heading back first.
Oh,
don’t pressure yourself.
You can take your time liking me.
No rush.
Here, yum yum.
Grow up fast, okay?
So when are you taking your kid back?
Are you just leaving him for me to raise?
You’re old enough to stay home and raise your grandkid now, Direk.
If I raise the grandkid, who’s going to earn money for you to spend?
True.
Then focus on your work, Direk. Got it?
Go to sleep, kiddo.
I’ll leave him with you for now, Direk.
I’ve been too busy to take care of him lately.
Oh, I just bought you a new car.
Seriously?
For racing.
You never do anything without expecting something in return, do you, Direk?
This match is important.
You’re racing against that family’s son.
If you lose, you’ll look like a damn fool. I’m telling you now.
So go practice.
Don’t you trust me, Direk?
I do.
But you’ve been away from the track for a while.
Don’t be careless.
I’m not sure if I’ll have time to practice, Direk.
Fourth year is insane. I barely have time to sleep.
Classes,
clinical rounds, exams—
it’s driving me crazy.
Then just drop out.
What?
Didn’t you say you wanted that degree to hang on your wall?
I was just saying that.
I just see how tired and stressed you are.
But if you graduate,
your mom would be proud.
Hmm. So proud.
"Dylan,
did you got F again?"
Hey, Direk.
I have something to tell you.
Did you get some girl pregnant?
No? That’s bad then, Direk.
Or did you kill someone?
- No.
- Don’t tell me you stole something.
This is getting out of hand, Direk.
- Did you do something illegal?
- Are you going to help me?
Yeah, to kick you while you’re down.
I’ve taught you that since you were a kid.
that you must never do anything illegal or cause trouble for anyone.
Oh, come on.
Fine, I’ll tell you.
Just don’t have a heart attack. You’re not getting any younger.
I like someone.
I’m courting him right now.
Shit.
This is worse than you killing someone.
Who is it?
What are you listening to?
The same playlist.
Let me listen too.
- Your shirt’s dirty.
- Hey, it’s washable.
Hey, my face.
It’s not a sketchpad. It’s my face. Move.
Then get up.
No.
How was class?
Same as usual.
My case presentation this morning was fucking awful.
Ward rounds were exhausting as hell.
Hey.
Hmm?
I want to ask you something.
What is it?
Why do you like me?
That’s a question I can’t really answer either.
I just know it has to be you.
Are you tired?
Not really.
Is there anything you don’t like about me?
Why?
Are you going to fix it?
I’ll do worse than that.
Nothing.
That’s impossible.
Why?
There has to be something.
Something you don’t like about in human.
But I won’t ask you
what you don’t like about me.
Why not?
Because you’d definitely say everything.
No, I wouldn’t.
Really?
Then…
what do you like about me?
You’re natural.
Me?
Yeah.
You don’t lie.
I feel comfortable when I’m with you.
Even if sometimes I don’t feel like being around you.
But when I am with you, I feel at ease.
Wait.
Hey.
I’m not ready for this.
Are you confessing to me?
Not at all.
It feels relieved, like when I’m with North.
But more annoying.
Way more.
Shit.
The way you talk,
damn.
If it weren’t me,
someone would be crying by now.
Good thing I’m built for all weather.
Even if you told me you hate me,
I wouldn’t be hurt.
I hate you.
Really?
Not exactly hate.
That still hit hard, damn.
Come on, say it again.
I hate you.
Damn, I really can’t handle that.
No, no. Don’t say that word again.
Even if you really hate me,
just
keep it to yourself. Don’t say it out loud again.
Mm.
My dad invited you over for dinner.
Don’t even think about it.
You can’t refuse.
Why did he suddenly invite me?
Well,
I told him I like you.
So he invited you.
Thanks for the ride.
Wait, wait.
Since I started courting you,
- How many points have I earned?
- None at all.
What?
None at all?
You’ve earned my gratitude.
Then where’s the thank you?
Thank you.
Thank who?
Thank you,
P'Arthit.
Smile too.
Do I have to smile too?
Mm-hm.
There.
Say it with a smile.
Thank you, P'Arthit.
That’s more like it.
That’s better.
Yeah.
Let’s go.
You’re surprised I invited you today, aren’t you?
Yes.
From when he was little until now, Arthit has never told me about something like this.
This is the first time.
So I got a little excited.
You understand, right?
I understand.
So,
he’s courting you, right?
And…
are you okay with that?
It must be putting you in a difficult position.
Let me apologize on behalf of my son.
He’s…
not very well-behaved.
He’s so spoiled.
And he has a sharp tongue.
Hey, Direk.
Why are you badmouthing me?
What?
I’m telling the truth.
It must be exhausting, huh?
I’m not exhausted.
I wasn’t talking to you.
I was talking to Daotok.
It’s tiring, right? Having Arthit follow you around like this.
It’s not tiring.
But it’s annoying.
That must’ve made you want to cry.
I’m fine.
I’ve had worse.
"You should spend your time on something else."
"Why do you even like me? Why don’t you like someone else?"
"Just give up. I don’t like you."
"Stop bothering me."
My son
got chased away like a stray dog.
The reason I invited you today
is to thank you about Arthit’s mother.
Since you came back from San Francisco, we haven’t had the chance to meet.
It’s really no problem at all.
Oh, and Arthit showed me a photo
of the painting you continued from Emma’s.
It’s very beautiful.
Would you be interested in doing a painting for me?
What kind of work do you like?
Hmm, I like acrylics.
The bolder the colors, the better.
Sure.
Really?
Then I’ll have my secretary send you the details.
You mean acrylic paint on canvas, something like that?
Yes. I’ll show you some examples of what I like.
Here, something like this.
You’re not uncomfortable, are you?
Not at all.
My dad’s always like this when he’s with me.
You’re okay, right?
Mm.
Of course I am.
Why did you bring me here?
Well…
I wanted you to see the real me.
This is my dad. My family.
There’s nothing left to hide from you.
If anyone says I’m not serious about you,
I’ll kick them in the face.
Thank you.
Huh?
For being serious.
Thank you for being serious about me.
Mm.
Not everyone
would trust someone like this,
bringing them home
the way you did.
It’s because you’re serious about me, right?
Why do you sound like you’re opening up to me?
Zero points.
What? Why?
Zero out of nothing at all.
From now on, I’m starting to count the points.
P'Earng.
If you want to play with Johan, just say so nicely.
I’ll leave the lights on for you.
Is the power out?
The other rooms still have power.
It’s not just a burnt-out bulb.
All the electricity in the room
is completely out.
Really?
It’s already late.
I’ll have a technician take a look tomorrow.
Tonight, Dao, you’ll have to sleep somewhere else first.
It’s okay.
I can sleep in the room tonight.
Hey, you can’t.
There’s no electricity, and the AC isn’t working.
How are you going to sleep? What if something happens to you?
And there are so many ghosts in that room.
No way.
He’s right, Dao.
If you don’t want the hassle,
you can sleep in the next room for now.
Mm.
You’re being unusually nice.
Really?
Yeah.
I’m being nice?
The nicest you’ve ever been since I’ve known you, P’.
Hey, you can let John sleep here.
Uh… how do I set this up?
Stay here, okay?
Mr. John.
Where did you even get John from?
From my old dorm.
They didn’t allow pets there.
Did you move because of him?
Yeah.
What are you, Cupid or something?
I think John likes me more than you.
Mr. John.
Don’t do that. Come back to me.
Come back to me, okay?
See? Now you’ve made him all dramatic over you. What are you going to do?
Do you like him more than me, Mr. John?
Hey, hey.
Go sleep properly on the bed.
Don’t sit on the sofa.
Go.
I’m going to sit and work. You go sleep properly on the bed.
Now.
Go sleep on the bed.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I’m not going to do anything to you.
Go.
Are you hungry?
Someone already fed you.
You can keep my spare keycard for now.
I went for a run this morning and passed by a soy milk shop,
so I bought some for you.
I’ve already fed John.
You’re awake?
You look so bright.
Ever since you started liking my boyfriend’s friend.
Who told you that?
Come on, I’m ready. Hit me with it.
Go ahead and scold me.
What?
You’re not going to scold me?
Why would I?
Well…
When Jo first started pursuing North,
I saw you grilling him relentlessly.
You and Jo aren’t the same.
You’ve never liked anyone before.
So this time,
you really like him.
Hill, my dear friend.
I knew it. You’d understand me.
You’re seriously a ride-or-die friend.
I’m not dying with you.
But I admit it,
I was a little surprised that you found someone you like.
If I say I’m proud of you…
would that be too much?
Damn it.
Are you saying you’re proud of me?
Hill.
Can you be my dad instead of Direk?
You’re so damn warm and kind.
I’m seriously touched by you, Hill.
I don’t want a son like you.
Aw, Dad.
I haven’t even called Direk “Dad” yet.
By the way, can I get some money to modify my car?
Go away.
You never chase Jo away like that.
- But you chase me away like I’m nothing.
- I chase Jo away too.
Talking to you is such a waste of time.
Hey.
Wait, Hill. Hey, give me some money first, Hill!
I heard P'Pae said your room needs repairs for several more days.
Yeah.
He said the electrical system’s broken.
Then you have to stay in my room for now.
Am I bothering you?
Bothering me how?
It was my plan all along—to make your room lose power.
Hey.
I’m kidding. Damn, did you actually believe me?
What kind of person do you think I am?
Try drawing what your dad asked me to draw.
I’m thinking about whether he’ll like it.
Of course he will.
This is totally Direk’s style.
Shit.
Go on, keep drawing.
You can use my head as a sketchpad.
I’m really exhausted today.
Then go sleep on the bed.
Sleeping on the bed won’t make me any less tired.
Not if you’re not there.
He looks really exhausted.
He studied hard all day.
And he has to wake up early.
Even if he’s rude
or seems a bit harsh,
his love is actually very pure, like a child’s.
If it’s this person,
it should be safe.
Yeah.
It should be safe.
If he can endure it.
Isn’t he the one you want?
The one who’ll wait until you're brave enough to open your heart.
Nothing’s certain.
People can change.
You're hoping, aren't you,
that he won’t change.
What are you doing?
Doing what I want to do.
You—
Get out.
You said you wouldn’t do anything.
I’m sorry.
I don’t understand it either.
I don’t know what came over me.
Does it hurt?
No.
It doesn’t hurt at all.
I really like you.
I like you so much.
I didn’t think it’d be this much.
It is that much.
Go sleep properly on the bed.
No.
You—
Do you want me to carry you?
Do you want me to deduct points?
Do you think I’m scared?
And you’re not scared?
Can you stop scaring me like that?
I’ll try.
And…
How many points are left now?
Minus one.
For scaring me.
Hey.
Come on.
I’ve already reflected on it.
Let’s cancel it out to zero.
Please?
- Oh.
- Mm.
You want zero?
Mm.
Since you feel guilty, I’ll give you two points.
Minus one leaves you with one.
But if you want zero, that’s fine.
One. One. I’ll take one.
Pleaaase.
One.
Please.
Okay? One.
I’ll take one.
After you graduate, are you going to work as a doctor right away?
Definitely not.
Why?
I promised my mom I’d study medicine.
So once I graduate, that’s it.
If I had to keep being a doctor,
I’d probably end up fighting with patients.
Even now, when I’m on ward duty,
I have to use up a lifetime’s worth of patience.
You’re doing really well.
Really?
Mm.
You’re amazing.
You’re praising me like I’m a dog.
Why don’t you pat my head then?
You’ve really done well all this time.
My tail’s wagging already.
Let’s go.
Are John and I the same status to you?
I love you.
Hmm?
I said I love you.
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
I just wanted to.
I thought it was just “like,” not love.
No.
I think it’s love now.
What are you smiling at?
Dad sent me a picture.
The one who used to come to your room.
Yeah.
That one.
Go break up with him.
Cut him off completely.
I can’t cut him off.
Why not?
Dad is my other father.
My mom and dad separated.
Papa started a new relationship with Dad.
They’ve both raised me since I was little.
Why didn’t you tell me?
How was I supposed to know you’d think like that?
So that means…
you don’t have anyone, right?
No.
If I did, I wouldn’t let you get this close.
Damn.
That makes me feel special.
Hey.
Why don’t you just be my boyfriend already?
No.
What? Not even for a second?
Just a little?
Just a little.
So what’s going on with you and P'Arthit?
When I first heard about it, I couldn’t believe my ears.
- When North told me, I believed it even less.
- Damn you.
Were you really that shocked?
Of course I was.
That’s P'Arthit we’re talking about.
- This is Dao.
- Yeah.
They’re both in the sky,
but one’s day and the other’s night. Like that.
Hey, but I think they match.
P'Thit is hot-tempered,
and you’re cool.
Opposites that fit perfectly.
Oh really?
- So you’re fully on this ship now?
- Of course.
He bribed me.
Right? You bought me a game, didn’t you?
I knew there had to be benefits involved.
You’re so easy to buy.
So Dao, what’s next?
What can I even do?
If he’s not okay with it,
just tell me.
- We’ll go tell P'Fah.
- Whoa.
I smell someone showing off his boyfriend.
Ouch.
That hurts.
You guys think I won’t do anything, so you’re getting bold.
Damn it.
If it were Nao, I’d rub my foot on his face already.
Whoa, someone’s fired up.
Hey!
Stop it. You ate the whole ice cream yourself.
We’re supposed to split it evenly, damn it.
Waiting for your boyfriend’s match?
And who exactly forced me to come?
So we can go back together.
I saw that you didn’t bring your car.
Waiting for me a bit won’t kill you.
When I play football, everyone stares at me.
Good for you.
Hey, don’t be like that.
You’re supposed to say—
"Someone’s hitting on you? Then...
I’ll have to come to watch you play every day."
Isn’t that how it’s supposed to go?
No.
Be jealous of me a little.
Come on, be jealous.
Please?
Yeah?
No.
Hey, Mhor.
Get over here.
Well then,
give me some encouragement.
Do your best.
Bring it on!
Even if all of you attack me at once, I can handle it.
Hey, slide!
What are you drawing?
Finished already?
Yeah.
Did you watch just now?
Mm.
So? Was it fun?
You played well.
Me?
Mm.
When you compliment me like that,
it makes me really happy.
Why did you draw me?
Because your smile is beautiful.
I just wanted to keep it.
You’re unbelievable.
Why are you doing this? We’re not even dating.
I ask you to be my boyfriend every hour. Just say yes already.
Kim Taemin.
Who’s that?
Oh, Daotok’s client—the writer, right?
I’ve got a feeling he’s not just an ordinary client.
Are you free next month? I’ve got an important race coming up.
I was thinking of asking you to come watch.