Can you please reduce the interest for me?
Fine. I won’t charge you.
Will you do anything that I ask?
Talk to me please.
You just tell your story.
Hello. I’m North.
I’m a respectful person and also a good friend.
- I’m rooting for you.
- Huh?
About P’Jo.
I think it’s cute when you guys talk.
Since when did you like me?
Since the very beginning.
Can I start all over again with you?
- I love you, Ter.
- I love you too.
Run run. Follow me.
Meet my double guns.
Upstairs. Upstairs.
Huhh.
You came home so late.
Went on a date?
There's no date.
Are you crazy?
Why is your face so red?
North!
It hurts.
Don't tell me---
Umm.
How? Tell me.
We just said love to each other.
Damn...
You said you love him?
So are you guys boyfriends yet?
- Not yet.
- Hey.
Why not?
He hasn't said anything about that yet.
Just saying love to each other.
But not boyfriends yet.
How?
It's like he's gonna do it later?
I don't know.
But that's good.
Why?
Good that you're being honest with yourself.
So he knows that you love him.
Umm.
I'm also glad that I finally get to tell him how I feel.
Good job, my friend!
I'm so happy for him.
I think he must be really happy.
Really?
That hurts.
Hey.
By the way.
What happened?
How come you guys ended up saying love to each other?
You just suddenly did it out of the blue?
Or the vibes lead you there.
- Tell me. Please tell me.
- No, I won't tell you.
- Please~ Tell me. Please. Please.
- No, I'm too shy.
But I wanna know.
We just went out and then...
there's a kiss on the hand.
- Hand kissing?
- Yeah.
Don't ask more.
- More kissing anywhere else?
- North!
- Anywhere else? Tell me.
- No, I'm not telling you anymore.
- Or here?
- No.
Where else did you kiss each other?
Tell me.
Tell me. Just a tiny bit.
Hey what?
Come help me.
Stop procrasinating. Here.
Just a minute.
North.
You bought a new phone?
Someone actually bought it for me.
Someone bought it for you?
Who is it?
Do you know P'Johan?
Johan? Yes of course.
He's the popoular one.
Yes that guy bought it for him.
And why did he have to do that?
Are you seeing him?
No, I'm not.
I was in trouble the other day.
And he kind helped me with that.
I broke my phone, so he got me a new one.
Oh.
I thought you are seeing him.
But I heard that he's a real player, isn't he?
But it's fine.
So you have a debt now?
Yeah.
Unpredictable creditor too.
If you need anything just let me know.
In case I could help.
Okay?
You can increase my salary.
That one is not possible.
Hey but my relatives just opened a new place.
They're hiring too.
It's a bar nearby.
Are you interested?
But you might have to go home late though.
I'm in.
I can go home late. it's fine.
But I don't have to work everyday, right?
I don't think so.
Wait a min.
You're working for 2 jobs already.
Are you sure?
I can do it. It's fine.
You're such a hard worker for a small guy.
I'm not a small guy.
Go go. Get to work.
Get to work already.
You're suddenly working hard, huh?
Go go.
Have to mopped here?
Oh North.
When you said you want extra jobs,
are you sure you can handle it?
I can.
I only work here on the weekends.
On weekdays after class, I'm pretty chilled.
How?
You already forgot about P'Yah's?
I only work there 2 days a week.
Not enough to cover my debt.
My creditor is also very unpredictable.
Hey carry this.
"Where are you?"
Shit. Speking of the devil.
Who is it? P'Johan?
Stop it.
At the coffee shop.
The one I told you I work here.
Make me 1 Americano.
Deliver here.
We don't do deliveries.
But YOU do.
I'll give you 30mins.
What the hell?
What do you mean?
I'm blushing.
My ship.
P'Johan wants me to deliver his coffee.
And what kind of coffee shops do delivery?
But some do.
Just shut up.
And where is P'Thun?
What?
You told me to shut up.
You're driving me crazy.
I think he went to the restroom.
There he is.
What's up?
- P'Thun.
- Yes?
Can I go out for awhile?
Sure. We don't have that many customers anyway.
You can go. Why?
And would you mind..?
making one Americano for me please?
Sure but...
do you drink coffee now?
No. It's not mine.
It's P'Johan's
Really?
Umm. I'll make one for you.
Thank you.
I'm here.
Come up on the 12th floor.
Your coffee is here.
Just woke up?
Come in.
Your coffee.
Did you make this yourself?
The owner of the shop made it.
I told you to make it for me.
I haven't learned how to.
If there's nothing else, I'll go now.
Not yet.
But...
I have to work.
- Just quit it.
- Huh?
Cannot.
And how am I gonna make money to pay you back?
You're not gonna increase more debt right?
Almost.
Good. It was just almost.
Err...
then can I...
sit here then?
P'Thun, I'll be back a bit late.
Why? Is something wrong?
Did he do something to you?
Nothing. Just some errands.
Don't be gone for long,
customers might come in.
You're not done working?
Are you gonna tell me to be quiet?
You know well.
Hello.
North.
My name is Prang.
I texted you the other day. You remember?
Yes.
I only heard your name,
now we finally met.
I went to Johan's this morning.
All the maids are still talking about you?
Really?
Especially Mr.President.
I heard that he's very upset...
that you broke his bottle of wine.
Some of them are very rare.
And Johan got in trouble because of that.
And why did he was in trouble?
It should've been me instead.
Johan took it to his responsibility.
He will have to replace for that bottle.
Probably difficult to find.
Oh but...
you've known Johan for a long time?
You face is not familiar to me.
No.
I just got to know him after an incident.
You guys are not like seeing each other right?
No, we're not.
You already delivered.
You may go.
Don't work to hard.
Work is not that busy, isn't it?
I just wanna clear everything.
Don't work too hard then.
I'm gonna go.
Bye bye, North.
See you.
If you're done working,
then I will go now.
Who said you can go?
I haven't drank the Americano.
But it is over there.
You haven't drank it,
and let them melt.
Cause you didn't make it yourself.
I'll only drink the one thst you make.
I haven't learned how to do it.
There's a coffee machine in the kitchen.
Is this my karma or something?
I shouldn't have gone to the bar.
And how is this thing work?
Oh.
You scared me.
You're not gonna wreck my house again, are you?
You're exaggerating.
Oh.
About the wine,
why didn't you tell your dad it was me?
You confessed,
then you're the one who's in trouble.
Oh...P'Prang told me.
If I said that it was you,
things woudl be more complicated.
Thank you.
Why are you standing here?
I will serve you at the table.
You can go sit and wait.
Please.
Why does he have to act so cool?
I'm so confused.
Here's your coffee.
My first Americano.
Enjoy.
How is it?
If I were the coffee shop owner,
You'll be the first one to fire.
Hey...why?
- It's that bad?
- Don't make anyone this ever again.
You're so mean.
I wouldn't believe that you're P'Hill's friend,
if I didn't see it with my own eyes.
Why?
You're so different from P'Hill.
I think you should take some soft side from P'Hill.
Because he's such a heart warming person.
What are you guys trying to play?
Last time, Hill was yelling at me.
For when Ter complimented me to him
and now you're--
Never mind.
Then...
I can go now, right?
Go make me another one.
Huh?
Make it until it's good.
Why are you still standing?
Go make one.
Here it is.
Not good.
Too bland.
Go make another one.
What?
You haven't taken a sip.
I can tell by looking at the color alone.
All coffees are the same, you should just---
It might be differ from one another.
Not good at all.
No matter how many times I've tried.
The smell alone is so sweet.
(You're doomed)
Please. This one is good for sure.
- You can go now.
- Hey.
What is up with you?
Why? Or you'd like to stay?
Who wants to be with a teaser?
I heard that.
I will go then.
You have no right to scold at me
or even bump up my debt.
I'm going now.
Try that.
This time
you might want to open a coffee shop for me.
Drink it up.
Why is it so sweet?
- Then remove it.
- Aha.
Then take it... distributor.
Say it after me.
Distributor
- Distributor
- With a bit of accent.
Put it here.
I'm back.
Hey you were gone for so long.
Should I deduct your salary?
Ughh P'Tun.
Please have a mercy on me.
You kinda deserved that.
Come here.
Come and learned how to make coffee with me.
Making coffee? Be my guest.
I will take a break for now.
Oh North.
I already talked to Chen, my relative, for you.
About the extra shift you want to take.
I will give you his contact, okay?
Thank you P’Thun.
You’re always so kind.
But are you gonna be okay?
It'll be late night shift everyday?
I think you should let me take you there for the first few times,
what do you think?
It’s fine.
I can find my own way.
But this is a bar…a drinking place kinda.
It’s not a club, more like sitting down and chill.
But let me take you still. I know the owner, okay?
Sure.
I will text the owner.
And if he answered, I will let you know.
Thank you, P’Thun.
No problem.
You can drink it.
You made it.
Okay.
I'll go pick you up today, okay?
What time will you be done with the class?
4pm.
You will be working again at 7pm.
Then we should have dinner first
before going to work.
Sure. See you.
Who’s that?
You scared me!
Who was that?
P’Thun.
3rd year. Management student.
He’s the owner of the coffee shop I work at.
He’ll take me to my new job today.
And why does he have to take you there?
He’s a relative to the owner.
He said he’ll take me there
for the first few times.
And how can I say no?
How are you going back today?
Are you gonna have him come pick you up too?
Yeah.
I guess so.
If not, how am I gonna go back?
Hey wait a min.
Is he trying to hit on you?
So? Is he?
Between 2nd year meds student.
and 3rd year management.
So what’s the verdict?
It has to be 2nd year meds student.
Cause I’m a shipper for these two.
I’m not choosing anyone.
P’Johan will be disappointed you said that.
Never in a million years to let us go early,
but today she does.
Yeah.
What are you guys doing after?
Do you wanna go have lunch? I’m hungry.
Sure. What about you, North?
You guys go ahead. I will go with P’Thun.
Huh?
I think he’s definitely trying to hit on you.
What about you?
Do you wanna come hang with us first?
You guys go.
I think I will stop by at the club.
See you.
What is up with him?
Did I just upset him or something?
No, you didn’t.
What the hell?
Is that dragon? Looks fun.
It's the cloud. The sky. Look.
- The sky is there. Stays there.
- Hey.
Just move!
- You'll get paint on me.
- Why do you have to be overprotective.
Aren’t you bored of drawing, Dao?
You do it everyday.
No.
Who would play around everyday like you?
You deserve that.
I wouldn’t let that pass,
if I were you.
Hey guys.
Let’s have dinner together this evening.
- Sure.
- Okay. Deal.
Yeah.
I already have a plan.
With who? P’Johan?
No, P’Thun.
He will take me to work.
And he asked me to join his dinner.
Hey scoot over. I wanna sit.
- There’s also space over there.
- You're talking too much.
Do you think P'Thun likes you?
Shipper spirit has already possessed you, huh?
What?
I only ship Johan and North only.
But really?
You don’t feel anything?
He padded your head
and always give you this kinda look.
To be honest,
I think deep down you know…
that he likes you.
Yeah.
Let's don’t think about it.
It might be awkward for everyone.
He might not trying to hit on me.
But we’re just thinking for ourselves.
And…
what if he really likes you,
what are you gonna do?
We’ll just brothers.
My ship has not sunk yet.
That’s great.
Why are you that happy?
Nothing.
sI just think it’s cute when you’re with P’Johan.
Are you done with your class, North?
Jo.
- You don’t have work anymore?
- Yeah. I cleared out some already.
Right.
Normally, we rarely sees your face in the class.
I’m surprised that he showed up today.
If I’m free, I’m always here.
Normally, you’re never free.
Always ask Hill to work for you.
Or should I ask you instead?
I know that you don’t wanna study.
But you’re already enrolled, you should be more responsible.
His fatherhood spirit is here.
You’re such a whiner.
- I’m gonna go.
- Hey.
To where?
Buy some coffee.
I’m out front.
At the gear courtyard.
I’m sorry to keep you waiting.
I wanted to be the one who waits.
Not you.
Why?
I wanna score some points with you.
Just kidding.
I just don’t like people to wait for me.
See you.
Yeah.
Where are you?
At the faculty.
Buy me a coffee. I will pick you up.
What coffee?
I'm not free,
but I guess I'll buy one for you.
Why are you not free?
Forget it. I'll pick you up.
On my way.
Ughh does he ever listen to people?
- Can I please have one americano?
- Sure.
- Please wait a moment.N- Yes.
I'm sorry, P'Thun.
I don't think I could make it.
Oh why? I'm almost there.
I'm so sorry.
I have something urgent came up.
Do you still want me to take you to the bar?
I'll go there by myself. I'm sorry.
You owe me a meal.
Sorry.
Here's your coffee.
- Here.
- Thank you.
I've arrived. At the front.
Your coffee.
Thank you.
And who did you have a plan with?
P'Thun, but you probably don't know him.
Um. I don't.
And where were you plan to go with him?
Dinner.
He's the owner of the coffee shop I work at.
He was gonna take me to work today.
Work?
Yes.
I got a new job.
He's a relative to that one place too.
Which place?
SeoulOut.
A bar?
Yes. You know?
Um.
And where are we going?
Get out.
Are we having dinner?
You want to have dinner, right?
P'Hill always bring me here.
Didn't know
that you always come here too.
What does Hill normally buy you?
Just normal stuff.
Meals, snacks.
But I normally don't order a lot.
I feel bad.
That's why money never ran out.
Huh?
What was that?
Can I borrow your phone?
I forgot mine in the car.
Why are you with Johan?
Is he doing anything to you?
Do you want me to pick you up?
Excuse me.
You're not gonna eat?
I will.
And you're not?
I'm not hungry.
You've been busy?
Even so,
I want you to eat something.
I only see you drink coffee
whenever I meet you.
Why?
Are you trying to reduce your debt?
Ugh.
I'm just worried about you.
How can you
take my kindness for granted?
But it's not working right?
You always watch me eat.
And always drink coffee when I see you.
i just want you to eat too.
I will eat later.
Just hurry up and eat.
I will drop you off after.
At work?
Just eat.
Then..
I won't hold back.
Are you taking me to work?
Hey wait.
This is not the way to my work.
And who told you I'm gonna take you to that bar?
And where are you taking me?
I have to work.
Back to your dorm.
Why?
I already told then I will start my first day today.
What did I tell you?
I won't ever let you work in a bar.
Oh.
Why did P'Johan dropped you off?
I thought it was gonna be P'Thun?
Hmm?
Why are you smiling like that?
Nothing. You guys are cute.
Long story.
It's okay. You don't have to tell me.
But I know that P'Johan picked you up.
That already makes me happy.
What a good captain for my ship.
And why are you not working?
Because of your Johan.
He won't allow me to work there.
And he just dropped me off here.
He also threaten to add more debt.
Why would he do that?
Yeah.
I also don't understand.
Or should I just sneak out and go to work?
Well...
I already told them that I'll be working there tonight.
P'Thun gave me the reference too.
If I don't go,
that is like I break my promise.
But if you go, P'Johan will be super mad though.
Why would he be mad?
It's a good thing.
I get to work and make money to pay him back.
He cares about you. That's why.
He doesn't want Nong North to work hard
and get home so late.
What if something dangerous happened?
What would you do?
Dude.
You're so taking his side.
I have to be a loyal shipper, right?
Oh snd P'Thun texted me too.
He asked whether you're okay or not.
He said you replied him oddly.
- Text?
- Um.
What text?
How am I supposed to know?
Check your phone.
- Why are you with Johan? Is he doing anything to you?
- F*ck off.
Shit!
P'Jo. P'Jo.
Hello P'Chen.
North, where are you?
Er...I don't think I can go in to work today.
Oh why? What's wrong?
Nothing...it's just...
If it's not urgent please come help me.
I really need some help. I don't have enough people. Too late to find one now too.
Please North.
Fine.
I will go in.
Hey thank you so much, North.
See you.
Ter.
Help me.
I'm not asking you to do anything.
But just...
don't tell anyone that I will go to work today.
North. I'm gonna be honest with you.
I care about you.
You work in a bar, go home late at night.
I actually don't want you to go.
It's fine. I can take care of myself.
You know that.
Last time you also said this.
And came back with how many wounds?
- It's all gone now, isn't it?
- You want a new one?
I think a few more wounds would be nice.
But please...don't tell anyone.
Paan.
He's the new guy. First day here.
Please look after him.
Hey relax.
Just serve and clean the table.
Nothing much.
If you have any questions, ask Paan.
- Okay?
-Okay.
See you.
Hi.
I'm Paan.
Hi I'm North.
Are you still in school?
1st year.
Woah and you're not tired working while studying?
Not really.
I normally do part time jobs all the time.
Pretty relax.
Then..
you go change at the back first.
And you'll come help me serve today.
You can ask me anytime.
Okay.
- This way?
- This way. This way.
- Order please.
- Yes.
Where's my food?
I've been waiting for so long already.
Please wait a moment.
It's fine. I'll handle it.
Thank you.
So? Are you exhausted?
We have many people today.
Still manageable.
Oh.
He's new?
This is Day.
He also works here.
And this is North.
He just started today.
Hello.
What are you studying?
Engineering.
Wow.
You must be popular.
Not really.
You're not seeing anyone?
No.
Then I can hit on you then?
- Please don't.
- Why?
You said that you're not seeing anyone.
Can you give me a chance?
- Cause you're cute.
- Hey I'm sorry.
I think...
let's not do that.
I just...
don't like it.
Stop teasing him.
I'm not.
I actually want to go out with him.
Day.
Why?
Excuse me.
Where are you?
Outside.
At 10pm?
With who?
With friends.
Where are you?
North.
Serve table 6 and clean table 8 too.
Sure.
What's up?
Why are you draging us out?
I'm bored.
You're bored?
Stop it, Mr.Know it All.
Jsut order and eat.
What happened earlier this evening?
Coffee from Engineering is that good?
Good 'til you have to rush there?
My business. Not yours.
And why do you want us here tonight?
I said I'm bored.
I'm sorry.
The number you have dialed cannot connected at this time.
Shit.
3 Missed calls.
I'm f*cked.
P'Prang,
did P'Johan add more debt to my account?
No.
What did you do?
Nothing. I just forgot to text him back.
It's just some texts. You'll be fine.
I once didn't text him back for a day.
Nothing happened.
If it's urgent, he will usually call.
But he called me 3 times.
That's odd.
Normally, he call once only even if it's urgent.
Oh you're still here?
I will soon.
Okay. Get home safely then.
Yes.
You guys are just gonna stay quiet like this?
Do you like liars?
You wanna speak now?
Hey don't ingterrrupt him.
He's finally speaking.
Why?
Who lies to you?
Is it what I think it is?
Probably.
Then you don't need to ask him further.
Why?
What are you guys talking about?
Can you help make me understand?
He wouldn't answer you, even if you asked.
Excuse me.
Can I have your LINE?
My friend likes you.
No, you cannot.
There you go.
Hill, what's wrong with you?
- Are you jealous?
- Jealous your ass.
Why didn't give her his LINE?
The tiger is about to remove his fangs and claws.
(Idiom: Quit being a player)
Why are you home so late?
The bar closed at midnight.
I had to ride my motorcycle here too.
It was so dark.
And the road was so secluded.
Not sure anybody was riding on the back with me or not.
Stop it. What are you talking about?
Dude look.
P"Johan went out tonight.
- Hey.
- But that's not your bar.
If he came to my bar,
I would have more debt by now.
I think I'm gonna call P'Hill.
So I can ask him
whether there's anyone hitting on your Johan.
Hello?
- Why did you put him on speaker?
- Cause I'm gonna ask him about P'Johan for you.
Yes. How is it?
Are you having fun?
Not really.
The one who dragged me here
just sit here and being pouty.
You mean P'Johan?
Um.
But never mind.
P'Hill.
Has there been anyone hitting on P'Johan?
Yes there was.
But I got rid of them.
Why do you ask?
Oh.
Nothing.
Well...
I asked for my friend.
Oh I see.
And what are you doing?
Why aren't you asleep?
Just chilling.
What about North?
He's with me here.
Why? What's the matter?
Nothing. Just wondering a little.
- You have a class at 9am, right?
- Yes.
I will pick you up. You sohuld go to bed now.
Sure. Sweet dream.
Sweet dream.
That's it.
You can now be at ease.
There's no one can hit on P'Johan.
P'Hill is a cockblocker.
You can be rest assured now.
No worries.
When did I get worried though?
You're so tight lipped.
I just wanna tease you and all.
This one?
Is the reason you have to go out of you way
to get coffee from Engineering?
What did he lie to you about?
He sneaked out to do part time job.
And how do you know that he's lying?
Right.
I drove passed.
Or drove by to check?
Wait.
Sneaking out to work late,
drives my friend crazy this much?
It's a bar.
But he tries to make money
to pay you back, doesn't he?
Yes, but...
bar is a risky place to work.
Then you send someone
to watch over him in your 'son of a mafia' way.
You're talking too much, Hill.
You guys don't understand.
Is it that difficult to say that you care?
Yeah.
I think your friend is in deep trouble.
Go in the woods.
Hide there. Here they come!
Ugh. You don't listen to me. They're coming!
Nice!
Nice. Come on.
- Woah.
- North.
- Dude.
- Huh?
Have you seen this?
I'm outside of your dorm.
Get down here.
I told you to not go anywhere, didn't I?
Ter.
Where are you taking me?
You sleep here.
You're gonna borrow mine, aren't you?
So protective. That?s the shirt of your soon-to-be boyfriend huh?
Stop it right there.
Why this one?
He's the type that Jo has a soft spot for.
Ter, you don?t know anything about Hill's grandma, do you?
About P'Hills grandparents,
Can you please tell me?