Hey but my relatives just opened a new place.
They're hiring too.
- Are you interested?
- I'm in.
North. I'm gonna be honest with you.
You work in a bar, go home late at night.
I actually don't want you to go.
You're not seeing anyone? Then I can hit on you then?
Excuse me.
Sneaking out to work late,
drives my friend crazy this much?
You guys don't understand.
Is it that difficult to say that you care?
- Dude! Did you see this?
- Huh?
Ter!
What?
You scared me.
Check this out.
P'Jo said he's waiting for me out front.
Huh!?
You invited him over?
Why would I do that?
- And why is he here?
- How am I supposed to know?
Why are you here?
I'm here to get you.
I give you 10 mins.
Can I shower first?
Sure. Pack for a sleepover too.
Sleepover?
Dude.
Ask him where is he taking you?
Wait...where are you taking me?
Ter.
He read but doesn't text me back.
What should I do?
What are you gonna do now?
Can I say no to him?
North...
do you think you have that kind of option hmm?
Do I have to come up there to get you?
He's rushing me now.
Fine fine. Let me just shower for a sec.
- Ter.
- Huh?
Put my stuff in the bagpack for me.
I have to shower.
But...what stuff do you want me to pack?
Anything. Just pack for me.
This one first then.
What do you need, North?
Uniform, books, and...
Err...some shoes for me too.
And what else?
Whatever you think it's necessary.
Here.
- My books?
- Already in there.
- Portable charger?
- All good.
- I also pack sunscreen and repellent for you.
- Huh?
Why did you pack me those?
Cause you said
you have no idea where's he taking you.
You have to be prepared for all kinds of situation.
That's crazy.
I have a class tomorrow. How can I go out of town?
You never know.
Just take it.
Hurry up.
He's rushing me again.
I'm gonna go now.
See you.
Will you be alright?
Weird.
This is so not you.
You would normally be so happy
if I go out with P'Johan.
Huhh. Why?
Are you sad that I don't ship you guys?
It's not like that.
It's not that I don't ship,
but I'm just worried for you.
If there's anything happened,
first one to call is me. Okay?
Sure.
You'll be the first person I'll call.
- I gotta go.
- Yeah.
Why so slow?
I tried my best.
Get in the car.
- Where are you taking me?
- I said get the car.
Buckle up too.
Your phone?
Do you want me to pick up?
Who is it?
May.
You don't have to answer.
It's fine. I can answer it.
Hello?
Jo why don't you text me back?
He's busy. He's driving.
And who is this?
You probably don't know me.
Can you put him on speaker? I wanna talk to him.
You can actually talk to me.
P'Johan is driving.
Can you ask him why he doesn't text me back?
P'Jo.
- Why don't you text back?
- You don't text me back. Not me.
No!
It's she who asked why you don't text her back.
He's busy.
Busy? Working?
and why did I see him at the bar?
I don’t wanna be over the line, cause we made an agreement.
But it’s like…
P’May…
Huh?
You should stop talking to P’Jo.
And start talking to me instead.
I’m still single.
Wait up.
Are you mad at me or something?
Are you jealous?
Well…
I was just kidding.
Yeah I'm jealous.
Wait for me.
Where have you been?
I…
- was out side.
- Where?
- To a restaurant.
- With who?
With friends but…
You probably don’t know them.
Is he gonna put more debt on my account?
Hey!
Where is it?
What are you doing?
Looking for my wallet.
But I think I forgot it at home.
You forgot your wallet...
But you brought a mosquito repellent?
Well…
I thought
you might take me camping on the mountain.
So I brought this just in case.
And..
you’re not working.
Why are you asking?
Cause…
I thought that you want me to hang with you
while you work.
Then why am I here?
Am I right?
Err…so…
Do you have a blanket?
I'm kinda...
sleepy already.
It’s in the closet.
Sure.
Why don't you go the other way?
What?
Are you gonna sleep on the couch?
Yeah.
And…
you think you’ll be okay there?
Sure.
This couch...
...is softer than the cutting board
back in my dorm.
He's giving me headache.
What’s wrong with him?
Amen.
- Nao. On your right.
- Yeah yeah. I saw.
- Help me.
- Yeah I’m coming.
Yeah like that.
Damn-- Ugh.
Hello what’s up?
Why are you calling me so late?
I know that you’re still awake.
Help.
I can’t sleep.
Hey hey, Suer.
I got shot.
There!
Okay so what’s up?
Are you with Ger?
Who is it?
It’s me, Suer.
(Suer in Thai means tiger)
North, your best friend.
Stop messing with me.
My name is Tiger.
Wow. So I can’t call you that?
- But why…?
- North.
What is up with you?
You're talking too much.
I suddenly wanna see Friend Zone movie.
Should I ask Nao to go see it with me?
F*ck you, North.
Why?
Are you afraid that he’ll find out?
You stuck in a friend zone for years.
He probably knows by now.
If he were to find out,
it should be from me. Not you.
But…
If I got some green tea tomorrow,
I think that might be great.
Sure sir. I will buy one for you.
Then please shut up.
And never mentioned this again.
You know my secret
and now acting so big and cool.
Does that help me? No?
Cause I don’t understand.
What do you see in him?
How can you not see his cuteness?
But that’s good.
Just leave him be. Go away.
He’s not suspecting or anything
that you’re sneaking out to talk like this?
It’s because of you.
Just shush it.
And why are you calling?
I cannot sleep
cause I'm scared of creepy stuff.
I need to talk to someone.
You can talk to me.
No, I want to talk to my friend!
Now, I’m dead.
I’m sorry.
North, did he hang up?
Can I talk to him?
Here.
Hello?
What’s up?
I’m really scared man.
I cannot sleep.
I’m so anxious wherever I look.
I’m afraid that there might be…
Ghosts?
Damn it. Don’t say that!
What?
Aren’t you with Ter?
I’m actually at P’Johan’s condo.
I know what you’re thinking.
But it’s not like that.
I haven’t said anything.
And how come you ended up there?
It’s a long story.
I will tell you about it later.
Hey.
My battery is running low. Hang on a sec.
Shit!
What?
My uniform is so crinkled.
I thought something bad happened.
Then go iron it.
Whenever I iron it myself,
it always end up crinkled.
You are at his place,
then you can borrow his jacket.
I can’t.
I do not dare to do it.
Then you just wear your crinkled shirt like that.
What are you doing?
Ghost. Ghost. Ghost.
Ugh!!
You scared me.
You’re still awake?
Cause you’re loud.
I’m sorry.
Dude I gotta go.
I cannot sleep.
Yes?
Can you fix me something to eat?
Are you like this often? Cannot sleep?
Sometimes.
And what do you usually do?
I'd work until I'm tired
and fall asleep.
Why would you choose to be in meds school...
even though you have a family business?
My mom applied it for me.
And I got in.
So I have to take it.
You're probably always tired huh?
I can handle it.
Do you want some warm milk?
I will heat it up for you.
Milk and some honey.
I heard that drinking milk with honey before bed
will help you to have a better sleep.
You always make things so sweet, don't you?
Huh?
Me?
How do you know?
If there's nothing else,
I'll go to bed now.
Good night.
Where are you taking me?
Hey wait!
Sleep here.
It's alright.
I can sleep outside.
You were loud when you were outside.
I can't sleep.
Wake up.
Morning already?
Almost 7am now. I'm running late already.
7am?
Why are you up so early?
Go change. Hurry up.
I have class in the afternoon.
I will wait outside. Don't be long.
I'm so sleepy.
Wanna borrow mine, right?
Oh thank you.
You're done.
We can go now.
Why is he in such a rush?
- Why are we taking this one today?
- I'm in a hurry.
Here.
Why are you so slow?
Hop on.
Hold on tight.
You're that scared?
Look at the way you drive.
- Right. I'm gonna go to class now.
- Hey and...
What about me?
I have class in the afternoon.
Do you wanna go to my class with me?
What am I gonna do in your class?
No.
I'll call my friends to come get me.
Fine. I'll go now.
P'...you forgot your money in your jacket.
You can keep it.
Keep it?
Why would you do that?
You forgot your wallet, didn't you?
You're really giving it to me?
You're not gonna add to my debt, right?
North?
Last night was not enough?
You have to wake me in the morning too?
I don't know who else to call.
So what's up?
Dude.
Can you help me with something?
What is it?
Pick me up.
P'Johan left me here on campus.
I have class in the afternoon though.
Wait.
Shit!
What the hell, Nao?
That hurts.
- I'm back.
- What's going on?
Suer talked in his sleep
and put his arm around me.
That's why
I was uncomfortable all night.
But I kicked him out of the bed already.
Calm down.
Get up here.
What time do you have class?
9am why?
Can you go pick North up
from meds faculty?
Why do I have to do that? Tell me?
Did you hear that?
He said
'Why do I have to do that? Tell me?'
Ask him for me
'Are you sure you said that?'
'Or he wants me to tell?'
He said...
'Are you sure you said that?'
'Or you want him to tell?'
Tell what?
What are you guys talking about?
Let me talk to him.
What's up with you guys?
North.
What a terrible liar.
Normally I'm pretty good at it,
if you do not call.
My poor little Tiger.
Don't forget about my green tea.
Sure. I will buy it for you sir.
I will go pick you up.
Here.
Hop on shithead.
Wear this too.
What are you looking at?
Just hop on.
Go.
So? How was it this morning
when you got kicked out of bed?
It's like...
a cat just kicked me.
Please.
Captain of the football team.
Prom king of Engineering.
You're nuts.
It hurts. Why would you ask that?
- It's because of you.
- Who in the world would think...
that you'll be this pathetic.
Sleep talking and then huged him like that?
Just wait for my turn.
I'm looking forward to my turn too, my friend.
Go.
Go buy me green tea.
- I wanna drink some green tea.
- Yes sir.
Prang: North. What did you do to Johan?
Why?
Johan added 3 more debts on your account.
Huh!?
3 times?
Yes. That's why I ask what did you do?
If you'd like to trasnfer the money, just let me know.
What did I do to make him added more?
P' Why did you do that to me?
Here.
Thank you.
Just leave it right there.
- I'm gonna go to my class now.
- You can go. I'll have mine in the afternoon.
- Afternoon?
- Um.
And where will you be?
You wanna come with me?
No, you can go. I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
You think I care about you?
Just go away.
Ger.
Thank you.
Are you really gonna read and not reply?
About the additional debts?
You gave me money
and added more debt like this?
Jo.
You're not going to have your coffee
from engineering today?
With that face,
he probably already met his nong in the morning.
Ton.
Your friend is about to quit being a player.
But he's so tight-lipped
...unlike his actions.
That's not surprising that he's tight-lipped.
But I'm just wondering,
he's not like this with the others,
But why this one?
To be honest, it's a long story.
Like...
He’s the type that Jo has a soft spot for.
How?
All weak in his knee.
Like more than just a type.
Hill. You're talking too much now.
Don't get me started with your story and Ter's.
Wow what is it?
Hey.
I'm here to interview you.
Do you have a min?
Sure.
- Should we do it there?
- Okay.
What are you guys doing?
- Working on the report.
- Oh.
It's not just a report.
More like someone is missing someone.
Who is it?
You cannot tell us, right?
Maybe I will tell, when I'm successful.
Do you think that person is watching this right now?
Probably.
Would you like to say something to that person?
I miss you.
Which faculty is that person studying?
Can you tell us?
Do you wanna guess?
Meds students have to be with nurses for sure.
No.
Then management?
Engineering?
No, I'll give you one more try.
I'll just randomly guess.
Vet student?
Correct.
We finally got a clue guys!
Last question
before I let you continue your study.
If you made it with this relationship,
what would you like to tell this person?
I'll do my best to take care of you.
Why am I not that person?
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I'll do my best to take care of you~
- I'll do my best to take care of you.
- Oh it has to be that tone?
Ter.
Hello P'Thunmild.
You're here for some drinks?
Yes.
Can I talk to you?
Sure.
How are you doing?
I'm good.
What about you? How are you?
Not so good.
It has always been you, hasn't it?
You know that I have a crush on Hill, right?
Always have.
Since high school.
But since then and until today...
Hill has never opened up his heart to anyone.
Except you.
But there's one thing I don't understand.
Why did you dump Hill?
I dumped him?
It was after the last orientation.
Hill was very sad.
P'Hill was the one who left me.
Hill left you?
Yes.
No way.
You didn't know about Hill's grandma, did you?
Hill.
That's enough.
I know about your grandma.
It's okay.
Everything will be okay.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Can I stay a little longer?
You have drunk a lot already.
He's gone.
He left me.
What about P'Hill's grandma?
What happened?
It's nothing.
There's something I don't know, right?
Why he has never told me anything?
I don't know what actually happened...
...between you and Hill.
But what could be the reason...
for someone to keep hurtful feelings to himself,
if it's not because...
to protect someone he loves the most.
Would you excuse me?
I have to go.
Good bye.
Yes?
Are you done with your class?
I am.
I'll pick you up.
You have to work today, right?
Yes.
I'm working at the union right now.
Wait for a min. okay?
Oh I'm nearby.
I will talk to you then.
Sure.
Hey where are you going?
To see Ter.
Hey wait Hill.
You brought us here to work on the report,
but now you're leaving to see Ter?
- Um.
- You're just gonna dtich us like this?
No, I won't be long.
Oh and do you want me
to pick up your guy?
No.
Stop right there, Mr. president.
Can I have a moment?
Professor is looking for you.
Will it take long?
Ter is waiting for me.
Not long. Just a min.
Let's go.
Text me when you're done with your class.
X,Y what are these?
Can you explain what is it?
P'Bua.
- Oh hi, Ter!
- Hello.
What's up?
Have you seen P'Hill?
Hill?
I saw him just now with his med friends.
He's probably at the union.
- Bye.
Oh Ter.
Hi.
What are you guys doing here?
We're bored of our faculty.
Anyways...have you seen P'Hill?
Oh he just left not long ago.
A professor is looking for him.
He left with Peem just now.
But he'll be back soon.
Can I ask you guys something?
Um.
So...
can you tell me more
about P'Hill's grandparents?
I think...
...we should just tell him. It's already this far.
You think it's a good idea, Fah?
I think Hill is not going to like this.
He doesn't like to tell other people about his family.
He's not gonna tell even if I ask?
Hey it's not like that.
How can we explain?
Hill is always like this.
He likes to keep it to himself.
But what he wants from you...is to trust him.
When he's done dealing with his problems,
he'll come back to you.
Sure.
He keeps to himself like this...is not fair.
But...
what do you want to know about his grandparents?
Everything.
What should I know?
Have you met his grandpa?
Speaking about him gives me goosebump.
Did you know...
that his grandpa thinks
I'm gonna lie and steal money from Hill?
I was so upset.
I also have money, you know?
Wait Jo. I don't think his grandpa was afraid
that you're gonna take money from Hill.
Right?
But I think he's more afraid
that his grandson will turn out bad like you.
- What the f*ck?
- Um.
What about you, Arthit?
Any interesting story?
For sure. I do have some stories.
What story?
He said I'm a bad kid. Drinks and smokes.
Clubbing. Nightlife
...not suitable to be his gradson's friends.
- But he's right, isn't he?
- Hmm?
Just like that.
I think out of all of us,
there's only Fah that he likes.
Of course,
I'm such a good person.
His grandpa is not on a good term
with you guys?
Something like that.
He's a stubborn old man.
And he's like this with Hill's friends.
Cannot imagine what would it be like for Hill's lover.
But I think Hill is uncomfortable too.
He apologized to us for so many times.
So I think...
just forget his grandpa.
Hill is our friend. Not his grandpa.
And since his grandma got into a car accident,
seems like his conditions are getting worse everyday.
It's like he's putting his stress and rage on his grandson.
I feel bad for Hill too.
So his grandma got into a car accident?
It happened...I think last year.
His grandma got hit by a car.
Pretty severely injured.
They have to cure her abroad.
Still in a coma until today.
Not only his grandpa,
but both of his parents and Hill, himself...
kinda also lost their ways.
If his grandma wakes up,
everything might be better than this.
Hey!
We told him all of it.
Hill must be so pissed at me.
P'Jo.
Do you remember when exactly from last year
that all these happened?
Probably from February to March.
Around that.
After the last orientaton.
Ter.
Yes?
Shall we go?
Yes.
I'm gonna get going guys.
Bye.
- Gotta go.
- See you.
See you dude.
Ter.
Yes?
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
P'Hill.
Yes?
I will wait for you.
Whenever you're ready,
you can tell me everything.
Let's go.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Jo.
North.
Can I borrow your jacket?
What jacket?
The one you're wearing. I'm cold.
(Nao in Thai means cold)
Oh I'm North.
Nice to meet you.
Very funny.
Come on. I'm freezing here.
And why do I have to let you borrow?
Oh you're so protective huh?
- It's your boyfriend's jacket huh?
- Stop it.
Come on.
Just put it over the both of us.
- Why are you so pushy?
- Give it to me.
Why don't you borrow Ger's?
No, I don't wanna bug him.
Don't wanna bug him?
You just kicked him out of the bed this morning.
- I'll text him. Let me do it.
- North.
Stay still.
Come on. Give it to me.
I'll just borrow yours.
Just let me.
- We both can have each of the sleeve.
- Just wait.
Dude.
Can you pass this to Duennao?
That guy told me to give this to Duennao.
Oh thank you.
- You're always meddling..
- Hey.
You said you're cold.
We took his jacket.
Are you sure he's not cold?
It's fine. He likes cold.
(Cold = Nao in Thai)
I mean the weather.
What are you talking about?
Almost slip out.
Text me when you're done with your class.
Almost done.
Ger is not going back with you?
Computer engineering has another class.
Are you straight to work after this?
Yeah I have to.
You can do it man.
You fight for your life, but sometimes life fights you back.
- We're gonna go then.
- Yeah. See ya.
- Bye bye.
- Bye see you.
- See you.
- Bye.
What are you doing after class?
Probably will have some food
then go to work.
How are you going to work?
The purple bus.
Then come with me.
Look up.
Ja came to see me. She said she needs to talk.
Can we star over again?
Can you tell me what happened when you disappeared from me?
Dude. I'm worried about you.
I don't want you to work at that bar.
Oh hey.
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm gonna make you mine.