BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM'S 100-YEAR BUILDING
- Come on.
- Go on.
Hey, No.
Don't do it.
There is a certain kind of madman
who happens to gain power.
They always try to cover up
their own wrongdoings
with other people’s scandals.
But…
when an elephant dies,
can you really cover the whole thing
with a lotus leaf?
BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM'S 100-YEAR BUILDING
THIS AREA IS UNDER RENOVATION.
IN 25 DAYS, BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM'S
100-YEAR BUILDING WILL OPEN
WILL THE 100-YEAR BUILDING
REALLY BE ABLE TO OPEN FOR USE?
Bangkwai Witthayakhom's 100-Year Building
has officially been handed over
following renovations.
But can it really be used?
The load-bearing columns
have major cracks in them.
The cement is below spec.
The steel doesn't meet standards.
This reeks of corruption.
Did you see what the Exclamation group
exposed about the 100-Year Building?
- How much do you think they embezzled?
- The photo is obviously the headmaster.
She's wearing red all over.
There's only one person like that.
- They're still going to open the building?
- That's scary.
Who would dare use the building?
Something's definitely going on.
Look at that.
Did they repair it, or just tear it down?
Yeah, what kind of cement is that?
Why did it crack so easily?
Look at that. The steel must be fake.
What about the other buildings?
Where are you?
I see Tae.
STORAGE ROOM
NO ENTRY
Everyone, the president's going inside.
EURO PANG
Who called this meeting in this spot?
Why aren't we using
the rooftop of Building 6 like before?
Weren't you the one
who typed that in the group?
I'm not that out of it, Wanda.
You're definitely out of it.
SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING
AT THE STORAGE ROOM UNDER BUILDING 2
Hey…
That wasn't me.
Are you teasing me?
I'll show you.
SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING
AT THE STORAGE ROOM UNDER BUILDING 2
Look. It wasn't me.
You're joking, right?
Beng, was it you?
Not me.
- Shit.
- What?
Someone else is in our chat room. Look.
Oops. I got caught.
Hey.
Whose voice was that?
Hi.
I'm Nanno.
I'm a new student here.
Mind if I join the party?
Who sent you? The headmaster?
No.
I came to help you, Pankham.
Oh? You two know each other?
I know the whole team.
Hey, guys, what's going on in there?
Shit.
The Boy Scouts are here.
Shit, do you have anything
you haven't told us?
I don't know her.
What are you doing here?
Where I sit is none of your business.
Do you see this badge?
I received orders directly
from the headmaster
to monitor those who undermine
and sabotage the school.
And I have a feeling
I can smell the rotten
Bangkwai Exclamation group around here.
Can you smell it too?
Other than your bad breath,
I don't smell shit.
‪NO ENTRY
‪Shit.
I think we're busted.
Hey. It's coming
from the front of the school.
Shit.
- Hurry.
- Damn it.
- Slowly.
- Sit there.
Be quiet.
No, no.
- Let go first.
- Alright.
Who's this?
Hi, Tae. I'm Nanno.
Nanno who?
Your gang is amazing.
The Exclamation gang.
You want to expose the corruption
in the building's renovation, right?
I have a plan. I'll help.
BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM
What happened?
- Shit.
Teacher, now the school's name is Bang…
BANGKHUAY WITTHAYAKHOM'S 100-YEAR BUILDING
Students, go to your classrooms!
Now. Go.
You too. Run!
How obscene.
#CORRUPTRENOVATIONWILLKILLUSALL
Instead of fixing their wrongdoings…
IN 24 DAYS, BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM'S
100-YEAR BUILDING WILL OPEN
…evil people choose to cover it up
with something else
to make others obedient
and easier to control.
How cute.
HEADMASTER YAEM THATSARAI
This morning,
what were the students screaming about?
Nothing, Headmaster.
They were just screaming
about a shipped couple they follow.
Mr. Dobby, do you also feel
that these people
are hiding something from us?
Come in.
Well, hello.
The students are shocked by the news
from this secret page, Headmaster.
Look, Mr. Dobby.
Are you scared?
Why don't you go run around for a bit?
Go take a walk.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This new student sent me an email
about the Exclamation group.
They're just an underground page.
They make things up
without having any real facts.
But the news is already out.
And the students already believe it.
Deputy Headmasters, perhaps you're too old
to keep up with the students anymore.
Maybe it's time
to let the new student handle it instead.
Just a moment.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Don't disappoint Mr. Dobby and me.
Yes.
Wait, Nanno.
From now on, don't do that again, okay?
What do you mean?
How do I say this?
Normally,
we teachers are the headmaster's advisors.
HAVING A JOB AND A SALARY ISN'T
AS IMPORTANT AS HAVING GOOD COWORKERS
But suddenly,
you reported directly to the headmaster
- like we are--
- Just useless ornaments?
Yes, ornaments.
Hey, you.
I'll…
- Take her away first.
- You.
Nanno.
I know you're a smart student.
Having you help keep an eye on things
makes me very happy.
But from now on,
if you find anything,
could you tell me first?
Hmm.
So, Deputy Headmaster Kai, you also don't
like students going over your head, right?
I understand.
So now I'm curious.
What will you do about the news
that the Exclamation group released?
DEPUTY KAI, DEPUTY NOO,
DEPUTY NOK, DEPUTY TAO
NANNO
The famous Bangkwai school shipped couple
secretly unfollowed each other.
Is their relationship about to end?
They said a shipped couple
is about to break up.
- Is it the same one?
- Yeah, the same one.
WHY ARE THEY BREAKING UP?
Such a shame about this couple.
BB and Taetae are breaking up?
Are they really breaking up?
They were so cute together.
- THEY'LL MAKE UP SOON
- GIVE IT THREE DAYS
- They really are breaking up.
- What a pity.
Didn't you say you wanted to join us?
I already told you.
I have a plan.
Here it is.
I've become
the headmaster's special advisor.
Has any Exclamation member
ever gotten access like this?
Keep your eyes on the flagpole.
IN 23 DAYS, BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM'S
100-YEAR BUILDING WILL OPEN
Hey.
Students, move aside.
- Move aside.
- Go.
EVEN THE FLAGPOLE DIDN'T SURVIVE
#CORRUPTRENOVATIONWILLKILLUSALL
Corruption was even involved
in the building of the flagpole?
Damn, then how bad
must the 100-Year Building be?
That's scary.
Yeah. Why hasn't anyone
spoken out about it?
They say the headmaster
is the one behind the corruption.
Really?
The Exclamation group is amazing,
exposing the truth for our school.
Yeah. If it weren't for them,
we wouldn't even know.
I bet the headmaster and her deputies
can't sit still right now.
I bet everything will go quiet again soon.
- They're awesome. Who are they anyway?
- Yeah, I want to join them.
Yeah, so we can expose this corruption.
Do you think
the Exclamation group will get taken down?
Come in.
How did the Exclamation group
get this information?
The rigged bidding and locked specs
for the flagpole, right?
The contractor was Ruja Construction,
the same company that handled
the renovation of our 100-Year Building.
What a coincidence.
Not a coincidence.
I approved it myself.
That company does good work.
It's reliable.
We've used them for years.
And it just so happens
that Mrs. Ruja, the company's owner,
is your wife.
Well, the 100-Year Building
is exactly what its name says.
The structure
has been around for a long time.
How could I let
an unfamiliar company handle it?
Of course I had to choose
a company I trust.
Trusting your wife is a good thing.
I won't keep beating around the bush.
I'm the one responsible for this project.
And I've already signed off
on its completion.
- If the building can't open on schedule,
- I'll be in serious trouble.
- you'll be in serious trouble.
Checkmate.
I understand.
Could you recommend
a feng shui master for me urgently?
BANGKHUAY WITTHAYAKHOM'S 100-YEAR BUILDING
IN 20 DAYS, BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM'S
100-YEAR BUILDING WILL OPEN
NO ENTRY
Hey, guys, check out this live stream.
What live stream?
BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM SCHOOL
Damn.
What the hell is this?
This is the real reason.
Underneath here are inauspicious things.
- Someone did this.
- Look at this.
That means they have ill intentions
and malicious motives.
And this is their symbol.
Shit.
- Shit.
- What the hell?
Hey, that's an exclamation mark.
- Let's leave first. Go.
- Yeah.
‪-Nobel.
‪-No, come on.
Slowly, carefully.
Come on.
Get up.
What's wrong?
Nanno.
Nanno is one of us.
Nanno brought the Boy Scouts this way.
What do you mean one of us?
Hey, we have to run first.
All our group data is in here.
Shit.
Hey, this way, guys.
Hurry up.
Go.
- You guys can go.
- Exclamation group! Open the door.
- I know you're inside.
- We'll handle it.
- Open the door.
- Go, Beng, go.
- Hold on tight.
- If you don't open it, I'll break it down.
- I warned you. Open it.
- Careful.
Break it down.
Students,
these two are members
of the Exclamation group,
the group that spreads false accusations
about our school without any evidence.
Their claim that
the 100-Year Building will collapse
is completely false.
And I'm not speaking without proof.
I have invited someone
with authority on the matter
to speak to all of you.
Please welcome him.
Hello.
I am the engineer
responsible for the 100-Year Building.
I assure all students
that the 100-Year Building
has been renovated properly, according
to all civil engineering standards.
You can rest easy.
All the rumors circulating in this school
are fake news.
So, if you don't believe an engineer,
who will you believe?
Exactly.
Therefore, what these two did
deserves expulsion.
Shit.
Expel them.
- Yeah, expel them.
- Expel?
But…
I'm a kind person.
I can't just expel them like that.
So I'd like to give them one more chance.
Potae, open it.
This is the face of the Exclamation group
that spreads fake news
to destroy our school.
Now you've all seen
how many of them there are, right?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
And five.
The other three members
are standing here right now, right?
If either of you can tell me
who the other three are,
I will regard you as witnesses.
That means
you won't receive any punishment.
No, remember our ideals. Don't do it.
You don't need to say their names.
Just point at them.
No, don't do it.
Just point.
- Remember our ideals.
- Come on.
Point.
Tell us.
Hey, No.
Point.
Hey, No!
Don't do it.
Point at them.
Hey?
- Potae?
- Really?
- Damn you.
- You? What the hell?
Down with the corrupt!
Long live Exclamation!
Do it for me.
Destroy them.
Ugh!
These two are hereby expelled
from Bangkwai School immediately.
Take them away.
Get out. Get out.
- Get out.
- Damn, No. I love you.
Get out. Get out.
Get out.
IN 20 DAYS
IN 19 DAYS
NO ENTRY
5:30 P.M. - THIRD FLOOR COMPUTER ROOM
What do we do now?
We have to do it for Nobel and Tae.
We have to stop
the 100-Year Building from opening.
But our futures matter too.
If I get expelled now,
my dad will kill me.
But if the 100-Year Building collapses,
we'll be dead too.
And in that case…
we'd be dead for real.
The engineer already confirmed
that the building won't collapse.
You actually believe that headmaster?
You saw the condition yourself.
Did you forget already?
But we're not engineers.
Even if it really collapsed,
no one would care anyway.
Why should we gamble our futures for this?
It's okay, Beng.
If you're not comfortable with this
or if you want to quit…
I understand.
BANGKWAI WITTHAYAKHOM'S 100-YEAR BUILDING
Even if it really did collapse,
no one would care anyway.
NO ENTRY
5:30 P.M. - THIRD FLOOR COMPUTER ROOM
5:39 P.M.
Sorry. I ran into some Scouts,
so I had to take a detour.
I thought you weren't coming.
Shall we start?
Sure.
What was that sound?
Ugh, not her again.
Did you bring Nanno here too?
I didn't bring her. I came alone.
You're telling me
you came in and didn't see her?
Listen to me first, Wanda.
Pankham, I can't stand you anymore.
I can't believe you brought Nanno here.
Nanno, how long have you been there?
And how did you know we were meeting here?
What's wrong with you, Pankham?
You're still talking to her?
She already got
two of our friends expelled.
Wait, Wanda.
I have something to show you.
How did you get this?
I was hiding in that room.
Just like I was hiding in this one.
You didn't even know I was here.
I'll send it to you.
If the Exclamation group
releases this clip,
they're finished.
The engineer who spoke earlier was fake.
It was actually Potae
from the Scout group,
deepfaking someone's face.
- And the person behind it is…
- I am the engineer.
I assure all students…
If they keep insisting
on opening the building,
it will collapse for sure.
#CORRUPTRENOVATIONWILLKILLUSALL
IN 17 DAYS
Guys, come look at this.
The engineer was fake.
I told you.
Shit.
Deputy Kai is corrupt.
They even used AI to fake an engineer?
- Then the headmaster is corrupt too?
- One hundred percent.
IN 16 DAYS
That Exclamation group
still hasn't given up.
Our students aren't even
paying attention to this anymore.
But the pillar is right there.
And the repair budget is already used up.
I don't want the headmaster to find out.
Maybe the sacred spirits can help.
HAVING A JOB AND A SALARY ISN'T
AS IMPORTANT AS HAVING GOOD COWORKERS
Taetae and BB broke up
because of a third person.
Hey, who is it?
Did someone really cause them to breakup?
BB blocked Taetae. Or maybe someone
used black magic on them.
Do they really have to do this?
How can we help them?
The Sacred 100-Year Pillar
grants every wish.
Twisting the truth and diverting attention
are the art of those who control the game.
What are you doing?
The school said this pillar is sacred.
Don't you know?
Everyone in this school knows that.
Nanno, whose side are you actually on?
IN 5 DAYS
Take it.
Maybe this is all we can do.
Honestly, I've been thinking.
What are we even doing all this for?
No one cares.
But I want us to be wrong now.
Maybe that building
is actually strong enough.
Maybe we're just being paranoid.
IN 1 DAY
Today is a special day as we finally
reopen our 100-Year school building
after a long renovation.
The headmaster will now cut the ribbon
to officially open the building.
Students, please follow the arranged lines
and walk into the building in order.
Your homeroom teachers will lead the way.
Headmaster, please cut the ribbon.
Ready?
- Headmaster, this way, please.
- Alright.
Mr. Dobby, let's go.
All the materials used were brand new.
Students, please line up
before entering the building.
There are signs inside.
Go directly to your classrooms.
First row, you may proceed.
What are we even doing all this for?
No one cares.
Even if it really did collapse,
no one would care anyway.
The famous couple has broken up.
Twisting the truth
and diverting attention
are the art of those who control the game.
Now, Pankham.
BB, come with me.
- What?
- Hurry.
Are you excited? Hmm?
Alright.
I was thinking of putting
a photo here, Headmaster.
Oh, what photo?
Let's discuss it in your new office.
- Sure.
- Please go upstairs.
The photo would lead people
to your office.
Oh, alright.
BB, hurry.
What the hell?
Why did you block Taetae?
And why did you delete
the photos from Instagram?
It's none of your business.
Your office is on the top floor.
The view from up there is great.
What did Taetae do to make you angry?
Tell me.
Oh, did Taetae send you?
Hey, answer my question.
What did he do to make you mad?
- Just say it.
- Are you crazy?
Hey! What are you doing?
BB.
I'm sorry.
Can we get back together?
Hey.
BB and Taetae.
Let's go.
It's so beautiful.
Why do I feel dizzy?
Maybe it's because the pressure
in my ears is uneven.
Don't do this.
The whole school is watching us.
Mr. Dobby.
Deputy Kai,
is this building really safe?
Yes, it is.
Everyone, go! Hurry!
Everyone, run! Hurry!
Run!
Everyone, run! Move.
Here.
The 100-Year Building…
It has now become a monument
to the Exclamation group.
Have you thanked me yet?
I should thank you too, Pankham,
for your cooperation.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, NANNO?
THE SKY IS NICE TODAY.
HELLO, SKY. THE SKY IS NICE TODAY.
Because the school's interests
must be the same
as the students' interests.
Hello.
I'm Nanno. My number is two.
My policy is "One Idea, One Kiss."
- Nanno. Nanno.
- We found evidence of fraud
in the student council election.
Humans tend to repeat the same mistakes
over and over again.
What makes you think
you're better than everyone else?
CONGRATULATIONS, MR. PARADON TANGNAITHAM,
66TH STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon