You need to hold Rosario's dead
so that he will be in the sea.
But you need to put it in order to live.
So you don't have to die in the family.
Ate!
Tinesting.
Sinuri.
Siniyasat.
Sa SHIELD Soap.
Patay ang 99.9% ng bakteriya at virus.
Dili ba mga nurse at si mommy?
Iwala ako sa SHIELD.
SHIELD Antibacterial Soap.
Para maging masaya ang bloody week,
tignan niyo ang lockers niyo.
May pangalan dun na dapat niyang patayin bago matapos ang oras.
Kung wala kayong pangalan, kayo ang hinatulan.
Mia!
Kinala kita.
Hindi mo kayang pumatay.
Nanggol manong sirim.
Wala akong kasalanan.
Emergency to.
Pukasan niyo ang pinto.
I'm sorry, pero...
Pukasan niya, mistress.
Pukasan niyo yung kainik!
Kung ako sa'yo,
ilalagay ko yung tapong ko sa tama,
hindi sa maling lasong.
I hope...
she was worth it.
Bukay ni Mia yun.
Ano ba ang parusa?
Kamatayan.
Ngayong gabi,
ipapakilala ko sa inyo
ang bagong core leader ng Black Blood Gang.
Magsigawan!
Para kay Matthew!
Aba!
Aba! Aba! Aba!
May bisita yata tayo, boss.
Di daw siya aalis.
Hanggit di kayo nakakausap.
Up! Up!
Pinagbigyan mo pa talaga yung hambog na yun.
At talagang dinala mo pa sa hideout natin.
Alis mo niyo.
Anong kailangan mo?
Dito ako.
Para may pag-usap sa'yo.
Gusto kong sumali ng gang niyo.
Ano ang kaalam mo sa gang namin?
Pipirma ka lang?
Ang membro ka na?
Pagpasensya man na yung mga alaga kung pangat yung bati sa'yo.
Baid ka nga ulit nandito?
Gusto kong sumali ng Black Blood Gang.
Hm.
Why not?
We need as many members as we can get.
But, I say,
let's give her a long time.
Matthew Hart,
I commend your courage coming here on your own.
Especially the bloody knight?
I want to know your reason.
Oh.
Tanami ka.
Sige.
Gawin natin mas simple.
Sa isang salita,
anong gusto mo na may bibigay natin?
Power.
But power is not given.
It should be earned.
Well, well, well.
Alam mo,
dumanak muna ang dugo naming lahat
para lang mapabila sa pangkat na ito.
Ang ibig kong sabihin.
Ano?
Natatakot ka na ba?
Gusto mo na ba bumalik sa dorm nyo?
Isa pang salita mo?
Baka hindi lang yung buhok mo ang magkulay dugo.
Okay.
Move, guys.
Look, huwag muna kami pahiya.
Huwag mo okay pahiya.
Huwag mo okay pahiya, Luke.
Huwag mo's.
Huwag mo...
Huwag mo!
Huah!
Huoh!
Huwua!
Huah!
Huuh!
Oh
Can I help I?
I'll see you next time.
What?
Because of me?
Because of you?
Maybe you are a valid reason.
You know why?
Because you are giving us something.
I'll see you next time.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch my friend.
I can't promise you anything.
As long as he stays out of my way.
He will be safe.
I'll see you next time.
You should go now.
Why didn't you leave me alone?
I won't be able to leave you there.
You're on you.
Is that what friends do? Lie? Pretend? Keep secrets? That's not friendship. That's bullshit.
You don't know anything.
Because you don't talk about anything.
We don't have to tell you because we don't want you to die.
Dave, we're all here. That's not and will never be a good enough reason.
You don't have to tell anyone.
We're all here.
That's a time.
Matthew, why?
Hindi ko kayang tumingin sa kanya na parang wala akong nalaman.
I don't know.
But why are you angry?
What's your name?
I don't know.
It's not.
It's like you're good.
It's like you're good now.
I think in your body.
Have you been sick?
I don't know what you're talking about, Ms. Shawn.
What's that?
Do you even say something?
Are you still not done talking to your cat?
Ah!
He said,
you're so cute.
Really?
Are you still cute, Matt?
Never mind.
You're still cute.
I love you.
I love you!
You're still cute.
Oh, my gosh.
Come on, Hoy.
Can you see it?
Hoy!
What is that?
She's standing here.
Do you?
Hoy!
What are you talking about?
Please, please, please.
Please, please.
Please, I can't wait for Mama.
Please, I'm supremo.
Please, please.
Please.
I'm going to get there!
No.
Just in my bed and process, please.
Please, dear.
Please, I'm like...
Why do you know our actions?
Lord.
You just have to go, Lord.
Don't go, Lord.
I'm going to go.
What are you doing today?
Don't go, Lord.
You can do it.
Please.
Don't go, children.
Why are you doing heavy기를 with eyes?
Stop!
Sobram,
layin mo ako dito.
Patayin mo lang ako.
Patayin mo lang ako!
I'm going to talk to you, right?
We're already waiting.
I don't want you. You're only waiting for me.
Can we try to do something?
Can we try to save them?
You'll die.
Please. Just this once.
Z... Z...
Please. Just this once, please.
Fine. Fine. Just this once.
Please.
Fine.
I'll take it.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
To Pramo.
Thank you, Pramo.
Thank you...
I'm still the Supremo of this school.
But I also know that if I want to protect myself, I can protect myself.
I can take care of myself.
Is it true?
Do you believe me?
That's not the Zane Show that I've known.
You've ignored that.
You've never seen it.
That wasn't Zane.
That wasn't my secretary.
I'm still Zane, Sean.
The weak have no place here.
They're nothing but garbage.
I've known him.
I have no place in my attention.
I've never seen it.
I've never met him.
I've never met him with my friends.
care of myself I'll be the judge of that but I'm sign taekwondo anytime SSG
office anytime you're free after the last period
humanda ka
na nangyayang bumalik na sekretary ko
hindi ba niya na ako samahan
saan sa Promo?
sa admin
para tuluin na natin maligtas sa magina
I love you, Violet and Francisco.
What a rare occurrence, Mr. President. What brings you here?
I'll speak plainly. Exception for Miss Aya.
Exemption?
Mr. President, there are rules and precedents to respect.
But who am I to turn down a favor from a Supreme Student Government President?
But I'm just wondering, why did you suddenly turn away?
There are still limits, Madam. Even in a hellhole like this university.
Mr. President, you must never forget the only rule of your position.
That you must never get involved with anyone.
You are not allowed to make friends. Never let your emotions hinder your path.
You don't have to worry about me. I know what I'm doing.
I really do hope so. Okay then. I will give them the exemption.
You tell them that they can breathe.
For now.
I'm nothing like him.
I guess you have a guardian aid.
Angel mission.
At sama naman na po ulit yan.
Sinandaan niya lang ako, ma'am.
Papalayain ko din, ma'am yan.
Sa lalong madaling panahon.
Tapos na ba tayo?
Sa ngayon, mata.
Attention students, the locker game is now concluded.
Any pending business is void.
Carry on with your remaining classes.
Tapos na.
Sa ngayon.
Pero hindi pa ito kapayapaan.
Do you have any suggestions, Michelin?
Huh?
Are you with us, Miss Sean?
Ikaw dapat ang nagpa-plano nito.
Ikaw ang secretary.
We are just here to approve your suggestions.
I guess leisure activities and games should be fun.
Unisimum.
Then write it.
I'm first.
You may not.
Bye.
Okay.
No.
I must say, this is a brilliant idea.
Is there no objections to this list?
Then I approve.
I keep telling you, she's more than qualified for this position.
If there isn't anything else, may I ask to take my leave?
Yes.
I think we have what we need, Ms. Chong.
You may go.
What are your thoughts?
Plus...
Napaka...
Komplikado ng mga baday, no?
Komplikado na nga.
Pinapakomplikado pa natin.
What the fuck do you want?
Busy.
Oh, huwag harsh mo naman.
Well...
I was just...
Wondering about a few things.
And maybe you could help me out.
Why do...
Feelings...
Suddenly change?
What are you trying to say?
I'm sorry.
What I mean is...
Why do...
People...
Change?
Because there's nothing permanent in this world.
But...
Kung tapos ka na sa mga nonsense mo na tanong,
pwede ka na mong umulis.
Hey, vet...
Vet friends.
Walang permanente ah.
I'll take note of that.
But anyway...
Salamat sa mga sakot.
Zeng.
Come.
I'll take note of that.
You stroaring...
If you're at home.
Oh long way.
The murderer cano cause you to...
Da him.
Yeah.
I said
You arevie.
Anything?
Miss Sean, get this little shit off me.
Are you afraid of cats?
Miss Sean!
Are you not afraid of cats?
I'm not afraid of them.
I just hate cats.
There's nothing to hate about cats.
You're just afraid of them.
Miss Sean, get him away from me.
Hey?
You know?
You believe it.
You're afraid of cats.
I'm a scrage.
I'm afraid of no one.
Especially another cat.
Well...
Daddy Ace!
I'm afraid of cats.
Oh?
Okay, okay.
I get it.
You're not afraid of cats.
Really?
But...
Are you afraid of me?
What are you...
Ouch!
Stop pinching, Zin!
Damn it.
It hurts.
What the fuck is it now?
You know, it's just a little bit.
And it's not easy to meet sometimes.
You're not worth smiling about.
Because I'm worth more than you can imagine.
Like...
Smile!
Never!
Ayaw mo!
Hindi mo ka naninig?
Smile!
Ayaw mo talaga?
Content ka na?
Ayaw mo! Smile ka na!
I'm gonna count.
One.
Sorry.
Two.
Hindi ko naman. Alam mo naman nagbibiro lang ako.
Three.
Ouch!
Are you ready?
If you're talking about my death...
Always.
You sure?
Still got a couple days left.
Maka...
Gustong bumingi ng tulong muna sa akin?
You can't do anything about it.
Kamu ba talaga ka babatingin mo sa akin?
You must know.
I am not named Ace...
without one.
Think about it.
You must know.
I'm not a girl.
Wait!
You're not a girl!
Oh!
What's she?
What's that?
She's a girl!
You're a girl!
Oh!
What's that?
I'm a girl!
Ito!
Yung sura niya, no?
Hey, hoy!
Ayun si boy.
Huwawa naman, eh?
Si hoy!
Matapakot-kapakot siya!
Nagka-phobia na dahil sa inyo!
Hala!
Ikaw nga ng batok dyan, eh!
Huy!
Huwawa naman!
Pasipit kulit!
Friendly batok lang yun!
Hulit-hulit mo kasi, tuloy!
Sige, go!
Meow!
Did you see Matt?
Are you going to play?
Or are you going to play?
No.
No?
And why are you guys avoiding each other?
That's it.
You need to talk.
Wala tayong dapat pag-usapan.
Ay, grabe.
Ang sakit bigla ng katawan ko, Mia.
Pamasahe nga.
Tara na.
Sorry.
Ang galing ko rin talaga eh, no?
Napapaliwala kitang...
Sorry, Oom.
Naging malamig ako sa'yo at...
sa mga nakarang araw.
Ang dami ko kasing iniisip.
You don't need to say sorry, Zane.
Wala naman akong pakialam kung bakit mo kiniwasan.
Huunawain kita.
Hindi mo rin kailangan humingi ng tawad
dahil...
wala ka naman kasalanan.
Ang paghingi ng tawad eh, para lang sa mga taong...
nakakagawa ng kasalanan.
I hate myself.
Nainas ako sa sarili ko.
Ang namin nangyari.
Tapos...
It's nothing.
Pasensyal na akong...
nararamdam ang mata.
Nika.
I hate you.
Because...
I can't trust you the way you obviously trust me.
I know you have a reason, Zane.
Hindi rin kita pipilitin sabihin sa akin kung ano yung rason kung bakit...
naging malamig ka sa akin.
Bakit tiniiwasan mo ko?
Dahil wala naman akong pakialam doon.
Ang importante sa akin...
alam ko...
sa bandang dulo...
ako pa rin yung iyakapin mo.
Ano ka nga dito?
Maybe I was wrong.
But it's never too late.
Kung nga naman ang rason mo...
nagtitiwala ako sa'yo...
Matthew Hart.
O, di ba?
Hindi ka na ka kami nagkamali sa pagpili kay Matt...
para maging representative ng class namin.
Woo!
Matt, go Matt!
Supre, let's go Matt!
Nanonood pa ako!
Tumay ka nga dyan!
Tabi!
Ay!
Tumayin ka sa akin ka mag-sama ka.
Ano ba talaga para sa'yo si Mission Supremo?
She's my secretary.
I need to protect her.
Gil for her.
I can't hear it!
Yeah!
Sayang ngayon dalak huyana, ku'y manana-ain
Ik-ik-ik-ik-ik .
El pa salat ang halian at tsaka hapunan
Patay ka pedong sa mikropon o hanggang sa pitan
Dirman ng araw pero di pa rin natitigilan
Di pa na hububos wag nyo ang ipipigit
Amo na, adi na, para tiri magbita
Klaro pa, bulat-abigkas ng letro walang aksaya
So, abing mga dula makikita ng mata
Nag-tupag ang salita di ba halata
You got ito nang gawin? Masirap sa tenga
Dali mapag-ako nakaisip ng idea
That's what I want to do
I want to do these things
Do you think it once?
I'll have a smile
I'll expand it
I'm not taking a look
I'm not even making it
I don't think I won go
I'm not a mess
I don't have to leave
I don't need to give it
I don't want to come
There's a day, but it's not that hard
It's not that hard
There's a fuss of light and light
There's a gap in the microphone
You don't hear that
There's a day, but it's not that hard
It's not that hard
We talk too much but never do much
All white flags
When it's a flush
Like a lot of people
You can't even try
You say you're not that hard
I'm only my god
Still got impressed
Headed alamat
On my chest
That's a different type of dress
Boy, I don't need a flex
Let the silence do the rest
I'm a manak
But I'm with the head
Like you could think I'm weak
Uh
Pick up the pace
Show me your face
Paano malami no?
Sino may taste
Casual disease
Paano wala mo no?
Take a face
I know what it is
I'm a manak
Mga di makawala
Luma ko to sa Pinas
Okay, kabalik ako
Mula lo'y zombie size
Ang gamang danok
At sinala kuyan
Ako'y mananatilin
Ng dati buto
Tito!
At basalat ang halian
At saka hapunan
Paday gabi doon sa mikro
Paano ang kapitan
Huwag naman man araw
Pero di pa rin natitigilan
Iwan ako
Basta pwag naman yung pipigilan
And I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like