TINESTING
SINURIT
SINIYASAT
SA SHIELD SOAP
PATAY
ANG 99.9%
NANG BAKTERIA
AT VIRUS
BILI BO MGA NERVES
AT SI MAMI?
IWALA AKO SA SHIELD
SHIELD ANTI-BACTERIAL SOAP
ACS
Hey, kaming makikipag-aregdo sa inyo!
Kahit ilang milyong baos pa ang e-debone mo sa malagon, hindi mo kakayanin ibigay ang ganito kalaking pera sa
pamilya mo.
Hayop ka talaga, attorney!
Seems like you caught what you wanted.
That's what differentiates the powerful from the poor.
Nandito po kayo ngayon sa Afterlife Relay Center.
Dito po dumadaan lahat ng mga pumapanaw.
Maaari namin kayong ibalik sa mundo ng mga buhay.
Mabubuhay ako sa katawan ng ibang tao for a month.
AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Mabubuhay ako sa mga mga mga mga eh!
Uy! Uy! Uy! Uy! Uy! Uy!
Okay, so I'm poor, and...
Married!
NAY!
Ay!
Kanino na naka?
SAYO!
You've made me a mother of not just one, but two!
They know what's a lot from grab me.
Excuse me, I don't cook. I'm too important to cook.
You're the lady, Jaja!
You're the lady, madam?
It's a happy time!
Hey!
Come on in with me.
Why did you come to me?
You said you were a kid.
Go!
I'm just laughing!
How long have I been doing this for a long time?
Why did I ask you to ask your mattress?
This is not my life. I'm not a life.
She's already in you now.
Jen, do you want me to?
Love you.
You're the one who's your husband.
You're the one who's going to die.
What?
You can't miss her, Jen. Don't miss her.
You're the one who's missing.
Please, now.
What are the boys?
Jaja, they're not going to die for a long time.
Isang ako?
Do you want to stay here?
Is it okay?
Ay!
Mrs. Annette, why is my pain?
When you leave here and you go back to your life,
you're still suffering from the pain of Justin.
Do you want to save your pain?
Do you want to love them?
I don't want to go back to your life.
If you're so good,
you're still able to keep your pain
when you're lost.
Sorry, vegan.
I'm a human.
I know.
Huh?
Tell me where you're at.
I'm a human.
But I'm not going to die
for the death of the death.
We can't save everyone.
Mission.
Oh, no.
There's no life of anyone here.
Even me.
Who are you going to die?
I know.
Diba?
Promise natin.
Walang imanin, diba?
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, Zane.
You!
Uy!
Why are you so happy?
It's good, right?
What do you need?
I knew there was something about your smile.
Happy birthday.
Zane.
Do you find Bloody Wink a little boring?
Then let's play a game.
Para maging masaya ang Bloody Wink.
Tignan nyo ang lockers nyo.
Sa akin nga ng kabatan may ahas na ahalik.
Tatawagin kang kaibigan na pinakamatali.
Pupulog ko sa liib mo't sisipsip kan yung dugog.
Ipapago ka sa cross
Kapag ikaw ay natiyo
Ngunit hindi nila
Kayang baliin ang iyong roob
Ang pag-ibig na hawak mo'y hindi malulubog
Umiyak ka
Umiyak
Ang mga tingwi, palakas ng palakas
Hanggang gumuho ang mga hadlang
Hanggang gumuho ang mga hadlangmag
-a-jung
Kailangan kong malaman kung anong tinatago nila.
Kailangan kong malaman.
I would like to see all of you.
Good morning, students.
Para maging masaya ang Bloody Week, tignan nyo ang lockers nyo.
May pangalan dun na dapat niyang patayin bago matapos ang oras.
Kung wala kayong pangalan, kayo ang hinatulad.
Did you know about this?
No.
Open it.
What do I have to?
How do I have to do this?
You can see it.
Okay?
Be поряд.
You can see it.
Beware.
I'm going to go to the Quentin's party.
I hope we'll drink our Lord once again.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to go to the Quentin's party.
You're drunk.
Eh, what if I'm asleep?
Even if I'm asleep,
I know you're still going to be like that.
Thank you, Matt.
We're still in the corner, and we're still asleep.
I'll be right back.
Please?
Please.
Even if he doesn't say,
I trust him.
I trust my friends,
Who's the target?
Do you have a bus locker?
Does it really matter?
Of course it does.
Do you have a bus?
I don't have a bus.
You don't have a bus.
They're all bullshit.
They're not my queen.
I don't have a bus.
They're the only one I want to be, Reyna.
And you,
they're my queen.
You're just going to sleep, Matt.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Oh, Dad.
Oh, wait.
Wait.
What's going on?
Matt, you're so bad.
Why?
No.
I had a stress test in practice.
It's not.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Hey.
Hey, man.
Kumbibito ah.
Tulungan na kita.
Come on.
I know a story.
It's a story.
It's a story for me.
It's a story?
There's a girl.
She's not a young person.
She's also a social person.
But she's a young person.
She has a stepmom and two step-sisters.
She's a good girl.
She's always a girl.
Because of this,
she became insecure.
She felt insignificant.
Because of this,
she felt invisible her whole life.
But one night,
there was a ball
near her village.
But she didn't see it.
It's like this.
It's like a remix.
And then,
she'd have a tricycle
before she became a golden coach.
It's like,
use your imagination.
Who's the prince?
Matthew.
That's me, Slim.
Slim,
they're known as a ball.
They danced the whole night.
in the end.
Before they get out of the night, they need to get out of the night.
Of course, they're still alive.
But that didn't stop them from having fun.
They're going to die, they're going to die again, they're going to die again.
They're like, they're not going to die in the world.
They had each other, even if it was just for one night.
Wait, I feel like they're going to die again.
At least the original.
But okay, what's the ending?
They lived happily ever after.
They were in love with each other.
Yes, ma'am.
Nice story.
But it's a different reality, Zen.
Even if you've known for a long time,
you'll be able to meet each other.
Sometimes, you'll be able to meet each other.
And you'll fall down here.
Is it right, Zen?
You're still alive.
Promise me, Zen.
I promise one.
I'm afraid that you know you're going to love your life.
You're going to love your life,
even if you know you're going to hurt yourself.
Why did you say that?
Do you want me to meet you?
I don't want you to meet you.
That's right.
Good night.
See you.
Hindi yun nakakatawa.
Alam ko.
Paalis naman na dapat talaga ako eh.
Kaso nakita kita.
Asal sila?
Ayun.
Sino yung kasama ni Van?
Si Leah.
Ano?
I know what you're thinking.
Alam mo?
Tulungan mo nalang kaya akong hanapin yung iba, no?
So...
Ano?
Sinong nabunat mo sa papel?
Anonymous.
May mga bagay na hindi na dapat tayo malaman.
Can you kill him?
Sorry.
Why not?
Kung yun nalang ang paraan para mabuhay.
Talaga?
Can you do that?
Ah...
Yes.
Alam mo?
Ito yung disadvantage pag ikaw yung joker ng grupo, no?
Talagang hindi nyo na talaga ako siniseryoso.
Sirong, kilala kita.
Hindi mo kaya matay.
Eh...
Eh, bakit?
Ikaw ba?
Ewan ko.
I mean...
Sinong nabunat mo?
Hindi maganda yan.
Alam ba yan ni Matt?
Last time siya ito gabi eh.
Hindi ko nga makausap na maayos.
Nag isang bote pa naman.
Straight.
Uy!
Si Mio!
Mia!
Napunap kita!
Hey.
Wala.
Are you okay?
No.
Can I go, Master?
Wala kang kasalanan.
Tara na, Jerome!
Kaso?
Pa...
Paano siya?
Dammit to go, Jerome!
Tara na!
Please.
Dave! Dave, patulog!
Mia!
Anong nangyari?
Patulog!
Jen!
Nurse siya!
Ang lalim!
Sa'yo!
Sa'yo binig!
Anong ginagawa niya dito?
Nakaka ba?
Kuhinig to, di ba?
Sa session na, pero close ang clinic ngayon.
Emergency to!
Huwag ka niyo binig to!
Ilan!
Ilan niyo!
To go!
Please!
I'm sorry, pero...
Yung!
To sa'yo binig cez.
Buk sanjir!
Aay?!
I'm toyo!
Piyad!
I'm to!
Kuhinig po to!
Buk sanjir!
Please!
To sa'yo binig!
Aay!
Piyad!
Ma si ka sa'yo niyo min semya!
Puyodala!
Piyad!
No ya ripenu!
Buk sanjir!
That's it!
What do you want to take here?
That one.
Miss Shawn, I'm glad you came.
Why are you here?
Miss Mama, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What are you doing now?
That's what we're doing now.
It's been locked because of the violation of violence.
If we don't have it,
we'll die again.
I really don't have time for this.
I can't help you, Miss Shawn.
Please, I'm breaking it, please!
Anyway,
we're here.
Miss Shawn!
We're breaking the number one rule.
That's the knife.
Wait a minute, huh?
That's the knife!
Miss Shawn!
You're not talking to me.
Bye.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm making a difference.
Like I should talk to you,
but I'm not thinking of it.
I'm thinking that's the truth.
I'm rather a debate.
You're not talking to me.
and I'm speaking to each other's teachers…
and I'm speaking to each other.
I mean I say that's how I am going to heal.
This is so much Ace.
Please!
I can only do so much, Michelle.
Even I can't override the orders of the headmistress.
But, for your friend, maybe I can make an exception.
But you understand, right?
What's wrong with this?
Oh, I don't know what's wrong with that.
You just need to fix your claim.
You don't know what's wrong with that.
What do you think?
The only thing that's wrong with you?
Pritzy!
Enough!
Michelle.
I'm sure you're going to do it.
Yes.
And if she will do the same.
Okay.
I'll continue.
But...
Keep this.
You need that more.
Especially when you're done.
I'll go.
Nurse, Chef!
Open the doors!
Now!
Resume your duties.
Gawing operational ang clinic.
Pero Supremo, utos ni Madam Violet.
Malino naman yung sinabi ko, di ba?
May pasen na gila ng tulong.
Marami pong sugatan.
Siya lang ang gagamutin mo.
Huwag ka magpapasos ng iba.
Na-apply pressure.
Sige, na-mangilip ka.
Mia.
Malapit kami.
I-mangilip ka.
Let's go!
Let's go.