=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 27=
ظآزBetween black and white,
ripples crossedظآز
ظآزLight encountered shadowظآز
ظآزIt pierced the darkness and the timeظآز
ظآزThe unbreakable fateظآز
ظآزSuddenly crackedظآز
We meet again,
Foxy.
ظآزListen, all sounds are roaringظآز
ظآزAs cold ice turns into tidesظآز
ظآزA century's loneliness melts dreamsظآز
ظآزFollowing fate's guidanceظآز
ظآزBy fate, our moments were exchangedظآز
ظآزThe heart wakes up all of a suddenظآز
(I must have lost my mind.)
(How could she be here?)
What a surprise
to see General Duan here.
What a coincidence.
Mr. Fang is here too.
I won't disturb you two.
I'll take my leave now.
It seems
that you've taken
a liking
to Mr. Wang's daughter.
Who's interested
in whom I favor,
you
or the Duke?
What do you think?
General Duan.
Fang Xianye,
I knew you meant no good.
You want to steal
Xu's date.
You, come with me.
Xu, go after her.
Go on.
Come here.
Fang Xianye,
don't you dare hinder Xu.
Miss Duan,
neither of them is wed.
How am I in the way?
Besides, Miss Wang
may not favor Mr. Duan.
Xu's affairs
are not yours to meddle in.
Xu is far better than you.
Even if Suyi rejects Xu,
she'd never choose you.
Nothing is settled yet.
Why speak with such certainty?
I...
Anyway,
stop hindering Xu.
Do not be upset.
I won't disturb
your stroll
in the garden.
- Iظخ
- Goodbye.
Wait.
How do you know the Six-Petal Knot?
Only Xu can tie that knot.
Why are you so annoying,
coping Xu in all things?
You want his date and knot.
I don't want to see you again.
You do have a sharp memory.
Little trinkets!
Come look, come see.
Weren't you at the banquet?
Why are you back so soon?
I did what my old man asked,
and I left.
Why are you here?
I...
I went to look for Xu.
He went to the banquet,
so I'll wait at Yuzao Pleasure House.
Xu is still inside.
Go wait for him. I'm leaving.
Why are you following me?
Aren't you waiting for Xu?
He
won't be out anytime soon.
I'd better head back.
Your home is that way.
I can get back from this way too.
How was today's banquet?
Not much to speak of.
Did you meet anyone
or anything
interesting there?
No.
It was terribly dull.
Let's go drink at Yuzao Pleasure House.
Sure.
I heard they had
a new batch of fine wine.
With your capacity,
you know the wine
at Yuzao Pleasure House?
I kept an eye out just for you.
You're my good buddy.
Come on.
Move. Hurry up.
- Zhou.
- Li.
Zhao.
Long time no see.
Indeed.
How have you been?
Not bad.
A few days ago, I read your prose.
You flatter me.
Great Ancestor,
you're back.
What did you find out?
Today, at the banquet,
I left marks on those
with deep obsessions.
Approach them
as the Prophet to gather
their obsessions.
Yes.
When you approach them,
look into them.
Song Xingyu will likely forge
a pact with such people as before.
If we find them,
we may find Song Xingyu.
Great Ancestor,
good for you.
did you see it today?
Duan Xu was
so attentive to that young lady.
What was that young lady called again?
Her name isظخ
Great Ancestor,
isn't this the life
you wanted for him?
Why take it out on me?
Go do what you should do.
Less talk about the rest.
Yes.
Xu, I'm coming in.
Xu,
from how you reacted today,
have you taken to Wang Suyi?
Can you help me meet her?
Miss Wang and I
do have some acquaintance.
She often attends
the Embroidery Society I run.
I still owe her
a Suzhou-style embroidered fan.
I'll deliver it tomorrow
and ask her for you.
As you asked,
I'm here.
Where are you?
Great Ancestor,
I am truly sorry.
I have to wait for the medicine.
Take a stroll. I'll come soon.
How dare you make me wait?
I am innocent too.
It is Ziji's fault.
If I skip the medicine,
she won't let me out.
I'll be there at once.
Great Ancestor, look.
She's calling me again.
I'm going now.
Forget it.
I'll count this as a day off.
Here, hold it tight.
Thanks.
Miss, would you like a sugar figurine?
I can make one now.
Baskets for sale!
Sachets! Trinkets!
Welcome inside.
Your wine. Please enjoy.
Mr. Duan,
you finally made it.
Come.
Mr. Wang.
Miss Wang.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was wondering
why Miss Wang would
ask to meet here.
So, it was you
who chose this place.
Bringing your sister here,
are you trying to embarrass me?
Mr. Duan, you jest.
I heard
you're a regular here.
And Luoxian, the lady of this house,
is your old acquaintance.
Since you mean to get to know
my sister better,
it is only natural
to bring her into your daily life.
Besides,
for men to seek pleasure
is common enough at home.
I understand you.
And look at my sister.
A noble lady, graceful and poised.
Why would she mind
your confidantes?
What a pity, though.
I have an appointment with Luoxian here.
She is likely waiting
quite anxiously by now.
Mr. Duan,
you must take good care
of my sister.
Of course.
Luoxian.
Since we parted,
have you been well?
Thank you for your concern.
I've been quite well.
In fact, you didn't wish
to meet me here.
- I...
- You said nothing to your brother,
but you mind that men
come here to seek pleasure, right?
Mr. Duan,
you're quite insightful.
I admire it.
But I can also sense
that you do not seem
so eager to know me,
right?
It's raining.
Yes.
A sudden summer rain.
(Sugar Figurine)
Who are you?
What a scoundrel.
You already forgot me?
My name is Duan Xu,
as in a supreme martial achievement.
My courtesy name is Shunxi.
He Simu.
You recognized me,
Foxy.
How did you know it was me?
Who else makes crow sugar figurines?
You've come to Nandu.
Why didn't you tell me?
I came here on my own business.
I didn't come here for you.
Why would I tell you?
So, you didn't plan to see me?
Nandu is only so big.
See? We met now.
What a coincidence, General Duan.
Why are you holding
my friend?
Prophet Hejia.
Have you finished
your official business?
Great Ancestorظخ
Miss He,
why buy another sugar figurine?
You can't even taste it.
Yet you still like such things.
Mind your own affairs.
Your health is so poor,
yet you chose a rainy day to roam.
Have you lived long enough?
I...
We all have our quirks. Let it be.
Let's go.
Come on.
Taste it for me.
See if it's sweet.
Here, take it.
ظآزMemories trail like a shadowظآز
ظآزScattered reflections
sink into my heartظآز
ظآزIf I could softly call you like thisظآز
ظآزAs gentle as a fleeting embraceظآز
ظآزThough apart, my thoughts still swirlظآز
ظآزA lifetime is given
for a name to be rememberedظآز
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
ظآزHope we'll experience them togetherظآز
How did you know it was me?
Who else makes crow sugar figurines?
(Just now, she was so far away.)
(I couldn't see)
(what He Simu was holding,)
(let alone make out)
(a crow's shape.)
(Exactly.)
(How did I know it was her?)
(How, in but a moment,)
(among countless plain,)
(strange mortal shells,)
(I knew the soul within.)
I'm the Sovereign
of Spirits.
(I have only known this soul)
(for less than half a year.)
(Everyone says)
(forgetting)
(is something)
(exceedingly easy to do.)
(Perhaps one day, when my temples gray)
(and I reach the age Father spoke of)
(when childhood bonds fade from mind,)
(will I still, in the vast crowd,)
(recognize her at a glance?)
(By the time that day comes,)
(even if I recognize her,)
(will I still, like today,)
(run after her without a thought?)
ظآزThere are passions and painsظآز
ظآزHope we'll experience them togetherظآز
(She's the first girl)
(I fell for,)
(the first girl)
(to awaken me,)
ظآزGrows dim and fades awayظآز
(the first girl)
(who came)
(for me)
(in that pitch-black darkness,)
(the first girl)
(who feels the world's beauty)
(and pain because of me,)
ظآزWorth more than any barren landظآز
ظآزI might as well
spend the rest of my lifeظآز
(and the girl who always calls me Foxy)
(and says, "I'll protect you,")
("but do not love me.")
But I am the wish you can't fulfill.
Take me out
of your wishes.
ظآزA dream I'm lost inظآز
(How ironic.)
(My original wish)
(was to live as an ordinary man,)
(free of the All-Knowing's shadow,)
(and learn to live like everyone else.)
(I tried so hard to do that.)
(But now,)
(everything has gone)
(the opposite way)
(from my original wish.)
(He Simu)
(has become my new wish,)
(the most shocking wish of all.)
(I will have no one)
(but He Simu.)
Hejia Fengyi,
your gift for divination
has truly grown by the day.
You asked me out only for this moment?
What a coincidence.
Who knew we'd run into him?
How has Duan Shunxi been lately?
Probably not well.
After he returned from the battlefield,
his military command was stripped.
He was given an idle post,
doing nothing.
Maybe he was hurt
on the battlefield.
He looks somewhat weak.
Drenched in rain in this weather,
he may well fall ill.
As for falling ill, I know it well.
Once men like him, who usually seem
so strong and healthy,
fall ill,
it can hit like a mountain collapsing.
It'll be perilous.
One lapse, and a small ailment grows.
Then a life is lost.
If you talk less,
will your whole body ache?
Yeah.
Great Ancestor, you know me best.
Are you afraid
my words will doom him?
Easy, easy.
I didn't use spells just now.
And even if I had,
it'd only be to pray
for his well-being.
I know.
You know?
So, you simply care for him
and can't bear hearing him die?
If you're unwell,
speak a little less.
How are you anything like Aunt?
Perhaps
I'm as pretty as she is.
Great Ancestor,
you asked me before
how mortals live in the Void.
I almost thought
he had become your beloved.
But after Duan Xu returned,
I could see
his resentment
was heavier than spirits'.
I had assumed
he was frustrated in court.
But then,
seeing how he grabbed you,
I finally understood.
It spelled out three clear words.
Troubled by romance.
Count yourself fortunate
to be here now.
That saved your life.
Great Ancestor, forgive me.
I saw how calm
you were just now.
I take it you've turned him down.
So, it has nothing to do with you.
I think he and Miss Wang
are getting along well.
They're probably in love.
Maybe he'll soon forget
the 400-year-old youظخ
a seasoned woman like you,
and turn to a fair beauty instead.
Great Ancestor.
Great Ancestor,
you have to hear the truth sometimes.
How was any of that the truth?
How was that not the truth?
Aren't you over 400 years old?
They were distant and polite.
But you called me over
to stir things up and twist the truth.
Who taught you to wag your tongue?
They are not in love at all.
I see.
That's the real point here.
But Great Ancestor, don't forget.
She's the one
Duan Xu proposed to.
You do have a silver tongue.
Have you finished
the task I assigned you?
Have you caught Song Xingyu?
Rest assured.
I've already been screening
those you've left marks on.
But, Great Ancestor,
you know the state of my health.
We must wait for an auspicious day.
Otherwise,
the little life I have left
will be worn down.
What if my health
is harmed?
A bustling place like Nandu
is full of splendor and temptation,
yet as far as the eye can see,
there's no spiritual aura or spirits.
Is Song Xingyu
behind this too?
I'll give you the obsessions tomorrow.
Let's call it a day.
Great Ancestor,
where do you actually stay?
Come find me tomorrow night.
Where am I supposed to find you?
Xu.
With an umbrella,
how did you get so drenched?
I didn't use it.
You didn't use it in the pouring rain?
What if you fall ill?
Why are you so careless
with your own health?
Exactly.
I knew I should use an umbrella,
yet I didn't.
I knew I should live well,
yet I refused.
What a madman.
Xu,
is something wrong?
I've fallen for a young lady.
Is she a lady from Nandu?
She is not from Nandu.
You met her on the battlefield?
She didn't come back with you?
She's the only girl in a good family.
If I were to be with her,
I'd have to marry into her family.
Then,
does she
like you?
She turned me down.
In her eyes,
let alone the Duan clan of Nandu,
even Great Liang, or the whole world,
means nothing at all.
What kind of lady is she?
A lady unlike any in this world.
- Xu.
- You wanted me?
Your friends are here.
I've seated them in the hall with tea.
All right.
Jingyuan,
have you had dealings
with the wife
of the Minister of Revenue?
I've crossed paths
with Mrs. Wang.
We're on fair terms.
Why?
Today, Mr. Wang
asked me to take Miss Wang home.
While I was talking with her,
I spotted a familiar face on the street.
They might be Chong spies,
so I went after them,
neglected Miss Wang,
and failed to escort her home.
All right, I understand.
I'll go visit Mrs. Wang at once
and apologize for you.
Wait, Xu.
Don't you already fancy someone?
What do you plan
to do with Miss Wang?
Do not worry.
I have my own plan.
What brings you here?
Xu.
Take a look.
Wu Shengliu asked us
to bring this to you.
Though the war has settled,
the border still sees unrest.
This was supposed to be a gift
for your promotion.
But he never expected
how things would turn out.
Judging by the style,
it belongs to at least a general.
Wu Shengliu did well.
Xu,
are we staying in Nandu for good?
What I want
has always been to reclaim
the 17 Prefectures
and have peace for the realm
and the people.
Great Liang seeks no war,
but North Chong still covets our land.
Once they get a chance,
they'll surely strike back.
We must prepare in advance.
Then, when do we leave?
I can't stay in Nandu another day.
I am stuck indoors, learning embroidery
and having blind dates.
If this keeps going,
I won't even lift my blade.
I have been idle in Nandu as well.
Right?
Yunzhou and Luozhou are back,
but Yunzhou's steeds
have yet to thunder
across the battlefield.
Luozhou's Tianluo Ore
has yet to arm our men.
Some matters
must be settled in Nandu.
(Yuzao Pleasure House)
This way, please.
I'm telling you.
Take care.
I'll be coming back to find you.
Ah, you're here.
This way, please.
Mr. Zhang, you're.
Yuzao Pleasure House.
Take care.
Come again next time.
Great Ancestor
surely knows how to have fun.
She became the top beauty.
Please head inside.
Sure thing.
Alright, alright.
You've finished a whole jar.
All right.
Why hasn't it reached
closing time?
Heavens,
I must have slept in too late.
I even saw the Prophet
come here for amusement.
Great Ancestor.
Great Ancestorظخ
Fine wine,
beauties,
tales of desire,
and obsessions at their peak.
Good for you, Great Ancestor.
See if it's enough.
I need a little more.
Great Ancestor,
have you ever thought
what the magical artifact will be like?
(In Yuzao Pleasure House,)
(the Prophet secretly meets Miss He.)
Sir,
please go upstairs.
You should leave now.
A spirit is here.
A guest has arrived.
Great Ancestor,
something is wrong.
This spiritual energy
is very strong.
I'll get you out of here.
Greetings, sir.
May I ask
what story you wish to tell?
The story begins
with a loyal prince.
He was promoted young.
He basked in imperial favor.
The court and the realm all believed
he would inherit the throne.
Yet history always leaves regrets.
His younger brother saw no hope
to vie for the heirship,
so he started a rebellion.
The prince was bound by kinship,
never knowing
it was a deadly trap
tailored just for him.
His brother framed him.
That loyal prince
suddenly became a rebel.
My Lady,
do you know how the prince
met his end at last?
Yan,
stop fooling around.
ظآزBetween black and white,
ripples crossedظآز
ظآزLight encountered shadowظآز
ظآزIt pierced the darkness and the timeظآز
ظآزThe unbreakable fateظآز
ظآزSuddenly crackedظآز
ظآزBetween black and white,
ripples crossedظآز
ظآزLight encountered shadowظآز
ظآزIt pierced the darkness and the timeظآز
ظآزThe unbreakable fateظآز
ظآزSuddenly crackedظآز
ظآزListen, all sounds are roaringظآز
ظآزAs cold ice turns into tidesظآز
ظآزA century's loneliness melts dreamsظآز
ظآزFollowing fate's guidanceظآز
ظآزBy fate, our moments were exchangedظآز
ظآزThe heart wakes up┬بall of a suddenظآز
ظآزWatch fireworks fall like starsظآز
ظآزThis bond is tangled into a threadظآز
ظآزWorldly reflections fade into mistظآز
ظآزBorrowing one fleeting heartbeatظآز
ظآزYou drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charmsظآز
ظآزThe heart wakes up┬بall of a suddenظآز