(Previously)
Grandma!
What if something happens to her?
Your grandma is going to be okay.
Can you forgive me?
But there is something...
I need you to help me with.
You've become much cuter than before.
Come and give Daddy a hug.
Come with me, okay?
"Love Like a Bike"
(Episode 6)
Hey. Hey.
Boyfriend.
Oh...
Look who's here.
How did you know I was here?
Dindin told me.
Come on, let's go home.
Can you walk?
Careful now.
Nava? What's wrong?
Nava. Nava.
My stomach hurts.
(Several months earlier)
Hey there.
How's it going?
Let me see.
This is amazing.
Gorgeous.
Did you know that client loves your work?
You're gonna make us rich.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Keep it up.
Go for it.
The 15-second board is roughly like this.
And the KV really fits
the 'Future of Pattaya' theme.
This isn't what I had in mind at all.
And isn't this KV too cluttered?
- But—
- Can you clean it up a bit?
But these are what you chose...
It doesn't look good now. Just fix it.
Yes.
Go. Hurry up and fix it.
Don't worry, he'll be done in 30 minutes.
Let's move on to the wardrobe.
Relax, have some water first.
Chai, put some more light in the back.
Mr. Nava!
Why isn't the model on set yet?!
I'll check right now.
Where is she?
She won't come out.
- Why won't she come out?
- Says it's too hot. I tried my best.
There are 30 minutes left.
Can you shoot something else for now?
How can I? There's nothing to...
- Nava!
- Yes, Ma'am!
What are you doing?!
The client is waiting!
- Go and get her now.
- Alright, fine.
It's boiling out here!
Why did you want to shoot under the sun?!
Okay, you can pose now.
Great. Please change a pose.
Looks good.
Stop! Stop right there!
That's the wrong product!
C… Cut.
- Not this one?
- No!
One moment, please.
- Please hold this one.
- When will it be over?
- Just a moment, please.
- It's so hot.
Nava!
- Yes, Ma'am?
- We're running out of time! And it's hot!
Yes! Please bear with me for a moment.
We only have the slot until noon!
Please have a look at the monitor.
Wake up!
Yes, Ma'am?
The deadline is 9 AM!
How can you finish it if you're sleeping?!
Yes, I'll be as quick as possible.
Are you sure?
If you miss this, the company
is finished because of you.
I… I'll get it done.
Then hurry up!
The deadline's coming
and you're sleeping!
Do I…
have cancer, Doctor?
Yes. You are in stage 2.
Fortunately, it's still treatable.
If we start the treatment soon,
there's a high chance of recovery.
Please make an appointment
when you're ready.
Nava.
You're too sick to work.
Just go get treated.
You can't work for me.
I can handle it.
Handle what? Look at your condition.
I really can.
You can't. Besides, I've already
found someone to replace you.
I can really do this, please.
Just go. I'll pay your severance.
Now, everyone, back to work.
Are you a relative of Mr. Nava?
Yes, I'm his boyfriend.
What's happening to Nava?
Mr. Nawa has stage 2 cancer.
Stage 2… cancer?
Yes, we've tried
to contact him for treatment,
but he never showed up.
The patient's condition
has weakened so much.
We must start treatment immediately
before it progresses further.
Nava.
How are you?
Please discuss this with him.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Please excuse me.
Nava,
why did you keep this from me?
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew.
I knew you'd be devastated.
Let's break up.
Nava…
I'm going to die anyway.
Leaving now...
or when I'm gone, it's all the same.
No,
I'm not breaking up with you.
I'm not going anywhere.
You're going to be okay.
The doctor said it's not terminal yet.
If we start now, there's still a chance...
What's the point, Sky?!
It's cancer.
I'm going to die anyway.
Treatment is just more torture.
Don't think like that.
The doctor confirmed that there's
still a high chance you'll recover.
Enough.
It's so unfair.
I lived a good life.
I didn't drink, I didn't smoke.
I gave everything to my work.
And what did I get?
A tumor… and a pink slip.
How is that fair?
It's so damn unfair.
It's okay, Nava.
It's okay. I'm right here.
I'm by your side.
I'll stay here until you're healed.
I promise.
Koh Larn, this way please!
Thank you.
Koh Larn, this way!
Thank you, enjoy your trip.
Koh Larn, this way! Thank you.
Enjoy your trip.
Hey, young man!
You filling in for Dindin today?
Yes. I'm taking over for Dindin today.
Did he trick you into doing this?
Not at all. I'm doing this willingly.
Alright then.
Koh Larn, this way! Koh Larn, over here!
Mr. Sailom,
I want to thank you for
coming back to see me.
You're welcome.
During our sessions, if there's
anything you'd like to share,
please tell me anything.
I'm here to listen.
Yes.
And everything we discuss today will be
kept confidential for your treatment only.
Do I have your permission?
Yes, you do.
Thank you very much. So...
did you have anything
for breakfast this morning?
Not yet.
I didn't really have an appetite.
You didn't have breakfast
because you didn't feel like eating.
Is there any food you particularly like?
Well... fish steak.
Oh, fish steak.
What kind of fish? Dory or Salmon?
Salmon.
Oh! I love salmon too!
And do you usually
have it with any side dishes?
Like som tam, fries, or salad?
Mashed potatoes, fries, and soup.
Sailom.
Where would you like to go today?
I'd rather go home.
Let's go to your place. To my car.
Let me try!
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, of course!
Okay, then give it a try.
Is this som tam noodles
or wide rice noodles?
Like this, right?
The Luang Prabang style.
Oh, then I’ll have
Luang Prabang style.
Luang Prabang som tam?
Really?
That's right! Now grab me chilli.
The green one or red one?
They might not look
as fancy as restaurant dishes,
but I guarantee they're delicious.
I think they look and taste amazing
because you made me
do so much of the work.
But I seasoned it.
I watched a Japanese food show once.
They said the secret to
delicious food is all in the cutting.
Okay, I give up.
Do you know why?
- Why?
- Because I'm starving. Let's eat.
Here, try your own masterpiece first.
Here.
Ahh…
Nom.
Mmm!
What does “Mmm” mean?
- Good.
- Really?
It's a bit too spicy for you.
My turn. Let me try some.
One, two...
- Wow! This is so good!
- Not yet!
Ahh…
Hope your grandma can eat this.
Old man.
Take your damn money back.
I never asked you to pay for
my grandma's medical bill.
I already paid. Just keep it.
Do you think I can't afford the bill?!
That's not what I think.
I just don't want to see you struggling.
Struggling? What struggle?
I'm fine!
Just admit that you have money problems.
Why else would you be singing,
taking boat tickets, and making sweets?
That's my business!
Stay out of it!
Because you're my employee!
If you don't show up,
my shop has nothing to sell!
If you really want to pay me back,
I can deduct it from your salary.
(Dick.)
But you have to pay interest.
What interest?
Drink with me every night.
Just say you're horny.
Yeah, I'm horny.
Is camping with a boyfriend
on your bucket list too?
Yeah.
This trip is actually one of them.
I've wanted to go camping
with a boyfriend for so long,
but I never had a partner
and time.
About when you got fired...
After I found out I had cancer...
I didn't want to live anymore.
I just thought
I'd try everything I'd never done.
Like… drinking,
hitting up host bars,
and having a boyfriend.
I wanted to live it up,
to make this life feel worth it.
Is there anything else you want to do?
Well...
I do.
There are places I want to go.
I spent all my time working
and never went anywhere.
Where… do you want to go?
I…
Want to travel abroad.
I've never even been to Japan.
Go…
see the London Eye,
try…
parachuting or skydiving,
visit the Great Wall,
Bali, Hawaii... so many places.
Mhm.
If that's what you want,
you need to get better first, okay?
Once you're better,
I'll take you everywhere you want to go.
I promise.
So... where should we go first?
I think…
London sounds interesting.
I've always wanted
to see the London Eye too.
Really?
Why are you crying?
Nabnueng,
you already know this.
The best form of healing is
rebuilding trust in humanity.
Or making Sailom trust someone
and learning to lean on those around him.
Sailom!
Are you ready?
Ready!
Let's go then.
Do you usually enjoy watching movies?
I love them.
How often do you watch them?
About once a week.
Wow! Once a week?
That means you watch
four movies a month.
That's right.
Is there a particular
movie that you love?
I really like “First Love.”
Oh, so you're a fan of romantic movies?
I love that one too!
Really?
I'm going to let it go now.
Slow and steady.
- Like this?
- A bit more. Watch out for the string.
Do you feel that? Feel the wind?
Run.
How are you feeling today, Mr. Sailom?
I feel like...
I can touch other people again.
Really?
I heard you did some activities
with your friends at the beach?
Yes.
We played Monkey in the Middle
and flew kites together.
So, during Monkey in the Middle,
you could touch your friends?
Yes.
While we were chasing the ball,
I was touching and bumping into others.
Yes.
In that case,
could you try touching my hand
like you did with your friends?
Like when you touched your friends.
Okay.
You've improved so much.
Now, may I have your
permission to touch your arm?
Yes, you may.
Well done!
This is wonderful!
I actually did it!
You were amazing!
Dindin.
Come have a drink with me.
Your life must be so stressful.
I see you drink all day.
Mind your own business.
Dindin,
are you gonna join me?
Yeah, let me finish
checking the stock first.
What are you doing here?
Just checking if you're done yet.
Be real with me.
You're horny?
Just let me finish this first.
Hey!
If you don't stop messing with me,
you're gonna be eating my fist.
Going to punch me again?
Is it a tradition to throw
a punch before we kiss?
Can we try kissing without
the punching for once?
Don't want to have a sore lip.
Come on, put your clothes on.
Why?
Well...
we go our separate ways after we're done.
Can I stay like this for a little longer?
(Savings Account: 47,596.59 baht)
I… want to travel abroad.
If that's what you want,
you need to get better first, okay?
Once you're better,
I'll take you everywhere you want to go.
Nava. I got a lot of vegetables today.
I was thinking of making stir-fry…
Nava? Where are you going?
I want to go home.
Why?
Why so suddenly?
Is there something wrong at home?
Everything's fine at home.
I just want to go home to die.
Die?
I thought we talked about this.
You were going to get treatment.
I don't think I ever said that.
You just assumed it yourself.
Nava…
I'm asking you seriously.
Did you ever once love me?
Or am I just some host
you used for fun before you died?
I feel like I mean nothing to you.
You want to give up, you want to die.
You keep saying that!
Have you ever thought…
about how I'll live...
if you're gone?
If you wanted to die from the start,
why did you make me love you?
Sky...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I do love you, Sky.
But...
I've run out of money.
I can't afford the treatment anymore.
I just can't.
I don't have the money.
Are you nervous?
A little. But I'm more hungry.
Hang in there. You can eat
whatever you want after the surgery.
I'll take you everywhere,
and we'll do everything
on your list.
Fight on.
Is this a hospital or a maze?
Took me forever to find this room.
I brought you some oranges.
Man, it's you…
Hey, show some respect
to your “Major Sponsor,” will you?
What sponsor?
Haven't you told him yet?
Sky?
P'Man,
please help my boyfriend.
Sky never asked me for anything,
unlike the other hosts.
That's why I like him.
Thanks for telling me
you like my boyfriend in front of me.
What does that have to do
with the money for my treatment?
Has the cancer reached your brain?
It's in my colon.
Whatever.
But use your head.
Someone who
never asks for anything for himself,
but comes begging me
to save his boyfriend…
Think about how much he loves you.
It hurts just talking about it.
Thank you so much, P'Man.
Huh? What did you call me?
P'Man.
And I'm sorry
for everything in the past.
Just get well soon
so you can work and pay me back.
Do you know how many
drinks this money could've bought?
Thank you.
I'm going.
Oh, and don't worry.
I won't use this money
as an excuse to mess with Sky.
There are plenty of other hosts.
P'Man,
I thank you again.
Happy to help.
P'Man, your hand…
Just a little bit.
Thank you, Sky.
For doing all of this for me.
Don't thank me.
You don't have to.
Just get better and stay with me…
That's all I need.
Sailom...
Will you be my boyfriend?
Is it going to be a burden
to be with a broken man like me?
I don't know.
We'll have to find out.
In that case...
do we try kissing?
(Next Episode)
Are you really cured?
Cured or not, but the doctor
asked me to be his boyfriend!
The boss sent me to collect the interest.
I'll do whatever
it takes to keep this house.
My mother told me to help
my sick biological sister.
- How?
- A bone marrow transplant.
It has to come from a full
sibling with the same parents.
Have you seen your sister?
I just saw her taking out the trash.
Who the hell are these bastards?