Why are you still dating U?
If he was using me,
he might have run away already.
So if he chooses to stay,
that must mean that he loves me.
As long as you’re still married to Tim,
this land is a marital asset
and belongs to both you and Tim.
I suggest you get a proper divorce
before managing this property.
You went to dinner
with Mr. Pai last night, right?
Didn’t you guys make up?
Pai said he wants a divorce.
I already agreed to it.
This is not a ruse, is it?
You’re always like this, baby.
I don’t like it.
What did you just call me?
From the look of it, I don’t think
they’re getting divorced.
I don’t think we have time
to do anything else today.
We’ll get a divorce some other day.
Yes!
Hey.
Are you sure this wasn’t a ruse?
Of course, it wasn’t.
I had to get stitches, you know?
I think you should take Tim
home to get some rest.
U and I will take care of things
at the bakery.
Can you even drive?
Of course.
You sure?
Yeah.
As if I can afford to be reckless
when Pai is with me.
Oh, wow, Mr. Sweet Talker.
You’re even more of a sweet talker
as an ex than as a boyfriend.
I’m not buttering him up.
I’m serious.
Alright.
Drive safe.
North and I will head to work.
Let’s get going.
You gotta hold on to me.
I’m still in pain.
I feel faint.
Quit the theatrics.
I just felt faint.
Quit it.
Hold on to me, alright?
U, you were going so fast.
Can’t help that
I have an amazing motorbike.
I bet that’s all that’s amazing.
I’m even more amazing.
Let’s go.
Oh, hey.
Perfect timing.
Vanness just texted me
about our end-of-the-year trip.
What trip?
The South African safari trip.
You free at the beginning of December?
Hold on.
If I’m not here, we can’t open the bakery.
Which means you’re free.
Alright. I’ll just confirm him.
Hold on.
I don’t think I can go.
Why not?
Well…
I don’t have money.
And I don’t think I can make enough
before December.
I’ll lend you some.
How about this?
My treat.
Take U with us.
We can all go.
That solves everything, right?
My treat.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don’t want you to.
I know now how hard
making money really is.
You guys go.
Just make sure you say hello
to Simba for me.
Fine, then.
That’s too bad.
How is Tim, though?
He went home to rest.
I WANT TO WIN
I WANT TO WIN THE LOTTERY!
What’s wrong?
You actually want to go to South Africa,
don’t you?
Of course, I do.
But when I think I have to
spend my friend’s money,
it just feels kinda weird.
Then I bet you’ll like your
grandfather’s offer, Mr. North.
Ms. Nana.
What offer?
Your grandfather wants you to go back
and learn the trade at Empire.
What?
What exactly are you doing, Grandpa?
I’ve been watching you and Pai.
And I have seen that
I can get by on my own, can work a proper job, with U still by my si..
I have seen that you cannot
get by on your own.
I can!
I so can!
Is that right?
If you were to work
somewhere else right now,
what skills do you think you have to offer?
And I’m not talking about waiting tables
and cleaning windows.
What happens next when
Pure gets sick of this bakery?
With Pai there, I guess
you can keep it up and running.
But if Pai finds something to do
on his own,
how will you support yourself, North?
Come back and work for me.
Prove to me that you’re mature enough
to take care of yourself.
If you prove yourself a capable employee,
I’ll forgive you.
If you want me to work for you,
U is coming with me.
Otherwise, it’s a no right here and now.
Sure.
What’s wrong, U?
North.
What do you think of
your Grandpa’s offer?
If you pass this training,
you have to work for Empire
for at least 10 years.
If I said yes, you’d be stuck
with Empire for 10 years.
But…
I think it’s best for you to take the offer.
I don’t think it’s going to be
as easy as you think.
I bet it’s just a ruse that
he wants us to be salespersons.
At Empire, everything we do
will be scrutinized.
It would be so uncomfortable!
North, you know what makes me
feel uncomfortable?
What makes me feel uncomfortable
is the fact that I can’t support you.
I can’t take care of you the way
you deserve to be taken care of.
So I will do anything.
If I have to force you,
or swoop your bum like a child to get
you to reconcile with your Grandpa,
I’ll do it.
Fine.
I’ll take his offer.
I just want to play hard to get for,
like, four… or five hours.
Oh?
Sure thing.
Let’s go.
Here.
Thank you.
Hold on tight.
I know that.
Can I come in?
Umm.
You know how to knock now.
Only because I thought Tim could be here.
I didn’t want to interrupt.
How were things at the bakery today?
Actually…
I wasn’t there.
What?
Then where have you been?
Grandpa sent Ms. Nana to fetch me.
So Grandpa wants me and U
to intern at the mall.
If we pass the training,
we’ll go on to intern at the office.
He also wants us to work there
for 10 years!
That’s when he’ll forgive me.
That was all?
I asked him about you as well.
Grandpa said…
“If he thinks he’s so smart,
he can think for himself what he should do
for me to forgive him.”
That’s it.
If he had planned to forgive me at all,
he would have made me an offer
like he did with you.
But that’s not the case.
So whatever I do, it’ll be futile.
Turn the light off when you leave.
I’m gonna turn in for the night.
It’s 7 p.m.?
I’m tired.
Where did you get those uniforms?
Ms. Nana sent them.
Right.
Pai is still asleep?
Was he up late crunching numbers?
No.
Pai went to bed at 7 p.m.
I’ll check up on him.
We’re getting a divorce before work today.
Why did you pack?
Are you moving house?
Where are you going?
That’s my business.
Ugh.
You don’t have to move.
I’ll let you stay even if we’re divorced.
When Grandpa softens up,
U and North will move back to the condo.
It would be weird for you and me
to stay under the same roof all alone.
It’s not!
See?
This has nothing to do with me, though.
Sure, it’s not.
But I still don’t want to.
Oh.
It’s time to stop playing around.
I’m getting a divorce today!
Sign it.
Ugh. This pen’s out of ink.
Divorce is off.
It’s working just fine.
It’s out of ink.
It’s not.
It is, sir.
I’m literally showing you I can’t write with it.
I told you it’s out of ink.
Take your pick.
No ink, either.
Uh, I can’t write with this one as well.
You gotta work on your quality control.
Behave yourself.
Don’t look so ecstatic.
I hope to never see you again.
I’m still working at your bakery, though.
You’re fired.
What?
You okay with that, North?
There you go.
Thank you, sir.
Pai.
Where are you going?
Do you need a ride?
No, I don’t.
I already have a ride.
What?
Don’t tell me it’s Kuea
My new date.
What?
Who is he? How did you know him?
When did you meet him?
Can you even trust him?
Is he a customer?
No.
I met him online last night.
Alright?
Are you Pai?
Yes.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
What on earth…
What the hell is he thinking?
I don’t trust him.
Y’all can tell that man’s a jerk, right?
Sure thing.
Right.
What if something happens to Pai?
We’d better follow him!
Tim, no!
Hold on!
Take it easy!
Tim.
U and I have to go to work at Empire.
It’ll be 10 p.m. when we’re off work.
Are we supposed to just let Pai go?
Tim.
You know you can’t stop Pai
once he sets his mind on something.
Alright.
I’ll find out where he’s staying right now.
How about that?
Thanks, North.
Uhh, what did you say
you do for a living again?
I have a dehydrated fruit business.
Our products are placed
at airports and such.
What about you, Pai?
What do you do for a living?
I run a mall
Wow.
Wait, no.
I help run a bakery.
Are you hungry?
I am beginning to.
Is there anything you like?
Anything’s fine.
How about steak?
Isn’t it too heavy for breakfast?
Congee?
Too light.
Noodles!
I’m kidding.
Steak is fine.
Shall we?
Of course.
This is unacceptable!
The ink on the divorce certificate
hasn’t even begun to dry!
Here is the information on all the products.
Right.
Oh, one more thing.
The board of directors issued a new
evaluation system on employees today.
These are the evaluation buttons.
Here.
RATE YOUR SATISFACTION
GOOD/NEUTRAL/AWFUL
OUT OF ORDER
TEMPORARILY OUT OF USE
Your life now depends on these buttons.
Are you serious?
AWFUL
I want it! I want it! I want it!
Don’t push that button, kid…
I want it!
That’s enough.
You can’t have it.
The toys here are expensive,
and you will only ruin it.
But I want it! I want it!
I’ll be fine as long as
there are no house geckos.
Does he know I live here now
and he doesn’t?
Grandpa put him in the kid department.
It was a miracle he could even drag
himself all the way home.
Pai.
Thank you for telling me where you live.
I promise I won’t tell Tim.
Forget about him.
He’s been following me all day.
I bet he knows where I live.
He probably thinks
he was being so smooth, too.
How was the date?
The food was great.
I’ll see you around.
Are you Mr. Pai?
Yes.
You have something in your hair.
You also have something on your face.
You look adorable, you know?
But you’re a bit skinny.
Let’s find something to eat, shall we?
S–Sure.
Mr. Pai.
Watch where you’re going!
I’m sorry.
I told you to watch it!
How dare you!
Hey!
How dare you touch me!
Mr. Pai!
Pai, you jerk!
It’s not working.
I don’t know what to talk about with them.
I don’t feel comfortable around them.
And some of them are
someone I’d never date.
Sounds scary.
If you’re not ready, I think
it’s okay to just take a break.
When Tim was injured,
I was just as scared as when I was
before I knew he was fooling me.
You still love him.
Yes.
And I can’t stop myself from believing him
when he talks about our relationship
as if it was all real.
You still love him and believe in him.
Why are you even looking
for someone new?
I want to start over.
Every time I see Tim’s face,
I can still picture our wedding.
Maybe forgiveness is beyond me.
It…
It would be easier to try
and love someone else.
Don’t you think so, North?
North.
Yes?
Go sleep in bed with U.
Good night.
U.
YOU HAVE A NEW MATCH!
TRY TALKING TO THEM.
ABOUT ME
I AM AN ARCHITECT.
THE ALGORITHM MUST KNOW SOMETHING TO BRING US TOGETHER.
“The algorithm must know something
to bring us together.”
(Is that really how you look?)
(You’re pretty.)
(If you say so.
You don’t show your face in the profile.)
(There are so many ways to know
someone more than just their face, right?)
(I can’t tell who you are from your photo.)
(Then how come you chose
to match with me?)
(I don’t know. I want to trust
the algorithm, I guess.)
Did you think I’d say you don’t look
like your profile picture or something?
Yes.
I didn’t want to be ghosted before
I even got to try to make this work.
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you so deadset on fooling me?
I’m not fooling you, though.
That’s my photo in the profile.
You said you’re an architect!
I am an architect!
I just got my permit.
I’ll show you if you don’t believe me.
I am a certified architect.
And I’ve been practicing on the side, too.
What about the name ‘M’?
M as in Me. That’s me.
What kind of person doesn’t recognize
their own boyfriend?
Hold on.
I didn’t lie to you at all.
I was being myself last night.
More myself than the Tim you knew.
And we got along just fine, didn’t we?
You must be delusional.
I only came today out of politeness.
You’re afraid you’ll forgive me.
Can you stop with that?
I don’t care what you believe to be true.
I’m gone.
My love!
My love, don’t leave me!
Don’t leave me like this.
Please, my love!
Don’t leave me.
What the hell is wrong with you?
If you abandon me,
how will our baby and I go on?
Baby?
What baby?
My love!
Polyester tent with waterproof coating.
- Fibergla—
- Excuse me.
I need a tent recommendation.
Something even a boy like him can set up on his own.
The easiest way would be to stay home.
Be damned with the tent.
North!
How could you say that to a customer?
Ma’am, I must apologize.
He’s new here so he’s still learning.
“He’s still learning”?
What if he sells me a product that doesn’t work?
The easiest tents to set up are the automatic and the inflatable.
Automatic?
That would take away the heart of camping.
How about…
This one?
It’s compact, dome-shaped, and made of polyester, and it’s waterproof.
The poles—
Can you demonstrate the setup?
What do these buttons do?
Of course!
Go on a date with me.
Come on.
Please!
I will agree if you stop making a ruckus.
So come with me so I can stop.
Where are we going?
Here.
What?
It’s a treasure hunt.
A thrift store like this is where you find rare items, you know?
I don’t want anything here.
They don’t have the kind of clothes I wear.
That’s why I want to take you here.
I want to see what this version of Pai would choose to wear.
“This version of Pai”?
You’re dressed like the CEO of a mall.
But you don’t need to keep up the facade or anything today.
You don’t have to care what your Aunt Kia says.
So you can wear whatever you want.
I’ll pay for it.
You have money?
Of course.
It’s 70 baht per 100 grams, after all.
And you?
Does this outfit reflect who you are?
This is how I’m always dressed.
But I’ll change if you want me to.
Right.
That’s fair.
Let’s go.
I’ll pick the best outfits for you. I’ll make sure you look great.
How about this?
Well?
It suits you.
Makes your skin pop, this one.
Hold on to this.
Hold it.
That’s an option. It’s a good one.
What about this?
Aunt Kia style.
Well?
I’ll add it to the pile.
No.
No?
It’s my personal favorite.
It is.
I know it’s not yours, and that’s okay.
It is mine.
You don’t normally care for T-shirts, though, do you?
Wow.
Now this is a killer.
Rock and roll, you know?
You like this?
You like that?
How about this one?
Here.
You like this.
Now that’s a hit right now.
POLCASAN, you know?
Where has Pai gone?
Camouflage.
I’m Pai of Empire.
You don’t think this is accurate?
Are you making fun of me?
Yes.
Go get changed right now.
Here.
That was tiring,
but it was fun.
Was it as fun as spending time with the other three or four dudes?
No.
You did not even come close to any of them.
Is that right?
How come you haven’t stopped smiling all day, then?
Oh!
The duckling returns!
Ow!
What now?
Well, we’ll grab dinner, and then maybe a drink.
And after that, if there’s still something we want to do, we definitely can.
Keep dreaming.
Hey!
If you get up right now, I’m screaming even louder than before.
I’m shameless, you know?
Try me if you want.
Why are you being so persistent?
You ever met someone so right for you
that no one after could replace him?
You just can’t let him go no matter what.
This is the “easy to set up” option?
Would I need to call a construction crew if this was a hard-to-set-up one?
If you can’t assemble a tent, give it up.
Book a hotel or a homestay instead.
But it was you who said it was easy to set up.
If I said it is difficult, who would buy it?
So you opted to deceive customers by overclaiming?
North.
You can not say that to a customer.
Apologize right now.
But—
No but!
It’s evident you can’t set up the tent.
You’re wasting her time,
and you’re being rude.
Aunt—
This customer—
Ma’am, I must apologize for this mistake.
It is my fault for failing to train my employee well.
Right.
I do hope to receive some good recommendations in the future.
I’ll come by again… to talk to this specific staff member.
Come on, Da Zhan.
Let’s take a look at the toy section.
RATE YOUR SATISFACTION
GOOD/NEUTRAL/AWFUL
Thank you.
Here.
Let’s go, Da Zhan.
What happened?
She just wanted me to recommend some toys for the boy.
So I asked him what kind of skills he’s looking to play the toys with.
And I gave them a demonstration.
They bought everything I showed them.
So she did the same thing.
What?
North?
By the time North becomes mature enough,
no one would care to come to our mall, Papa.
Come in.
What complaint do you have now?
Auntie.
If I could assemble the tent I recommended, you’d buy it, wouldn’t you?
Of course.
I wanted to help you out.
But look how you treated me.
I’m sorry.
I thought you were just trying to mess with me.
Listen to me, North.
The people who come toour mall aren’t here to shop.
They’re here for a walk, for a stroll.
Our job is to entice them into shopping.
Because at the end, it doesn’t matter what they’re doing in your department.
What matters is what you’re doing in your department.
Ugh!
You’re selling tents but you don’t know how to set up a tent.
You’ve been working at the bakery. Did you try all the pastry you’re selling?
No.
Marvelous.
Oh, North.
I advise you to focus on getting through this trainee program.
Otherwise, you wouldn’t survive anywhere.
Y–Yes.
I have to get back to work.
Go on.
Papa.
Don’t baby him.
It’s better he hears all this from me
than for him to go viral on TikTok because he offends some customers.
But North isn’t used to being criticized.
And that’s why he is the way that he is.
It’s the middle of the day.
Why are you screaming?
Where the hell did you come from?
North, you alright?
U…
I’m a loser.
No, that’s not true.
All I do is make mistakes.
I want to comfort you.
But I can’t understand a word you say.
U!
Well, I couldn’t understand.
The most infuriating part was that…
They were right about everything.
When I started this bakery,
I was truly clueless, just like Grandpa said.
I’m just so…
How about this?
Hold on.
Why don’t you try coming up with a recipe?
Maybe make a drink.
Choose what you like.
By the end of the day, you can tell Grandpa
you even came up with a menu item.
Careful.
I’ll add a lemon slice.
Here.
Why did you buy it?
Grandpa won’t soften up just because you made one purchase.
You got it wrong.
I didn’t buy it so you could meet your sales target.
I bought it so you could learn how to assemble it.
What?
How could you come up with that?
That is so thoughtful.
Oww!
Right.
Let’s begin.
Go on.
Alright.
Do you need my help?
No, no, no.
First of all, connect the poles.
Connect the poles.
That doesn't look promising.
Let me help.
No, no, no, no.
I have to learn how to assemble it.
Is this where this goes, U?
Yes.
Now this is getting to the hard part.
You’ll have to help me hold this.
I’ll grab it.
You get that.
There’s no way his grandfather wouldn’t soften up after seeing this.
Oh, my voice must be in the video.
U, I did it!
I assembled a tent!
Good job.
It really is durable.
You’ve never slept in a tent before?
I have, but in the kind of tent that comes with air-conditioning and a bed.
I’ve never slept in the kind that I have to assemble myself before.
You wanna sleep here tonight?
So you can tell customers how it is.
You’ll be an expert on this.
Alright.
Let’s do it.
Hey, you’re going to knock it down.
It’s strong enough.
Don’t knock it down.
Well?
It’s amazing, right?
You’re not even going to take me to a nice bar?
This is my kind of hidden bar.
And this is my special cocktail.
Are you sure it’s edible?
Of course.
It’s full of your favorite things.
It’s good.
See?
I told you it would be good.
Hey.
Slow down.
It’s strong.
But if you want to get drunk, by all means.
I’ll give you a ride home.
No.
I prefer having all my wits about me tonight.
I prefer that, too.
So you can’t blame the alcohol if you decide to fold.
You said this place is special.
There’s nothing special about this.
Come.
Sit down.
Look up.
What is all this, U?
North.
Come here.
What?
Sit down.
Oh!
You see that, North?
Over there.
What?
Here.
Look.
Where?
There.
There?
A tiger?
We could be eaten.
Oh, my!
We’re going to be eaten.
I’m so scared.
You’re unbelievable.
I can’t take you to South Africa.
So I’m bringing South Africa to you.
You sure this is just as good?
Of course.
Well…
What else is there?
Of course, there is.
Oh, that’s bad…
Look.
A herd of zebras.
On the neighborhood’s shrine.
Oh, U!
What are you laughing at?
Did you drop your car key?
Why did you tell me to take you here?
I just want to know if I meet this version of you here,
would I like you.
Why did everything have to be a lie?
I’m sorry.
It’s been a very good date today.
But I don’t know if it’s because I like who you are,
or if it’s because I’m still in love with you.
I want to fall in love with someone else.
Anyone who resembles you even just a little.
But there’s no one.
Resembles me?
Do you mean…
the me that I am now or the one you fell for?
My life used to be full of mess,
but now I have no one.
Even Grandpa chose only North.
I should be furious that you’re being so hard to get rid of,
but all I feel is relieved that I still see you every time I turn around.
I told you
I’m not letting you go.
How could our relationship work, Tim?
How could I forget everything that happened?
You don’t have to forget.
If you have to be mad at me for the rest of our lives, I’ll be here.
I told you not to cry.
You look like a duckling.
Duckling, my foot.
I’m serious.
What are you doing here?
The mall is closed!
Run!
Wait.
Where are we going?
You don’t own this place anymore, you know?
Run!
I have to be at the client’s office.
So I’ll be busy.
Someone misses him like crazy, huh?
I don’t miss him!
Someone in the same department broke up last week.
I don’t want to break up!
What?
I’m sorry for making you feel bad.
I made this for you.
The weather is perfect.
We just need a blackout and we’re all set.