Tim and I will probably be busy with
preparing for the wedding next week.
I’ll try to be there.
Give me one last hug
and we have ourselves a fair deal.
I’m giving you back the 250 million.
We’re getting a divorce.
I don’t want anything from you, North.
Somebody as nice as you
would never hurt me.
I’ll go.
Wait.
You said you wouldn’t give up.
How the hell did it turn out like that?
Honestly, I think it’s because
North still has feelings for me.
What about you?
Aren’t you getting married?
What?
Why aren’t you dancing on air?
What’s wrong?
I’m happy.
I’m just figuring something out.
Oom can’t be at my wedding anymore.
What?
Why not?
That’s some nerve you got there
asking me that.
Did you forget the same mom incident?
Oh, yeah.
You’re right.
My plan was that
I’d hire Oom as my mother,
so she could keep everyone who plays
my relatives and groomsmen in check.
But now that she can’t be there,
everything is derailed.
How about you let me help you?
I’m good at this, you know.
It’s too risky.
Tim, listen to me.
I only know a handful of people.
You, North, Ms. Nana, and Mr. Pai.
Keeping a low profile at the wedding
wouldn’t be difficult for me.
It’s easy-breezy.
But I think—
Don’t say no.
Believe me.
I’m the perfect guy for the job.
I swear anyone else you hire
would turn their back on you.
But not me.
Alright?
Fine.
What did you tell Mr. Pai
about Oom, though?
I really need to apologize
to you and Pai, love
I’m in London right now,
and I don’t feel very well.
I don’t think I can fly back in time.
It’s alright, Mom.
I’ll see you when you feel better.
Mom.
Mom?
Mom
Mom, the connection’s not good.
I’ll hang up and we’ll talk soon.
Take a rest, Mom.
Bye.
Ugh, what a drag.
I hope you don’t mind,
but I’m taking a few of these home.
It’s too bad.
Yeah.
But there’s nothing we can do.
I’ll go get ready.
We have so many things
to sort out at the hotel.
Are you getting nervous, baby?
Yeah.
I got all anxious about it all of a sudden.
We’re getting married soon.
You don’t have to be.
How about this?
I’ll be there for you.
I’ll be a groom, too.
You won’t have to do it all alone.
That sounds good?
Umm.
Alright?
Alright
Nervous, are you?
I’m gonna take a shower.
No need to be nervous.
Oh, Kuea.
Hey, Pai.
You can wait in the groomsmen’s
waiting room over there, Mr. Kuea.
Of course.
See you.
Good luck.
This way, Mr. Pai.
The venue is upstairs, sir.
Please.
Over there.
Hello, Ms. Nana.
Right. I’m here.
Where should I wait?
Should I…
I’m alright.
Yes.
All done, sir.
Thank you.
Can you excuse me for a minute?
Ms. Nana.
Yes?
Do you happen to have
a necklace for me to borrow?
I want to be at the gold and silver gates.
Mr. North,
there’s no gold and silver gates
at a Chinese wedding procession.
Oww.
There goes my extra pocket money.
I’m here.
Right.
Thank you.
I’ll take it from here.
Mr. North, please wait in the hall
with all your relatives, sir.
As for Mr. Tim…
Yes?
Please follow me.
Of course.
Best of luck, Tim.
Thanks.
I wonder how much that is.
I heard it’s 69 million.
It’s Mr. Tim’s whole life savings.
I see.
I’m sorry.
You have the same build
as my boyfriend’s.
I…
I was careless.
Sorry.
It’s alright.
Excuse me.
Bye.
Ho, hi ho hi ho hi ho…
- Hew!
Hew!
Let’s go.
Please give a round of applause
to our newlyweds!
Mr. Tim, please pick up the ring.
You can now put it on
Mr. Pai’s left ring finger.
Mr. Pai, please pick up the ring.
Please put it on Mr. Tim’s left ring finger.
And from this moment on,
Mr. Thanin Chaiyanuwat and
Mr. Jirachote Jeeramongkolthanun
are now husbands.
Please give them
another round of applause.
MARRIAGE CERTIFICATE
To sanctify their love,
in front of all of us as witnesses,
what should the newlyweds do?
- Kiss!
That is loud and clear.
So please, kiss!
In one,
two,
three.
The newlyweds will now visit each table
to show their gratitude for your attendance.
Another round of applause, please.
Hey.
I’m gonna go grab some wine.
You want anything?
One for me as well.
White wine, please.
I hope the food is to your liking.
Hello.
Hi.
I can’t help but wonder if you have
a drinking partner tonight.
Uhh…
I’m Tim’s groomsman.
I see.
I’m Pai’s cousin.
What are you drinki—
Crap.
Are you alright?
Please let me know…
Careful, boy!
Stay away from my boyfriend.
Hey—
Excuse me.
Pai.
What are you doing here?
What do you want?
I…
North, did you know about this?
I didn’t.
This is the first time I saw him.
Mr. Pai, I can explain.
Go on, then.
What are you doing here, U?
I…
What do you want now?
What happened?
I missed North.
Are you out of your mind?
You broke up.
What would you want to see him for?
I couldn’t stop myself.
Pai, let me deal with this.
North, take your brother and go.
Come here.
- I didn’t—
- Just come on.
Forget it.
North.
Are you sure you didn’t know about this?
I really didn’t.
I found out the same way you did.
Mr. Pai, sir.
Mr. Pai.
My name is Airy.
And we have something
we’d like to tell you, Mr. Pai.
Ms. Airy.
Please, Ms. Airy.
Let’s talk outside.
Let go of me.
Please listen to me.
Why don’t we talk outside?
Please, let’s talk.
Please.
Mr. Pai, we are all here to tell you the truth
about what your groom did to us.
Tim?
What’s going on?
I can explain, Pai.
There’s actually nothing serious.
Let’s talk outside.
It’s better if you hear it from us, Mr. Pai.
Last week, Hong and I—
Oh, I’m mistaken.
Tim and I… We just broke up.
If I didn’t get suspicious,
I wouldn’t have found out
what an awful man your groom is.
Tell me everything.
He’s here with different women every day.
You’re not the only one.
What you don’t know is that
Tim was going out with all of us.
When I said he was going out
with all of us,
I did mean that he was cheating on you,
while getting more than 10 million
in total out of all of us.
Is that true…
Tim?
Tell me it isn’t true.
Tell him, Tim.
Or is it Hong?
Or is it Mek?
Or is it Vee?
Please, stop, Airy.
I’ll admit it.
I’m sorry.
You think an apology is enough?
I’m not suing you today.
But I’ll at least do this!
Girls, get him!
Security!
Make him pay for all the money
he took from us!
I don’t remember!
I’m sorry!
No photos, please!
Pai.
Pai, hear me out.
Hey.
You awake?
How are you feeling?
What happened?
One of your girls threw
a wine bottle at you.
It knocked you out.
I didn’t know what to do
so I took you to the hospital.
You’re alright, though.
The doctor said you should just
take a rest and you’ll be fine.
Hey, hey, hey.
You don’t need to get up so soon.
Where’s Pai?
Is that the only thing
on your mind right now?
Mr. Pai?
Worry about yourself first.
Tim!
Tim, what would the doctor say?
That’s everything I know.
You and Mr. North had no idea
Mr. Tim is a con artist?
As we said,
we only learned that about U.
As for Tim… We had no clue.
Ugh.
What a mess.
Da Zhan, don’t play with that.
I’ve heard everything from our lawyers.
Let me talk to Pai.
You two, stay.
The rest of you, go and wait outside.
Pai.
How will you take responsibility for this?
I admit it was because
I wasn’t being careful.
I’m willing to pay for everything.
But I ask for one thing…
Call me if anything comes up, alright?
Of course, Auntie.
Da Zhan, wake up, dear.
Let’s go and take you to bed.
North.
Where is Pai?
He’s getting lectured by Grandpa in there.
- Hey, hey!
- Tim.
Do not enter, sir.
Why not?
Wait out here quietly with me
if you don’t have a death wish.
I have to see Pai.
You can’t.
U, let go of me!
Please.
Pai!
Tim.
Let go of me!
Pai!
What’s the ruckus?
Pai.
What are you doing here?
Don’t show your face here again.
Both of you.
Baby, listen to—
Don’t call me “baby.”
I don’t even know who you are.
Pai.
Please calm down and listen to me.
I won’t sue you,
or press any charges.
I only ask that you both leave us alone.
What do you mean
you won’t press charges?
I talked to Grandpa.
I admit it was because
I wasn’t being careful.
I’m willing to pay for everything.
But I ask for one thing…
Please don’t press charges
or sue both Tim and U.
Pai?
To preserve our family’s reputation and
to reassure Empire’s businesses,
I will resign as the CEO of Empire.
Do you think your resignation
will fix anything?
Well, then…
Cut me loose from this family.
I want nothing to do with this family.
I will not spend the money or use the
privileges from my previous role at work.
Will that…
be enough for you?
I’m useless to you now.
So, please…
Just get out of my life.
Pai.
Pai, wait.
Tim.
Mr. Pai.
Let him be.
You can talk to him later.
Grandpa can’t do this.
How could he disown Pai?
North!
You two are not allowed
to help him in any way!
How could you do this, Grandpa?
If you’re going to disown Pai,
you might as well disown me too!
I don’t want Pai to take responsibility
for this alone.
North!
You never scold me
when I do something wrong.
I’m not done dealing with this.
I don’t care.
You have no right to do this to Pai.
If you disown Pai,
I won’t talk to you again!
Good!
Then you can both go, the lot of you!
Seize both of their credit cards,
as well as their bank accounts.
Take back every single car,
and every single home,
and all of their assets.
They will go with nothing but
the clothes on their backs.
North?
What happened?
How come you’re locked out, too?
I…
I put up a fight against Grandpa…
For you.
I guess I’m also disowned now.
North.
Why would you do that?
I can take care of myself if I’m on my own,
but you…
I don’t know if I can take care of you.
It’s alright.
As long as we have each other,
I know we can do it.
You’re locked out, too?
I guess Grandpa won’t even
let us pack our bags.
I told you I don’t want to see
you two again.
Don’t you understand?
I do.
But I still want to see you.
So I don’t think I can do
what you told me to.
Mr. Pai.
We really want to help you and North.
What can you do?
Did you not cause
enough problems already?
I can take care of myself.
Can you drop the tough guy act for a sec?
You don’t have to act like
you’re strong in front of me.
I know you’re exhausted.
Let me take care of you.
Once you’re back on your feet,
we can go from there.
Pai.
Please.
I have a house.
It’s big enough for all of us.
Let’s stay there for now.
We can work the rest out later.
Listen to me.
I will never step foot in your house.
How about you staying at my place?
North and I will stay at Tim’s.
You don’t have much choice
today, you know?
Just shut your mouth.
Let’s go, then.
What are we waiting for?
Let’s go.
Pai.
Pai!
You and North stay here tonight.
We’ll sort things out tomorrow morning.
Thank you.
Tim.
Can I talk to you for a bit?
Can you wait outside?
Sure.
Don’t take long.
I’m scared of ghosts.
Come on.
We’ll be a minute.
Please.
I don’t know what this was all about.
But…
Are you in love with Pai?
If I say yes, will you believe me?
Okay.
That’s all I need to hear.
You should go to Pai.
Tim.
Don’t fool him again.
I’m begging you.
I promise I won’t lie to him again.
North.
I think this place is haunted.
Don’t be ridiculous.
- I mean it!
- Just go take a shower.
U.
Hmm?
Can you get in bed with me?
I’m scared of ghosts.
You were just calling me ridiculous.
Well, you kept mentioning ghosts!
Come on.
Of course.
U…
Hmm?
Did you know about Tim before?
U!
I’m sorry.
I actually got to know Tim after I met you.
He and I clocked each other
the minute we locked eyes.
So we promised to have each other’s back
if we didn’t betray each other.
You conmen are unbelievable.
Look at us.
None of us has anything
to our names now.
I have nothing for you
to swindle off of me anymore.
So if you want to leave,
this is when you make a run for it.
North.
I’m not going anywhere.
I brought you here.
I have to take responsibility.
Come.
Come here.
I won’t let you go through this.
I promise everything will be alright.
I’ve brought you a change of clothes.
Well, at least he took it.
Help!
Pai, what’s happened?
Pai!
That hurts!
Pai, what’s wrong?
Pai!
What’s happened?
Gecko!
Where?
Where is it?
Gecko! It’s in my shirt!
It’s in my shirt!
What you looking at?
Get out!
I’m here to save you, you know?
What happens
if another gecko falls on you?
I was only taken by surprise.
But I’m more cautious now.
I can take care of myself.
Get out!
Alright, good boy.
Don’t shout for help
if you see another one.
That’s scary.
Put a shirt back on.
I’ll take you to breakfast.
No need.
I’m more than capable of
having breakfast on my own.
Get out!
GRANDMA’S MADE-TO-ORDER
Hello.
Hey, U.
A table for how many people?
Three, please.
Sit down.
Table for one, sir.
Pai.
(Next up, let’s see a pregnant
mother cow in Khon Khaen.)
(Cows normally carry their pregnancy
to nine months…)
I thought the wedding yesterday
would be on every channel.
Grandpa would never allow it.
I’m sure he paid them a hefty sum
to cover up the news.
We’re lucky it’s not a scandal.
Most people wouldn’t know,
but our business partners
must have learned about it.
They’re probably only keeping it quiet
for the sake of manners.
Can we please order?
GRANDMA’S MADE-TO-ORDER
Help me out.
How is it, Mr. Pai?
Are you full?
Please enjoy yourself.
This meal is on me.
It’s your responsibility anyway.
You’re right.
Tim told me—
Don’t say that name in front of me.
Of course.
A thief told me you had an encounter
with a house gecko in my room.
I’m really sorry about that, Mr. Pai.
My place is actually crawling with geck—
Stop talking about house geckos.
Just say what you want to say.
Shouldn’t you stay with us?
Yeah, Pai.
Move into the house.
We slept like a rock last night.
Come on.
I’ll put your things upstairs.
You two.
Can I talk to you?
What about?
Did you really get a divorce?
Or did you fool me, too?
We really got a divorce.
If you did,
how come you’re still clinging
to each other like that?
You ever heard of ‘a slip of the hand’?
Don’t be ridiculous.
U, tell me and be succinct.
North and I really are divorced.
I was going to leave him.
I even packed my bag.
But North looked like
he was on the verge of tears,
and then jumped into my arms,
and kissed me.
So we…
Slept together.
U!
‘Slip of the hand,’ you know?
Enough.
I’ve heard enough.
I’m going to take a nap.
Hey!
Where’s my room?
Come upstairs and find out.
You complain a lot, don’t you?
And he nags a lot, too.
North.
Yes?
Actually, I haven’t talked to you about this.
What?
Let’s start over.
Start over?
Let’s start over and go out properly.
Let’s keep no secrets from each other.
No paranoia.
No con this time.
Let’s do it.
Yes!
Under one condition.
What is it?
Please don’t lie to me again from now on,
no matter what it’s about.
Agreed.
Okay.
You can sleep here.
I promise there are no geckos.
Here.
What happened to you?
Oh?
This?
Someone threw a wine bottle at my head.
As for this on my hand,
I shoved the IV off when
I needed to get out of the hospital.
You were at the hospital?
Why did you leave?
I left because I was worried about you.
I didn’t want you to go through
the mess I made on your own.
You should get the wounds dressed
if you don’t want an infection.
Worried about me?
Can you help me with it?
Why don’t you take care of yourself?
Go.
TIM AND PAI’S HOME PROJECT
I really did study architecture.
Why are you so spooked?
This house really isn’t haunted.
Don’t worry about that.
It’s not ghosts I’m afraid of.
I’m more worried about getting haunted
by someone who’s still living.
Honestly, what have you been lying to me?
I lied about being an interior designer.
I do have a degree,
but I never quite got to work
in that field of expertise.
I’m not polite, calm,
or remotely gentlemanly.
That was just a character
I created to gain your trust.
But that wasn’t the case at the end.
What do you mean?
I let my true colors slip out
when I was with you.
It got harder and harder to stop myself
when I fell in love with you.
If you don’t love me, don’t say that.
Pai.
I really am in love with you.
Maybe not from the first moment we met,
but I am in love with you.
I know I was wrong for what happened.
I’m sorry.
Don’t think I’ll forgive you
just because I agreed to stay at your place.
I’m not giving up on you.
Just watch out and try not to fall for me.
Be my guest.
Well, I did ask.
Gecko!
Where?
Where’s the gecko?
There it is!
Did you lie to me?
Aren’t you a fighter?
Fight me.
Fight me!
Let go of me!
Why don’t you fight me back?
North!
Don’t bother North.
Help!
Mr. Pai?
Pai?
It’s just some ghosts, North.
Let’s go back to bed.
Hold on.
North can’t help you.
Don’t you see that he’s sleeping?
Hey!
I guess North really can’t help
since he’s sleeping.
Just take North to bed, U.
I can exorcise this ghost on my own.
Wait.
- Let’s go.
- No way.
U!
Hold on!
If it’s just about money,
I’ll agree to a divorce.
But can we share a nice meal
one last time?
Why are you still seeing U, North?
If he wanted to fool me,
he would have run.
It must be love if he chose to stay.
It’s a shame.
I would have loved to meet him
one more time.
You mean the Tim you knew?
Yeah.
Alright.
Hey, baby.