Sign it.
Are you Pai?
Yes.
This is unacceptable!
The ink on the divorce certificate
hasn’t even begun to dry!
Work for Empire.
I think it’s best for you to take the offer.
I’ll take it.
Go on a date with me.
I will agree if you stop making a ruckus.
You ever met someone so right for you?
How could our relationship work?
How could I forget everything
that happened?
You don’t have to forget.
If you have to be mad at me
for the rest of our lives, I’ll be here.
Hiking is definitely
going to be the new luxury.
I think this can definitely mint money
if we just know how to pitch it.
We met on a hike, didn’t we?
Right.
Thank you.
You guys should hurry up and leave
if you want to beat the morning traffic.
Oh, right, Pai.
Grandpa invited me over for dinner
at home after work.
You wanna join us?
Who did he invite?
Me.
But that’s as good as inviting you.
I doubt it is.
Come on.
You’ll never make up with him
if you keep sulking.
I’m not sulking.
You know how busy this place gets.
I don’t have time for dinner.
Just go to work.
Alright.
I’m leaving.
Bye, Pai.
Bye, Tim.
Goodbye.
Let me carry this.
Work?
Oh. Right.
I told you I got a job, right?
But I’ll have to be at the
client’s office a lot, though.
I’ll be busy for a while.
That’s perfect.
I could use some peace and quiet.
I’ll try to make time for you.
And I’ll keep you updated.
Alright?
Why would you do that?
It’s not like we’re dating, you know?
But last night you said
you wanted me to sta—
That didn’t mean I wanted
to get back together.
Okay.
Fine by me.
I have to go to work, though.
Can I get some emotional support?
No.
I’d say yes.
Hey!
If you hit me again, I’m kissing you.
Alright.
Bring it on.
Bring it.
Another shove, huh?
Alright.
You wanna try that again?
Oh, alright!
Fine by me!
There!
Okay!
TWO MONTHS LATER
See?
I told you it takes less than
10 minutes to set up.
With friends, I’d say it can take
as quickly as five minutes.
This is super fun, Mama.
Here.
I’ll take two.
Alright, Auntie.
We see a 13% increase
in hiking gear sales, sir.
As for children’s toys, it’s a 25% spike.
Customers’ satisfaction in the past
two months is much better, sir.
And their managers’ evaluation?
For Mr. North, the comment says,
“He’s always trying to improve himself
without being told.”
For Mr. U, it says,
“Thorough attention to details.
A caring staff and colleague
who makes working more pleasant.”
I think it’s time to start training at the office.
I’ll put you two on the same team.
You both need to learn how to separate
your personal matters from work.
Thank you, Grandpa.
And don’t worry. We can definitely do that.
Am I right, U?
Right.
I do believe so.
And you can move back into the condo.
Thank you.
I love you so much, Grandpa.
You’re not mad at me anymore, are you?
(Pai?)
(U and I passed the first test.)
We’re moving to the sales promotion team.
(We’ll be dining with our team tonight.)
It’s a thank-you dinner, that kind of thing.
You should come.
I can’t.
Pai.
I just want to tell you that…
Grandpa forgave me.
(He gave me back all my credit cards.)
(Should I give you one?)
You don’t have to.
Where are you staying right now?
Wanna stay at my place for a while?
I can take care of myself.
Okay.
Oh.
(Hello.)
(Oh, your parents are here.)
(I’m on the phone with Pai.)
(You are?)
(Yes.)
Pai, how are you, love?
(You never come to see your old man.)
Oh, we’re busy at the bakery right now.
I have to go.
Bye.
Oh, honey…
What a shame.
I guess he’s busy.
Your parents didn’t even try
to help you out or send money?
No.
They have to heed Grandpa’s words.
But you’re their child.
I don’t know.
They had never been much help
in the first place,
so to them, it’s just as it always was.
But you always get by on your own,
so they never have to worry about you.
Unlike North.
That dude is worrisome
whether he’s in a pinch or not.
But it’s nice having you
around the bakery, Pai.
You don’t skip work,
you don’t bother people.
And people don’t seem to dare
mess with you.
You’re definitely worth your salary.
I’ll give you an extra 600 baht.
Do you know why no one
dares mess with me, Pure?
…Right.
I–I have a call.
Excuse me.
Our next project is a
new promotional campaign
under the slogan “Gifts for Lovers.”
You guys are dating, right?
This must be easy.
You know all about each other.
How about we have a little challenge?
We’ll split into two teams.
Each will come up with their
own ideas for the campaign.
U, you’re on Team A.
North, you’re on Team B.
Of course.
How serious is a challenge
like this usually?
Very serious.
There’s a prize.
A prize?
That’s right.
This new project is a welcome ritual
for our new members.
As for the prize…
The winner will pass the probation
right away.
What happens to the person
who doesn’t pass it?
I mean, Grandpa wouldn’t fire me.
I believe he plans to put
you back in camping gear.
I won’t go easy on you, U.
“Now that everyone’s busy,
it gets lonely around here.”
“Is this what it feels like to be forgotten?”
Stop it.
That’s not what the voice
in my head is saying.
Oh, but Pai,
is Tim working an office job now?
I haven’t seen him in a while.
I thought he’s a freelancer?
He said he had to be at the office because
of some computer program and discretion.
He’s only here a few days a week.
I’m sure someone around here must be
missing him like crazy right now.
I don’t.
I’m happy he’s not here since
he’s always such a fuss to deal with.
So you don’t miss him?
Not at all!
Well, what do these
duckling cookies mean?
It’s just a character.
It doesn't represent anyone.
Oh?
Tim just sent in an order.
He said he needs it delivered to his office.
“I must ask Pai to make the delivery.”
“I miss him.”
Nonsense.
Alright.
I’ll call some delivery guy, then.
No.
I’ll go.
Let’s think about cost.
Give me the key.
Quickly.
Sure.
Pai.
Hmm?
Did you forget the food?
Oh, I’m getting it done.
I’ll get it done right now.
You must be in a hurry.
That yearning rushes you, doesn’t it?
Keep talking.
I won’t!
(You can come in when you’re here.)
Hello?
Yeah.
It’s here.
I found it.
It’s on the table.
You said it was in a folder.
You idiot, I was looking everywhere for it.
You guys gonna be here soon?
Right.
I’ll call you back.
Wanna come in?
No, thanks.
You should get back to work.
I don’t want to bother you.
It’s more than alright.
Just come on in.
Why did you even let me in here?
It’s okay.
What? It’s alright.
Give it here.
I’ll get it.
Hold on.
This… I made this for you.
You did?
What is it?
Cookies?
Adorable.
You’re just my test subject
in case this isn’t edible.
Did you name it?
You try it and name it.
Oh, I don’t think I can take a bite.
Look at it.
It’s so adorable I don’t think
I have the heart to eat it.
Just give it back here if you don’t like it.
Hey.
I like it.
I’m just saying it’s too cute to eat.
Just eat.
No.
Here.
I’ll make more.
It’s good.
But… it smells familiar.
I knew you liked lemon
so I put it in as well.
Any ideas about the name?
How about IMY and ILY?
What?
It’s short for “I miss you” and “I love you.”
No.
That’s not adorable at all.
What about Immy and Illy?
“Hello. My name is Immy.”
“I’m also Illy.”
“Nice to meet you, Pai.”
“Please don’t eat me.”
Stop it.
Take it back.
You’re so unimaginative.
Ahem!
I’ve never felt more single in my life.
I probably should go.
You should not.
Stay.
No way.
You’re at work.
I’m an outsider.
“Outsider”?
Don’t you say that again.
He’s right.
Please make yourself at home, Pai.
You know me?
Of course I do.
Hey! You can’t use that as your desktop.
People could see!
What’s with that?
Don’t worry about us.
Tim talks about you every day.
I feel like we’re friends already.
Stop it, all of you.
You’re selling me out.
I doubt it.
We’re just making fun of you.
Make yourself comfortable.
“Lil Immy wants to be eaten.”
“Ah!”
This is so nice.
We work and take breaks
at the same time.
I can be clingy any time I want.
Ahem!
Oh, dear.
You two are just like Mr. Pai and Mr. Tim
when they were going out.
Really?
I thought Pai would be
more composed at work.
He let it slip sometimes
when I forgot to knock on the door.
I can imagine that.
How’s your first day at work?
Amazing.
Everyone on the team is so nice.
It’s been fun.
That’s a relief.
Did you know a couple on your team literally just broke up last week?
The tension in the meeting room
was insane after that.
Why did they break up?
Because they worked together.
They quit, though, so everyone
can breathe now.
Quit?
Yes.
Both of them.
Both of them?
That’s why we had two empty chairs
for you both to fill.
Oh, we’re filling in!
But I believe you two love each other
enough to not fight over work.
I have to get back to work now.
Right.
So we replaced them, huh?
Alright, guys.
I think there should be an event for
couples to exchange gifts as a contest.
Make it viral.
The audience will get to see
the products we’ll put up for display.
Yes?
Wouldn’t that be too activity-focused?
It wouldn’t help with sales.
How about this?
We give some discounts
for paired up products?
Make it cheaper to buy
two products together.
I think that seems like the best option
for what we’re aiming to do.
But everyone is doing that.
We’re looking to hold an event.
We have to do something special.
But you can’t be too focused on the event
that you forget to boost sales.
Did you listen to what I said at all?
Of course, I did.
I was listening.
That’s why I raised the question.
But your idea is something that can
work with even online shopping.
But your idea depends on things
going viral, which is too much risk for us.
Are you saying my idea is bad?
That’s not what I mean.
That’s exactly what you mean!
It just needs more thoughts.
I don’t think it always works out.
If your plan is to break them up,
I think it’s working, Papa.
It’s not.
I wanted them to work together so
they could become life long partners.
Where is Tim?
He’s still at work.
I see.
Uhh, is everything okay between you two?
- No.
- Yes.
Is it about work?
It’s nothing, Pai.
It just seems that I’m incapable of
coming up with good ideas.
North.
You can’t sulk because of
that comment I made at work.
Oh, sure.
I’m a loser and also a sulker.
My bad.
I’m a bad boyfriend and a bad colleague.
What?
North.
Just go.
Bye.
Here we are.
Oh, where did they all go?
I’ll take all of that.
Sure.
I’m gonna go.
I can’t anymore.
I’m too tired.
Hello, Pai?
(It’s nothing. Bye.)
Hold on.
What’s the matter?
(It’s nothing.)
Just stay put. I’ll be there.
I have to go.
See you.
Here.
You can go home.
I just needed someone to open the bottle.
What’s wrong?
You can talk to me, you know?
I don’t know.
Everything that used to be easy suddenly
becomes harder when I’m alone.
All this time, I thought I’d done everything all by myself, without anyone’s help.
But now that I’m left behind,
it just hurts more than I thought.
Pai.
Am I such an awful person
that no one wants to stay with me?
Pai.
No one hates you.
They just don’t know if you need them.
I don’t know.
No one ever made me feel
that way except…
Except who?
No.
No one.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
I just never thought I’d get to see
this side of you again.
Sorry it makes me happy.
This side of me?
Well, the side that gets scared and…
makes you think you’re unlovable.
Aside from me, I don’t think anyone
has ever seen you like this.
Honestly…
Why do you even like me?
Why this question all of a sudden?
Because I don’t have an answer
for that question myself.
to think that no one loves me.
It is so much easier
Pai.
They love you.
You can call me a liar on anything.
But at least believe me when I tell you this.
Ugh, this is awful.
I don’t want to fight.
We get to work together as a couple.
I don’t want to break up!
What?
Break up?
Ain’t no way!
Come here.
I’m sorry I made you feel bad.
I’m sorry as well.
Come to think of it,
you were right.
Should we work together
instead of competing?
Here.
When you bought me this guy,
why did you decide to buy it then?
Why not wait for an occasion?
Hmm…
When I want someone I love to be happy,
I just want it to happen
as soon as possible.
The sooner the better.
This campaign is called “Now is the Best.”
Most people believe they need special
occasions to buy their loved ones a gift.
But what we’re doing is urging people
to buy them right now.
Then let’s try this campaign right now.
U!
Yes!
- Thank you.
Pai, dear.
Papa? Mama?
What are you doing here?
Pure called us.
Pure?
Yes.
He told us you want to talk to Grandpa,
but you don’t know how.
Let’s go, Pai.
Life must have gotten too difficult to bear
for you to crawl your way back here.
Not at all.
I can get by just fine.
Just say what you’re here to say.
I don’t have all day.
Why do I need a reason to see you?
Am I just a former employee
rather than your grandson
that you have no reason to talk to
now that he’s quit your company?
Did you know that
we never made small talk?
Every time you called me,
it was either about work…
Or about North.
Do you all even think of me as your family?
Don’t you feel anything for losing me?
And why are my mistakes always
much bigger than everyone else’s?
That scam hurt me more than anyone.
That day,
all you asked me was how I was
going to take responsibility for it.
You didn’t even care how I felt.
It was me.
I forbid everyone from reaching out to you.
Your Papa and Mama pleaded for you
every single day.
I must admit I forgot…
that you’re just a child as well.
I was angry
because I didn’t think you would
make such a big mistake.
I cast you away, knowing full well
you’d make it on your own.
But still, in your worst moment,
I abandoned you.
I’m sorry.
Will you forgive me?
I will, Grandpa.
Pai!
Are you moving back into your place, Pai?
Yes.
Will you come back to work
for Empire as well?
I’m not sure about that right now.
I still have to work at the bakery
until I find someone to replace me.
I told you Pure called us.
But Pure confessed
Tim made him make that call.
Did you finally make up with your family
or did you steal someone’s car?
Both.
Should I make dinner
and draw a bath for you tonight?
No.
It’s been a good day.
Hey.
I was told you forced Pure’s hand.
I just thought your parents wouldn’t
listen to me if I called them myself.
You poked your nose
where it doesn’t belong.
Who’d be able to stand
seeing someone so miserable?
But you didn’t have to do anything.
I’d feel better on my own.
You know,
I used to think you were heartless.
But when I saw you cry that day,
I just knew that wasn’t the case.
When someone as strong as you gets vulnerable like that in front of their eyes,
no one can keep being mad at him.
Why are you suddenly saying all this?
You’re not planning to run off
somewhere now, are you?
Did Grandpa say he’d forgive everything
if you left me alone?
If that was the case, what would you do?
I would…
You would what?
I would be happy.
Umm.
Congratulations, then.
That’s exactly what I’m planning to do.
No!
I’m kidding.
Who’d be able to do that?
Hey.
Are you fooling me again?
I’m not.
I’m just teasing.
Same difference.
How can I leave my boyfriend
when he’s so adorable?
That’s ‘ex-boyfriend’ to you.
Fine by me.
Come in before it starts raining.
You should stay until the rain lets up.
Driving in this storm is too dangerous.
What perfect weather.
If there was a blackout,
it would be almost too cliché.
I was waiting for you
to come here tonight.
And you did.
How’d you know I’d come?
Well…
When something weighs on your mind,
I’m always the one you run to.
I’d love to stop doing that.
You don’t have to.
I’m here if you ever need me.
You don’t give me a break at all, do you?
I like you.
What is there to like?
I didn’t give you an answer.
I like you because
you’re good at everything.
You get stubborn at times,
and sometimes a little sensitive,
but you’re a romantic person.
When you love someone,
you really care for them.
Who wouldn’t fall in love
with such a lovable soul?
Pai.
Wanna go to work together?
Pai!
- North.
- P—
What’s the matter?
Oh, I was gonna ask if you want
to go to work together.
But…
Whose clothes are these?
They look familiar.
Oh, I… stopped by to see Tim last night
and it happened to rain all night.
So I thought it was better to stay over.
Stop it.
There was nothing going on.
I didn’t say anything.
Your face already did.
Do you want to get changed first?
Or are you planning to use this opportunity
to mark your territory?
Of course I’ll change.
But I have to be at the bakery today.
I can’t just leave like that.
Alright.
We can still go to work together.
I’ll drop you off at the bakery
on my way to work.
What?
Why do you insist on us going
to work together today?
It’s…
It’s just how I want to show my affection.
My love language, you know?
Okay.
Oh, right.
They’re having the event U and I
came up with today at the mall.
You should totally take Tim there.
It’s for couples.
Get away from me.
Come on. I was wracking
my brain for that campaign!
Well done, North.
Finally the day is over.
I thought it would be more tiring.
Adulting, going to work, and…
Feeling drained, you know?
You did well.
You work and take care of your family.
You’re all grown up, alright.
But did I take care of you properly?
We spent all day together.
But when I work, I focus on work.
When I’m with Pai, I focus on Pai.
I didn’t make time for you today.
Oh, it’s alright.
I’m not gonna hold that against you.
I won’t let you get to that.
Tell me where you’d like a massage, sir.
I’m sore everywhere.
Especially over here on my shoulders.
Here?
That’s right.
This side, too.
Here, too?
Right.
It hurts so much it shoots
right up my head.
It does?
My head hurts.
Aw, that’s nice.
My cheek also hurts now.
Must be the migraine.
Your cheek, huh?
That’s right.
Here?
Aw!
My lips also kinda…
Your lips?
Yes.
What about you? Does it hurt anywhere?
Here.
I love you, U.
I love you, too, North.
We finally wrapped up our project.
I’ve been exhausted.
I’m working.
Sit properly.
So do I have to look for a new hire?
I’m not sure.
We’ll have to see after I talk to them.
But if I really am leaving, I’ll make sure I
draft up something for a smooth transition.
Are you going back to being a mall owner?
We’ll have to see what
the board of directors thinks.
My trustworthiness was quite
heavily damaged.
Sorry.
But how will I see you after this?
I don’t think I can march up to your office.
It doesn’t seem like your Grandpa
is going to forgive me any time soon.
Are you going to give up?
No way.
I won’t give up.
We’ll work something out.
Alright?
Hey.
Whose love language is this now?
Come in.
Your Grandpa is here.
And welcome back, sir.
Hello, Grandpa.
Did you get everything in order
at Pure’s bakery?
I’ll help him out the best I can
in case I have to leave suddenly.
I’ve made up my mind.
If it’s okay with you, I want you
to resume your former position.
I’m happy to.
Is Aunt Kia alright with this decision?
About that, I’ve been thinking your
Aunt Kia should take over my role.
It’s about time I retire.
I just want to be home and
play with my grandchildren.
You’ll have to keep a low profile
at work for now, though, Pai.
Once the board approves,
you can take your title back right away.
Thank you, Grandpa.
How are North and U doing?
Not bad.
They’re getting better and better.
They didn’t look so promising at first,
but they’re no quitters, either.
I think North has become
so much more mature.
I agree.
You’re more mature as well, Pai.
Going through something like that,
the options were either to
grow as a person or death, Grandpa.
How are things with Tim?
I’ve had my eye on you guys, of course.
I know what’s been going on.
It is as you can see.
Tim refuses to leave.
Well, then, I have one request.
Do not love him just because you think
he is the only person who loves you.
If you want to give him a chance,
you have to know him through.
Who he is, where he’s from,
what sort of family he grew up in.
And I need to know these things, too.
Does that mean you want
to know Tim better?
Well, you wouldn’t leave him, would you?
So just take him in where I can see you,
like North did.
Of course.
Well…
Do you like them?
The photos.
I love them, Grandpa.
Don’t hit that one, North.
Here. Spin this.
What if I just do this?
North, do it here first.
- Here?
- The blue one.
Your turn.
There.
U, that’s the wrong side.
Why don’t you two go back
and play at your home?
Don’t worry about leaving me alone.
I’m beginning to miss my solitude, actually.
Where do I hammer
if I want the orange parts?
Here or here?
Hmm…
Could be your personal chef.
Why don’t you go get him?
And you acted like you didn’t hear me
when I told you to go.
Was it a good day or a bad day?
Bad day.
Alright.
Bad day, it is.
Hey, North.
What are you making today?
Steak.
Why don’t you sit back and relax?
This is dangerous, Pai.
No, the red part is here and
there are two blue pieces.
This is ice, you know.
Can you break the ice, Pai?
Food is here.
This is for you, North.
Thank you.
Thank you, Tim.
Stop it.
Alright.
If you had a friend like that,
I’d die of jealousy.
Pai!
I never stopped loving you, Tim.
But when I think I have to trust you again,
I can’t help but get so scared.
Can we really marry
the same person twice?
He still has much to prove.
I’m more than willing to
spend my whole life doing it.