We’re making a profit!
to close this place down?
We can keep going!
I barely did anything.
It’s all thanks to your own effort, North.
Hey!
I can’t bring myself to trust a scammer.
I’ll do whatever it takes
for you to trust me again.
I want to resign from my role as the CEO.
If you chose me and it didn’t work out,
you’d lose everything you’ve built
with your family.
I’d lose everything but still have you.
I’ll always choose you.
Then I choose you, too.
I’ve never stared at the living room’s
ceiling like this before.
I just noticed that the light bulb
is not working.
Oh, you’re right.
If we weren’t lying down here,
we wouldn’t have seen that.
This is all the more reason to do it
on the couch more often.
Baby.
I mean, we have to keep an eye out
for this kind of thing, you know?
Who knows which other
light bulbs are also broken?
I wonder if the one on
the balcony is still working.
Hey!
Why are you blushing?
We literally just did it.
Tim.
Fine. I’ll shut up.
That almost didn’t sound like you.
Do you like it?
Of course.
Very much.
CHANHOM
(Are you free today, Mek?)
Was that work?
Yes, something came up.
I have some errands to run
but I’ll see you in the afternoon.
NANA
(The chauffeur is waiting for youdownstairs, sir.)
I’m late.
I have to go, baby.
CHAMHOM
(Well, darling?)
BREAK UP WITH
AIRY
CHANHOM
MON-ING
FAHSAI
I’m really sorry, Chanhom.
But…
I think we should call it quits.
Let’s not see each other again.
I knew it!
I spent all that money on you and you
wouldn’t even go to a hotel with me!
CHANHOM
Oww…
Chanhom, checked.
My foot!
That hurt.
Ice, sir.
Thanks, Max.
AIRY
(See you tomorrow.)
(I’m excited to hear what
you need to talk to me about, Hong.)
The interview for the wedding
will be tonight, Mr. Pai.
Shall we take some photos?
Please stand close, sirs.
Right next to each other.
Can you please look at each other?
Why are you blushing?
What happened to Mr. Confident
from this morning?
No, it’s…
You look nice today.
I know.
The next suits are for the party.
This is the twelfth suit.
How many more
do we have to try on, Nana?
There’s the suits for the tea ceremony,
for the press conference,
and for the god worship ceremony.
Can’t we… skip the god worship?
No, we can’t!
The Master said this is the
most auspicious time to pay respect
and the opportunity doesn’t come by often.
The ceremony will be quick and harmless.
Please, sir.
Ladies, will you please make way
so Mr. Pai can go and get changed?
This way, sir.
Please, get changed.
Alright.
You too, Mr. Tim.
What do you want?
(Hello.)
I need your advice.
(Why are you whispering?)
Why are you whispering?
What do you need my advice for?
I want North to trust me again.
(You have any ideas on how to do that?)
Aren’t you always so cocky?
Just deal with it yourself.
(I can barely save my own butt right now.)
Come on.
Alright, tell me what I can help you with.
I’m good at giving advice, you know?
It’s okay.
Why don’t you save that advice for yourself?
If you’re so smart, fix it on your own.
Stop running to me for advice all the time.
Tim, come on.
It’s just this once.
Please.
Help this sinner turn himself around.
What can I do to make North
trust me again?
Please, Tim.
You’re such a bother.
(Off the top of my head,
I think you should…)
WE ARE ALIVE AND WE REMAIN OPEN.
This is cute.
It’s so quiet on weekdays.
It’s only normal.
That’s business for ya.
And it’s because U isn’t here
to attract customers as well.
Oh.
He’s not with you today?
Are you out of your mind?
Why would he be with me?
That’s my… disputant.
Oh, disputant, huh?
I don’t see you making
any effort to sue him.
I’m working on gathering evidence.
Right.
Let me just say…
You won’t sue him.
Not as long as you still like him.
Hey, hey, hey.
How’d you know that?
You have a mirror at home, bud?
Just go and look at the mirror,
and you’ll see that it’s written
all over your face.
Anyone, even from Mars, can… tell.
Oh, there he is, the proof.
No investigation needed.
North.
Oh, U.
What are you doing here?
I need you to come with me.
I’m working.
The place is packed, you know?
It’s damn deserted, dude.
You said so yourself.
Come with me.
No, I’m not going.
And step aside.
You’re blocking the entrance.
If you don’t come with me, I’m telling Pai
you’re not closing the bakery down.
Hey.
You wouldn’t dare.
Hey, North. North.
U.
Stop it.
U!
North.
U.
U!
North, dude.
Take it easy.
Please.
Let’s talk it out.
What’s it gonna be?
Please, U.
Love thy neighbors.
If you don’t come with me, we’re all dead.
Take it easy.
There’s always tomorrow.
What?
If you don’t love your neighbors,
with whom will you sing the choir
when the judgement descends?
That’s enough, you two.
Just don’t say no and come with me.
Yeah, North.
You should go with him.
That’s for the best.
Dude.
Don’t be a problem.
Fine.
I’ll go with you.
Good job.
You didn’t need to make such a fuss.
I can walk on my own.
Again?
You’d better not get me killed on the road.
I won’t.
Here.
Come on.
Alright.
Hold on tight, kiddo.
Let’s go.
Let me help.
Why did you take me here?
Because I missed you.
Mom?
This is my place.
This is everything I have.
North, take a seat.
Sit on the sofa.
Hey.
Don’t do this.
If you sit on the floor, I sit on the floor.
Oh.
I wanted to see you today,
because I need to tell you
what was real between us, and…
what wasn’t.
What isn’t true?
(North doesn’t trust you now
because you lied to him.)
Why don’t you come clean?
Tell him what was real and what wasn’t.
(Maybe that’ll help.)
Do you remember the first day we met?
You… saved me from falling into the water.
Hey!
You.
I thought I was dying in those woods!
If it wasn’t for you,
I wouldn’t have sprained my ankle!
And we wouldn’t have to
stay the night in the forest!
Hold on, North.
It was my fault that you fell into the water.
But getting lost in the woods
was not my plan.
Yeah, whatever.
What else?
Actually…
This is my place.
The house we went to was a rental.
I knew that.
And…
I am also part of the rental.
I’m not his mother.
What?
Then, who are you, Auntie?
This is Oom.
I’m not his mom.
Yep.
I’m his aunt.
Aunt.
And that Auntie you met
at the house that day, North…
That woman, yes.
She’s not his aunt.
She’s my mom.
Her name is Nart.
And this woman here is Oom.
My aunt.
Is that everything?
Nothing more to confess, is there?
Actually, there’s another person
who’s been helping me,
and it’s
U.
Okay.
I think…
I’ve heard enough for today.
North.
Are you okay?
I think… I really can’t trust anyone again.
U.
Go and wait outside.
I need to talk to him.
Go on.
Come on! I won’t scam him!
Go.
Of course.
North.
Do you remember U’s mother?
Nart, the woman you met
at the house in Sathorn?
Nart is a con artist, just like us.
But Nart is more callous than
any con artists I’ve met.
How so?
When Nart had U,
she raised him like a thief.
She made a living as a thief.
She taught him her trade all his life.
And U just didn’t know
how to live any other way.
U.
For your education.
Thank you, Ta.
I have to go for now.
Right. Of course.
Ta doesn’t know what kind
of man you are, does she?
If she found out you’re a con man,
it would break her heart.
With his mother constantly betraying him,
he just became wary of
everyone he meets.
But he trusts you, North.
Really?
I want you to know how hard
U is trying to change.
But whether you forgive him or not,
that’s for you to decide.
What you looking at?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
I’m going home.
Do you need a lift?
No. I booked a ride.
I don’t want to risk my life
on the open road.
Pai.
Let’s go.
I was taking a break that night,
strolling in this garden.
That’s when I met Tim.
How did you feel
when you first met him, Mr. Pai?
I thought he was… handsome.
Something like that.
He said he dropped his car key
into the water and lost it.
As the owner of this mall,
I have to help my customers, don’t I?
But as I was helping him,
I fell into the water myself.
Tim probably didn’t want me to feel
embarrassed so he jumped in with me.
Can I ask you something?
Hmm?
Did you like me right away?
Not right away…
But I did think you were interesting.
What are you smiling at?
Nothing.
When did you fall for me?
Me?
If I have to be completely honest,
as in, seriously honest…
I liked Pai the moment I saw him.
THREE MONTHS BEFORE PAI MET TIM
How do you feel about this grand opening
for the perfume, Mr. Pai?
First of all, I must say I am honored
to be here working with Richie Bloom.
As you all know…
I kind of knew Pai is the owner of the mall,
I thought right away how different we were.
I didn’t think we’d get along.
I like quite a number of…
But when I talked to him,
and got to know him,
I learned what kind of man Pai actually is.
It just makes me love him
and care for him even more.
It was already too late to back off
once I knew I fell for him.
When I was young,
I always saw how loving my parents were
and how happy they were.
I never thought a life like that
was possible for me.
But then I met Pai,
and he made me realize that it could be
even better than I imagined.
Can you all… look away for a second?
What?
U
You didn’t have to come back if you were
gonna come back when we’re close.
Well?
Where did U take you?
Spill it.
What’s wrong now?
Are you gonna tell me today or
should I wait for next week’s episode?
Just spill the tea.
Don’t be afraid.
I’ll scream at you either way.
I’ll admit that I like U.
And I told him as much.
I just can’t trust him again.
So he came clean this afternoon.
Came clean?
About what lies he was telling me.
But instead of hating him,
and taking his confession to the police,
I…
I’m just sitting here confused and upset
that he came home late.
North.
I guessed you haven't had dinner.
I bought you some rice porridge.
You might not want
to see my face right now.
You can take the dining table
and have dinner.
I’ll wait downstairs in the lobby.
I don’t even know
if the person I fell for even exists.
But then, I also can’t leave him.
Honestly, North,
I wouldn’t know what to do either
if I were you.
I put Mr. Kuea down for
your morning appointment today, sir.
The rest of the appointments for Empire
will begin in the afternoon.
Thank you, Nana.
You can go back to the office.
Pardon?
Of course.
Baby, what was that for?
We’re going to see Kuea soon.
I don’t want you acting up
out of jealousy again.
That’s the reason?
I’m not one to get jealous
so easily, you know?
You can trust me.
Are you sure?
Of course.
I did want kids at first.
But whenever I think of Da Zhan’s face,
I just have this urge to push him to the ground.
That’s mean, Pai.
Da Zhan is still just a kid, you know?
But I don’t like him.
Give it to me.
I’ll do it.
Tim.
Come here.
Where are we going?
Get in there.
Why?
I’ll give you a cure for that jealousy.
I wasn’t being jealous.
It was my fault.
I was caught up in talking to an old friend
and ended up neglecting your feelings.
You didn’t do anything, baby.
It was Kuea who was bothering you.
Baby.
Kuea isn’t in love with me.
How do you know that?
He and I have been friends for ages.
He isn’t in love with me.
You don’t need to get jealous.
Baby, I told you I’m not being jealous.
I’m, like, so cool with it.
I’ll give you a kiss
if you admit you’re jealous.
I should have punched his teeth in.
To be honest, I was holding back for you.
He’d better not do it again.
I was burning with jealousy, Pai.
That Kuea jerk.
Get in there.
But I
Do you want that kiss or not?
You can do it here.
What are we sneaking about for?
We can’t do it here.
My employees are around.
But you kissed me right
in the middle of the crowded mall.
Those people mean nothing to me,
but it would be embarrassing
in front of my own employees.
Make it a combo.
Kiss me here, here, here, and here.
Just get in there.
This is the initial plan I came up with.
I’m thinking of an English-styled house,
with plenty of space and Tudor decor.
You came up with all this by yourself?
Yes.
You’re even better than Pai told me.
If there’s nothing more to sort out,
let’s pause the project for a while.
Tim and I will probably be busy with
preparing for the wedding next week.
Let’s talk more about it after the wedding.
Of course.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
Baby, can I have the invitation?
Sure.
Here.
We just got them today.
We’ll look forward to seeing you, Kuea.
Save the date.
I’ll try to be there.
Thank you.
(I’m on my way to Bangkok.)
(See you tonight.)
U.
You need to stop waiting outside my
bedroom door first thing in the morning.
I’m sorry.
What do you want?
Whoa.
I’m giving you back the 250 million.
Although, this is only 249 million.
I’ll have to owe you the rest.
Nart stole one million from me.
So you’ve been disappearing lately
because of this?
Yeah.
I’m sorry it took me a while
to return the money.
I don’t know how to write a check.
So I’ve been withdrawing cash
so I can return it to you.
Can you believe me now that
I don’t want anything from you?
The money you returned
is nothing compared to
the marital assets you would get.
Don’t ever think I’m not smart.
Do you really think of me that way?
Yes.
Because marrying me is
a guaranteed ticket to one billion.
Everyone knows that.
Well, then…
There’s no other way.
Can I have the car key?
What for?
U!
Let’s go.
Let’s go where?
Where are we going?
Just come.
U.
North, come on.
Come with me.
U!
Where are we going?
Mama.
Get in the car.
Pure.
Where are we going?
Just hop in.
Alright.
Everyone, get off.
Where are you taking me?
District office.
We’re getting a divorce.
I didn’t order that.
Hmm.
Hong.
You look amazing today.
And you look beautiful as always, Airy.
You sweet talker.
The usual, please.
Yes, sir.
Airy.
There’s something
I need to ask of you today.
Of course.
How much do you want?
Just tell me.
Oh, it’s not that.
It’s…
Here.
This is everything you gave me.
I want to give them back to you.
It’s everything I could find.
Does breaking up with me scare you?
Uh…
Hong.
I knew you’d find the right person
one day and want to stop doing this.
I might be a tiny bit sad today,
but I always knew
it was never going to be me.
Congratulations, Hong.
You should keep these gifts.
I gave them to you because I wanted to.
I’m sure you need them more than I do.
But I really wanted to
return them to you, Airy.
How about this?
Give me one last hug
and we have ourselves a fair deal.
Alright.
AIRY
Hello, Mama
(Yes, love?)
I’m calling to tell you
I have to postpone my visit.
I got a new job.
(That’s more than alright, love.)
(You’re doing well, I hope?)
Yes.
Mama.
I have a boyfriend.
He’s really nice.
I’m sure you’ll love him.
Yes.
See you.
Do you have witnesses with you today?
Yes.
There.
Please sign here.
I didn’t agree to this divorce
because I gave up on you.
But if getting divorced makes you trust me,
I’ll gladly do it.
DIVORCE CERTIFICATE
ISSARA PREECHAJIT
NITIPON JEERAMONGKOLTHANUN
Hold on…
Who are you?
I’ll return this, too.
The day you gave me this plushie
was the same day that my own mother
stole everything from me.
It was also the first day
I realized I might be falling for you.
I believed that
somebody as nice as you
would never hurt me.
What do you mean?
in my entire life.
I never trusted anyone
I could never be sure if someone
I talked to or worked with
would stab me in the back
or disappear from me.
But…
That day when I woke up next to you
was probably the only time in my life
that I felt safe.
So I…
I want to wake up next to you every day.
U!
I know.
Trust is hard to earn.
I never trusted anyone myself.
But you’re the one who changed my mind.
I’ll go.
Wait.
You said you wouldn’t give up.
If you gave up just because of this,
how could I ever trust you again?
MEMBERSHIP APPLICATION FOR ARCHITECT COUNCIL
THANIN CHAIYANUWAT
You don’t need that.
I do.
Our wedding is next week.
I don’t want my skin to look dull.
But I want to see you when you’re old.
Old? No way.
What?
You don’t want to grow old with me?
Just because we’ll grow old together
doesn’t mean I have to look old.
Give me that.
Nope.
No way.
Stop teasing me.
Give me that.
No way.
Give it to me.
I won’t.
Give it back.
Stay still.
Give it back to me.
You’re being so stubborn.
Give it to me.
You want this?
Shall we?
Please give a round of applause
to our newlyweds!
What are you doing here, U?
Mr. Pai.
We’re here to tell you the truth.
Another one gets kicked out
of the family, huh?
I know you’re exhausted.
Let me take care of you.