If he wants to play this game,
we’ll play, too.
And we’ll win.
What do you mean?
Convince him to get a divorce
and give you back everything.
Use me.
What?
Use me to fake an affair.
Get away from me!
He’s the only man I love.
I’m faithful to North.
I don’t want to live like this anymore.
I want to step down
from my role at Empire.
What?
Maybe we can start
a gated community project.
I just want to be with you, Tim.
I don’t know what I’m feeling.
My head is a mess.
I don’t even know
if I still love you.
Well, shall we find out?
I don’t feel a thing.
What are you smiling at?
Nothing.
I’m gone.
Hold on.
North.
I’ll do whatever it takes
for you to love me again.
GRANDPA
Hello.
(Pai.)
(Is everything alright with North?)
(I barely see him this week.)
(He rarely picks up the phone.)
North… is a little under the weather.
He probably just doesn't want you
to get sick, too, Grandpa.
Is that so?
(Well, then, will you please give him
a basket of fruits for me?)
How is his bakery doing?
Any progress?
To tell you the truth,
it’s like North didn’t learn anything
this past whole year.
(Is that right?)
Would you mind looking over
this matter, Pai?
(If North really can’t get by, like you said,)
maybe it’s time for him to come back
and learn something at Empire.
Of course, Grandpa.
Are you still in pain?
I completely forgot.
I’m okay now.
You can hug me all you want.
Are you still tired?
Why don’t you sleep in
for 10 more minutes?
I can’t.
I have so many things to do today.
Grandpa was just on the phone,
telling me to handle North’s bakery.
Good thing he didn’t scold me for
taking time off to take care of you.
I’m sorry.
If I didn’t get hurt, you wouldn’t have
to waste all this time to be with me.
It’s alright.
I’m happy to do it.
Do you remember my friend Kuea who
works on a gated community project?
Yes.
I have an appointment with him
this afternoon.
I want you to come with me.
Alright.
I’ll have Nana send you the location.
I have to get something done
in the morning.
Of course.
I’ll go take a shower.
Stop it!
Surprise.
North, do you like it?
It’s adorable.
But what money did you buy it with?
Is it the 250 million I gave you?
Yes.
North, North, North!
North, calm down!
This trick would have worked,
if I didn’t know you’re a con man.
North.
So…
How are things on your end?
I think North still has feelings for me.
But?
But… he’s in denial that he does.
Honestly, recently, he kissed me.
I knew right away that he still likes me,
but he wouldn’t admit it.
So I plan to make him
fall in love with me again.
Is that what the balloons
and flowers are for?
Yes.
Listen to me, U.
This simple trick would work
if he didn’t know you’re a scammer.
Then what should I do?
You have to do what he wants deep down
without having to ask.
Such as?
Such as…
Taking care of him,
being there for him
when he needs someone.
And do it effortlessly.
Make it seem as normal as possible.
That’s profound.
Where did you learn all this?
I just… watch and learn.
Let’s talk about you.
Are you sure you want
to do this with North?
I don’t want to keep living like this.
How can you be sure he will forgive you when he knows who you are now?
What choice do I have
when I’m already in love with him?
There’s nothing else I can do but my best.
North, it’s me.
Are you home?
Go hide.
Go and hide!
Hide!
Why?
Just hide if you don’t want to die.
Are you worried about me?
Go on!
Are you home? What’s taking so long?
I’m here.
I was naked.
Is U here?
No, Pai.
Why are you giving me this?
Grandpa asked me to.
Okay.
What’s with the dog crate?
Do you have a dog now?
You can barely take care of yourself
and you want to have a pet?
That’s where U sleeps.
Good.
Why… are you here to see me?
I’m here to ask you
how you’re doing on the divorce.
It’s…
I’m gathering evidence.
I’m–I’m almost done.
You have to take this seriously.
Give U a reason to want a divorce.
Don’t cave in.
Do you understand?
Okay.
Anything else?
I just went through
your bakery’s financial report.
All this time,
your bakery never made profits at all
since its opening.
If we let it go on like this,
it will only get worse from here.
I talked to Grandpa.
We want you to shut it down.
You’re going to work at Empire.
I’ll be keeping my eye on you at all times.
I hope you understand what I’m saying.
Oh, hey, there.
How are things?
You talked things out with U yet?
Everything okay now?
What?
What happened?
Did U tell you he’s actually a millionaire
who’s been testing you?
Or did your grandpa finally
tell you you were adopted?
No!
What do you mean, “adopted”?
I don’t know.
You just don’t look like your grandfather
so I assumed.
Don’t you ever wonder
that maybe you’re the son
of a housemaid?
I’m not adopted!
Then what are you so unhappy about?
It’s…
Pai went through our bakery’s
financial report
and saw that we’ve been making
loss after loss.
He told me to shut this place down
and work for him.
I guess it’s time to accept the fact that
I’m a loser.
You don’t need to blame yourself like that.
He’s right—Wait.
What are you doing here?
I followed you.
How long have you been here?
Since Pure said
you were the son of a housemaid.
I’m not!
What are you smiling at?
North.
Between us, it wasn’t your fault.
It’s not right to blame yourself.
But this place isn’t minting money anyway.
I still have to shut it down.
Why don’t we give it one more try?
One last time. One last chance.
“We”?
Yes
I’ll help you.
Pai.
Oh, Tim.
Hello, Tim.
We didn’t get to be properly
introduced last time.
I’m Kuea.
I’m Pai’s friend.
I’m Tim.
His boyfriend.
We’re getting married.
Right.
I want to introduce you two because I think
it’s best we all get to know each other,
seeing as we’ll be working as a team now.
Right.
I talked to Pai last time about
this gated community project,
and this is the piece of land I had in mind.
It’s been an empty land
since I was in high school.
You’re right.
It’s close to our school.
Yes.
You know this neighborhood
has everything.
It’s the perfect spot.
I didn’t even remember there’s
a piece of land like this around our
Reminds me of the good old times.
This kinda makes me want some
mini pancakes from Jeab’s.
Oh, you’re right.
I heard that place is still open.
Really?
Maybe we should—
Shall we stop talking about the past
and focus on the present?
Speaking of which, Pai,
this piece of land sure is lovely.
We can build a house here
after we get married.
I’ll buy mini pancakes at Jeab’s
for you every day.
Are you hot?
Do you want to stand in the shades?
You have more appointments
in the evening.
Excuse us, we have to sort out
a lot of things about the wedding.
Pai and I are getting marri—
Yes.
You said that, Tim.
Right.
Kuea.
Can I talk to my boyfriend for a second?
By all means.
Where are we going?
What’s wrong with you?
Nothing’s wrong with me.
What’s wrong with Kuea?
Nothing’s wrong with Kuea.
It’s you.
Are you being jealous?
No, I’m not!
I was just telling Kuea
we’re getting married.
What?
You don’t want people to know
we’re getting—
Baby.
I really want to do this project with you.
But we need Kuea’s help.
He’s in this industry
and more experienced than we are.
I want you to respect him.
But you didn’t need to bring up
Jeab’s mini pancakes.
Hey.
I’m sorry.
You’re not jealous anymore?
I’m not jealous anymore.
I’m all yours, alright?
Alright.
Did you take your blazer off?
You’re ruining the collars.
Did you take it off for that Kuea jerk?
You just said you’re not jealous anymore.
I’m not.
I’m just asking.
What you’re holding is the
initial report on this piece of land,
including deeds verification, possession
history, land survey, and other things.
Is it okay?
Did you check whether this is
in the expropriation zone?
I’ll check again with the DPT.
As long as it’s not
in the expropriation zone,
I have nothing against the rest of it.
I’ll send all the numbers to Pai later.
As for the supervising architect
for this project,
Pai said you’d be in charge.
I’ll wait for your proposal
so we can all see the picture.
Oh, it’s…
Can I have some time to consider
Of course.
OUR LAST DAY IN BUSINESS
BUY 1 GET 5 FREE
Does he really have
a degree in marketing?
OUR LAST DAY IN BUSINESS
BUY 4 GET 1 FREE
What would you like?
Any recommendations?
Everything’s good, ma’am.
Then, can I try this one?
This one?
This is too bad.
But I’m taken.
Let me pick something else for you.
I’m sure you’ll like it.
Of course.
Alright.
That’s more than enough.
Yes, ma’am.
North, get the bread out
of the oven for me.
I don’t wanna burn it.
Ploy.
North!
North.
Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
Not badly.
Okay.
Pure.
Take over for a bit.
I’ll take a look at North.
Of course.
Thank you.
Why don’t you man the cashier?
Don’t get too close
to the oven again, alright?
Yeah. I know that.
(For almost a year,)
(this little bakery has been
a safe space for me and Pure)
(to hide away from the busy world.)
(We’re happy that our little bakery
has put a smile on your face.)
But it is time for us to face the music today.
Now that I’m shutting the place down,
I can’t help but have this sinking feeling.
It’s okay.
Oh! It’s green!
The number in the report is now green!
Look. Look.
Green!
We’re making a profit!
Hold on.
260 baht.
That’s just today, right?
At least it’s a profit!
Since we’ve been open almost a year ago,
we never had a day like this.
Does that mean we don’t have
to close this place down?
We can keep going!
But… it’s just today?
Yes!
All Pai wants is proof!
I just have to keep it going
like this for a month.
And we’ll throw our financial report
in Pai’s face and say,
“I can make it on my own!”
On our own!
Good. Good.
Itadakimasu!
Wanna sit with me?
Yes.
Thank you for today.
I barely did anything.
It’s all thanks to your own effort, North.
I’ll give you all of these.
Your favorite dumplings.
Some pork, too.
You have nothing left in your bowl.
It’s alright.
I use the wrong end of the chopsticks.
I’m too full to go back
to the bakery for the car.
Oh?
How about this?
What, U?
I totally didn’t expect a motorcycle.
I promise to ride safely.
Alright?
Let’s go.
Here.
Hold on to me.
You’re so…
Why are you flexing your muscles?
Let’s go.
I wasn’t even flexing, though.
Just go.
Alright.
Ready?
We’re here.
Let me help.
Hey!
North!
What was that?
DO NOT FALL FOR THE TARGET
AT ALL COSTS!
Are you… secretly rich?
Come on in.
My family was dirt poor when I was a kid.
All three of us used to live in
a tiny one-room flat.
But my parents gritted their teeth
and worked hard to save up
until they had a sum of money.
They invested in a direct marketing
business and made a killing.
They had money to buy this house,
asked for more loans,
and expanded their business.
But one day, they hit a roadblock.
Papa. Mama.
I got a job.
Papa? Mama?
Hello.
(Tim, it’s your Mama.)
(Your Papa and I are in China.)
(Our family won’t be the same
from now on.)
My mother left me some money.
She told me to sell this house.
But I couldn’t.
Why not?
I want my family to come back
and live here with me.
Tim, you idiot.
What was that for?
For being a stubborn idiot.
Selling this house would pay back
at least half of your debt.
I’m not selling it.
I’m never going to sell it.
What did you call me here for, then?
I need advice.
About what?
Since I was a kid,
I wanted to be an architect.
But when my family went bankrupt,
I pressed pause on that dream.
But then Pai offered me this supervising
architect role for his gated community.
He did?
Did you say yes?
Da Zhan.
Da Zhan, dear.
Yes, Pai?
Where’s Aunt Kia?
Isn’t she with you?
What if I ruined everything
and I have nothing left?
I made up my mind.
It’s your dream, right?
I do have a degree in architecture.
But I have never worked in that field
since I graduated.
It’s risky for the operation.
If this plan to marry Pai falls through,
I’ll never get to bring my parents
back to this house.
Then stick to your plan.
Marry him and divorce him.
Do everything the way you've planned it.
But…
But you don’t want to anymore, do you?
Baby.
What are you doing sitting here all alone?
I’m just thinking.
You can talk to me, you know?
It’s nothing.
Long day, baby?
Yeah.
After meeting up with you,
Grandpa came to the office to see me.
What did he say?
We had a huge fight.
Because…
I told him I wanted to quit as the CEO.
I made up my mind.
I want to resign from my role as the CEO.
If you resign, what will become of Empire?
But I have a right to live my own life!
I won’t allow it!
Did you even think about the consequences of your actions?
Did you?
I want to work on
a gated community project with Tim.
And I want it to be
a separate business from our family’s.
Every baht spent on this project
will come from my own pocket.
I really want to do this with Tim.
Are you saying you no longer want to
take over my role when I can’t?
I ask for permission to take responsibility
only for Empire as a mall.
But the rest of our family’s businesses,
I want no part in it.
Thanks for your honesty.
As for whatever project you want to do,
I wish you both luck.
I don’t know when
you threw all your rules away.
But isn’t it obvious that
you’re in love with him?
Once you can admit it to yourself,
this plan of yours will be useless.
You might want to come up
with a new plan for your new life.
What happened then?
You know, baby,
besides executive management,
I don’t know anything about anything else.
Let’s start our own family.
Will you stay and help me out, Tim?
I really want to do this with you.
You might have had
two options before this:
bring back your old family
or start a new one with Pai.
But maybe there’s a third option
where you can keep both.
Aren’t you scared?
If you chose me and it didn’t work out,
you’d lose everything you’ve built
with your family.
I’d lose everything but still have you.
I’ll always choose you.
Then I choose you, too.
TIM AND PAI’S HOME PROJECT
Are you agreeing to work on this
gated community project with me?
Thank you.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Morning, North.
Shall we go to work early today?
I’ve come up with
so many good promotions.
Or maybe you want to play squash today?
I’ll give you a ride.
U.
Can you give me a minute?
So…
I was thinking about us last night.
Me, to—
I’ll admit that…
I really like you.
But!
I just can’t trust you again.
Do you understand?
You were fooling me.
Actually—
You’re a scammer.
I can’t bring myself to trust a scammer.
It’s never going to work.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
North.
What now?
I’ll do whatever it takes
for you to trust me again.
It’s not gonna work.
I’ll do whatever it takes
for you to trust me again.
Ugh!
Did you hear me?
I’ll do whatever it takes
for you to trust me again.
I’ll make you trust me again.
You hear me, North?
Baby?
Did you even get any sleep?
I didn’t.
I got too excited.
I’ve never seen you
in your work mode before.
You look so cool.
You think so?
You look adorable, too.
Do you have to go to work early today?
Why are you blushing?
Because you look so adorable today.
Hello.
I want North to trust me again.
This is my place.
This is everything I have.
I believe someone as nice as you
would never hurt me, North.
Why did you kiss me?
We’re going to meet Kuea.
I don’t want you acting up
because of jealousy again.
Mama.
I have a boyfriend.
It was too late to back off
the moment I knew I fell for him.