You don’t know who he is.
How can you love him?
Why don’t we get to know
each other right now?
You watch my back.
I’ll watch your back.
Nana.
Look U up for me.
What do you think you’re doing?
This is so disrespectful
to me and my husband!
Pai.
I want to be alone right now.
There’s no way I can let that happen.
Come here.
You’re adorable when you’re angry.
Are you sad because of what I said?
You make a face like a little duckling
when you’re sad.
Don’t be sad again, you hear me?
Well?
Everything okay on your end now?
Pai took some painkillers and went to bed.
Same here.
These cousins are adorable, aren’t they?
Stop that nonsense!
Don’t you know that
ever since you came into the picture,
Pai barely thinks about getting married.
It’s affecting me!
Well, help me out then.
When Mr. Pai and North stop fighting,
we can both do our own things.
That line of thinking doesn’t work on Pai.
Which line of thinking works on him,
then, Mr. Pai’s Boyfriend?
Listen to me.
Pai doesn’t trust you
because he doesn’t know you.
The further you bring North away from him,
the more worried he gets.
You need to gain his trust.
That’s how we end this, you got it?
How can I even do that?
He won’t even look at me.
I have an idea.
We have to start tomorrow, though.
Our targets are vulnerable right now.
This is when we strike and knock them out.
Okay.
What’s the plan?
North.
Wake up.
Go get ready.
Can I have one more hour?
Let’s go talk to Mr. Pai.
What’s more to talk about?
We’re all good, right?
Things are all good with you,
but apparently not with me.
I want to win him over, too, you know?
You don’t need to.
It’s too much trouble.
We’re better off staying away from him.
Wait.
North.
Think about it.
The longer we keep our relationship
secret from Grandpa,
the worse he’s going to think of us.
If we want to be openly in love
in front of Grandpa,
we need to get through Mr. Pai’s first.
Please?
No more sleep.
I don’t want to be your secret husband.
I want to be the husband
you can be proud of.
Please?
Alright.
Let’s get you dressed, then.
Let me sleep in a little more, first.
I’m still tired.
I’ll join you, then.
Hey, I thought we’re going to sleep.
Sure.
(North agreed. We’ll be at his office today.)
Where are you going today, baby?
You’re up early.
We have an appointment with Nana
about wedding planners.
We do.
I was busy worrying about North
so I… forgot.
It’s alright.
I understand.
I know you’re tired.
Can we stay like this for a minute?
I had such a bad headache last night.
This is nice.
Don’t stop, baby.
What’s wrong?
Oh…
It’s just you aren’t usually so affectionate.
I don’t know what to do.
I told you I’m just tired.
What’s with you?
Me?
You have this awkward look
on your face.
Just like when we started dating.
Awkward?
Why would I be awkward?
But look at you trying to
keep your hands busy.
But why would I be awkward?
I should be the one asking.
Oh!
Look at me.
My hair is a mess. My eyes are swollen.
My nose is red.
Why didn’t you say anything?
Because there was nothing to say.
You look adorable.
You’re being so weird.
Weird?
I’m not being weird.
It’s not weird.
You need my help with that?
I got it.
I totally got it.
You go and get ready.
Wear your belt properly.
Your fly is down.
Pai!
Get dressed properly.
Why don’t you get ready?
I’ll wait outside.
Bye.
Go straight ahead.
Please be careful.
Those files are important.
Proceed carefully, please.
Turn left.
Oh, sorry. It’s the room on the right.
Sir, careful with that photo.
Nana.
Yes?
What’s going on?
Mrs. Kia wants to set up
her private office here.
Why?
I don’t know, sir.
Why the long face?
Isn’t that good?
Aunt Kia will stay away
from your office from now on.
That’s not a bad thing, actually.
Just be out of each other's hair
so we don’t have to argue.
She’s just looking out for you guys.
It’s just her way of showing she cares.
Don’t worry about it.
I want to be half as patient as you, baby.
Let’s get to work, shall we?
“Baby.”
Nana.
Yes.
Here.
I picked out only the planners
who have managed weddings
for celebrities, politicians,
and businessmen.
I guarantee they will do a good job
for your and Mr. Tim’s wedding.
I went to almost all of these weddings.
All they’re concerned about
are their images.
Tears of joy or otherwise, everyone has to
get it together for some photos.
Can you find me more genuine planners?
Of course.
Lively and genui—
You should have knocked.
I didn’t realize aunties needed to.
Even Grandpa does.
Fine, sure, of course.
No one is above you in this company, Pai.
You can order anyone around,
or overlook them, for that matter.
Even our Master.
Why don’t you say
what you’re here to say, Auntie?
I will be working here from now on.
I heard work has been neglected lately
for personal pleasure.
I never do that.
How do you know that, Pai,
when no one seems to dare
to oppose you or give you a lesson?
Of course, everyone is telling you
you’re doing a good job to your face.
Behind your back, they’re all complaining
about how tired they are of you.
It’s not me, sir!
I am never tired!
Without your money,
who’d even put up with you?
I have to sacrifice my time to take care—
If it is so much trouble for you,
stay away, Auntie.
No one opposes Pai
because they respect his judgement.
You should try that, too, Auntie,
if you still know what to do.
Nana.
Yes?
Show Aunt Kia to the meeting room.
Da Zhan.
Let’s go.
Make yourself scarce.
Let adults talk.
This way, please.
I don’t need a chaperone.
I know my way around.
Baby.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
I’m going to step out for some fresh air.
I’m sorry, Pai.
I’ll apologize to Aunt Kia right away.
Take your time to feel better first.
I feel awful.
You didn’t need to see that.
You totally surprised me.
It wasn’t like you.
I promise I won’t let it happen again.
Aunt Kia is infuriating.
It took you a long time to explode.
That was already impressively calm of you.
You’re…
Not mad at me?
You were so cool.
You should get angry more often.
This is no time to be joking, you know?
Alright.
To be honest, it’s like I just got to
know you even better.
I loved it.
Damn it.
The hell?
What the hell was wrong with me?
The Tim everyone knows
is a calm and collected guy,
but I had to freaking snap.
You let your intrusive thoughts win, huh.
Do I look like I’m in a laughing mood?
Well, after he saw your rotten nature—
I mean, after he saw your ‘true colors,’
how did he take it?
He loved it.
Well.
There ya go.
Another fan of the red flag, I guess.
You know what?
Screw it.
I promise I won’t lose control
like that again.
What made you snap, though?
That aunt of his is always nagging, right?
But Pai was tired today.
He went through something last night.
He barely got any sleep and his head hurt.
Don’t you think that’s frustrating?
Can’t she let my boyfriend have
even a minute of peace?
Bro.
Snap out of it.
You call him your “boyfriend” now?
Not your “target?”
“Target,” my ass.
This ain’t freaking archery.
You dare talk back to me?
Careful.
- Oh, bring it.
- Yeah?
I ain’t scared of you.
What?
I think you clocked yourself
getting soft on him
and needed me here
to help you snap out of it.
Alright.
I’ll slap some sense into you.
What?
What’s that?
Oh, now why the hell are you
ruining it like that—
Do. Not. Fall. For. Your. Target.
At all costs!
I’m… I’m not—
You’re welcome.
I’m not falling for my target.
I’m just…
seeing him differently
because I saw a part of him that…
A part of him that makes me protective.
But I don’t feel differently.
Yeah.
If that’s the case, then bravo.
But to hear the word “protective”
come out of your mouth.
It can’t be good.
Hong.
What’s wrong with you today?
Are you bored?
You’ve been awfully quiet.
Sorry?
You weren’t listening, were you?
I’m sorry.
I just happen to have
a lot on my mind lately.
Are you going through something?
You can tell me, you know?
For you, I’m willing to help
anyway that I can.
You’re too nice to worry about me.
I’m going to fall head over heels
for you at this rate.
Oh, Hong, you.
Your mouth is as sweet as your face!
You adorable thing!
Oh?
Hong.
I have to take this call.
- Of course.
- I’ll be right back.
Of course, Airy.
Uncle, buy me the plushie.
“Uncle”?
Kid.
Can you let Uncle have this one?
You pick any of these.
Maybe this one?
It’s bigger.
Or this?
I want this one.
No way.
I told you I want it!
How much is this?
My son!
Are you alright?
Let’s go to a different store.
Hong.
Yes?
Is everything okay?
Yes, it is.
Oh, is this for me?
It’s not!
Oh, I mean, you don’t deserve
a plushie like this.
You deserve something
pretty and beautiful.
If it’s not for me, who is it for?
It’s for some kid in my neighborhood.
He happens to look
exactly like this plushie.
I thought I’d buy it for him.
Oh, you must really adore
this random kid, then?
If you don’t adore him, things like this
wouldn’t remind you of him.
I see.
Hong, there’s something I want over there.
Come shopping with me.
Let’s go shopping, shall we?
You make a face like a little duckling
when you’re sad.
Duckling?
Yeah.
There’s nothing else today, is there?
There is.
Mr. North asks to see you, Mr. Pai.
North wants to talk to me?
Yes.
Mr. North is waiting outside, with Mr. U.
Shall I bring them in?
Bring—
We were kept waiting forever!
You should have knocked.
I didn’t know I needed to.
What did you need to talk to me about?
I didn’t.
U did.
Go on.
I wanted to invite you over
for dinner at home.
We’ll have a small party
and cook something.
We can get to know each other better.
I’ll see if I’m free.
Just name the day.
If we wait for you, it will never happen.
You can pick any day, Mr. Pai.
We’re alright with anything.
I see.
I don’t think I’m free at all this year.
Maybe next year.
Ms. Nana.
Yes!
Oh…
Mr. Pai is busy all through this month.
What about tonight?
Any time is fine.
Wouldn’t it be too soon, North?
He’s right, North.
When does Pai get off work tonight?
At half past seven.
We’ll see you at U’s place at 8.30.
- North!
- What?
It’s settled!
What?
You’ll only be free at 8, Mama?
Can you call the real estate place
to sort out the house first?
(Alright.)
(Good thing I took some photos
of what was where.)
(I’ll get it done.)
Right.
Thanks.
See you.
North.
They even have coconuts, U. Look.
What are all these for?
What are we making?
I don’t know.
I’m grabbing everything just in case.
What do you think we can make
out of these?
Uh…
I don’t know.
I don’t cook.
Oh?
Oh.
Two bitter melons, some young
pork ribs, whole white pepper,
and minced garlic.
…Garlic.
Yes, sir.
Come in.
Oh, you don’t need to knock, baby.
It’s okay.
What are you doing?
I got your text saying
we’re having dinner at U’s.
What is that all about?
North forced my hand.
So I thought I might as well
show off my best dish.
I’ll go get the ingredients ready for you, sir.
Are you going to cook?
Don’t tell me you finally give in.
No.
This is an opportunity to show North that
U can’t take care of him
as well as our family does.
This bitter melon herbal soup is unrivaled.
CLOSED!
Your friend is a pastry chef, isn’t he?
He can do anything.
The drink and dessert menus of this place
are all his doing.
Of course, they are
when a partner like you never bothers
to show up.
I even have to mop the floor myself.
Let me see.
Impressive.
You finally made the perfect
fried fish after five tries.
If I knew you’d wasted all those sea bass, I’d have made you practice on tilapia.
I’m nervous.
Let me try it.
Let’s go.
What’s wrong?
I know we haven’t started
but I’m already tired.
Maybe we can just make a run for it?
North, hold on.
We’ve been practicing.
There’s no need to run.
Stay.
U, it’s not the cooking that exhausts me.
Just the thought of
having a long conversation with Pai
makes me tired.
Can I ask you honestly?
Why do you always avoid him?
Wow.
The ubiquitous half-used limes.
They’re really doing a good job
setting up this place.
I’ll get them.
Okay.
Come on in.
Please, come in.
Please.
Hello.
How was traffic?
Typical.
North, where’s the bathroom?
- It’s…
- Over there.
Baby.
Yes?
How’d you know that?
I mean, it’s a common house plan.
You walk in and the bathroom
is usually the first room you see.
Why don’t you go?
Hurry up.
Go on.
Where’s your mother, U?
Oh, Mom went to Chiang Mai
with her friends.
But she’s catching a flight back.
Oh, too bad Chiang
didn’t get to stay longer.
What is that you have with you?
Pai said he’d cook.
These are the ingredients.
Do you cook?
little.
Help me, then.
We can get to know each other better.
Of course, Mr. Pai.
North and Mr. Tim,
please make yourselves at home.
No need for the ‘mister.’
Tim, it is.
U.
Right. Please.
Do your best.
Do you think… they’re going to be alright?
I guess so.
You wanna be in there with them
just in case?
Yeah.
Let me help.
I also want to cook.
Get on it.
I’m here to officially ask for
Pai’s hand in marriage to Tim.
Holy crap!
Baby?
Yes?
Are you alright?
Oh, it’s… Holy crap!
Wow!
U is a talented guy, baby!
He is?
Yeah.
Come and look, baby.
What?
Look.
He’s an arm-wrestling champion…
in third grade.
You were in an arm wrestling contest
in elementary school?
I was.
Wait.
Who on earth rang their own doorbell?
Baby.
Y–Yes?
I need to pee.
I’ll be right back.
I can’t hold it in anymore.
Goosebumps and all that.
(U and I can’t have the same mother!)
(Go home. I’ll handle this.)
Baby.
Yes?
What’s wrong?.
Oh, it’s nothing.
was just checking out the door over here
and I thought…
The architect didn’t do a good job.
U. U!
U, hey!
Yes?
Do you need my help?
It’s alright.
I’ll handle it. I’m an architect, remember?
You just stay put, Pai.
Alright?
U!
What?
Your door is broken.
Let’s come and take a look outside.
My door?
It’s so badly done!
Come here, you.
That was a close call.
If I didn’t see Mama Oom,
we’d have to come up with a sob story
about how we’re two estranged brothers.
ap!
You hired her, too?
Hell yeah.
That was so close.
What do we do now?
I’ll get back inside first.
You follow me later.
You have to tell Pai that
your mother can’t make it anymore.
Okay.
And you’ll have to keep letting Pai
take his frustration out on you.
Damn it.
You almost blew it.
Everyone’s taking their frustration
out on me right now, apparently.
I can help with this, you know?
Give it here.
North.
Fine.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Mr. Pai.
There’s a big thunderstorm in Chiang Mai.
My mother’s flight is delayed.
I don’t want her to keep waiting
for her flight like this.
You should tell your mother
Right.
I’m sorry about this.
I’ll tell her.
All done.
Come and help me in the kitchen.
Yes, Mr. Pai.
Why don’t you go set up the table, North?
But if I leave you alone with U like this,
are you sure you won’t start fighting?
How about this, guys?
Let’s set up a table and have dinner
on the front lawn outside?
Come on, North.
Get back to work.
Yes, sir.
Don’t worry.
Pai won’t hurt U.
I cannot not worry, Tim.
Forget about them getting along,
just convincing Pai that U and I really
are in love seems almost impossible.
What makes you so in love, though?
Didn’t you guys just meet?
Did it take you and Pai a long time             to fall in love?
For me, when I fall in love with someone,
it takes only an instant to know
they’re special.
And what matters is
what comes after, anyway.
Once you know you like them,
that’s when you decide if you want to
make a move or a move on.
You’re more mature than I thought,
you know?
You only ever see me through Pai’s eyes.
Of course I won’t come across as mature.
To wash away its bitterness,
cover bitter melon in salt
and refrigerate them for 20 minutes.
You can cook whatever dish you want
while waiting.
I see.
I’ll fry some appetizers
like nuggets and fries.
North loves those.
You shouldn’t let him eat
something so unnutritious.
But if he doesn’t enjoy nutritious food,
he’ll still eat the unhealthy food
when he’s alone anyway, Mr. Pai.
I’ll just…
What do you like about him?
Did you know who he is from the get-go
or did you find out later?
Oh…
I only learned his family owns Empire
after I married him.
But if you’re asking me
when I fell for him…
When I got to talk to him, I guess.
Well, why?
Who wouldn’t like someone like North?
Answer me!
Right.
I like North because he’s kind.
He doesn’t wish anyone harm.
He’s the kind of person
you know can’t hurt a fly.
North is too naive.
We’ve been trying to fix that about him.
But I don’t think he needs fixing, Mr. Pai.
He should be free
to live his life the way he wants.
Only from now on,
I’ll be watching his back.
How would you do that?
Let’s say…
If North still believes in Santa Claus,
I’ll dress up as Santa every year.
He doesn’t believe in that.
I was the one who told him
Santa Claus isn’t real.
Mr. Pai.
I believe there is
more than one way of growing up.
It’s possible for North to see the world
while keeping his optimistic outlook.
The world is a nice place because there
are people like North in it, don’t you think?
Let’s keep cooking.
I have to apologize again that my mother
cannot come to dinner tonight.
It’s alright.
Try it.
Yes.
It’s just as good as ever!
This is the first time
I’ve had anything like this.
The herbal soup recipe is
our ancestors’ secret.
We’ve even received an expensive offer,
but we refused to sell it.
I see.
You know why?
Is there a prize if I get the answer right?
Watch it.
Sorry.
Because we save the best things
for our family.
That’s our family motto for everything.
That’s why no one takes better care of us
than ourselves.
Enough, Pai.
Why are you scaring U away like that?
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
Pai.
Stop treating U like he’s planning to take me away to the North Pole.
Did you know what he said to me               when we got here?
Can I ask you honestly?
Why do you always avoid him?
Because Pai is so strict.
Why is that?
U.
Are you teasing me?
Of course not.
But take a moment to think
why that is the case.
I promise I won’t say a word.
Because Pai is so strict.
Whatever I say or do seems to be wrong.
I once told him a joke,
and Pai turned it into a full-hour lecture.
I understand—
And all I do is make Pai’s life harder.
That’s why I want to stay away from him.
So that, whatever mistakes I make,
I have to deal with them myself.
I don’t want to be a burden to anyone.
I think…
You’re taking it a little too far
since you don’t let him in on
what you’re doing with your life at all.
He’s been kept out of the loop on
how you’re dealing with your problems.
When he can’t estimate the situation,
he feels the need to take the matter into
his own hands and fix all your problems.
So if I talk to Pai more,
he’ll leave me more room to breathe?
I don’t know.
I just think it could be a good strategy.
You’ve been avoiding him
and it didn’t work, right?
Maybe it’s time to change things up?
We can even start today.
And one more thing,
U has been trying so hard to ensure
that this dinner is perfect.
He just wants to impress you, you know?
This fried fish,
we literally just learned
how to make it today.
You don’t have to worry that
U will take me away from U, Pai.
What U is doing is the opposite, actually.
I… never said
I was ever worried about that.
That’s your assumption.
Thank you.
Not bad.
That was hardly a compliment.
I’m actually happy the fish is even cooked.
What?
Of course it is fully cooked, U.
You practiced so much, you know?
You try it, too, Tim.
Of course.
Let me debone it for you guys.
Eat lots of fish, North.
Since we’re all together,
I’ve been curious about this.
How did you two meet?
Uhh…
How we met, huh?
Should I tell them
or do you want to, North?
I’d better do it,
because I don’t know how badly
you thought of me when we first met.
No way. Then let me tell them.
Let me tell them.
Here’s the thing…
U.
Is everything actually really good
or am I just drunk?
It’s really good.
I didn’t have a sip
and even I am having a good time.
I can’t believe it.
I told you Pai would listen to us
if we talked to him nicely.
He just needed some time to accept that
his beloved little cousin is married, after all.
Are you really my husband?
You keep taking Pai’s side.
Are you friends with him now?
You seem happier when
you’re not fighting with Pai, you know?
Actually, Pai told me
what I feel for you isn’t love.
He said it’s just a whim.
And I couldn’t help but agree.
I was uncertain.
I don’t know if it happened too fast.
I don’t know if this was love.
But today really made me realize that
I really do love you, U.
Oh.
What a relief!
Can you start off with an “I love you”
next time before you say the rest?
I was scared for a second!
U, stop it.
I can’t help it.
It was fun today.
Thank you.
Of course.
Thank you for such an amazing meal.
Let’s have lunch
at our family’s home sometime.
Wait!
Does that mean you accept U now, Pai?
Yes!
I’m just introducing him to the family,
not telling them you’re married.
Thank you, Pai.
Yeah.
Congratulations, U.
Congrats.
Alright.
Sorry about that.
Take it down a notch, you con.
See you.
Baby.
If I still believed in Santa Claus,
would you tell me the truth
or would you
dress up as Santa on Christmas?
I wouldn’t tell you the truth,
but I also wouldn’t dress up as Santa.
If you got sad that you didn’t get any
presents from Santa, I’d give you one.
You’d stop looking forward to Santa
and look forward to seeing me instead.
You and U somehow feel very similar.
How so?
You both fell first, and fell hard.
How does it feel to fall first, I wonder.
How does it feel to fall first, huh?
Someone who falls first doesn’t want anyone to find out how cute his crush is.
He can’t wait to win his crush over
as soon as possible.
And once that happens, he wants to make
sure everything works out between them,
because he just knows in his heart
it can’t be anyone else for him.
You’re exaggerating.
I’m not.
I mean it.
I love you so much, you know?
I do.
This tells me everything.
I got it.
U looks at North the way you look at me.
Baby.
What’s that bag?
I almost forgot it.
I found this today and it reminded me
of you so I bought it for you.
A duckling?
He’s cute!
Let’s see.
He looks exactly like you.
He does not.
Take him back.
You’re totally hurting my feelings.
eally?
Alright.
I’ll agree he’s cute.
Let’s go home.
We really did it.
There’s nothing to worry about
from here on out, right?
Pai is the hardest to impress.
If we don’t have to keep this
a secret anymore,
do you want a wedding, North?
I didn’t, at first.
But then I think you’d look really good as a groom and I can’t wait to have a big one!
A big one?
I want a funny wedding video.
My friend, Pure, can
make our wedding cake.
That will be good PR
for our bakery as well.
And the suits?
I wear white and you wear black.
I’ll sing for you as a surprise that day.
No, don’t tell me!
It won’t be a surprise.
But you don’t know
which song I’ll sing, right?
But I already know you’re going to!
Well, guess I’m not signing, then.
Wait, I’ve totally built up an expectation.
You’re serious about all this, aren’t you?
It all sounds really fun, actually.
I guess we’ll have to wait for Pai to go through with his before we can go ahead.
That’s a few months from now.
Our wedding should be, like,
a week right after his!
Oh, that soon?
That soon!
This is nice.
It’s like I finally have a family today.
Me, too.
I love you, North.
I love you, too, U.
U!
You seem stressed, baby.
What?
You know you can be honest with me.
I…
If we don’t get legally married,
it means my effort would be for nothing.
I know the truth now.
You need to divorce my cousin.
No, I refuse.
I’ll stay here with North.
You’re my whole world, Tim.
I can’t live without you.