Thank you all for coming
to my birthday party today.
Enjoy yourselves, everyone.
Enjoy yourselves.
North.
Why are you avoiding me?
Hi, Pai.
When did you get here—
Why aren’t you wearing red?
Don’t you know it’s not auspicious?
I forgot.
Put this on.
We don’t want anyone scolding you.
Thank you.
That’s so romantic.
He’s proposing in front of
our whole family,
and on Grandpa’s birthday, too.
Grandpa must be so surprised.
Grandpa already knew about it.
What do you mean?
It’s a strategic marriage.
Their family is a
gas station franchise owner,
and our family owns
a convenience store chain.
Eventually, our convenience stores
will be available at all their gas stations.
For someone like us, North,
marriage is just something
that is arranged to benefit both families.
Ugh.
You’re so unromantic, Pai.
I don’t think it’s just for business, though.
They agree to get married, after all.
I’m sure they must have feelings
for each other, at least.
I’d like to hope so.
I must, once again, congratulate
our family’s newest couple.
Once you tie the knot,
make me proud and
have children right away.
And thank you, all of you,
for coming to my birthday party today.
How glad I am to see our family
prosperous and expanding.
I hope you will all continue
to work hard to fulfill your duties.
It puts my mind at ease
to see our family doing so well.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Grandpa.
- Happy birthday, Papa.
- Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Pai.
You’ve been managing our shopping mall
for a while.
How is it going?
It’s been great, Grandpa.
We’re reshuffling our marketing strategy
to fit with new customers.
I believe the numbers will turn out better
by the end of the year.
I see.
Any plans to get married soon?
Pardon?
Getting married.
Do you have any plans to?
Doesn’t matter if you marry
a woman or a man.
You know I don’t mind that kind of thing.
It’d give me some peace of mind to know
you have someone nice
to take care of you.
It’s only been a while
since I became the CEO,
I don’t think I have time
for a relationship right now.
You don’t have time for a relationship?
I was watching that show,
Bangkok Gossip,
and they said you’ve been dating,
who is it…
An actor whose name starts with J.
I broke up with him, Auntie.
There’s no reason not to
find someone new.
I’m sure it’s not beyond your ability.
But I think—
Just do it for Grandpa’s peace of mind.
Of course.
Da Zhan, take this as an example, love.
Don’t be stubborn like your cousin Pai.
He can’t even make Grandpa happy.
Grandpa.
Hmm?
Don’t you want to see me
married and settled, too?
You were only asking Pai.
How could you get married, North?
You’re a child.
Just stay with Grandpa for now.
Wait a few more years,
and if you want to get married,
I’ll be on board.
You promise, Grandpa?
Thank you.
Speaking of which…
Don’t you want your cousin to teach you
the ropes of our trade, North?
I…
I think I…
I want to try and learn to do business
on my own.
How so?
Well…
I actually…
I have an idea…
My friend and I want to open a bakery.
Please, Grandpa?
Well, I don’t see why not.
Oh, I love you so much, Grandpa.
New Caption
I’ve placed your new suit in your office, sir.
You have an interview with Fobes
at half past noon.
I have drafted some answers
for you for the interview.
There’s a board meeting at 2 p.m.
And at 7 p.m., a one-hour call
with our Khon Khaen branch.
After that, you have dinner with Mr. Win.
I’ve rescheduled it for 8.30 p.m.
What do you think, Mr. Pai?
Why did we reschedule?
Uh, I thought you might be too tired.
It’s alright.
It’s just dinner.
Let’s not inconvenience him.
Are you alright?
You’re panting.
Oh, no.
I am not panting.
Ouch!
Yes!
Ugh, I’m not playing with you anymore!
Oww.
Dang it.
Pure.
Let’s open a bakery.
What?
What are you trying to do?
Well, I…
I want to try my hands at small business.
Small?
What about your hair salon, car wash,
Labubus, and photo booth?
- Ugh!
- Huh?
There’s no point dwelling on
what’s in the past, you know?
We should focus on something positive.
Fine!
Grandpa wants me to work with Pai,
but I don’t want to.
The bakery is just an excuse
for me to get out of it.
Now that sounds more like you.
Let’s do it anyway.
Help me be free from my cousin
for at least the next two years.
Honestly?
I don’t understand you and your cousin.
One is an all-rounded gentleman.
The other is…
Handsome?
A loser!
Watch it.
But to tell you the truth,
I can’t even blame Pai.
It was my bad luck that my parents
both died right after I was born,
and I had to live with Pai.
Why don’t you just try to be nice to him?
He stresses me the hell out.
He’s such a stickler.
He gives me an earful
for even the smallest mistakes.
Gives me goosebumps.
Please?
Fine.
Yes!
I’m due for a date.
Bye.
Oh.
You’re just gonna run off, huh?
Another business failure incoming.
(Photos from Grandpa Soepohn’s birthday
party shot by Da Zhan.)
JEERAMONKOLTHANUN (20)
Nana.
Ms. Nana.
Ms. Nana!
Y–Yes, sir!
I already got it done.
I’m going on a walk.
I’ll finish the rest of the work afterward.
Why don’t you go home and rest?
Are you sure, sir?
Hello.
I… dropped my car key into this pond.
I don’t know what the owner of this place
was thinking to put so many ponds in here.
Maybe they believed
their feng shui master so much
that they forgot to think about
customers’ safety.
I guess so.
Oh.
I’m Tim.
I’m an architect.
I was here to meet my client about
interior design.
We lost track of time while talking.
Next thing we knew, the mall was closed.
I’m Pai.
Do you work here, Mr. Pai?
You can say that.
Your boss must be really harsh
to lock you in here
and make you work well into the night.
I’m happy to do it.
Did you find your key?
No.
You fell down because
you were helping me.
I couldn’t possibly let you
get in here alone, could I?
Or we can just go crazy?
Tim!
There!
Pai!
We’re not children.
Who would even do that?
You started it.
You splashed me first.
Tim!
Take that!
Mr. Tim?
Are you alright?
Gotcha!
3-58 is over there.
Thank you so much, Mr. Pai.
If it weren’t for you, I’m afraid
I might have to sleep here at this mall.
Aren’t you going home?
Please don’t tell me your boss
really does lock you in here.
Tell me if that’s the case. I’m reporting
your boss to the Ministry of Labor.
Actually… I own this place.
Ah…
This is like one of those micro-dramas.
About what I said earlier at the fountain
and other stuff,
I’m really sorry.
It’s alright.
I’m not a big fan of the fountain
in that particular area myself.
But I really couldn’t go against
my family’s feng shui master.
Well, then I guess
you need to take responsibility.
For making a customer like me fall…
into the water.
Maybe a meal?
I’m not sure if I have time.
It’s alright.
Whenever that’s convenient for you.
Maybe next time, or even the next.
Just please don’t turn me down.
It’s a bit damp, but please take it.
I’d better go.
Goodnight.
TIM THANIN CHAIYANUWAT
“THE HANDSOME AND YUMMY
ARCHITECT”
Of all the posts I accidentally liked…
What is he going to think of me?
ONE WEEK LATER
My goal in this trimester is
to attract popular brands online
as our main selling point
to create a flow in our mall’s traffic.
If you have any more questions,
I’m only one call away.
Thank you.
Thank you for trusting me.
Mr. Pai.
Mr. Pai, sir.
Yes?
The new zone we’ve been planning,
where would you like it to be?
On the first floor.
Let’s take a look at it, shall we?
Nana, why don’t you take them there?
I’ll be right behind you.
Of course.
This way, please.
TWO WEEKS LATER
On today’s agenda, at 10 p.m.,
you have a meeting with the foreign board.
At 3 p.m., you have a meeting
with a client at our Sathon branch.
At 5 p.m., there's dinner with
Ms. Ae’s marketing team.
- Yes.
- And at 8 p.m—
Mr. Tim.
Excuse me for a moment.
Oh, Mr. CEO.
Are you here to see a client?
You can tell?
I’m sorry I didn’t say hello the other day.
It just so happened that the client
I was with was interested in a project.
We had to hurry back
to sign some contract.
It’s alright.
I was talking to some partners as well.
Hold on…
Since we run into each other like this,
it would be alright for me to remind you
of your promise, right?
Promise?
You promised you’d buy me dinner because you made me fall—
Of course!
Of course.
Alright.
I have a degree in architecture
from Bartlett, UCL.
My family isn’t wealthy, though.
My parents just wanted me
to have a good education.
I had to get a job right away
to pay them back for all the troubles.
Mr. Tim.
What’s the matter?
Oh, no.
I’m alright.
It’s just… family matters are kind of
a sensitive topic for me.
I’m an only child.
So my parents want the best for me.
But that’s a lot of pressure, you know?
It’s like I’m carrying their
hopes and dreams on my shoulders.
I have to go.
Nana is calling me.
It’s time for me to go as well.
Mr. Tim, please wait.
Yes?
This is my personal contact.
Well…
Would it be alright if I contact you romantically?
Be my guest.
Well, I did ask.
ONE MONTH LATER
THREE MONTHS LATER
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
Baby, please.
I’m just teasing you.
Baby!
FIVE MONTHS LATER
I thought you could do better.
I know I’m not good enough for Pai.
And I’m sure you said
what you said just now
out of love and care for Pai.
But I will prove to you all
that I love Pai
no less than anyone in his family does.
You’re perfect for Pai, Tim.
Thank you.
Baby.
Hmm?
Will you come with me to see Kuea
tomorrow at noon?
Baby.
Did you forget our appointment?
You agreed we’d see my friends.
I’m sorry.
I guess I got the dates mixed up.
It’s alright.
I’ll reschedule with my friends.
Thank you for understanding me.
Wait, baby.
Who’s Kuea?
Hey, Kuea.
Hi, Pai.
Hello.
Come on in.
Thank you for coming all the way here
to take a look at my project, Pai.
I can’t miss your big moment, can I?
How are things?
Ever since taking over this project
from my family,
it’s been nothing short of chaotic.
But with a grandfather like yours,
I guess you understand.
I guess so.
What do we have here?
Have you been dating him long?
It’s been about a year.
Wow.
Well?
Are you happy?
I am crazy happy.
If you’re happy, then I’m happy.
You and Kuea seem like
really good friends.
I don’t usually see you
so comfortable with anyone like that.
I’ve known him since middle school.
What did he want with us today?
His family has been hinting that they want
me to invest with them for a while.
I showed up today as a good gesture.
You’re dating me, so you might need to
get used to something like this.
Aww.
Are you tired, darling?
Well, I’ll take care of the baby today.
Hmm?
Isn’t he cute?
Baby, is everything okay?
Baby.
Do you ever think about having children?
You want kids?
I don’t know.
But I can totally imagine
how our family would look if we had some.
So can I.
Tim.
Do you want to marry me?
Uhh..
I…
Never mind.
Just thought I’d ask.
It’s…
Wait a moment.
This is my mother’s ring.
She gave it to me
before I went to London.
I was going to ask you…
But I was afraid you’d think
it was too soon.
But if you want to get married…
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
(I’m actually not big on shopping malls.)
DON’T HAVE SEX TOO OFTEN!
(If I have to go to a shopping mall,
I prefer closing hours.)
DO NOT THINK PAI IS CUTE!
(If I have to go to a shopping mall,
I prefer closing hours.)
PROPOSE.
(I’ve never thought about marriage.)
(But maybe I’ll change my mind
when I find the one.)
PROPOSE.
DO NOT FALL FOR THE TARGET
AT ALL COSTS!
What’s wrong?
I’m asking you what’s wrong.
Can you stop making me
worried about you?
I just broke up with someone.
So it’s just that…
Go take a shower right now.
Aren’t you even gonna
feel a little sorry for me?
What is there for me to feel sorry for?
I told you, North, that it was not going to
work with someone like that.
It’s your fault that
you’re not a good judge of character.
What business
do you have with me today, Pai?
Or did you come all the way here
just here to make me feel worse?
I’ll tell you some other time.
What? Just tell me.
You’re heartbroken.
I don’t think this is the right time.
Ugh, just spill it.
Tim and I are getting married.
Really?
You are?
Come on, North.
Go take a shower and get dressed.
Take yourself out there to see the world.
Don’t make me worry about you.
You’re an adult now, you know?
Well…
Congratulations.
Thanks.
What’s the matter?
I’m just curious…
When did you know
you wanted to marry Tim?
I just know I want to be with him every day.
I know every problem will turn out okay
as long as we go through it together.
When you can’t stop thinking
about your future with someone,
I guess that’s when you marry them.
I have to go to work.
Put yourself out there into the world.
Take Pure with you if you must.
Do that for me as a favor.
Okay. Fine.
Just go.
You’re gonna be late.
Don’t forget to take a shower.
Who’d forget that?
(Hello?)
Hello, Pure.
Where are you?
(I’m at Ikea.)
(I’m buying supplies for the bakery.)
Let’s go somewhere.
I wanna go hiking.
(Sure.)
(When?)
In two hours.
(Dude, I’m not in Thailand.)
Oh? But you said you were at Ikea.
(Yes, in Stockholm, Sweden.)
Did you have to go all the way
to Sweden for that?
(Yes, I did.)
(The products I want
are only available here.)
(Can’t you just wait for me to come back?)
Dude, I want to go today.
(Hang tight.)
(I’ll be back in seven days.)
Seven days…
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
I can’t take it anymore!
Oh, crap!
Crap!
Hey.
Are you alright?
Hold on. I’ll come get you.
Hey.
I think
you need to take your shirt off.
Put this on instead.
You don’t want to get sick, do you?
It’s alright.
I’m not really cold.
Come on.
Go on.
Oh, okay.
Hey, what’s your name?
My name is U.
It’s North.
I’m done changing.
North, are you okay, though?
You took quite a plunge into that river.
Are you hurt?
I’m all fine.
Let me check anyway.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Sure.
Let me see.
What about here?
Allow me.
Oh.
Crap.
Excuse me.
This is bad.
I think you should rest here.
We’ll keep walking when you’re better.
What do you think?
What about your stuff?
They must be drenched.
I’ll leave them out to dry in the sun.
It’s dead, huh?
He treated me so badly.
I’m in shambles, really.
But I realized I shouldn’t spend so much
time being miserable over some guy.
Right?
Actually, I asked Pure
to come hiking with me.
But he was busy.
So I thought, “Fine, I’ll go by myself!”
“I ain’t gonna die in the woods.”
But then…
It’s been barely half a day, and here I am.
What about you?
Oh, I was just bored.
Thought it would be nice
to go out for once.
Maybe I’d see something
nice and beautiful, you know?
I’m sorry, then.
You’re stuck with me so I doubt
you’ll see anything nice or beautiful.
Well…
I wouldn’t say that.
I think we should hurry up
and get out of the forest.
It’s getting late.
Can you even walk?
I have no choice, do I?
Alright.
Let me help.
Careful.
Is it far off, U?
I don’t know.
Hold on.
We’ve been through here five times.
I think we’re really lost, North.
North?
What should we do?
I want to go home.
If we get out of here,
what is the first thing you want to do?
I’m not even sure we’ll find our way home.
But if we’re out of here,
I’ll eat everything I want.
I won’t even worry about sodium bloating.
I’ll just order everything
in my shopping cart,
and open them all in one sitting!
Every game I haven’t finished playing,
I will finish them all!
Even when Pai tries to stop me,
I’ll tell him,
“Leave. Me. Alone!”
Honestly, when I really think about it,
there are so many things I regret.
From now on,
when there’s a good opportunity for me
or when I want to do something,
I won’t wait for the right time.
What about you?
What do you want to do if you get out?
Me?
I want a family.
I’m tired of being alone.
When you’re on your own too long,
it honestly gets lonely.
You’re not taken?
No, I’m not.
Haven't met the right one yet.
Don’t even know
what that person’s going to be like.
I’m curious about that as well.
I was just asking Pai about this.
He said I’ll know when I know.
But to tell you the truth, I still don’t get it.
It’s not like you take one look at someone
and know right away
that they’re your soulmate.
Right?
Uh…
Let me see.
Oh, North, I think you have a fever.
I’ll be fine.
Allow me.
I didn’t say you’re allowed.
Oh.
Sorry.
It’s alright.
Hey, you there.
Hey.
Oh!
U!
We’ll be fine!
Help me up, please.
Help me up.
We’re gonna make it, U!
Okay.
North.
Thank you, U.
I thought I was gonna die in the forest.
You’re exaggerating.
I was told we were less than 100 meters
away from the main trail.
But it felt so real.
I thought I was going to die there.
Good thing you were there with me.
I was happy to be there with you, too.
Here.
I saw it in the coin machine and thought it was adorable so I got one for you.
It’s just something to remember me by.
I guess this is where we say goodbye.
U.
Can I have your contact?
Here.
Alright.
I’ll… keep in touch.
(When did you know
you wanted to marry Tim?)
I just know I want to be with him every day.
(I know everything will be fine
as long as we go through it together.)
(When you can’t stop thinking
about your future with someone,)
(I guess that’s when you marry them.)
SRI YAN MEATBALLS
U!
North?
How did you find me?
Let’s talk about that later.
I have something important to ask you.
Yes?
Since I got back from the hike,
I keep thinking to myself that
if I were to really die,
what I would regret.
The only thing I can think about
is you.
I know it sounds completely crazy.
But I just don’t want
to waste any more time.
U.
Will you marry me?
What?
But I… have nothing, North,
only the clothes on my back.
I don’t deserve someone like you.
I don’t care about money.
I already have everything.
I don’t want anything else from you.
But—
How about this?
If you agree to marry me,
I’m giving this to you.
Consider it my dowry.
Will you marry me?
Are there any witnesses with you today?
There they are.
Sign here, please.
Yes.
Your turn, U.
Alright.
Jeeramongkolthanun…
Yes?
Oh, no.
It’s nothing.
Alright.
All done.
250 million!
Jeeramongkolthanun.
Why does that sound so familiar?
JEERAMONKOLTHANUN
THE FAMILY BEHIND
TEN BILLION-WORTH BUSINESSES
Crap!
Ten billion?
Crap.
Oh, wow!
THE FAMILY BEHIND
TEN BILLION-WORTH BUSINESSES
Yes!
THE FAMILY BEHIND
TEN BILLION-WORTH BUSINESSES
HOW TO FIND A RICH PARTNER
2) HANG AROUND RICH PEOPLE
GO TO PLACES RICH PEOPLE LOVE,
LIKE NATURE HIKES.
Hey, baby.
You’re home.
Uh, yes.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
You haven’t taken a shower, baby.
I’m about to—
I…
I’ll hop in the bath real quick.
Do not fall in love with the target.
When did you get in?
Just now.
I didn’t want to wait to use the bathroom
so I thought we could do it together.
What’s wrong?
Are you being shy?
No.
I’m just afraid
I won’t be able to hold back—
Why should you?
We’re going to be married soon.
DO NOT THINK PAI IS CUTE!
DO NOT FALL FOR THE TARGET
AT ALL COSTS!
To hell with it, then.
Confess right now.
You know about this?
Get our attorney
to divorce them right away!
You dropped this.
I found it.
Do you happen to pick up
a lot of lost wallets?
Maybe I really don’t know you well enough.
We can start right now.
If marriage really was between two people,
it would be nice, right?
I want to get married right now.
Tim!