Please give a round of applause
to our newlyweds!
Mr. Pai, we are all here to tell you the truth.
I’m useless to you now.
Just get out of my life.
I think you can trust him again when
he has no reason to scam you now.
Let’s start over.
Start over?
If you don’t love me, don’t say that.
I’m not giving up on you.
Just watch out and try not to fall for me.
Gecko!
Where?
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
Hey!
What’s that for?
Serves you right.
You don’t take good care of your house
that it nearly makes someone slip,
and you laugh?
Hey, have a little respect.
I let you live here rent-free.
You’re even wearing my clothes,
you know?
I’m not staying for free.
I’ll pay you back when I can.
Don’t you worry about that.
You don’t need to.
I’m more than happy to let you live here.
Stay forever if you like.
I don’t mind.
Hey.
What now?
I want a divorce.
Today?
I’m busy.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Let’s see…
It says here there will be
heavy rainfall tomorrow.
It is advised to stay inside
and just be nice and stay put.
Are you messing with me?
I’m not.
Look at this.
That’s what it says on the news.
“Adorable people should
refrain from going outside.”
“Handsome people shoul—” Ow!
Can you stop throwing
someone else’s stuff?
Then be rational.
How am I not being rational?
I told you I’m not getting a divorce.
You want a divorce?
Sue me.
And stop throwing my things.
Everything’s ruined.
Allow me to explain
what is going to happen.
Upon signing this contract,
you agree to a conciliation.
You are no longer allowed
to make further claims whatsoever.
You will not pursue any legal actions
or engage in public defamation.
If you have any questions,
please consult the contract carefully.
In return, Mr. Tim agrees
to compensate you for your troubles,
which amounts to 69 million baht in total.
I’m kidding, Tim.
You’re lucky Pai’s family insisted
they didn’t want your money.
Otherwise, you wouldn’t be able
to afford to compensate these ladies.
But since we’re on the topic,
how the hell did you slip up so badly?
You knew damn well love affairs are
always impossible to slither out of
If I didn’t do that, how’d I find enough
money to pay Mr. Prasit back?
Did you forget I have a
monthly debt commitment?
Basically, you’re broke now, aren’t you?
I’m not entirely broke, though.
Besides the house and the car I won’t sell,
I have 15 baht left in my bank account.
That’s not a lot?
As you’ve all learned,
we have been excluded from the Jeeramongkolthanun’s beneficiary list.
From now on, our lives depend on
what we have with us right this moment.
Why do you look confused?
Why do you talk like that?
What do you mean?
It sounds like we’re in a board meeting.
It doesn’t.
This is how I talk.
You.
You’re responsible for
today’s minutes of meeting.
Y–Yes, Mr. Pai.
North.
What are minutes of meeting?
Just write them on your phone.
What am I supposed to write?
Your feelings, duh.
Just write it down.
This is my wedding suit.
I’m sure we can sell it.
I also have some cash on me…
327 baht.
How much do you guys have?
I already returned
the 250 million North gave me.
North.
Where is that money right now?
It’s in my bedroom.
Typical North…
You, too.
How could you return
the money so willingly?
What?
MINUTES OF MEETING
(Pai is poor.)
What are you guys doing?
Hey, Tim.
We’re trying to sort out
how much money we have.
Pai wants to know how long
what we have will last us.
I see.
Whoa.
Do you carry the rings around
with you all the time?
Yeah.
Just in case I need to propose again.
Thanks.
But I don’t take anything from a thief.
And don’t you wear that ring again.
North.
Don’t you have any cash or asset
that don’t belong to the family?
Grandpa used to give you money
on the side, didn’t he?
Right.
Hey.
How are you, dude?
You alright?
I…
No.
North.
I told you to close this place down.
You’ve been lying to me all this time?
Pai, before you say anyth—
Thank you, North.
We’re saved!
CLOSED!
FOR OUR FIRST EVER MEETING
I have to admit that you and Pure
make really good pastries.
But…
But what now?
But if you continue your business like this,
it won’t turn a profit even in 10 years.
This place has made us money before,
you know?
One day doesn’t count.
Don’t make such a fuss, Pai.
If you want it to make profits,
I’ll pay for that myself.
How would it be called profits
if you did that?
One more thing, we are not
borrowing money from anyone.
North, you’re not allowed
to be in debt or cause trouble now.
The only way we’ll survive this
is to make this place turn a profit.
I want you to hire me as your employee.
I ask for only 500 baht a day.
And I guarantee a 3000% growth
for your business.
Alright.
You’re hired.
We’ll start with cost-cutting by removing
any menu items that don’t sell.
Hold on.
No.
That’s a no-no.
I said no.
I want you to bake based on
the ingredients in the fridge.
You’re not allowed to order more supplies
unless you run out
of the pre-existing ingredients.
Is that a dare?
Not unless you can’t do it.
Do your best, bud.
Excuse me.
Yes, Mr. Pai?
I’m sorry but your service
is no longer required here.
A resignation letter?
Yes.
MATCHA YUZU CROISSANT
AND BASIL LEMON TART
Oh, you’re back to work now.
I am.
Hello.
What can I get you today?
Of course.
Donut?
Here is your orange americano.
Thanks.
Pai, careful. It’s hot.
I told you to bake croissants.
North, careful!
Just take this.
Pai, let me know when you’re home.
Here.
Oh.
Come and have dinner, you guys.
It’s still hot.
Come on.
Stop looking for excuses.
I won’t charge you for this.
That’s a bitter melon, North.
Well, I used to study abroad, you know?
Thank you for your service.
Over there?
That table, U.
Just go.
North.
Americano?
Pai, one americano, please.
I’ll put them here, Pai.
Thanks.
Here’s the food.
What would you like?
I won’t let you change my recipe
just like this.
Just get off my back.
I’m not trying to pick a fight, Pure.
I just don’t think we need to import
the chocolate straight from Belgium.
But it’s my recipe!
Tarte au chocolat noir blanc.
It needs ‘chocolat noir blanc.’
It wouldn’t be “tarte au chocolat
noir blanc” otherwise!
It wouldn’t!
I won’t let you—
What are you doing here?
I just want to try North’s pastry.
We’re out.
You are?
You must do really well.
You need any new hires?
No.
We’re managing it fine on our own.
You sure about that?
Iced chocolate coming up, ma’am.
Irasshaimase!
Oh.
Tim.
Hey, Tim.
When did you get here?
Are you hungry?
I’ll find something for you to eat.
I’m fine.
What are you doing here anyway?
I was wondering if you need someone
to work here part-time.
You’re hired!
North, no.
Why not?
We’re at our limits!
Having more help during this time is good!
I don’t mind working as an unpaid intern.
I just want something to do
before I start my new job.
Aren’t you curious about my new job?
No one is.
I’ll start tomorrow.
Wow.
I have to go.
I have to talk to a potential buyer.
They’re interested in
distributing our pastries.
Can I give you a ride?
Leave me alone.
I don’t think it’s a good idea
to be strolling around here.
Hello. We have so many
new flavors of macarons.
- Hello. We have so many
- Why?
Hello. We have so many
new flavors of macarons.
Well, now that I’m broke,
I feel like I’m just here to watch people eat.
But I can’t buy anything if I want to.
What’s wrong, North?
I don’t want to torture myself.
Oh?
Why’d you let go of my hand?
Hello.
Hello, our special customer.
We have a TikTok dance challenge promotion, sir.
TikTok…
Dance challenge?
Hold on.
Alright?
One, two, three.
U, go for it.
U!
Alright.
So this is what it tastes like to be human.
That was so good.
Oh, I forgot to share it with you.
I’m sorry.
I got it.
It’s good.
Sweet.
Are you embarrassed?
Does it look like I am?
No.
But I am.
Good morning, brothers.
Good morning, Mr. Pai.
Sit down.
We’ll have breakfast.
What is Tim doing
having breakfast here alone?
I’m fine.
I am fine, sir.
Mr. Tim here wants some privacy.
Totally, North.
I love private breakfasts.
But seeing as Pai must be lonely,
I came and sat with him.
Go on and have breakfast, you guys.
Morning, by the way.
Morning.
You okay?
Yeah.
Right.
Oh, right.
How was it talking to the…
potassium slider… slim?
Potential buyer.
It’s someone who’s interested
in buying our products.
I think it’s interesting.
They want to put our pastries up
in convenience stores.
If it really does happen,
our daily income will likely
exceed our expectations.
Does that mean we’ll be rich again?
Yes.
But I don’t think we’re ready for that.
Why not?
If we agree to this deal,
we have to increase our product output,
and thus, also our manpower
just to meet their demand.
That will require at least a million that
we don’t have right now.
What if we asked Pure for the loan?
I understand you don’t want
to borrow anyone’s money.
But if it’s the money to expand
our business,
I think it makes sense.
I contacted Pure.
He said a million would be quite troublesome for him as well.
But he always travels.
I believe he’s been pressured by
the family to not help us out.
The mess we made might not
become a national scandal,
I’ll try to look more into it.
Do your best, guys!
We got this.
You put us in this situation so shut up.
Yessir!
Shall we have breakfast?
What did I just say?
Sorry.
Thank you for arranging this.
Of course.
Just talk to her nicely.
Right.
There she is.
Oom.
You told me you wanted
to talk to me about work.
I have to go.
I just remember I left the iron running.
It must be burning at this point.
Are you scamming patients now?
Just leave me be.
Say what you want to say.
Mom.
You remember the one million
you stole from me?
What money?
I don’t remember that.
Don’t lie.
We both know it was you who took it.
Just give it back to me.
The person that money belongs
to really needs it right now.
Is that so?
Do you mean the grandson of a tycoon
If he’s in trouble with money,
that means he’s useless to you now.
Why don’t you just leave him?
I love him.
I don’t want to cause trouble
for someone I love.
I thought I taught you better than this, U.
Love is useless to the likes of us.
Unless it’s our weapon.
And since it’s a weapon,
you shouldn’t use it to hurt yourself.
Love makes you weak.
And weak people are taken advantage of.
Mom.
I never asked anything of you.
But I’m asking you this.
Give me back that money.
If you want it, you will have to
call the cops on me.
Thank you.
He is so easy on the eye, isn’t he?
Wanna join my “my boyfriend
used to be a conman” club?
You’re talking nonsense.
Where’s U today?
He has some errand to run.
I think he’ll be back by evening.
North.
Yes?
Why are you still dating U?
He scammed you
Yes, he scammed me.
But he doesn't do that anymore.
How do you know he’s not
fooling you right now?
I mean, if he was using me,
he might have run away already.
But I’m no use to him now.
So if he chooses to stay,
that must mean that he loves me.
Aren’t you mad at him?
Well, I was.
But I don’t think you can
stay mad at someone forever.
Hey, Tim.
What are you talking about?
None of your business.
I’ll go put this in the kitchen.
I don’t wanna be caught in the crossfire.
Tired?
Do you want a massage?
Come here.
I’m good at this, you know?
Is it here?
Your iced yuzu, sir.
How did you know I’d be here?
A friend of mine said they saw you
at this cafe.
How are you doing?
I’m getting by.
Why didn’t you tell me?
You know I’m always here for you.
You know I don’t want to
owe anyone anything.
Why are you still with…
Forget that.
Why did you come to see me?
Pai.
Can we talk outside?
I don’t feel comfortable talking in front of...
It’s hot outside, though.
LAND TITLE DEED
It’s the title deed of the land of
our gated community project.
I’m returning it to you.
I just thought you might need it.
Thank you, Kuea.
This totally saves me.
He’s lost it.
Look at him pacing the floor.
Poor man.
I have to go.
Thank you
Bye, you guys.
- Bye.
Hey.
Tim.
Me?
Yeah.
What’s up?
Would you like to have dinner tonight?
…Yes.
You promise?
I’ll call and reserve a table.
Hello.
Have a little patience, Pai.
Tim seems down bad lately.
North.
I’ll leave early.
Make sure you hurry home
after you lock up.
I’ll see you at home
Okay.
Just go.
I’ll handle the rest.
Pure, let me help.
Thank you, man.
I’m sorry, but we’re closed.
You don’t have the kind of money
that can reserve this whole place
Just forget about that kind of thing.
I took out a loan on my car.
You shouldn’t live beyond your means
Don’t you realize we’re legally one person.
I don’t want to have to be liable
to any debts you incur.
I just…
I want to give you what you were used to.
Why… did you suddenly want
to have dinner with me?
I want a divorce.
Don’t change the subject
I want to have a serious
conversation about this.
Did Kuea put you up to this?
Yes.
He suggested I get a divorce from you.
I’m worried about you, Pai.
As long as you’re still married to Tim,
this land is a marital asset
and belongs to both you and Tim.
I suggest you get a proper divorce
before managing this property.
But even if Kuea didn’t say anything,
I still want a divorce.
Think about it.
I don’t know you at all.
I married someone I barely know.
You understand, don’t you?
Please.
Give me a divorce.
Let’s not take this matter to court.
If this is about money,
I’ll divorce you.
But…
But can we just have
this one last proper dinner?
Oh, you’re back.
Yeah.
I went to the bakery, but it was closed.
So I guessed you must have come home
But…
Where are Pai and Tim?
They’re at dinner.
What?
Right?
I was just as confused.
I didn’t see my boyfriend all day today.
I miss you.
Come here and let me get my fill of you.
Did that hurt?
Sorry.
It didn’t hurt.
Your eyes are swollen.
What’s happened?
Have you been crying?
Uh…
I… went to see Nart today.
I wanted her to return the
one million she stole.
I guessed it.
What do you mean you guessed it?
So… Nart came to see me
at the bakery today.
What?
I don’t know what she wanted.
She was speaking in circles like
she just wanted to get close to me.
But since I knew
what kind of person she is,
I just don’t trust her anymore.
Did she get anything out of you, North?
Of course not.
I don’t have anything
for her to take, you know?
Okay.
But let’s talk about you.
Why were you crying?
It’s just the same old thing
that ends the same old way.
I love my mother.
I just don’t think
she can turn herself around.
I think all you can do is let her go
and be with people
who love and care for you,
and hope she doesn’t hurt you again.
I care about you, you know?
I really do.
Thank you.
Was I an easy target?
Not really.
You’re kind of stubborn.
You like challenges
even when you keep complaining
that it’s exhausting.
So I put you in some
challenging situations at first.
Once you accepted the challenge,
you began to have fun.
Once you had fun,
you let your guard down.
After that, I just let
my gentlemanly side take the lead.
You stripped me bare, didn’t you?
Do you have any more questions?
Is Tim really your name?
It is!
You didn’t even think about using an alias?
It just kinda slipped out
the first time I met you.
That moment felt really special.
It didn’t feel like I was scamming anyone.
Oh.
I’m Tim.
I’m Pai.
So I let my actual name slip out.
It was like…
I was actually flirting
with someone I really wanted.
Was it hard playing Tim?
What do you mean?
Well, you know…
Being someone who was
created exactly just for me.
It was hard.
Like I said, it wasn’t me at all.
To tell you the truth, I don’t think
someone like him exists.
He’s like…
A unicorn.
Too good to be true.
It’s too bad.
I’d love to meet him just one more time.
That Tim?
Yeah.
Alright.
Hey, baby.
What’s the matter?
Don’t laugh.
You’re making me break character.
Now I have to start again.
Alright, alright.
I won’t laugh.
Come on.
Hey, baby.
What’s the matter?
I have something to tell you.
Close your eyes.
I can give you an extra discount
if you pay cash upfront.
What do you think?
You can tell we use all the best materials.
The construction is stable
and durable so—
Hello, Mom.
Why don’t we move inside?
Please.
I’ll be right with you.
What is it now?
I told you I won’t give it back.
If you want it so bad, call the cops.
I did.
It’s thanks to North that
now I understand I should be
with someone who loves me,
not someone who only hurts me,
and take advantage of North.
I can’t let you do that, Mom.
I call your bluff.
I know you don’t have the guts to do that.
I raised you myself.
I…
I didn’t do it myself.
He did.
His name is Prem.
He is a criminal defense attorney
behind our country’s top con artists.
I already asked him to handle everything.
If you ever want to turn over a new leaf,
I’ll be here, waiting to be your family again.
Sir. Ma’am.
Go home.
This woman is a con artist.
I know because
she has conned me before.
You’re up.
Yeah.
I had something to do this morning.
How was it?
You okay?
With you here, of course, I am.
Thank you.
For what?
I don’t know.
I just want to thank you.
You’re being weird.
I don’t want to get up.
But I need to do my laundry,
and Pai wants me to go to
the district office with him.
What is he doing at the district office?
I don’t know.
Well, why don’t I do the laundry?
Go back to bed.
You’re the best.
Good night.
Oh, hey.
Can I put my laundry in your load?
Hey.
Hey!
You need to use the washing machine?
Yeah.
Where’s your mind at?
You look like a kicked puppy.
You went to dinner
with Mr. Pai last night, right?
Didn’t you guys make up?
Pai said he wants a divorce.
I already agreed to it.
That’s why you’re going to
the district office.
Come on.
It’s alright.
Take it easy.
I got divorced before
getting back together as well.
There’s still hope.
Don’t be discouraged.
Alright?
Smile.
I’ll go.
Thanks for this.
Where is Tim?
Why isn’t he here?
I just met him out back doing laundry.
Hey!
Is he trying to get out of this?
Hey.
Are you hurt?
What’s happened?
Hey!
North! U!
North!
Pai?
Yes?
Oh!
- Tim!
Tim.
Mr. Thanin is safe now.
Can I see him?
Yes.
Thank you, Doctor.
This is not a ruse, is it?
Why were you so careless?
I told you to scrub the algae off
that part of the floor.
I’m sorry.
You’re always like this, baby.
I don’t like it.
What did you just call me?
Don’t make fun of me.
I’m still shaken.
Sorry.
From the look of it, I don’t think
they’re getting divorced.
The worst part for me is that
I can’t be there to support you.
Just come to one date with me.
Please!
Stop making a ruckus.
If you’re still in love with him
and believe in him,
why would you need someone new?
You ever met someone you know
was the one for you
that you can’t love someone else?