I dropped my car key into this pond.
I guess you need to take responsibility.
This is my personal contact.
Would it be alright if I contact you romantically?
Be my guest.
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
Crap!
Hey.
You need to take your shirt off.
You don’t want to get sick, do you?
When did you know
you wanted to marry Tim?
I just know I want to be with him every day.
Will you marry me?
JEERAMONGKOLTHANUN
Ten billion?
PLAY WITH HIS FEELINGS,
NOT YOUR OWN.
DO NOT THINK PAI IS CUTE!
DO NOT FALL FOR THE TARGET
AT ALL COSTS!
Why should you hold back?
We’re going to be married soon.
To hell with it, then.
Do not fall for your target.
Hello?
Oom?
Are you free tomorrow?
I have a job for you.
Alright.
I’m here to officially ask for
Pai’s hand in marriage to Tim.
It’s a pleasure.
We have all seen how consistent Tim is.
We have no objection at all.
That’s right.
Isn’t that right, honey?
Thank you, Grandpa, and also
Papa and Mama.
I am so grateful to hear that,
especially after listening to Tim
bragging about Pai all the time.
When they started dating,
Tim called me every day
asking about how his father used to
woo me when we were falling in love.
He thought he’d use the same trick, I believe.
Really?
Maybe a little.
Let me get some for you.
Here, Mom.
Thanks, love.
But you don’t have to worry about me.
You should take care of Pai.
Excuse me. Can we have a fork?
Auntie, Da Zhan is a grownup now.
Why don’t you let him try using chopsticks
so he can finally use them?
Oh, don’t you berate your cousin when
you have a boyfriend who does it for you.
I’ll get some food for him.
What do you want, Da Zhan?
Har gow, please.
Okay.
Uh…
There you go.
Thank you.
Maybe I can teach you
how to use chopsticks later?
Nah.
No?
Here.
You’re giving me both fish collars?
Let me share one with you.
Thank you.
I’ll give you two more next time.
I’m really sorry I can’t go with you today.
Oh, it’s alright, love.
You should spend time with your family.
I’m already so happy today.
I am overjoyed.
I’ll be smiling all the way back to London.
If Tim is ever bothersome,
you have to let me know, love.
Of course.
You’re going to be in trouble.
Mom.
Don’t you think it’s too soon to love Pai
more than your own child?
What’s not to love about him, am I right?
Safe travel, Mom.
Of course.
I have to go for now.
I’ll see you later.
Are you sure you’re alright?
Umm.
Everyone seems like
they’re in a good mood today.
I don’t think there’ll be any cause
for headaches.
Call me if something happens.
Do not bottle it up all alone, you hear me?
Just go.
Your mother is waiting.
Bye, then.
Tim!
It’s too bad.
If I wasn’t playing a rich lady today,
I would have asked them to pack up
some of that mushroom soup for me.
Good job today, Mama.
And to think that was all unrehearsed.
As expected of
the number one in the industry.
Of course.
In this line of work,
you need to be ready to take on any role.
You do remember
what you said to them, though?
You’ll meet them again
at the wedding, you know?
Oh, I’m sure rich people don’t pay
any mind to every single small detail.
Aunt Kia remembers everything.
But that Pai kid is adorable, though.
And I notice that Mr. Soepohn
smiles with his eyes when he talks to you.
He seems to really adore you.
Of course, he does.
That’s the point of this whole scam.
Honestly, though.
Why don’t you just fall in love properly
and spend your life with him?
I’d be insane to do that.
If this whole thing ever came out,
people like them would
totally have me ruined.
It’s a shame, you know.
You two have chemistry.
Here is your paycheck.
Fabulous.
Thanks.
- Bye.
- I’m off.
How is North doing?
Did he start working at the office?
I’m still trying to coax him into it.
You know how stubborn he is, Grandpa.
Pai.
North is a poor kid.
I would never die happy
if I didn’t see him get his life together.
He’s one of us, Pai.
We can’t simply abandon him.
Of course, Grandpa.
Goodnight.
(Hi, baby.)
Did you leave the airport?
(I’m still at the airport, actually.)
(Do you need me to pick you up?)
(I can leave right away.)
It’s alright.
You should spend time with your mother.
I’ll have a chauffeur drive me home.
Alright.
I’ll see you when I’m done here.
Bye.
You lie with a more straight face
than a lawyer like me, dude.
I mean, I’d make a good lawyer.
I could defend some criminals and steal your job.
Nope.
I won’t allow it.
If you stole my job,
how the hell would I feed myself?
On shaved ice, apparently.
And it’s good, too.
But why don’t you hurry home
and keep up the scores with Pai?
Listen, dude.
I know when Pai needs me,
but I won’t let him get his way every time.
This will keep him wanting me more and more,
and doesn’t take me for granted.
Sounds cool.
But that’s a useless tactic for a lawyer.
Use your brain sometimes.
Hey.
It’s late.
I have to meet Airy tomorrow.
Sure.
But do think of Attorney Prem here
when your scheme falls apart.
Don’t jinx me like that.
You want me to tip the shaved ice
over your pants, dude?
Don’t waste food like that!
Gotta go.
- See ya.
- Good luck.
Hello, sir.
Same table?
Yes.
Welcome.
Hong.
Airy, hello.
Sit down.
Hi there.
Oh, Hong.
Yes?
You’re sitting so far away from me.
It’s like you don’t even miss me.
I just want to make sure you’re comfortable
in your seat, of course.
Shall we try something new or
should I order your favorite dish?
I want to try something new…
Oh?
Like you, Hong.
Not only are you beautiful,
but also funny.
Of course.
I spent a hundred thousand on you, I don’t
intend to just hold hands, you know?
Airy, but you said I’m not like
your other sugar babies?
You have to win me over first, remember?
Aren’t you a charmer?
I love it.
Right.
What would you like?
IN LOSSES
He did not make one bit of profit since day one?
How come the place didn’t go out of business already?
I was told Mr. North tided it over out of his own pocket.
So much for ‘learning business by himself.’
If it went on like this, he wouldn’t learn
anything even in 10 years.
Unreachable yet again.
Bring him here right away, Nana.
Of course, sir.
You’re still busy?
I’ll wait outside.
You can stay, Tim.
We’ll only be a minute.
Just confess.
You know you can’t hide it from me.
Y–You…
You know?
Nana told me everything.
It was my fault for not telling you
before I went ahead with it.
But…
I want you to be happy for me and my new relationship.
MARRIAGE CERTIFICATE
What?!
- What?
MARRIAGE CERTIFICATE
But who is…
Who is this Issara Preechajit guy?
Alright.
Whatever happens,
at least I have some cash on me.
My boy…
We’re going to be filthy rich!
NORTH
Hello, North?
(U, hi.)
(Are you busy right now?)
(There happens to be an emergency.)
Oh.
Pai, please calm down—
Who are you?
Where are you from? How old are you?
What do you do for a living?
Why did you marry my cousin without telling his family?
Huh?
Calm down.
How can I calm down?
North, what were you thinking?
Were you drunk?
Call Attorney Vicha and we’ll get you divorced right now!
Divorce? I’m not getting a divorce!
This is exactly why I had to
get married without telling you, Pai!
You certainly did!
I’m a grown man!
I can think for myself!
If that’s the case, then tell me who he is
and how come you’re married to him!
Well, I…!
I don’t know.
- North!
- Calm down, baby!
Pai, calm down.
Uh, North and I met when we went hiking.
We were lost in the woods together for a night.
We thought we wouldn’t make it.
But that night was beautiful. It really was.
I knew right away that
I found the right person for me.
I didn’t want to waste any more time.
“Waste time”?
You think getting to know him
and meeting his family is a waste of time?
I told him not to!
But if you want to, Pai—
That’s Mr. Pai to you!
Mr. Pai.
If you want to know me better, Mr. Pai,
I can tell you everything about myself.
I’ll go and pay my respect to North’s grandfather, too.
Pai.
Grandpa and everyone else can’t know about this.
Attorney Vicha as well.
Why not?
Imagine what would happen if Aunt Kia found out.
It’s best we deal with this ourselves,
don’t you think so?
Don’t tell anyone about this until I approve of it.
As for this.
Divorce is still an option.
Don’t think you can make
any demands from my cousin!
Do you hear me?
Of course, Mr. Pai.
I’m going to the bathroom.
Of course.
It’s over there.
Right.
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
I’m sorry.
I was in a hurry and didn’t see you there.
It’s alright.
I’ll be a minute.
I’ll wait outside.
You dropped this.
I found it.
Oh, thank you.
You’re forgetful, aren’t you?
Excuse me?
Do you know what the number
at the bottom of the card means?
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
This number indicates how many times you have a new card issued.
And yours says…
Wow.
19 times.
If it’s not because you’re forgetful,
why else would it be?
I’m sure I didn’t drop my wallet.
For you to pick my pocket so easily
when you bump into me like that…
Do you usually ‘find’ a lot of wallets?
HEY, LOOK INTO THIS GUY FOR ME.
I’m sorry, sir.
Nana.
Look U up for me.
If there’s any suspicion that he could
be using North, let me know.
Of course, Mr. Pai.
Ah. Excuse me.
Come here.
I don’t understand North.
What was he thinking to marry a total stranger?
You should be nice to him.
Are you taking his side?
Of course not.
I just want you two to talk nicely.
So your eyebrows don’t have to
work overtime like this.
I know.
Mr. Pai!
Nana.
I told you to knock.
I wanted to ask about the papers
you need for today’s meeting.
But I can come back later, sir.
I think this room is big enough for two people.
The kitchen is over there.
I barely use it.
The bathroom is beyond that.
I see.
This is all your stuff?
Oh, yes. This is everything.
I travel light.
Shall we take a look at the bedroom?
Okay.
This is my bedroom.
Oh, I see.
It’s big.
Which side of the bed do you usually sleep on?
I sleep in the middle.
But you can let me know which side you prefer.
I’m okay with anything.
I sleep in the middle as well.
Oh?
How about this?
Oh, U.
What’s wrong?
What are you thinking?
No, it’s just…
I’m thinking about what Pai said today.
I couldn’t answer any of his questions.
Maybe I really don’t know you well enough.
North.
Why don’t we get to know each other right now?
How fast we go… I’ll let you set the pace.
Good idea!
Let’s go on a date!
Date?
Yeah!
U.
What is that?
What are you hiding?
Here.
What is that?
You’ll know soon.
I have a plan for our date, though.
I only need one hour.
Alright.
Good.
Please.
Thank you.
Let’s put on a seat belt for your safety.
You ready?
For a while now.
Let’s go.
Come on.
Move your legs.
Is there a hole in the middle
of your racket or something?
I’m gonna get serious now.
Alright.
North, you.
Yes?
Is that the best you can do, U?
Are you tired?
Breathe in and breathe out.
Honestly.
Not counting the hike,
this is the most exhausted I’ve been.
Did you have fun, though?
I did.
But I thought we were getting to know each other.
We’re doing that through sports.
You’re strong-willed.
You believe in your own strategies.
When under a lot of pressure,
you let go of everything and just wing it.
Am I right?
What about you?
Did you get anything on me?
Can we try again?
My eyes were only on the ball.
You’re so amazing.
You were playing and analyzing and still won.
Did you use to be an athlete?
No.
It’s just my mother taught me how to read people.
That must be nice.
I only got to live with Pai and Grandpa.
They never taught me anything.
All they did was scold and scold and scold me.
Sometimes I wonder,
if I’m so much trouble for them,
why won’t they just leave me alone?
Oh, North.
Don’t say that.
I’m sure they do it out of love.
You’re so optimistic, U.
You must have such a lovely family.
Can I meet your family?
Uh…
I rented the same house.
Remember, you’re a single mom
who works as an accountant.
When I was in school,
I was on scholarship
because I wanted to help financially.
Also…
I believe in love at first sight.
How does that have to do with anything?
I’m sure an amazing actor like you
will find a way to fit it into a conversation.
Don’t screw up, Mama.
This guy is my retirement plan.
As if I ever screw up.
But let’s talk about you.
Did you clean things up on your end?
On my end?
Nart, duh.
She just got out of jail.
If she knew you caught such a big fish,
I don’t think she’d go down without a fight.
In my entire career,
I never met anyone as talented
and as dangerous as your mother.
Yeah, she fools me all the time.
If she knew about this, I’m sure
she would just do what she always does.
I really hate your mother, you know?
Who doesn’t?
Well, you.
Come on in.
Excuse me.
Come in.
-Make yourself at home, love.
-Yes.
ISSARA PREECHAJIT
Oh.
You also like the Honnomo plushies?
Wait, but…
I’ve never seen this model before.
Oh.
It’s a knock-off.
My mother bought it for me.
She found it at the mall
and didn’t know it was a knock-off.
Old ladies, am I right?
How was I to know?
I wanted to buy a new one
now that I make my own money,
the real thing, as well.
But then, I realized I don’t want it anymore.
You have to see this.
This is unmissable.
Look at these, love.
This is adorable.
This is his childhood photo album.
See how chubby his cheeks are?
I’ve never seen U open up to anyone before.
But you, North, makes him believe in love at first sight.
Mom.
You’re embarrassing me.
Oh.
I ordered some snacks.
I’ll go get them.
Of course.
What was that?
It slipped out.
Breathe!
Okay.
Uh…
Guys.
My name is Nart.
I am—
Auntie!
Aunt Nart.
She’s my aunt.
Auntie.
That’s right.
His Aunt.
I see.
Hello, Aunt Nart.
Hello.
What are you doing here, Mom?
What are you planning?
I…
I heard you’re quitting because
you’re getting married to someone.
I just wanted to see
what kind of person had won you over.
Congratulations.
You’ll finally have a place to call home.
I’m sorry
I couldn’t do a better job at raising you.
I’m really happy for you.
Do you…
have a place to stay?
Don’t worry.
I’ll find some room to rent for the night.
You can stay at my place.
I’ll give you a ride.
Let’s begin.
Give me your hand.
A strong fate.
You are destined for great things.
But you must be wary of
who you surround yourself with,
since people are drawn to you
to take advantage of you.
This is especially true during this time.
He must be talking about U.
Definitely.
Very possible.
Your hand.
What happened?
You look alarmed.
They are soulmates.
They have been soulmates in every lifetime.
Though they don’t always end up together in all of them.
But in every lifetime, they always find each other.
In this one, though…
They will face a grand obstacle.
If they’re able to get through the hurdle,
their love will be very strong.
But if they fail to do so,
the paths will diverge for good.
But we’ve never even fought.
Are you sure you were reading the right line?
Pai!
How could you say that to Master?
Master.
When is the best time for them to get married?
In four months.
That is the most auspicious.
So in the middle of the year?
Oh, but we’re opening a new branch
abroad during that time.
We have Halloween, Christmas,
and the New Year at the end of the year.
At the beginning of next year, there’s Lunar
New Year, Valentine’s, and Songkran.
With that alone, we’re already
more than a year behind.
When is my day off?
Your only days off are the 13th through to the 15th…
of next month.
How about this?
We’ll pick the most auspicious day
between the 13th and 15th of next month.
That sounds good.
We’ll do that.
We will not!
Master will find you the perfect day.
Remember that our family is only here
because of Master’s great guidance.
So the fact that I work hard to the point of
having only three days off this year
means nothing, then?
I just want to get married on my terms.
Is that too much to ask?
I’m literally helping you.
I think this is it for today.
Pai and I will talk about this.
How arrogant of them.
Do whatever you want, then!
Nana.
Yes?
Sir?
Don’t forget about what I told you to look into.
I won’t, sir.
You can’t even take one more step, love?
No, I can not.
I’m so exhausted.
Why does everything have to be so difficult?
Is it a bad day for you, baby?
So bad.
Alright. Wait right here.
Medium rare, per usual?
Baby.
How did you know watching you cook
makes me feel at ease?
I don’t know that.
I just want to make you something delicious.
If marriage really was between two people,
that would be nice.
I want to get married right now.
Like North did?
I’m joking.
I’ll have the bath running after dinner.
We can try that new bath bomb.
Let’s take a bath together?
You know, Mom,
you can actually stay as long as you want.
You know I can’t stay put too long.
I mean, those cops still found me even
when I was moving around so much.
You don’t need to work anymore, Mom.
I can take care of you.
You can just have this room.
You still like that thing?
Yes.
Well, it was the last thing you gave me.
I have to keep it.
You told me to exchange some receipt for my birthday gift at the mall.
That thing is what I got.
When I came home, you were gone.
I’m sorry.
What?
Crap.
Damn it!
It was my fault for trusting her.
People are nothing but selfish.
Don’t think that.
There are good people out there.
You know, I myself have let so many of my targets go.
You?
It’s just…
I think some people, if they weren’t unfortunate enough to meet the likes of us,
are good people who can make the world a better place.
How can you tell who those people are?
You’ll know when you meet them.
You can tell when someone is incapable of hurting anyone,
and you can’t help feeling bad for hurting them.
Even someone of your calibre went through something like that?
That’s why we set up the rule:
Don’t fall in love with the target.
What are you doing?
Oh!
You said you were going to stay at your place.
What are you doing, North?
I’m not doing anything.
U—
What’s this?
Open it.
Surprise!
I got you this plushie since you said you wanted it
…as an apology.
Apology?
Your family is so nice to me.
My family is awful to you.
So I thought I want to be extra nice to you to make up for that.
It’s authentic, you know?
U, what’s wrong?
It’s just…
The real one
…is beautiful.
Thank you, North.
Thank you.
Of course.
It’s nothing.
If I knew you’d like it this much,
I’d have bought ten more.
Why did you want to meet me here?
You said this suspicious U guy took North to his family home in Sathon, right?
The estate agent turns a blind eye and rents this place out to scammers.
Many of my clients have rented it.
I asked the agent if it was rented recently.
And it was.
If he really was here, there must be something left inside.
You want to talk to me?
Stop renting that house in Sathon.
It’s overused.
What are you talking about?
If you know that much, I don’t think we’re all that different.
Let’s talk as people in the same line of work, shall we?
What the hell do you think you’re doing?
Exactly the same crap you’re pulling.
Be respectful.
I’m older.
I’m also your in-law.
Fine.
Respect, it is.
Let’s say, if you stay out of my way, I’ll stay out of yours.
You watch my back.
I’ll watch your back.
And we can be on the same turf.
Fine.
I don’t trust you, though.
Neither do I.
Who is that for?
It’s a gift basket for Mr. North.
What?
I’m sure U doesn’t love North.
I just need evidence.
You’re gonna bug them?
Don’t you think this is too much, Pai?
This is nothing compared to the airtags in the bags
that are their wedding gift, sir.
Pai.
If he proves to be trustworthy,
I’ll leave them alone.
I just need to be sure first.
(Code Red!)
It’s okay, U.
I’ll get it.
Okay.
Who does Pai want me to give this to now?
That’s not the case, sir.
This gift basket is for you to congratulate you on your newlywed life.
“Congratulate” me?
Yes.
He’s right across the hall.
Why isn’t he here to “congratulate” me himself?
Oh.
Pai is currently very busy.
He feels that his initial reaction was exaggerated by his surprise,
but he’s okay with it now.
May I come in and place the gift basket inside for you, sir?
Sure.
Oh, no need.
This looks gorgeous.
I’ll take it from here.
This, too?
Oh, she wouldn’t let go.
Let me help.
Right.
Send our gratitude to Mr. Pai.
Of course.
Thank you.
Do you need my help with that?
It’s alright, Nana.
Thank you.
I am more than happy to—
That was weird.
Super weird.
I don’t think so.
Maybe Pai really is happy for us.
Oh, matching bags.
Let me see.
We can match.
What’s wrong, U?
I think the zipper’s stuck.
Can you help me with it?
Let me see.
An airtag?
I guess Pai doesn’t want us to lose the bags, huh?
Oh, sorry.
It’s alright.
I’ll pick it up.
Pai, you jerk!
Tim, where is Pai?
Uh…
What do you think you’re doing?
This is so disrespectful to me and my husband!
I’m worried about you.
You don’t know who he is.
How can you love him?
U and I are not inmates that need to be under constant surveillance.
What will you have me do?
Nothing!
It’s my life!
It’s your life, but it’s my responsibility.
If anything happens to you, they will blame me.
They will blame you?
So you’re just trying to save your own butt?
Honestly, Pai, do you ever care how I feel?
Don’t say that.
Why can’t I?
You can leave me alone now.
My life would be absolutely perfect without you in it.
I’m done.
- North.
- Let’s go, U.
- Calm down.
- U, come on.
- Talk to him nicely.
- U.
North. North.
Pai.
I want to be alone right now.
There’s no way I can let that happen.
Come here.
I’m never talking to Pai again.
And he’s not allowed to talk to me, either!
I’m sure he’s just worried about you.
But don’t you think that was too much, U?
Pai treats me like I’m his pet dog.
Might as well just get me a microchip.
Why are you laughing?
I’m boiling!
You’re adorable when you’re angry.
Pai must have raised you really well.
U, that’s not funny.
Alright, I’m not teasing you anymore.
What are you gonna do now?
Can I talk to you?
Tim.
Alright.
But we talk here, in front of U.
Please, do me a favor.
Will you apologize to Pai?
No.
I didn’t do anything wrong.
If that was all, excuse me.
North.
I am begging you.
He… Pai is miserable.
He refuses to eat.
I’ve never seen him like this before.
Pai cares about you a lot.
I don’t know what to say to him.
Can you, please, talk to him?
Is he really in such bad shape?
Pai!
Hey.
Got caught up, did you?
Like hell I did.
Pai.
Are you sad because of what I said?
I’m sorry!
I didn’t mean to!
Are you not mad at me anymore?
How could I be mad at you?
Goodnight, Pai.
Bye, Tim.
Baby.
What did you say to North?
He’s usually very stubborn,
but he easily apologized this time.
All it takes is telling them you’re sad and it gets everyone in a panic.
No way.
Really.
Well, when you’re sad, it’s…
What is it?
It’s funny.
You make a face like a little duckling when you’re sad.
Duckling?
Yeah.
Don’t be sad again, you hear me?
There.
What was that for?
You called me a little duckling.
You really look like one.
Watch it!
I’m not talking to you anymore!
Baby!
Come back here!
What?
Where are you going?
I didn’t do anything.
You hit me?
You won’t catch me!
Stop it.
Do you surrender?
Alright!
You do?
I would like to invite you to dinner at home, Mr. Pai.
Please, come in.
Help me in the kitchen, then.
How are you in love already?
You just met.
Did it take you and Pai
a long time to fall in love?
You’re blushing.
This is like when we first started dating.
I just happened to see the side of him that makes me feel protective over.
It feels like I just got to know another part of you.
I like it.