Where’s the bathroom?
- It’s…
- Over there.
Baby.
How’d you know that?
You and U somehow feel very similar.
How so?
U looks at North the way you look at me.
It’s like I finally have a family today.
I love you, North.
I love you, too, U.
NO SALTED ROLLS BECAUSE WE
DON’T KNOW HOW TO MAKE THEM.
Try this.
Happy to.
- So good.
- Smells amazing.
Can I take a few boxes home?
It’s for my family.
A few boxes?
Do you plan to spike up
your Grandpa’s blood sugar?
It’s not for Grandpa.
It’s for my boyfriend’s mother.
Oh, my. Oh, my.
Love is in the air and it stinks!
Alright.
Take whatever you want.
But ask her to vote which of these
we should put on the menu.
I’ll just grab a few…
All of this.
See you.
Bye.
Thank you for this.
The house is quite spacious,
just like how you requested.
I am relieved you like it.
We can…
Excuse me, did you have an appointment
to see the property?
I’m only available to be here
for the next 20 minutes.
Oh?
Why did Mom suddenly
want to sell this house?
That would be too bad.
Maybe I should buy it.
It’s full of memories.
I’m not sure what you mean, sir.
The owner of this house is a foreigner
who has returned to Denmark.
I think there’s been a misunderstanding.
Hold on.
Ma’am, sir, excuse me for a minute.
Look.
I don’t think this house belongs
to your partner’s family.
This house… it’s often rented out
to con artists to scam people.
That’s not true.
The house is full of my boyfriend’s stuff.
ISSARA PREECHAJIT
They haven’t taken anything much
from you, I hope?
Oh!
Hey!
Oh, you’re all here.
Did something happe—
I know the truth!
North.
What are you talking about?
I went to that house today.
The real estate agent told me everything.
North.
I— I can explain.
Go on.
I can’t wait to hear
what the hell all this was about.
Well?
WOMAN SCAMMED BY
HANDSOME CON MAN
You’re going to jail.
Nana.
Yes?
Call the police.
Nana, hold on.
If this makes headlines,
things could blow up in our faces.
I don’t care.
I’m making sure he’s going to prison.
You need to get a divorce right away.
Right now.
But it is past district offices’ working hours.
Go and wait outside their building!
No.
I don’t want a divorce.
I love North.
North, you have to believe me.
I really do love you.
I’m not lying.
Who’d be stupid enough to believe you?
You have the audacity to say that now?
Pai!
Sir, no!
Pai, calm down!
- Sir, please let go!
- Calm down!
- Please let go.
- Pai, stop this.
Calm down!
Now call the police.
But if we do and your family finds out,
you will be in trouble, sir.
Can we pay the press to keep quiet?
I’ll check.
Pai, you know…
We won’t be able to press any charges
without evidence anyway.
The only way to hold him accountable
is to sue him.
Nana.
Yes?
Get me an attorney.
I don’t want anyone my family knows.
Yes, sir.
But this will take a while since
your family knows all the best lawyers.
North.
Gather evidence.
Yes, Pai.
I don’t know if
I’ll be able to find any, though.
North.
Please let me explain.
Keep your excuses for the court.
Pai.
Let’s call it a day.
I’m tired.
Please. I just want to be alone.
But what will we do with him?
Tied him up here until the police get here?
Can we at least have him locked up
at the police precinct?
I’m not going anywhere, Mr. Pai.
I’m staying right here with North
until we’re through with this.
What right do you have to do that?
I do, though, legally, too.
Legally speaking,
the ones who are trespassing are us, sir.
Damn it!
The thief is sitting right in front of us
but we can’t do anything?
What do I have to do
for you to listen to me?
There’s nothing you can do
for me to give you a second chance.
Can I talk to North alone?
How can I be sure you won’t hurt him?
I would never hurt North—
I don’t believe you!
Stop it, all of you!
Get out of here.
Let me talk to him alone.
Pai.
This is a sensitive matter.
I think we should
give North some room to think.
What if he runs away or hurts North?
How about this?
There’s a camera in this teddy.
Please forgive me.
Excuse me.
I found it!
Face scan, please.
I’ve downloaded a tracking app
on this phone, sir.
We will be notified wherever he goes.
Can you let me talk to North now?
Don’t cave in, North.
Yes, Pai.
At least this is better than U getting away.
I must come across like such a fool to you.
I admit I used to be a con artist.
But I quit, North.
Because of you, I realized
I don’t want to do that anymore.
I’m serious.
Come on.
I don’t think I can trust you anymore.
Go away.
I’d rather we stay out of
each other’s way from now on.
I’m not going.
I’ll do whatever it takes
for you to believe me.
Go on and slap me if you’re so mad at me,
but I’m not going anywhere.
You slapped me!
Well, you told me to!
Oh, was that a lie as well?
How can I even trust you again?
Sit down.
Sit back down!
North.
I wasn’t lying—
Stay put!
Hold on, North.
I thought you were letting me go?
Crap!
You’re finally awake.
I’m going to have breakfast.
Oh?
What about me?
I can’t let you run away,
but then I can’t trust you if you stay.
What a headache!
Should I just take you to an animal hospital
and get you a microchip?
What vet would agree to do that?
How about this?
If you’re so afraid I’d run,
take me with you everywhere.
I’m okay with that.
Alright?
Stay where I can see you.
Don’t talk to me.
Don’t bother me.
Yes.
I’m going to sue the hell out of him.
I’ll make sure he has no place
in the world after this.
Good morning, Mr. Pai, Mr. Tim.
How was it?
Is everything okay?
Do we still have eye on U?
Mr. U shows no sign of running away, sir.
I have my eye on him at all times.
As for the shooting instructor,
I’ve found you one.
Shooting?
Yes.
Your schedule is currently full,
though, Mr. Pai.
What about Saturday morning?
Aren’t you and Mr. Tim going to a district
office for your marriage registration?
That’s right.
I’m sorry.
I’m so preoccupied with this matter
with North that I forgot.
It’s okay.
I understand.
We’re not in a rush anyway.
Well, cancel that, then.
I want to learn how to use a gun
as soon as possible.
Of course, sir.
All of these were given as gratuitous gifts,
as evidential on our Instagram posts.
I’m good to go.
He’s learning how to use a gun
just because his cousin gets scammed.
If he finds out he’s in the same boat,
I’m gonna be dead on the spot.
Can this get any worse?
Hello, Mr. Prasit.
You look amazing.
Hello, sir.
It’s been a while, Tim.
Oh, I’ve just been busy.
You gotta make time to pay back
what you owe me, kid.
I’m sorry.
Everything okay with you?
I’m kinda in a pinch lately
and I thought maybe you can give me
just a little more time.
Of course. Time, I can give you.
I don’t recommend you
disappearing on me, though.
You’ve been doing so well
at clearing your debt.
Right.
I’m definitely not going anywhere—
I’m just tying my shoe laces, sir.
Don’t worry.
Not a thing to worry about, sir.
My plan is coming along nicely.
All I ask is that you are
a little patient with me, sir.
Thank you.
I thought we’re done talking?
Can I go?
Please.
Right.
I’m really sorry, sir.
Bye.
Pai.
Oh, that…
I didn’t know
people still send hard copy invitations.
Exactly what I was thinking.
Who even does that anymore?
Where were you today?
Why is your bag so bulky?
Oh, I went to the gym.
How come you’re home early today?
Nana found me a lawyer.
I hurried home to deal with this matter.
Good job, Nana. Good job.
I’m gonna go unpack in the bedroom.
Stay here, Pai.
I’ll go with you.
You seem tense, baby.
Is everything alright?
Oh…
You can be honest with me, Tim.
Are you…
Mad at me?
What?
You were chopping your words and then
barging in here to get away from me.
Something just feels wrong.
What are you mad at me about?
Oh.
It’s…
You’ve been very busy and tense lately.
We barely had any alone time at all.
You’re right.
I’m sorry.
Can you forgive me?
We have 40 minutes until the appointment.
Alright.
What am I, a dog?
Thanks.
Yes, Pai?
Everything’s okay.
U is still here.
Look.
Good.
See me at the meeting room
in the common area in 10 minutes.
I got us a lawyer.
Yes, Pai.
Baby?
Pai got us a lawyer.
You’re dead meat, U.
Hello.
My name is Prem.
I’m U’s lawyer.
TWO HOURS PRIOR
YOU KNOW WHO IS BAD
(Here’s the contact of the lawyer I know.)
(I told him about you.)
(He’s going to take the job.)
(Delete this chat after you read it.)
Let’s begin.
Pai, there’s this guy—
North, don’t interrupt.
From what I was told,
I think we can sue him for fraud.
Does that mean we can
take legal actions right away?
Yes.
However, this will likely become a scandal.
Once we gather enough evidence,
please proceed right away.
Between fame and revenge,
I prefer the latter.
Allow me a question, sir.
You want to sue him for fraud.
On what ground are you accusing him?
My name is Prem.
I am Mr. U’s lawyer.
That’s what I was trying to tell you, Pai.
He’s a con artist who coaxed
my cousin into marrying him.
That should be enough to put him in jail.
If it is that easy,
there would be no need
for four years of law school.
Hey.
Your cousin was the one who proposed.
My client explicitly told him that he did not come from a wealthy background,
to which your cousin said he did not mind.
Which means that my client had no intention of deception from the beginning.
I think renting a fake house
was pretty intentional.
But that is not fraud.
My client did not demand
anything from doing so,
except the peace of mind of his husband
and his husband’s family.
It is a fraud.
Because he knew that if he impressed me,
he would be one step closer to
claiming Empire’s money.
Is there any evidence of
Mr. U’s intention in that regard?
I’m not sure.
But I don’t think there is…
Mr. North.
Please refrain from answering.
Wait.
U took 250 million from me.
That’s evidence.
- What?
- What!
What did you say?
I wrote him a check.
Mr. North.
Did my client specifically ask you
to give him 250 million?
Mr. North, do not say anything.
Right.
I will explain in his place.
When he was proposed to,
my client turned Mr. North down.
His reason was that
their social statuses were too different.
Your cousin, then, offered this 250 million
by way of leveling their statuses
in order to convince U to marry him.
North!
Can we stop?
I can’t listen to this anymore.
Of course we can.
This is a waste of time, anyway.
If you agree to settle,
we’ll immediately drop this matter.
No!
I insist on pressing charges.
My client finally agreed
to enter into this civil contract.
He has lived with his husband ever since
with no sign of running away.
Would you say that is a fraudulent action?
If we can’t sue him for fraud,
we’ll sue him for divorce.
Are we… done talking?
Done talking?
We haven’t even started.
I think it was the right decision
to fall back for a consultation, Mr. Pai.
That attorney—
I freaking hate his guts!
U dared pull this stunt because
he had connections with such a lawyer.
Anyone who’s friends with that lawyer
must be a dirtbag!
Excuse me.
That went down the wrong pipe.
Please go on.
Dirtbag, alright.
As for suing for divorce,
the legal grounds for that include adultery, insanity, misconduct, incurable disease,
or physical disability that prevents the couple from fulfilling married life.
Misconduct!
He definitely has done that.
In that case, his misconduct must
already have an effect on Mr. North.
Are you saying there has to be a scandal that causes our family financial loss
or defamation before we can sue him?
Yes.
The easier way out would be to both agree
to file for an uncontested divorce.
However, reclaiming back
the 250 million would be—
Ugh!
Just let him have it!
No.
Letting him fool us and walk away free
with 250 million in his pocket?
Only in his dreams.
What do you want me to do?
There’s nothing we can sue him for.
Mr. Juean.
What does my cousin have to do
to get his money back?
Negotiate with the other party
to agree to an uncontested divorce,
and have him write a contract to return
the money after the proceedings.
But… I don’t think they will agree.
North.
We need to talk.
All of you can go home.
That’s it for today.
North!
I’m coming!
Let’s go talk somewhere else.
Did the housekeeper
forget to come in today?
Come on.
Your bed is a mess. Oh, sh—
Pai, you’re not allowed
to scold me anymore.
I can’t take anything else today.
If you scold me, even one word,
I’m going to run off and become a monk!
North, a monk has to
wake up at 4 in the morning,
live without air-conditioning units,
and eat only until lunch.
You can’t even stick to
an intermittent fasting program.
If he wants to play this game,
we’ll play, too.
And we’ll win.
Game?
What do you mean?
Convince him to get a divorce
and give you back everything.
I must ask you to do three things.
Do not believe a word
that comes out of his mouth.
Second,
do not let anyone
know about this.
Third…
Do not fall in love with him again.
I can do that… probably.
We won’t let him have anything.
I’m sorry, Pai.
I didn’t think a sheet of paper
like a marriage certificate
would be such a big deal.
WHAT TO KNOW
BEFORE YOU SAY “I DO”
MARITAL PROPERTY
PROPERTY ACQUIRED DURING A MARRIAGE IS SHARED EQUALLY BETWEEN PARTNERS.
YOUR OWN KIND OF DIVORCE
Hello, Nana.
You didn’t sleep well?
You seem tired.
Baby.
Is there anything you want right now?
Something like watches, cars, or a condo.
What would I need them for?
I already have them.
Why are you asking?
Are you trying to make up
for something you did?
Come on.
Talk to me.
What happened?
I…
I don’t want to get married anymore.
If we’re legally married,
it’ll be harder to manage our assets.
And it will be even harder for me
since my assets are tied to Empire’s.
You’re worried because of what happened
with U and North, aren’t you?
It’s not that I don’t trust you, baby.
I just need time to sort out my assets first.
So that was it.
You scared me for a second.
I thought you were breaking up with me.
You’re not mad at me?
I’m not.
When do I ever disagree with you?
I’m alright as long as we’re together.
eally?
Come on here.
Look at your face.
If you’re going to stay here,
this is how we live.
If you can’t live like this,
then go ahead and divorce me.
I’m more than ready.
I’m staying because
there is no need for me to run away.
You’re not running away because
you don’t want to be sued for fraud.
No.
It’s because I love you.
I don’t believe you!
If you stay, I’ll make sure every day
is a living hell for you.
You’ll beg for divorce and for your life!
I’m so scared.
I get chills down my spine.
I’m gonna cry.
Scared, are you?
You’re so great, huh?
Thanks, North.
You threw me these pillows because
you’re worried about me,
aren’t you?
Worried? As if!
Someone’s in denial.
North.
I need to pee.
♪ Why must it be me who hurts ♪
♪ For loving you ♪
Stop right there!
What do you think you’re doing?
Get back in there.
♪ Why must it be me ♪
♪ It’s a lie ♪
♪ Why do I feel like I’m about to die ♪
♪ For loving you ♪
♪ …who cries ♪
♪ I heard love’s good for the heart ♪
♪ For loving you ♪
What are you doing?
It’s me who has to ask you that.
I’m not doing anything.
“Playing with a dog
will get your lips licked.”
You heard of that?
Who’s playing with you?
Not me.
North.
Stop. Stop right there.
Stop.
Okay.
Stop it, North. Stop.
Don’t be swayed.
Don’t cave in.
Hey!
I told you to stop!
How did you get out of there?
I sneaked out.
I have to be back soon
before North finds out.
You’re freaking annoying, you know that?
You got everything you wanted
and got away with it.
Meanwhile, I did everything right and my
plan still went sideways because of you!
Hey.
Your target is as vicious as a dog.
You can’t blame me for that!
If he and I don’t get married legally,
I will have done all this for nothing.
Then you have to do whatever it takes for
Mr. Pai to sign that marriage certificate.
And how do I do that?
Enlighten me, Mr. Amazing.
There are actually a few reasons
why people get legally married.
There are certain rights only
the spouse or family can exercise.
We still see a decrease in tourist number
within this trimester.
We have come up with campaigns and
had collaborations with different banks
to ensure more credit card privileges.
Ugh.
Your phone keeps ringing,
did someone die?
Excuse me.
(Hello.)
(Are you
Mr. Thanin Chaiyanuwat’s family?)
Yes.
Did something happen?
(Mr. Thanin was in a car accident.)
What?
What did you just say?
Please, be careful.
Baby.
Pai.
I’m sorry.
Are you in pain?
What did the doctor say?
Is it serious?
You ask more questions than the doctor.
What exactly happened?
TWO HOURS PRIOR
(The main reason
people get legally married)
(is the right to decide
during medical emergencies.)
Medical emergencies…
How hard can it be?
Crashing at 30 km/h
will only dent the bumper.
For it to be an emergency, I gotta go at 60!
Come on!
Who the hell would do that!
Oh, shit!
Someone bumped into the back of my car
and I swerved off the road into a tree.
But the doctor said it’s nothing serious.
I thought I’d never see you again.
Don’t say that.
Are you in pain?
I’d love to act cool and tell you I’m not,
but…
It hurts.
Pai, be gentle!
Don’t you have to go back to work?
I’m troubling you, aren’t I?
You were in a car crash.
I don’t care about anything else.
It feels nice to have someone
take care of me when I’m not alright.
You know…
I’ve never been more scared of anything.
When I was on my way to the hospital,
I couldn’t even cry.
It was reasonably scary.
You’re my whole world, Tim.
I don’t know how I’d live without you.
I’m so glad I’m still alive.
When you’re all recovered,
let’s get married at the district office.
You changed your mind?
We’ve planned to do
a lot of things together,
let’s start now.
How do I win a divorce case?
Popular legal grounds for divorce sustained by court include:
sexual affair from either party or bigamy,
in which case usually successfullyresult in divorce given enough evidence,
such as chats, photos, videos, cohabitation, or children.
Too difficult.
Give me something easier.
Come on in. Come on in.
What are you doing?
Why are you looking into that?
I want to divorce U.
What?
Divorce?
When did you even get married?
It’s a long story.
I’ll tell you later.
But right now, I want a divorce!
You want a divorce.
Was it like, you were drunk,
and got married in Las Vegas?
Was it like that?
Something like that.
But he refuses to get a divorce.
Or… You can use me.
What?
Oh.
Are you here to see North?
Yes.
Can I wait inside?
North will probably be home late.
Of course.
(He told me…)
(I need to make you like me.)
(When did you do that?)
(I didn’t see it.)
(How can I find time to do it?)
(Use me to fake an affair.)
You can use this as evidence to sue him.
Oh, this is so scary!
What is?
We’re not watching a horror film.
I’m scared of the dark.
The dark?
Should we change the channel?
Something like a seahorse documentary?
What do you think?
Let’s watch this.
It’s fun.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
I’m your best friend’s boyfriend!
Don’t you care about North at all?
Shhh.
If we both stay quiet,
nobody has to get hurt.
Get away from me!
I’m faithful to North.
He’s the only man I love.
Don’t worry about North.
He handed you down to me.
North won’t be mad at you.
Stop!
That’s enough, Pure.
Why are you interrupting me?
We almost got it!
Why did you have to stop me?
North, North.
Get a grip, dude.
You’re hurting me.
Crap.
I’m sorry.
Are you upset because you still love him?
No.
Why don’t you work things out with
the Inside Out in your head first?
Do you even want to get a divorce?
Of course, I do.
North.
You’re not someone who
ignores his own emotions.
This is probably the first time.
It’s only normal that
you find it difficult to do.
I want a divorce, but he doesn’t.
He wants my money.
Really?
But the look on his face when I told him you gave him away was really sad.
He handed you down to me.
What?
What did you say?
North and I always do this
when it comes to something
we think is disposable.
You don’t have to worry.
North won’t be mad at you.
What were you trying to do?
That’s my business.
It is your business,
but it almost became mine.
If you were just a little bit too late,
I would have—
What?
If I was too late,
what would have happened?
What would have happened, I wonder,
if you didn’t come in…
North!
Are you really mad at me?
What the hell?
This was his idea.
North!
So here you are.
Stop.
Don’t go.
I’m the one who should be mad at you.
I’m not mad.
I want a divorce.
North.
Why are you doing this?
Did you really give me away?
Or were you just trying to fake evidence?
Which case do you want it to be?
The latter.
The former would break my heart.
Will you just stop lying to me?
I stopped trusting you a long time ago.
I haven’t been lying for a long time now.
You know everything
that happened was real.
North.
Will you please talk to me?
I don’t know what I’m feeling.
My head is a mess.
I don’t even know if I still love you.
Well, shall we find out?
The dishes we’ll be serving today
are the samples of the dishes
you chose for the wedding, sirs.
Right.
Allow us some time to consult.
I’ll let you know through Nana
what we think.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Baby.
Is everything okay?
I was butting heads with Aunt Kia
before I came here.
About what?
About leaving work to take care of you.
She called me irresponsible and unable
to separate work from my private life.
She kept saying
I was wasting everyone’s time.
I’m sorry for putting you through that.
When money and profit are at stake,
no one cares that I am
just a human being with feelings.
I don’t want to live like this anymore.
I want to step down
from my role at Empire.
What?
Maybe we can start
a gated community project.
You’re an architect, after all.
Let’s make something of ourselves.
But—
Please?
I can’t keep living like this.
I just want to be with you, Tim.
Listen to me, U.
You gotta do what he wants deep down
without his asking.
I’ll do everything in my power for you
to fall in love with me again.
Where did you get all these ideas?
I just… watch and learn.
Stop it, you!
Do you remember Kuea, baby?
My name is Kuea.
I’m Pai’s friend.
I’m Tim.
His boyfriend.
What’s wrong with you?
Nothing.
Are you jealous?
Let’s start a family.