Bro
You skipped school last week
Were you scared to see Keiko
Eat, kids shouldn't worry about these things
I'm sorry
If you want me to apologize to Keiko
I will
Do you really
Not like Keiko
I just don't like you being nice to other people
Bro
Will you always take care of me
Of course
Then I'll go apologize to her
And explain things clearly
Forget it
No need
Dating
Breaking up and getting back together is normal
This matter
I'll handle it myself
You need to focus
On your studies
Um
Yutong
Hey, Keiko
You look really pretty today
You asked me to meet you today just to compliment me
That underwear
Was my prank
Why
Here
This is
Do you know
The story of The Nightingale and the Rose
Read this diary when you have time
Okay, sure
Bye
How should I refer to him
As my brother
Or my...
It's him, he has this awesome move that's super cool
Hey, this one
But
I don't seem to want him to be my brother
Hey, which person are you interested in
Ah
Oh, this one, this one
Hold it up, don't get it wet
He always gives me the best
He thinks it's family love
But I think
This should be what romantic love looks like
Haoman
Keiko, why are you here
I came to see you
To see how you're doing
You must be tired, let's take a break
Um
Let's go
Being an older brother must be really hard
Why do you ask
Your parents aren't around
You have to handle so many things on your own
It's alright
I'm used to it
You know
Actually, in my eyes
You're still a little brother who needs to be taken care of
Haoman, I'm starting to really like you
What about before
I liked you before too
Now, how do you say it in Chinese
Admiration
Haoman, ah
From now on, let me share the burden with you
Um
Quick, make a wish, make a wish