Hey
Ah
You silly kid, where did your wish fly off to
All the way to the clouds
No way
You took so long
What did you wish for
Mm
I can't tell you
You little smartass
Since it's your birthday, let's have some mochi
Okay
Come on, try it
See if it tastes like my dad used to make
Mm, it's so good
Hey, how's your dad doing lately
I don't really know
He won't say anything when I ask
But your mom seems serious this time
She might really leave him
Wait
Or
Why don't you talk to your mom
I just feel so awkward
I used to call him dad, now what, do I call him uncle
I don't get it
At their age, acting like they're playing house
It makes things awkward for us too
No matter what happens between them
Remember, I'll always be your brother
Yeah, bro
Oh
Open it up
This is
Wow
Remember last time when you saw these
And couldn't move your feet
Bro
You've been working part-time all last month
Just to buy these for me
Happy birthday
Quick
Thank you, bro
Come on
Eat up
Okay
You eat too, bro
Mm
Oh man, bad timing, you're taking a bath again
Bro's so sweaty, I really can't stand it
Sorry about this
It's okay, bro
We've always bathed together since we were kids
Yeah, as long as you don't mind
I don't mind, take your time, it's fine
Mm
Ah
Oh
Mm
What's wrong
Didn't you just say you don't mind
Stop it
Wait
Bro's is pretty big, right
Mm
Yeah, really big
Don't worry
Once you get to college, yours will be as big as mine
I don't want to be like you
You need to be like me
Exercise more to stay healthy
Stop getting sick all the time
And also
You gotta exercise
Get good at sports
Then girls will want to date you, you know
Tch
Lots of girls are chasing after me
Yeah yeah yeah, you're the best
Wait
Ah
Oh
Hey, scrub my back for me
Hmph, I thought you were so capable
But you still need me to scrub your back
Yeah yeah yeah, my good little brother, I can't do without you
Without you, even taking a bath is hard
Hurry up
Well, I guess so
Put more strength into it
Oh
What's wrong
Ah
Oh, it's nothing
Put more strength into it
Oh