Given that parabola is C
Y to the power of 4 equals 4X
Focus at F
There's a circle with radius 1
Then line i
Are you even listening seriously
I am listening
Listening?
Why do you keep making mistakes on such simple problems
Bro
If I can't get into university
What should I do
Like my dad said, you won't find a job
If I can't make money in the future
Will you take care of me
Of course I will, what kind of silly question is that
Ugh, studying is so tiring
I don't want to study anymore
I want to stay by your side forever
Be more serious
Studying isn't something to take lightly
Then what can be taken lightly
I'm getting angry
Alright, alright
I'll study seriously
Well, I guess so
Study hard, even if you can't get into university
I'll always take care of you
Mm
Time to get up
To-today is weekend
Even on weekends you should get up
It's almost 8 o'clock
I think Keiko is really great
I plan to
Keep dating her
But
I'll always be
Your brother
I know
You probably
Don't like Keiko
But I hope
You can accept this
What
Are you not feeling well lately
My brother's still studying
My dad and his mom aren't here
As his brother, I need to supervise his studies
We shouldn't disturb him
Oh
You're so thoughtful
Then we could go stay somewhere else
Can't do that
Tomorrow morning I need to make him breakfast
If he studies late
I need to make him a late-night snack too
Keiko, I'm sorry
Why are you apologizing
You brothers have such a deep bond
No need to apologize
Mm
Let's rest early
It's ready, Yutong
Eat while it's hot
Thank you
Um
My brother's clothes
I've always been the one doing his laundry
Ah
It's okay, your brother told me you're busy with studying
Don't let these things distract you
Oh
Yutong, can I ask you something
Sure
Your brother
Has he brought other girls home recently
Mm
That's my brother's privacy
I can't say
I'm home
Oh, Keiko
What's wrong, give me a hug
Bro
Will you scold me