Wow, Haoman, happy birthday
Quick, make a wish, make a wish
Blow out the candles
Birthday present, open it
You should really thank the piggy bank for this
Bro, so you like these shoes too
Mm
Yeah
Haoman passed by the mall several times but never bought them
These are Haoman's favorite shoes
Keiko
Thank you
Yeah
Keiko
Don't mention it
We're family, right
Let's eat cake anyway
Eat cake, eat cake
I want this piece
Eat the strawberry
What are you doing
Bro
Keiko seems to really understand you
Why do you say that
I never knew
That you also liked those shoes
These are just small things
Just like when we were little
Back then you said you didn't like meat
You always gave me your meat
But later I heard from your friends
That you actually loved meat the most
I'm your brother
Bro
You should treat Keiko well
I think
She's really good for you
Oh
I forgot to mention
My mom went back to China
I'm planning to go back to find my mom
And also
I've applied to universities in China
Such a big thing
Why didn't you tell me beforehand
Bro
I've already made up my mind
And Keiko is really wonderful
With her taking care of you
I can rest easy
Bro
Can you hold me
You have to be happy
Bro
Bro, you're awake
Haoman
Haoman, you're awake, come have breakfast
If you miss him that much
Go see him off
If you leave now, you can still make it
I
I'm afraid
Even if I see him, I don't know what to say
Do you love him
Since we were little
I just couldn't stand to see him hurt
Isn't that love
I think
It's still brotherly love
Yutong seems immature
But he really cares about how you feel
He came to apologize to me
Hoping I would come back to you
And also
The fact that you like those shoes
He's the one who told me
I'm sure he really wants to see you at the airport right now
Because just like me
We both love you
Bro
You have to be happy
I want to stay by your side forever