Wake up
Lazy brother, time for school
Mm
Quick
You're up so early
I got up to make breakfast
You're so sweet
What did you make for me
Uh
It's not for you, it's for my brother
Oh, so it's not for me
He has to go to school
What's wrong
Are you hungry
Mm
I'm hungry
Then I'll go make some for you
Wait
Haoman
You are my breakfast
What's wrong
Not hungry anymore
Hungry
So hungry
Bro
Can you not let Keiko
Stay overnight at home
Why
She
She walks around in her underwear
And this is our home
She just touches things in the fridge
And drinks my protein powder
These are all small things
I'll remind her
And also
You two, aren't you being too loud
It's really awkward
I thought you were experienced
Hey, didn't you say
Lots of girls at school go on dates with you
I
Turns out
You were lying
I'm not eating
Mad now
Okay, we disturbed your studying
I'll keep it down from now on, okay
No
My good little brother
Why are you so angry
I
I'm just angry
Alright, silly brother
Bro
I don't want you to have a girlfriend
Why
Having a girlfriend is normal
You'll have a girlfriend someday too
Because
You can only belong to me
Are you crazy
I'm your brother
When my mom married your dad
He was already her third husband
She never cared about how I felt
I was timid
When I was little, I was scared to go home alone after school
It was you
You always
Took the long way around to walk home with me
That was the first time I felt safe
I'm your brother
We're not even related by blood
I think of you as my real brother
Bro
Unless you tell me clearly
That you don't care about me at all
In your heart
I don't have even the slightest place
Then I'll completely give up
Bro, tell me
Tell me you don't care about me at all
It's not the same
Understand