Bro
Can I sleep with you
I'm a little scared
What's wrong, did you have a nightmare again
Mm
Come here
Cover up properly
Mm
Bro
Can you tell me a story
Like when we were little
Why, you're not a kid anymore
I want you to tell me one
Alright then
The Nightingale and the Rose
Mm
She said if I bring her a red rose
She will dance with me
Cried the young student
But where in my garden is there a red rose
The nightingale heard this from her nest in the oak tree
She looked out from the leaves
And wondered
There are no red roses in my garden
The student's beautiful eyes were already filled with tears
To attain happiness
Depends on such a small thing
I have read all the writings of the wise
And all the secrets of philosophy are known to me
Yet my life
Because I cannot find a single red rose
Has become so miserable
Here is a true lover at last
Said the nightingale
Although
I do not know him
I will sing for him every night
Every night I will tell his story to the stars
Now
I have finally met this lover
His hair is as vibrant as hyacinth flowers
His lips are red
Like the rose he desires to obtain
But intense passion
Has made his face pale and wan
Sorrow is also etched between his brows
The prince is giving a ball tomorrow evening
Said the student
My beloved
Will be going
If I bring her a red rose
She will dance with me until dawn
I can
Hold her in my arms
Let her head
Rest upon my shoulder
Her hands clasped in mine
But I cannot find a red rose in my garden
I will just sit there lonely
Watching her pass by me
But she won't notice me
And my heart will break
You're Yutong's guardian, right
Yes, teacher
Yutong's grades have been dropping rapidly lately
And I've noticed what's on his mind
What is it
Do you know the story of The Nightingale and the Rose
I do
Isn't that a love story
I understand, but did you know
Only male nightingales sing
Hello
Who are you
I'm your brother's classmate
I'm here to study language with him
Oh
Keiko
Haoman
Why did you come today
Is there any difference between today and tomorrow
I want to study Chinese now
Hehe
Ah
Keiko is second generation
Her Chinese isn't good
She comes to practice with me
It's okay, bro
Keiko, let's talk in the room
Okay
Watch the step
Mm
Haoman
Wasn't it supposed to be the day after tomorrow
But you said to come earlier
I am your destiny
You mean
You are my destiny, right
Yes yes
That's it
You are my destiny
Haoman
Ah
Oh my god
No
Ah
Haoman
Stop
Ah
Haoman
No, no
Ah, Haoman, ah
She really came to study languages
Haoman
Stop