Everything's been cleaned up?
Yes.
We went to all that trouble
staging that assassination,
yet we still got nothing out of her.
"Still got nothing out of her?"
You mean
you still believe Chu is only pretending
to have lost her memory?
Your Majesty,
I'm just worried
that even if Lady Chu doesn't
remember now,
something might
trigger her memories one day.
If she remembers
after she's already become
the Queen of our Great Yan,
it would be a disaster
for Your Majesty and the state.
What more do you want?
Kill her
to eliminate the threat at its root?
Your Majesty,
everything I've done...
Enough!
This ends here.
Su.
The Queen has awakened not long ago
and has lost most of her memory.
You should know
what can
and cannot be said.
I understand.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 2]
Waiting here for me so late...
What's so important?
Your idea was completely useless.
After all that trouble—
disguising ourselves as Moon Guards
to stage an assassination
and even using a fake corpse of Zhuge Yue—
Chu Qiao didn't reveal a single flaw.
I'm afraid she has truly
lost her memory this time.
If she truly remembers nothing,
you should count yourself lucky,
General Cheng.
If Chu Qiao remembered how you
used her to kill Zhuge Yue
and wipe out her Xiuli Army,
given her personality,
you would've had a hard time
in the army, wouldn't you?
If she truly remembers nothing,
she'll soon marry Yan Xun.
Lady Helian, wouldn't your Helian Tribe
and your ambition
to be the Queen of Great Yan...
all be in vain?
General Cheng, you asked me
to come so late.
Surely it wasn't just to mock me, right?
[Helian Ling,
Lady-in-Waiting of Great Yan]
Tell me,
what do you want?
I was just thinking
that her old friends,
those people
in the Universal Harmony Guild,
probably wouldn't want her to
return to Great Yan and become queen
any more than we do.
My movements within the army
are restricted.
So, I'll have to
trouble you to make a trip
for some matters, Lady Helian.
Elders of the tribes,
so you would rather stand by
and watch General Huan
and my 20,000 Black Eagle Army soldiers
die at Meilin Pass
than send reinforcements?
[Great Yan-Great Yong Battlefield]
[General Huan Huan, Chief of
the Snowy Region Tribe of Great Yan]
Your Majesty,
[Elder Gelin, Chief of the Gelin Tribe
of Great Yan]
today, not only will my Gelin Tribe
not send troops,
but the Lanchuan Tribe
and the Hongchuan Tribe here
will not send troops either.
Our cavalry is
meant to protect
the people and land of Great Yan,
not to be used by the Yan family
to settle personal vendettas!
General Huan,
General Cheng is here!
General Cheng is here with reinforcements!
If the Black Eagle Army and General Huan
die at Meilin Pass because of this,
then the person who killed them
is not this old man—
but Your Majesty!
General Cheng,
how many men did you bring?
None of the tribes are willing to
send reinforcements, are they?
Except for the main force
of the Black Eagle Army
and the warriors of
our Snowy Region Tribe,
His Majesty has no more troops,
right?
Here's His Majesty's written order.
Take a look.
[Great Yong's provisions have arrived
in Yunbi. Gather a unit at once.]
Yunbi?
The Yong Army's provisions
have just arrived at Yunbi?
Does His Majesty intend to...
Your Highness,
Yan Xun has launched a surprise attack
and burned our granary!
[Zhao Che, Seventh Prince of Great Yong]
We...
We've fallen into a trap!
Seventh Prince,
at this point...
stop your futile resistance!
Soldiers!
The Yan Army has burned our provisions.
There's no way back for us now.
Either we cut Yan Xun down—
or we become lambs to the slaughter!
You're mistaken, Seventh Prince.
You have one way left.
That's surrender to my Great Yan!
Father once believed
that you wolf whelp had truly submitted.
Yet you repaid us
by slaughtering Zhenhuang City.
Zhuge Yue treated you as a brother,
and now he has died without a grave!
I never said
there would be a day of reconciliation
between my state and yours!
I just want the soldiers of your state
to see clearly—
your Seventh Prince, Zhao Che,
is leading the army out here,
while your Thirteenth Prince, Zhao Yang,
fearing he will steal the glory,
deliberately delayed
the delivery of supplies,
driving you into this desperate situation!
And your Emperor is
even more foolish and incompetent,
allowing all of this...
with no regard for your lives!
Zhao Che,
I gave you a chance today.
Since you insist on having your own way,
don't blame me
for disregarding our past friendship!
Yan Xun,
it is you who insists on this path!
Soldiers,
form ranks!
Go back and tell your Emperor
everything he's done to me, Yan Xun,
and to Great Yan—
I will make him pay a thousandfold!
Your Majesty,
why not kill him
while we have such a good chance?
We're letting a dangerous enemy go free.
Their granary has been burned.
Their defeat is sealed.
Sending him back to fight Zhao Yang
is far more useful
than killing him.
Your Majesty,
are you alright?
They all say
I used to lead troops into battle
and kill countless enemies,
yet why do I have
no martial skills whatsoever?
You haven't fully recovered yet,
so don't be impatient.
Besides, His Majesty said
that once this war is over,
he will take you back
to the Capital for the wedding.
By then,
you'll be the rightful Queen of Great Yan,
and you won't need to
go into battle anymore.
So I'm just supposed to become
a useless woman
who can't even lift a sword?
Back when His Majesty was trapped
in Zhenhuang City,
you were the only one who protected him,
escorting him
all the way out of Great Yong
and back to Great Yan.
And after returning,
it was also you who helped him
reclaim the tribes here
and unite the land.
How could you call yourself useless?
All those things...
How do you know about them?
Those things...
Everyone knows about those things.
Everyone says so?
But I remember none of it.
Instead, there are a few things
that make me suspicious.
Since I was once a slave of Great Yong,
who taught me my martial arts?
With such a humble background,
how did I ever get the chance
to help the former Heir Apparent
of Great Yan
rebel against the Emperor of Great Yong
and even
pledge ourselves to each other for life?
Lady Chu!
Lady Chu,
His Majesty has ordered
you to return to the itinerant court
in the Capital immediately
to recover.
The Capital?
Where is Yan Xun?
The battle is at a critical point.
His Majesty is leading troops
against the Great Yong forces
and cannot personally look after you.
This is all very sudden,
so you'll have to bear with it.
Your Majesty.
Chu,
we've repelled the Yong Army.
Within three days, they will withdraw.
Your Majesty.
Where is Chu?
Miss Chu...
Your Majesty,
with you away at war
and the camp crowded and chaotic,
and since Lady Chu has just recovered,
I've already had people ahead
to escort her back to the itinerant court.
When did I give the order
to send her away?
Your Majesty,
the itinerant court
has the best physicians
to help her recuperate.
Cheng Yuan...
I know what you're thinking,
but you should also know
what I'm thinking.
I don't care how much
you and Chu dislike each other,
or what position you are in
to worry about me—
I'm warning you:
don't do anything to her.
If anything happens to her,
I will never forgive you.
Guards,
go find Chu and bring her back to me!
Yes!
It's getting late.
Are we going to keep traveling?
General Cheng has ordered
that, to prevent any accidents
on the road,
we must rush to
the itinerant court overnight.
Sorry for the hardship, Your Majesty.
Thank you, General.
A sandstorm is coming!
Who exactly are you?
Why are you kidnapping me?
It's...
U-Universal Harmony Guild's arrows.
Quick, g-go report to General Cheng.
Your Majesty.
Where are they?
They should have fled in that direction.
After them!
Miss Chu!
What happened to your martial arts skills?
Who are you?
You recognize me?
You don't remember me?
[Zhong Yu; Universal Harmony Guild]
I'm Zhong Yu.
You wrote to me,
telling me you'd woken up
and didn't want to marry Yan Xun.
You asked me to bring our men from
the Universal Harmony Guild to rescue you.
I wrote to you?
I never wrote any letters,
and I don't know you at all.
Also...
why wouldn't I want to marry Yan Xun?
Miss Chu, have you forgotten it all?
Our Universal Harmony Guild
has always stood for justice
for the people,
hoping one day to achieve a world
of universal harmony.
But Yan Xun—
he's been trying to
wipe us out completely.
And the Xiuli Army.
To seize full military power,
he ordered your Southwest Xiuli Army
to attack Meilin Pass.
Facing Great Yong's 100,000 troops,
your Xiuli Army was nearly
completely wiped out,
and He Xiao died in battle!
All of that happened
before you fell into your coma.
Don't you remember?
Everything you're telling me...
I don't remember any of it.
Why should I believe you?
What proof do you have?
What about Zhuge Yue?
Yan Xun used you to ambush Zhuge Yue.
Do you know Zhuge Yue died in battle
because of you?
And it was to save Zhuge Yue
that you jumped into the frozen lake.
Used me?
You remnants
of the rebel Universal Harmony Guild!
How dare you
abduct the Queen of Great Yan!
Seize them!
Stop!
Don't run!
[Zhao Chun'er,
Former Princess of Great Yong]
Guards!
Bring me two more bottles of wine.
Your Highness, you're drunk.
Your Highness,
you can't drink anymore.
What did you call me?
Your Highness.
What did you just call me?
You called me "Your Highness," didn't you?
We're acting under His Highness's orders
to look after you,
so we wouldn't dare
treat you as anything less!
Good.
Since you still regard me as a princess,
then get me some more wine.
I haven't had enough!
Your Highness,
you've already had too much!
His Highness the Seventh Prince
has ordered
that you should rest properly...
Since you know
I'm the Seventh Prince's sister,
how dare you disobey my orders?
Listen up,
even if I've been demoted to a commoner,
I'm still of the imperial bloodline
of Great Yong.
You lowly creatures,
with just a word to my brother, Zhao Che,
and I can have your heads!
Enough! Stop hitting her! That's enough!
Yan Xun's wedding robe?
Yan Xun...
I'm a dignified princess of Great Yong,
yet you dared to slap me?
Do you believe
I'll have my brother kill you?
Your brother?
His Highness' army
is locked in battle
with the Yan Army at Meilin Pass!
He has no time for you!
You're nothing but
a deposed princess who was kicked out!
You were almost executed by the Emperor,
and you were the cause
of your own mother's death!
What right do you have
to act so high and mighty?
If it weren't for us
slaving away for you,
you would've starved to death long ago—
becoming some nameless
wandering ghost in these mountains!
Come on, let's go. Let's go drink.
Crazy woman.
Let's go.
Yan Xun...
Where are you?
I've long heard
that Princess Chun'er of Great Yong
is stunningly beautiful.
Now that I've seen you,
you've truly lived up to your reputation.
You're not a woman from Great Yong,
yet you greeted me
with Great Yong etiquette.
What do you want?
Princess, you need not concern yourself
with who I am.
I'm just here
to deliver an invitation to you.
An invitation?
I'm here to deliver
the Emperor of Great Yan
and Queen Chu Qiao's
wedding invitation.
Chu Qiao?
Didn't she fall into the frozen lake...
and die?
His Majesty gave the order
that even if we had to
drain the entire lake,
we had to find her.
Heaven rewards those who persevere—
His Majesty finally found her.
He then sought out
the finest physicians far and wide
to nurse Lady Chu Qiao back to health,
and she's almost fully recovered.
Soon,
when your country withdraws its troops,
His Majesty will marry her
as the Queen of Great Yan.
Chu Qiao...
She is so lucky.
Not only did she survive...
but she's going to marry my Yan Xun.
Come to think of it,
I really feel sorry for you, Princess.
ou were the one meant to
marry His Majesty.
Lady Chu Qiao is, by birth,
nothing but a slave.
To have your love stolen by a slave—
it must be very painful.
Who exactly are you?
What is your purpose
in coming here to sow discord?
Naturally, I have my purpose.
But
you have your regrets too,
don't you, Princess?
I'm no longer a princess,
and I'm of no use to you.
You should leave.
I've delivered the invitation to you.
I'll take my leave now.
Once a princess,
always a princess.
And likewise,
once a slave,
always a slave.
Chu Qiao,
I'll make you wish you were dead.
Your Majesty,
this is not a place you should come.
I want to see Miss Zhong,
who's being held inside.
Your Majesty,
His Majesty has ordered
that no one is to
have contact with the prisoner.
Must I bring Yan Xun with me
for you to open the door?
We're simply following
His Majesty's orders.
His Majesty said
that no one is to
have contact with the prisoner,
including you.
Chu,
this is the southwesternmost town
of Great Yan.
It used to be a barren wasteland,
but now
it's become a key passage for merchants—
with shops, markets,
and inns where travelers can rest.
Chu.
I have kept the promise I made to you.
I've been working hard
to revitalize Great Yan,
to restore it
to what I described to you back then.
I don't remember
what happened in the past,
and I don't know the promise
Your Majesty is referring to either.
However,
I do remember something else.
What?
I want to go see the frozen lake.
Chu...
why do you want to go there?
I find myself constantly
thinking about that lake.
Even in my dreams,
it's always that lake.
I just feel that place
must be very important to me.
I want to go there and take a look.
It doesn't matter
if you can't remember the past.
You've only just recovered
from soaking in freezing water.
It's not suitable for you
to go to the frozen lake right now.
Come on,
let's go get something to eat.
Chu,
is something weighing on your mind?
Ever since I woke up
after falling into the frozen lake,
I haven't regained my memory.
What are you worried about,
Emperor of Great Yan?
Ever since I brought you back
after you fall,
you've been unhappy.
Emperor, why won't you
let me see Miss Zhong?
Why do you want to see Zhong Yu?
What are you hiding from me?
Zhong Yu's identity is unclear.
She's a very dangerous person.
As ruler of Great Yan,
I have made many enemies.
Many people want me dead.
I'm afraid that because of me,
you might be harmed.
That's why I didn't want you
to see Zhong Yu.
Really?
But I feel
that's not the whole of it.
Since I woke up,
you've always been by my side,
treating me with great kindness
and telling me many things.
But I still have no memory.
What you've told me
is only bits and pieces.
How am I supposed to know
that you aren't lying to me?
Or perhaps,
is it possible
that you are the most dangerous one?
Chu!
I'm only speaking objectively,
just considering a possibility.
Why are you so anxious, Emperor?
Chu?
Chu!
Chu...
Yan Xun!
These iron chains are
the kind my brother, Zhao Che,
uses in the army
to bind prisoners of war and slaves.
I hadn't intended to bind you with them.
But if I hadn't,
I might never have gotten to
see you at all.
Chun'er?
Yan Xun,
it's been so long.
Are you happy to see me again?
I dressed up
specially just to see you.
You had us seized and brought here—
what do you want?
Yan Xun,
do you remember
this wedding robe I'm wearing?
You can still change your mind.
Chun'er is waiting for you in the palace—
waiting for you to become
Great Yong's imperial son-in-law.
If you marry her,
the Emperor of Yong
will lower his guard just the same.
Chu,
there's no turning back.
In a moment,
we'll fight our way out of Zhenhuang City
and back to Great Yan.
No more living in fear,
no more crawling like rats under
the thumb of the Emperor of Great Yong.
Never turning back.
Avenge the fallen souls of Great Yan!
Yan Xun,
what exactly is going on here?
Let go of me.
No, Yan Xun.
You must have your reasons, right?
Is it Chu Qiao?
That slave must have instigated this
and bewitched you!
I, Yan Xun...
and you people of the Zhao family,
in this lifetime and the next,
there will only be hatred between us!
Yan Xun,
take me with you.
Move.
I won't let you go.
Don't think I won't kill you.
Yan Xun...
If you leave, my heart will die.
I'd rather die by your hand!
Yan Xun...
I hate you.
I hate you!
Chu Qiao...
I will kill you.
Turns out...
you've long forgotten.
It's alright.
I've never forgotten.
Back then, I spent a long time
carefully selecting everything.
Even a single flower on the wedding robe—
I had the embroiderers
revise it repeatedly.
I looked forward to our grand,
long-awaited wedding for so long.
But on our wedding day,
you tore this robe to shreds.
Because under your wedding robes...
you wore your cold armor.
I spent so long
stitching it back together,
piece by piece.
But it's still tattered.
What's broken is broken—
it can never be mended.
Just like me...
I can never go back to who I was.
Chun'er...
The grievances between us
were settled long ago.
What are you trying to do,
acting like this now?
Settled?
Could they ever really be settled?
What?
His Majesty and Chu Qiao
have both been taken?
We didn't anticipate it—
the assassin disguised himself
as a beggar,
drugged His Majesty and Miss Chu,
and abducted them both.
Bring some men and follow me!
Every day and night,
I'm trapped in nightmares.
The same things
repeat themselves over and over.
I die again and again.
I'm afraid to close my eyes,
but I'm afraid to stay awake too.
I can only drink myself into a stupor,
over and over.
Why?
Yan Xun, tell me, why?
Why am I the only one
who lives in such misery?
Why do all of you
get to live so well?
I don't understand.
I really don't.
What's so special about you?
Why do you get to have all of this,
while I, the most noble princess
of Great Yong,
live in this drafty, leaky hut,
unable to get anything I want?
Zhao Chun'er, what are you doing?
In Great Yong,
some noble clans
brand their slaves
with a mark,
just as they would brand
the cattle and horses in their households.
You're a slave,
so you should be marked as one.
I'll brand the word "slave"
onto you—
a mark you'll carry
for the rest of your life!
Stop!
Zhao Chun'er, have you lost your mind?
Chu Qiao is innocent!
Yan Xun...
am I not innocent?
What did I do wrong
to deserve all that suffering?
Don't run!
Let go of me!
Chun'er,
you are innocent.
If you want revenge, take it out on me.
You can even take my life.
Please, let Chu go.
I'll repay
what I owe you myself.
Then I shall grant you that.
Are you crazy?
Chu Qiao!
Chun'er, don't!
I'll give you whatever you want!
Chun'er!
Yan Xun,
as long as you're willing to
put on this wedding robe
and marry me,
I'll let her go.
Okay.
I'll marry you.
Bottoms up!
Where is Chun'er?
Yan Xun,
you once shattered my heart.
Now, it's your turn to know how it feels
to lose the one you love
on the eve of your wedding.
I don't want you to marry me.
I just want Chu Qiao dead.
Why are you just standing there?
Kill him
and claim the reward
from the Seventh Prince!
T-The Great Yong Granary!
They've gone to the granary!
Do you know what these vats
are used for?
What exactly do you want?
Our Great Yong's granary...
Yan Xun burned our military provisions
a few days ago.
These vats...
were originally used for firefighting.
But what use are they now?
People
always seem to love doing futile things.
You dragged me all the way here
just to say that?
Of course not.
What I want to say is,
I'm going to marry Yan Xun.
Are you sad?
Why should I be sad?
Is Yan Xun that important to me?
Yan Xun isn't important to you?
For your sake,
he ruthlessly abandoned me
and rebelled on our wedding day.
He rode his horse over me,
tore through his wedding robes,
and stormed into my father's palace!
Did he do all that for me?
Wasn't that all for Great Yan?
You heartless woman!
Ever since Yan Xun was in Great Yong,
he's been protecting you!
He even lost a finger for you.
Now he wants you to be his queen.
And you, a lowly slave,
dare to say such things?
I truly can't understand—
what is so good about you?
Why is it that Yan Xun—
and everyone else—likes you so much?
You want to know?
Come closer.
I'll tell you.
Do you take me for a fool?
You're not a fool...
but not smart enough!
I may not be able to
break free of these chains,
but I can make you feel what it's like
to be bound in them like a slave!
Didn't you say
these chains were made
especially for lowly slaves?
I'd like to see
what difference it makes
when they bind a noble princess like you.
Let me go!
[Ximeng City]
He's been taking
the Bone-Chilling Grass for a few days.
Why hasn't he woken up yet?
Qianzhang Lake
has been frozen for many years.
The cold has invaded his internal organs.
No ordinary person could
withstand such cold!
Whether he wakes
depends on Heaven's will.
From now on,
you'll be the Queen of Great Yan.
Our child
will be the Heir Apparent of Great Yan.
The long blade of Great Yan
is not used like that.
Great Yan's warriors
only strike forward—
never retreat from the enemy!
Where is the Queen?
Where is she?
Kill Chu Qiao for me!
Nonsense!