Your Highness,
why is it you?
I didn't kill Xu.
It wasn't me who killed him.
You wicked woman.
During the incident at Xuri Palace,
I risked my life to protect you and Xu,
but you ended up in Li Jiao's bed.
For the throne,
Li Jiao wouldn't even
spare my child left behind.
He will come to a bad end,
and so will you.
No!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Did you have a nightmare again?
I'm fine.
[Li Jiao]
Your Majesty,
I'm sorry for being late.
You had a dream again?
It was just a dream.
Don't take it seriously.
Ziyu,
do you think I am terrifying?
I'm carving a memorial tablet
for my husband while he is still alive,
and I showed no mercy
to my own child.
I have never had such a thought.
You are wise and intelligent.
You know what is most important
in this palace
and what is not.
I never wanted to hurt my own child.
For so many years,
I've been putting up with him.
As long as he obediently remains
a useless man,
I can guarantee him a peaceful life.
His Highness is reckless at his age.
Please don't let him ruin your health.
You're wrong.
Do you think I would believe
that what the Crown Prince did today
was because he truly loves that woman?
To men, women
can satisfy their desires
and continue their family line.
Men need women
and dote on them.
They would decorate them
with gold and jewels,
and entice them with sweet words.
But they would never
truly risk anything for a woman.
Men...
can only be seduced by power
and take risks for it.
What that woman brings to the Crown Prince
is definitely not just love.
They must be plotting
against me.
Zhen,
I will uncover the truth for you.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 8]
Chun'er,
what are you doing?
Leaving here.
Leaving you.
Why?
Li Yan,
you're not some ordinary man.
You are the Prince of Luo in Biantang,
a royal descendant.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I don't want to have anything to do
with the royal family anymore!
Chun'er!
Chun'er.
I told you
that my name is Li Yan.
After my father passed away,
I observed 3 years of mourning.
I stay away from court affairs
and enjoy farming and studying.
All of this is true.
It's true that I never told you
about my status as a prince,
but that's because my father,
the Prince of Chang,
was suspected by Biantang Emperor
in his early years.
He was confined in Jincheng his whole life
and died of depression.
As his son,
although I inherited the title of prince,
I could only live in seclusion
observing mourning,
and without an imperial decree,
I could not enter the capital.
I know very well
that I am not of high royal blood.
I just wanted to face you
as Li Yan.
There's no use saying this now.
In my eyes,
you are the Prince of Luo,
and that makes you royal.
Whether you are in power or favored,
you are worlds apart from commoners.
Chun'er.
Then can you at least tell me
why you hate the royal family so much?
Because all nobles
surround themselves with concubines,
and the beautiful female slaves
around them
are countless.
I can't stand this.
I don't want to have anything to do with
the sons of noble families anymore.
Chun'er!
Wait a minute.
From today on,
you are free from slavery.
Whether you want to go home
or get married,
it's all up to you.
This money is enough for you
to settle down.
We were master and servants once,
but we will part ways here.
You can live a free life now.
-Thank you, Your Highness!
Come and get the money.
Thank you, Your Highness!
Thank you, Your Highness.
Chunxing,
you don't want the money?
Your Highness!
I was sold here when I was little.
I know nothing else but to serve you!
Please let me stay.
I am willing to work like a dog
to serve you for the rest of my life!
Okay.
Then you can stay.
Thank you, Your Highness!
Mozhan, what are you doing?
I...
I also want to spend my whole life
working like a dog to serve you.
Both of you can stay.
You may leave too.
Yes.
I am also willing to work like a dog
to serve you for the rest of my life.
Thank you, Your Highness.
If only Yan Xun...
could be like this.
Chun'er,
what are you talking about?
Why did you do this?
You are not him.
What's the use of doing all this?
Chun'er,
what's wrong?
Chun'er!
This is the third thing Qiao promised you,
the portrait of Fu you wanted.
Thank you for your help
at the palace banquet the other day.
This portrait was kept in the palace.
How did Your Highness get it?
I am the Crown Prince, after all.
I just spent some money
and got it out of the palace.
But I have another question.
Please go ahead, Your Highness.
Why did you help us?
Your situation is no better than mine.
Is it just because of this portrait?
Aren't you afraid
of getting into trouble with the Empress?
Your Highness,
do you remember when we were young?
Of course I do.
We both fell in love with Fu
at the same time,
and even fought over her.
Yes.
We were very childish back then.
But actually,
I've always felt there was a
mutual understanding between us.
To say something presumptuous,
you and I
have suffered alike.
When His Majesty ascended the throne,
because my father
and Crown Prince Maocheng
were born to the same mother,
he was ordered to live in seclusion
in the remote Jincheng.
Later, my father passed away.
I was 14 then,
coming to Tangjing for the first time.
To show his magnanimity and compassion,
His Majesty made an exception
and made me a Prince.
Though I was young,
I knew very well
that even a eunuch
or a maid by the Empress's side
had more power than me
and could hold their heads higher.
Li Yan,
all these years,
I know you must have had a hard time too.
Your Highness,
do you remember
the day Fu went to war with her father?
I do.
It was raining that day.
We went to see her off together,
all the way to more than 30 miles
outside the city.
You were completely soaked
but refused to go back.
Actually, I had a chance back then
to plead with the Empress
to let Fu stay and marry me.
But because I was concerned
about my status
and feared the Empress, I didn't dare.
So I missed the only chance
to save her.
Last night in the main hall,
somehow,
I felt like I was back to that day,
the day we saw Fu off from the capital.
I felt
this was heaven giving me another chance
to make up for my regret.
That's why
you wanted to help us?
I have missed my chance once
and lost Fu forever.
But I don't want
the tragedy to repeat itself on you.
Even if you have to break the ice,
you must find her!
Your Majesty!
Lady Chu fell into the lake a month ago.
The frozen lake spans thousands of miles,
and the ice on the surface never melts.
Breaking it open
might be impossible.
Your Majesty,
we found an underground river nearby,
leading to Ximeng.
This ornament
was found by the underground river.
Chu is not dead.
You must find her!
Arrest the manager of this store!
Yes!
Move!
Have you seen Chu?
If she's still alive,
she will definitely try to contact
your Universal Harmony Guild.
The Universal Harmony Guild
has long been gone,
but you have a family,
a wife, children, and parents.
If you don't know,
I will personally ask your family
to see who
is willing to tell me.
Yan Xun,
you ungrateful wretch!
Without the help
of the Universal Harmony Guild,
how could you have escaped
from Great Yong, that hell?
It wasn't enough
that you killed Miss Zhong,
and you won't even let go of Lady Chu.
What did you say?
Who killed Miss Zhong?
Did you use Miss Zhong
to lure Lady Chu out
just to kill them all?
Fortunately, heaven showed mercy
and let Lady Chu survive.
Not to mention
that I don't know where Lady Chu is.
Even if I did,
I would never tell you.
Congratulations, Your Majesty!
Your martial skills are even better
than before your recovery.
Chu Qiao, that femme fatale,
leaving Great Yan is a great fortune
for both you and Great Yan.
Cheng Yuan, let me ask you.
Why can't you let go of Chu?
Over and over again,
you betrayed and disobeyed me
because of Chu.
Your Majesty, in my heart,
you're the only King of Great Yan.
I have never betrayed you.
You told me
that Zhong Yu died suddenly in prison,
but it was actually you who killed her
and used her to kill Chu.
You think I don't know that?
Your Majesty,
kill me.
Chu Qiao will only be a stumbling block
on your path to revenge!
She...
must die.
I will not spare
anyone who hurts Chu.
And I won't keep you.
I don't want to see you again
Close the door.
Close the window.
This is a Xuanji Bell.
There used to be many in Qingshan Manor.
It sounds like an ordinary wind chime,
but it's extremely penetrating.
It can be heard for miles.
If someone comes uninvited
to your mansion,
I can hear the noise.
There is one more thing,
and it's the most important.
What is it?
It doesn't matter
that you don't know martial arts.
I'll teach you three moves.
At a critical moment,
they can not only save your life,
but maybe also save others.
The move just now is called
"Two Dragons Playing with a Pearl."
It's for when someone attacks you
from the front.
You can use it to injure the enemy's eyes,
buying you a chance to escape.
Try it.
This move is called
"Divine Dragon Wagging Its Tail."
It's for when someone
tries to sneak up on you.
Good move.
There's one last move.
The last move.
Awesome!
What is this move called?
It's called...
"the Quick-Foot Flee."
Commonly known as
"Running Fast."
"Running Fast"?
You don't have any foundation
in martial arts.
No matter how much I teach you,
you won't be able
to master it in a short time.
The key is
that when you encounter danger,
you need to be able to run away.
Don't sleep tonight.
Practice these three moves 30 times.
Thirty?
Is this also something
you learned from Zhuge Yue?
He doesn't need this.
It's Lord Zhan's order.
Yes, My Lord.
Princess, you are here?
We thought
you weren't here.
We just wanted to come and see you.
Why are you so cruel to us?
See me?
Sneaking around to see me?
Yes.
You misunderstood, Princess.
We just wanted
to come and play games with you.
We thought you weren't here,
so we dared to come in and look around.
♪ The flowers fall into the sleeves ♪
♪ They do not understand my sorrow ♪
♪ With a pot of wine ♪
♪ My longing surges ♪
♪ I become haggard ♪
♪ Light rain falls on the window ♪
♪ Awakening from the dream,
I no longer know what year it is ♪
♪ Love never stops ♪
♪ Yet we are already far apart ♪
♪ What I seek in life ♪
♪ Is nothing more
than to look back once more ♪
♪ With the fragrance still lingering ♪
♪ The shaking hands ♪
♪ Are still hiding affection ♪
♪ Words left unspoken ♪
♪ Turn into guilt ♪
♪ Hidden in the stars ♪
♪ Rippling throughout this life ♪
♪ I ask the vast sky ♪
♪ The wind is light,
but my longing is heavy ♪
♪ How to start over ♪
♪ How do we love
and hold on without parting ♪
♪ Without misunderstandings? ♪
♪ Do not let me only understand
the meaning of a fleeting glance ♪
♪ When my eyes are red with tears ♪
♪ What cannot be kept,
can only be sent away ♪
♪ In the end ♪
♪ It can only be praised ♪
Where is your King Li'an?
Since he has been defeated,
why doesn't he come out of the city
to welcome King Ximeng?
Our King knows his sins are grave.
He sincerely wants to surrender to Ximeng.
He has now taken off his armor
and is waiting for punishment
in the prison.
Please enter the city, King Ximeng,
to receive his respects.
Where is your king?
Bring him out for an audience.
King Ximeng!
You will die in Li'an City today!
You go first.
General!
King Ximeng
has surrounded us with his army!
We've been tricked!
That old bastard King Ximeng
used this brat to lure us away.
Our plan failed.
Then let's take this brat down with us!
Go!
I want him to be my shadow,
to act as a decoy
in Li'an City in my place.
♪ We mock karma ♪
♪ For being unfair ♪
♪ Why is life ♪
♪ Often filled with regrets? ♪
♪ The snow falls ♪
♪ With fate ♪
♪ It will eventually ♪
♪ Fall before ♪
♪ The dawn ♪
♪ As a foreigner ♪
♪ Don't look, don't ask, and don't speak ♪
♪ Wander ♪
♪ With no resentment at all ♪
♪ The lock in my heart ♪
♪ Put the memories ♪
♪ In the silence of the night ♪
♪ Wait ♪
♪ For the stars and moon
to part ways again ♪
♪ As a foreigner ♪
♪ Don't look, don't ask, and don't speak ♪
♪ Wander ♪
♪ With no resentment at all ♪
♪ Traveling alone ♪
♪ In a world ♪
♪ Where fate is unkind ♪
♪ Look ♪
♪ The mortal world has forgotten me ♪
♪ I wish ♪
♪ You'll forget me ♪
Xing...
I can't hold on anymore.
Zhuge Yue,
you taught me
that no matter what situation we're in,
as long as we're not defeated,
we can be reborn.
♪ Facing the wind, I tread through frost ♪
Zhuge Yue...
♪ Measuring rivers and hills,
hooves rise light ♪
stay alive.
♪ The horizon lies far ahead ♪
Xing...
♪ Swaying gently ♪
You taught me
that we should stay alive
even in the dark.
♪ Through pine mists, past 1,000 hills ♪
♪ Wrapped in the vast moonlight ♪
Let's fight our way out together.
♪ Having drunk the surging waves ♪
♪ I care not how far the road ♪
♪ When I was young ♪
Xing,
♪ I wrote poems
praising the prosperous world ♪
let's fight our way out!
♪ The wind was not yet full,
the moon not yet round ♪
♪ Rushing me to charge forward ♪
♪ Strong wine to the wild plains ♪
♪ Beyond the pass,
sand blows like arrows ♪
♪ I ride and whip my steed ♪
♪ Chasing 10,000 miles of cloud and mist ♪
♪ Mountains and rivers fade behind ♪
♪ The wind crowns me ♪
♪ Your eyes glow with flame ♪
♪ Strong wind breaks the lute strings ♪
♪ Playing for 5,000 years ♪
♪ I ride my horse toward the south ♪
♪ Endless spring beneath my hooves ♪
♪ Hoofbeats fade away ♪
♪ Rolling over peaks and ridges ♪
♪ A single neigh echoes
between heaven and earth ♪
♪ Treading on the clear wind ♪
♪ The realm unfolds like a scroll ♪
♪ Chasing the bright moon ♪
♪ My spirit swallows
mountains and rivers ♪
Qiao,
you got hurt?
Great!
I can finally pick up a sword!
Zhuge Yue,
I did it!
Please forgive me, Lord Zhan.
That woman is very alert.
We tested her several times,
but she didn't give herself away.
People are alert when awake,
but not necessarily...
when on the verge of death.
Help!
Help me!
Zhuge Yue...
You are Chu Qiao,
not Princess Fu, right?
What are you doing here?
What are you and the Crown Prince
planning?
Li Ce...
Li Ce said I am Princess Fu.
I...
Where is she?
Since you like making deals,
let's make another one.
Mother
seems very certain
that you are Chu Qiao.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, you can't go in!
Everyone knows
the Crown Prince is useless.
So I took the liberty to see you.
Chu Qiao?
Zhao Kuo!
Kill her!
Then let's see
who is faster.