Do you still remember
the day I left for Great Yan?
You told me
you needed me.
Now,
Zhuge Yue,
can you stay for me?
Qiao!
Qiao...
You're injured.
What happened?
How did you get hurt?
Li Ce.
My eyes are healed.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 7]
[Lvwan Restaurant]
Zhuge Yue,
what are you doing here?
Zhuge Huai,
the fire from your Hongshan Manor
has spread all the way
to my Qingshan Manor.
Shouldn't you compensate for it?
Why?
Is your Qingshan Manor so poor
that you need to settle accounts
for some shabby rooms?
Qingshan Manor
has always had clear accounts,
unlike your Hongshan Manor,
which is a mess.
You can't manage your people
or settle accounts.
Zhuge Yue,
are you here to make fun of me?
I have no time for such things.
It's just that my Qingshan Manor
can't suffer losses for no reason.
Since you can't manage
these female slaves,
they are useless.
Take them to the hunting ground
to feed the wild wolves.
Why?
Can't bear to do it?
No wonder His Majesty values you.
When it comes to ruthlessness,
it has to be you, Zhuge Yue.
Take them away.
Go east,
leave Zhenhuang City,
and never come back.
What are you waiting for?
Do you truly wish to be fed to the wolves?
All of you, step down.
You two as well.
Come out.
There are wolves here.
You'll lose your life.
With your poor martial arts,
you still dared to break into
Hongshan Manor alone to save people?
I'm afraid that if you
hadn't come to save her,
your little sister
could have lived a few more days.
You were already dead.
Don't think that because you
let everyone go,
I will thank you.
You and that Zhuge Huai
are birds of a feather.
Do you want to continue fighting with me,
ending up dead at my hands,
or do you want me to teach you
how to survive
in this cruel and ruthless world?
It's up to you.
King Ximeng only gave you
a 10-day antidote.
I didn't expect you to hold out until now.
I really underestimated you.
Even if you hold on to
the poison of Blood on Snow
for just a moment,
next,
you will be more painful,
a fate worse than death.
Still hoping
to run away with your beloved one?
Dream on.
Qiao,
I can't reach the food on your side.
Help me pass some tofu.
This mutton looks really good.
Have some more of this.
If you don't eat this mutton,
it will get tough.
You are a wanted criminal in Great Yan.
How dare you invite me to eat hot pot
within Great Yan's territory?
If we don't eat today,
after the big battle,
there will be even less chance to eat.
After this battle,
I don't know how many innocent bodies
will be covered under the heavy snow.
Xing,
have you ever regretted your choices?
I have no regrets
because I had no choice.
I was born a slave of Great Yong,
a worthless maid in Qingshan Manor.
Whether I fight alongside Yan Xun
or serve as a general of the Xiuli Army,
you
will always be on the opposite side.
If you were just Xing,
and I wasn't a general of Great Yong,
could we leave here together
and no longer bear those responsibilities
and hatred?
But we are not like that.
I won't forget my name,
and neither will you.
You can never cast off the Zhuge name,
and I can never let go
of my responsibilities.
We are destined
never to stand together.
Come on, eat more.
You need to be full
to have the strength to find Zhuge Yue.
Slap him twice
and kick him down!
Here, dip some of this.
Qiao,
I have an idea.
I'll go to the palace right now
and tell them
Zhuge Yue,
Chief of Great Yong's Qingshan Manor,
is in Tangjing.
I'll ask my mother
to order the entire Biantang
to issue a warrant for Zhuge Yue's arrest.
Before he runs far,
we can definitely catch him.
Who asked you to issue a warrant for him?
Why do you want to catch him?
Catch him to beat him up.
Acting all solemn and playing dead, huh?
With your slender waist and small figure,
you can catch Zhuge Yue?
Qiao.
I'm trying to figure out
a way to vent your anger.
Why do you still look down on me?
But anyway,
Zhuge Yue is still alive.
He hasn't lost an arm or a leg.
You've also recovered your eyesight,
and you can still see his cold expression.
Sometimes when you like someone,
-as long as—
-Who said I like him?
You don't like him?
That was before.
Now he doesn't recognize me and avoids me.
He also broke his promise to me.
I might have to reconsider this.
Li Ce,
don't worry.
I will live well.
Qiao.
Then consider me.
I'm way better than Zhuge Yue
and his cold expression.
I'm handsome, suave,
elegant, and talented.
Straighten your back!
Hurry up!
Get up! Get up!
Speed up!
Up.
Hurry up.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Congratulations
on being under the protection of the gods
and surviving the disaster.
General Huan,
you've worked hard recently.
I am guilty.
You quelled the internal rebellion
and stabilized the Great Yan army morale.
What crime have you committed?
I privately commanded the whole army
and dispatched the Yan Army
and the Black Eagle Army together
to suppress Katuo's tribe's rebellion.
But if I had done nothing,
I'm afraid Great Yan
would have undergone a great change.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
General Huan, you're tired
from suppressing the rebellion.
Go back and rest.
The soldiers of the Snowy Region Tribe
and the border troops
are also looking forward to
your return day and night.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
The dignified Black Eagle Army
should be open and aboveboard.
Yet you hide your heads
and show your tails,
shameless.
General Huan,
we are also acting under orders.
Since you are courting death,
I will grant your wish.
Your Majesty,
the whole of Great Yan
knows that the black eagles
brought you back from death,
and that the gods
of Mount Hei
protect the ruler of Great Yan.
From now on,
even the tribal elders of Great Yan
won't dare to
have any disloyalty
toward you, the ruler of Great Yan.
Your medicine is quite useful.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I just used
some herbs that attract beasts.
It's just a small trick.
Your Majesty.
I laid an ambush along the road
to intercept General Huan,
but she fought with all her might.
She...
What happened?
She escaped, and her fate is unknown.
You saved my life
and put on such a great show with me.
I will reward you handsomely.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Why?
Only if you die
can I truly become the ruler of Great Yan,
who were resurrected
by the gods of Mount Hei.
General Huan?
Why would General Huan
be treated like this?
His Majesty is the ruler of Great Yan,
protected by the gods of Mount Hei.
General Huan overstepped her authority
and seized military power
while His Majesty was in a coma.
This is His Majesty's punishment for her.
General Huan disobeyed the King's orders,
privately mobilized troops,
and rebelled against the decree.
During the turmoil in Great Yan,
she fought for her own selfish interests.
She was executed today,
but her crimes are unforgivable.
Her corpse will be exposed
for 3 days as a warning to others.
From now on,
gather strong soldiers
and brave generals from all tribes
to flatten Great Yong with me!
-As you command, Your Majesty!
[Ximeng City]
Zhuge Yue,
you broke your promise
and tried to walk away.
I thought you
could really withstand
the torture of Blood on Snow.
I am already living like a ghost.
What does it matter if I die?
Your martial arts
helped you survive this many days,
which is quite surprising to me.
So I won't let you die.
I need
capable slaves.
I'll give you another chance.
This is the 10-day dose.
In exchange,
you have to do something for me.
What
do you want me to do?
From now on,
you are not only my slave
but also
my shadow.
[Boque Palace]
Are you sure it was a woman
who entered your room?
I can't be wrong.
She must have come to spy.
She opened the secret compartment
under my bed.
The flag of the Xiuli Army is in it.
I have 14 concubines and maids
in my mansion,
all nominally granted by the Empress.
But it's also possible
that Zhan Ziyu secretly planted
someone among them.
It's hard to investigate
with just this information.
Are there any other features?
Let me think.
She is quite thin.
She should be
between an inch or two shorter than me.
But unlike Linlang and the others,
her strike is powerful.
She must have practiced
martial arts since childhood.
One more thing.
Her martial arts look familiar to me,
but I don't completely recognize them.
What about her scent?
Was she wearing any perfume?
Since it's a woman,
was she wearing any jewelry?
None of those.
Your Highness.
Lord Zhan just passed on
an oral edict from the Empress,
saying she heard
Princess Fu has been found
and requests you
to bring Princess Fu
to the palace for a talk immediately.
When we enter the hall later,
just wait on the side.
I'll deal with Mother.
I pay my respects to you, Your Majesty.
I pay my respects to you, Mother.
Fu, you've been away for many years.
A girl changes a lot as she grows up.
I almost couldn't recognize you.
You may rise.
-Thank you, Mother.
-Thank you, Your Majesty.
You indeed look quite different
from when you were a child.
These eyebrows and eyes
and this thin figure
do look somewhat similar.
However...
you don't seem like Fu.
You look a bit like...
the escaped slave
Great Yan and Great Yong are hunting down,
Chu Qiao.
Your Majesty,
who are you talking about?
Chu Qiao was a female slave of Great Yong,
who later, surprisingly,
became a female general of Great Yan.
Now both Great Yan and Great Yong
are hunting for her everywhere,
causing a huge uproar.
Even our Biantang has no peace.
Ce,
when you were in Great Yong,
didn't you say
you wanted to marry Chu Qiao?
Look closely at her.
Doesn't she look a lot like Chu Qiao?
You must be joking, Mother.
How could Fu and Chu Qiao look alike?
Your Majesty.
When I was wandering outside,
I heard that the Crown Prince of Biantang
went to Great Yong as an envoy
to marry a female martial arts instructor
of the imperial guard.
I wonder, Your Majesty,
if you're talking about that Chu Qiao.
Fu,
don't be angry.
The reason I wanted to marry her back then
was that she looked somewhat like you.
And I thought you had already...
You can't blame me for this.
Mother, please don't mention
the past in front of Fu.
Since you say you are Princess Fu,
let me ask you,
do you remember how old you were
when you came to Biantang?
When I was 6,
His Majesty granted my father
the title of Prince of Pingnan
and my mother the title of Lady Dingguo,
as well as the Prince of Pingnan's Mansion
in the west of the city.
I then followed my father and mother
to Tangjing.
Who on earth is Princess Fu?
Fu's father
was the Prince of Pingnan.
Her mother
was Lady Dingguo.
Then do you remember me?
I remember seeing you 3 times.
Once at His Majesty's birthday banquet,
once when praying to Heaven
for the Empress,
and another time
at the Crown Prince's birthday.
But I only saw you from afar
and didn't have the chance
to get close to you.
My mother once said
that you and she were close friends
before you both got married.
However,
after she married Fu's father,
she moved away from Tangjing
and gradually grew distant from my mother.
Mother,
why do you suspect that she is not Fu,
but Chu Qiao?
Ce,
don't blame me for being suspicious.
This is a matter of great importance.
It happened suddenly.
I must figure it out.
I deeply appreciate
your good intentions, Mother.
However,
Princess Fu has not fully recovered
and has been exhausted for half a day.
If you have no more doubts,
why not let me take her back
to rest early?
All right.
Then today,
you may take your leave.
-Thank you, Mother.
-Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I can guarantee with my life
that the woman
His Highness brought back
is the general of the Xiuli Army,
Chu Qiao.
Lord Zhao,
it's not that I don't believe
what you said.
It's just that I have never seen
the famous Chu Qiao,
and this is the first time
I've met you too.
But I
did see Princess Fu when she was young.
The woman the Crown Prince brought back
does resemble Princess Fu.
Your Majesty,
I was once a trusted advisor
to a noble family of Great Yong,
the Muhe family.
I have seen Chu Qiao many times.
After the Jiuyou Platform accident,
Yan Xun was imprisoned.
Young Master Muhe Xifeng and I
once went to the prison.
Yan Xun was highly protective of Chu Qiao,
even cutting off one of his own fingers.
I was at the scene at the time.
After this,
Yan Xun and Chu Qiao
hate Lord Muhe to the bone.
They plotted to kill him.
Whether this is true or false,
you can find out
by sending someone to investigate.
From what you said,
it doesn't seem to be false.
Lord Zhao,
please go back first.
I will take my leave.
Your Majesty,
but now the Crown Prince insists
that she is Princess Fu.
We can't find any flaws
for the time being.
Then keep a close eye on her
and the Crown Prince's Mansion.
I'd like to see
what the Crown Prince
can possibly accomplish
with this fake princess he brought back.
Yes.
By the way,
the Prince of Luo
has completed his 3 years of mourning.
By my calculations,
he should be on his way back now.
I understand.
I will go and welcome
the Prince of Luo back to the palace.
Your Highness.
Her Majesty knows
your mourning period is over.
She sent us to wait here
and welcome you
into the palace for a chat.
Why does Her Majesty
summon me to the palace so suddenly?
Can you tell me in advance, My Lord?
You will know once you enter the palace.
Please wait a moment.
Chun'er.
I have something to attend to.
Li Yan,
who exactly are you?
Why would the Empress
summon you to the palace?
Who is he?
You go back to the mansion first.
I will explain everything
to you when I return.
Your Highness.
An imperial edict has come
from Her Majesty in the palace.
It says it's a joyous occasion
that Princess Fu has been found,
so a banquet will be held in the palace.
Princess Fu is invited
to enter the palace immediately.
Immediately?
Immediately.
Remember,
your mother was an only child,
and your parents have passed away.
Even if there are kin in the family,
none of them have seen you before.
They won't be able to tell
if you're Princess Fu.
The Prince of Pingnan
was not from Tangjing,
and his relatives aren't here either.
No matter what they say,
don't believe them.
The Princess Consort of Pingnan and I
used to be like sisters.
The Prince of Pingnan died for his country
on a battlefield thousands of miles away.
I originally thought
the Princess Consort of Pingnan
and Princess Fu had tragically perished.
I didn't expect Princess Fu
to be blessed by heaven.
I am happy for Princess Fu.
Today, I have invited an old friend
especially for Princess Fu.
I am Prince of Luo, Li Yan.
I pay my respects to you, Your Majesty.
Princess Fu.
You couldn't have forgotten
the Prince of Luo, could you?
He is your childhood sweetheart,
your betrothed husband.
He is most familiar
with your looks and habits.
Others might mistake you,
but he
definitely won't.
Prince of Luo.
Since your marriage to Princess Fu
was arranged by your parents,
there's no need for formalities.
Go and sit next to Princess Fu.
After the banquet,
I will have the Ministry of Rites
choose an auspicious day
for your wedding.
Prince of Luo.
What's wrong?
You haven't seen Princess Fu
for a long time.
Aren't you happy?
Or is the person in front of you
not Princess Fu at all?
Prince of Luo,
answer me.
Is the woman in front of you
Princess Fu?
Your Majesty,
I haven't seen Princess Fu in years.
It is inevitable that appearances change.
Perhaps Your Majesty,
you could allow Princess Fu
and me to talk in private.
Your Highness.
I don't know who you are,
but you're definitely not Princess Fu.
What do you want?
It's easy for you to kill me now,
but you'll implicate Li Ce,
and you won't walk out of the palace
alive yourself.
I want you to go out now and confirm
that I am Princess Fu.
Saving me
is also saving Li Ce.
I'm right behind you.
If you say one wrong word,
I'll kill you on the spot.
Answer me 3 questions.
If you answer them,
I'll go out with you.
Speak.
First question.
Who exactly are you?
Although you look a bit like Fu,
which made me almost
get the wrong person just now,
you are not her.
Fu is dead.
Who exactly are you?
I am not from Biantang.
I am from Great Yong.
I was a slave.
When Li Ce went to Zhenhuang City
as an envoy,
we met there.
Alright.
Second question.
Why did you pretend to be Princess Fu?
And what is your purpose here?
Because of me,
many things happened,
and many people were implicated.
Now Great Yan and Great Yong
are both hunting me down.
To save me,
Li Ce brought me back from Great Yan.
In desperation, he lied
and said I was Princess Fu.
I don't care about my own life.
But Li Ce
took a great risk for me.
I don't want him
to get hurt because of me again.
What is the third question?
It
is a deal.
I want you to promise me one thing.
Your Majesty,
the woman in front of us
is indeed Princess Fu
who has been missing for years.
Princess Fu's return
is truly a joyous occasion.
But Princess Fu and I
haven't seen each other for years,
and we have grown apart.
Getting married at this time
might be a bit inappropriate.
I appreciate your kindness, Your Majesty.
I sincerely ask for your permission
to postpone the wedding.
I heard that since Princess Fu returned,
she's been at the Crown Prince's Mansion
under your care, Your Highness.
I thank you for that.
Li Ce.
There is something I've never figured out.
Aren't you the legitimate Crown Prince
born to the Biantang Empress?
Why is she so wary of you?
In the royal family,
blood ties are the most useless thing.
In order to fight for the heir apparent,
my father killed his own elder brother,
Crown Prince Maocheng.
He placed Crown Prince Maocheng's
full brother, Prince of Chang,
under house arrest in the remote Jincheng.
The Prince of Luo, Li Yan,
is the only surviving bloodline
of the late Prince of Chang.
So, although the Prince of Luo
holds the title,
he's the descendant of a condemned prince.
Yes.
My mother
is a woman of courage and vision.
But she's far colder about feelings
than most people.
I was raised by a wet nurse.
When I was young,
every time I tried to hug her,
I would be coldly pushed away by her.
Growing up,
I found that compared to me,
she seemed more interested in power.
The further away I stayed from power,
the more pleasant she would be to me.
So all these years,
I have been playing the role
of a playboy and a spendthrift.
They're just a few beautiful spies.
I have dealt with countless ruthless spies
in Qingshan Manor
who wanted me dead.
Li Ce,
don't worry.
Once my arm recovers,
not only will I protect you,
but I will also help you
take back everything that belongs to you.
King Ximeng,
Li'an City
will be your burial place today!
She
must die!
Help!
You are the Prince of Luo of Biantang,
a noble of the royal clan.
No!
Zhuge Yue,
you must survive.
Break the ice open.
You must find the person for me!