I am Zhuge Yue,
the Fourth Young Master
of the Zhuge family,
a noble family of Great Yong,
and the Master of Qingshan Manor,
a hereditary position in my family.
[Zhuge Yue, Master of Qingshan Manor,
Great Yong]
I pledge loyalty
to the Emperor of Great Yong
and eliminate his dissidents.
He's Yan Xun,
[Yan Xun, Heir Apparent of Great Yan]
the Heir Apparent of the Duke of Dingbei.
The Yan family guarded Great Yan,
but was feared
by the Emperor of Great Yong.
The entire family was wiped out.
We were once close friends.
But now,
we are bitter enemies.
Young Master!
Yue Qi!
My Lord,
it's Miss Chu.
Zhuge Yue!
[Chu Qiao]
Xing.
Move.
Zhuge Yue,
I am sorry.
Yan Xun!
Kill me first!
Zhuge Yue!
Xing...
I'm here.
Run.
No.
If we leave, we leave together.
You've always been protecting me.
Now,
it's my turn to protect you.
Zhuge Yue?
I will definitely get you out of here.
Xing...
You...
will definitely...
get me out of here.
Zhuge Yue?
Zhuge Yue!
Wake up.
Wake up. You promised me
that we would leave together!
Zhuge Yue!
Don't leave me all alone!
No!
Chu,
actually, I have never changed.
It's just that you never knew
what I truly wanted.
Chu!
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 1]
Great Yong,
Biantang,
and Ximeng
divided the land among themselves.
Biantang is prosperous
and peaceful.
Ximeng is bitterly cold,
and its people are suffering.
Great Yong, with its strict hierarchy
and fierce army, became a dominant power.
Great Yan was originally
a vassal of Great Yong,
but, feared for its achievements,
it fell out with Great Yong
and eventually broke away
to establish its own rule.
The young masters
of Great Yong's noble families
enjoy watching slaves fight beasts
and even hunt slaves for sport.
The orphan Chu Qiao
was a slave in her youth.
She despises Great Yong's slave system
and vows to abolish it
and end the violence.
Keep up!
Stay in Qingshan Manor.
From now on,
your name is Xing.
I recognized her unique talent
and trained her as a spy.
Zhuge Yue,
this Xing in your courtyard
has quite the nerve.
I like her.
She's too bold.
She needs strict discipline.
No need for that.
Just give her to me.
No.
Pick another maid.
I beat you every time.
Why do you never get mad at me?
Because...
you're my only friend.
It's not that Great Yan wants to rebel.
It's that Your Majesty wants it to.
I know
you and Yan Xun are close.
I will grant you a favor
and spare Yan Xun's life.
As for whether he will live or die,
it depends on whether you can
take care of this matter for me.
On Jiuyou Platform,
the Emperor of Great Yong ordered Yan Xun,
the hostage prince,
to identify the severed heads
of his family.
Yan Xun, after witnessing his family burn
and his mother die tragically,
felt as if he were falling into an abyss.
Yan Xun!
Zhuge Yue!
Why are you hiding from me?
Or...
are you guilty about something?
His Majesty
wanted to move against Great Yan.
No one could stop it.
Fine.
From now on,
you are the heir of Qingshan Manor,
a promising subject of Great Yong.
Chu and I—
one is the imprisoned descendant
of a disgraced king,
and the other is the Zhuge family's
most insignificant slave.
You don't need to visit us anymore.
We don't want to see you either.
Yan Xun,
I used to see you as a trusted friend.
That's why I petitioned His Majesty
to remove your name
from the execution list
of the Yan family.
As for Xing,
you should know
that to me,
she has long ceased to be
just a slave in Qingshan Manor.
Chu and you—
and your Qingshan Manor—
have long severed ties!
Zhuge Yue,
from this moment on,
we are no longer friends.
We are strangers.
Yan Xun was convinced
that everything was the doing
of Qingshan Manor
and completely broke with me.
Xing rebuilt the Xiuli Army
and helped Yan Xun
escape back to Great Yan.
Xing,
come back with me.
Yan Xun's rebellion won't succeed.
Zhuge Yue,
you once spared my life,
and I am grateful for that.
But that does not erase
the grievances between us.
You are a noble son, high above all.
You care nothing for the lives of slaves.
But they are human,
the family I care for most!
You shot and injured Yan Xun back then,
preventing our escape from the capital
and causing us years of imprisonment.
You and I
have always been on opposite sides.
That can never be reconciled
and will never change.
Xing,
do you really trust Yan Xun so much
and believe he can give you
everything you want?
I trust him.
The morality,
justice,
and ideals you speak of
are not as simple as you think.
Zhuge Yue,
that's the difference between us.
How about we make a bet?
Let's bet that one day in this world,
good will be rewarded,
evil will be punished,
and everyone will be treated equally.
Yan Xun.
Are you ready?
Once this moment passes,
we will never have a chance to turn back.
After ending all of this,
we will return to Great Yan.
I promised you
that I would restore peace to the world.
Avenge the dead of Great Yan!
They wanted to create
a vast world where everyone
could live freely,
with no distinction between high and low.
But Yan Xun's heart
was already soaked in blood and vengeance.
He used my feelings for Xing
to lure me to the frozen lake.
By the time Xing realized
what was happening,
it was too late.
Yan Xun!
Kill me first!
Zhuge Yue!
I am sorry.
No!
Miss Chu, you're awake?
[Su, A Maid of Great Yan]
And your fever has broken.
Who are you?
And where am I?
Miss Chu,
you still don't remember anything?
Miss Chu?
This war has been raging on and off
for nearly 3 months.
Although Great Yong
has fewer troops than Great Yan,
Great Yan is bitterly cold.
In terms of climate and provisions,
they are better suited
for prolonged warfare than we are.
The Seventh Prince,
Zhao Che, who leads their troops,
is a tough opponent.
If he drags this out,
[General Shiyan, Commander
of Black Eagle Army of Great Yan]
I'm afraid General Huan
and the Black Eagle Army
may not hold out.
Zhao Che is holding back his full force
to wear our army down
and force us to retreat.
If we give up now,
[General Cheng Yuan, Guardian
of the Black Eagle Army of Great Yan]
all our efforts will be in vain.
Your Majesty,
Great Yong has already
lost 5 cities in a row,
and their strategist, Zhuge Yue,
has died in Great Yan.
If we push too hard,
I'm afraid both sides
will suffer heavy losses.
Even if we win,
for Great Yan,
the cost will be tremendous.
Your Majesty, please proceed with caution.
Your Majesty,
Miss Chu is awake.
Chu, you're awake?
Doctor,
check on the Queen.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
have you remembered anything?
Why doesn't she remember anything?
Her Majesty's fever
hasn't completely broken,
and she's still not fully conscious.
It may be temporary,
or it could be due to external injuries.
We won't know
until she's
fully awake.
I remember...
you are a doctor.
As for the rest...
I had a dream.
I dreamed I was in a frozen lake.
I was trapped at the bottom of it,
unable to breathe.
Why has she only woken twice
in 3 months,
and each time she was delirious,
unable to remember anything?
Your Majesty,
please do not worry too much.
After falling into the frozen lake,
Her Majesty had a high fever for several days.
The hypothermia in her body
has not completely dissipated.
The fact that she can now
speak and move freely
is already a great relief.
For now, rest is the most important.
As for when she will regain her memory,
you must be patient.
Your Majesty, you can talk
with Her Majesty about the past.
This
may help her recover her memory.
You're saying…
I am the Queen?
Yes.
You are my betrothed queen.
We were to be married
before you fell into the frozen lake.
Married?
Let me show you something.
Chu,
this is the wedding dress
I prepared for you.
We have faced life and death together
and have long committed to each other.
Three months ago,
if not for the scoundrels from Great Yong
sneaking into our land
and attempting to assassinate us
on our wedding day,
you would already be the rightful Queen
of Great Yan.
Great Yong?
Great Yong.
Chu, do you remember?
When I was young,
I was forced to serve as a hostage prince
in Zhenhuang City of Great Yong.
I met you at Qingshan Manor.
Later, my family suffered disaster,
and it was you
who protected me and kept me alive.
Yan Shicheng, Duke of Dingbei,
amassed troops for personal gain,
defied heaven and earth,
deceived the throne,
and misled the people.
He even secretly mobilized the Yan Army,
inciting rebellions across the land.
His disloyalty is known to all.
Fortunately, His Majesty is wise
and blessed by Heaven.
The rebellion of Great Yan
has been quelled,
and the traitors' clan has been executed.
Considering that Yan Xun
grew up in Zhenhuang City
and was not involved in the rebellion,
he is now ordered to identify
the severed heads of the traitors
[Zhuge Huai from the Zhuge Family
of Great Yong]
to atone for his crimes.
Yan Shicheng—
the hereditary King of Great Yan,
the 24th-generation descendant
of Emperor Peiluo,
with the 576th spirit tablet enshrined
in the Chengguang Ancestral Temple
of Shengjin Palace;
the Grand Marshal
of the Northwest Army of Great Yong;
and the King of Zhenxi of Great Yan!
He was executed
at Huolei Plains in Great Yan
on April 14.
Zhuge Huai, I'll kill you!
Yan Ting, eldest son of Yan Shicheng,
King of Zhenxi of Great Yan,
was executed on April 14
at Xunlie Terrace in Great Yan.
The names have all been read.
Heir Apparent Yan,
please identify the traitors.
Accept the decree.
Yan Xun,
hurry up and accept the decree.
Go up there and look at the heads
of your old man and your brothers.
The traitor's son, Yan Xun,
has defied the imperial decree!
Seize him!
Yan Xun!
No!
Yan Xun, you fool!
Do you want to die?
No need to identify anymore.
Arrest the criminal Yan Xun!
Zhuge Yue!
The order from Zhenhuang City
was for him to identify the bodies.
How can we go through the motions?
By doing this,
aren't you afraid
His Majesty will blame you?
Whether he blames me or not
is none of your concern.
If you insist on protecting him,
you have to see if he appreciates it.
Guards!
You Great Yan bastard!
I want you to watch with your own eyes
as your family and relatives
are burned to ashes!
Yan Xun!
Are you going to identify them or not?
Zhuge Huai!
Zhuge Huai, I will kill you!
I'll kill you!
I will identify them!
[Bai Sheng, Wife of Duke of Dingbei]
Xun.
Mother.
Don't cry.
The children of our Yan family
shed blood but no tears.
Mother,
what exactly happened?
Do you believe in your father?
I do.
In this world,
not everything
can be explained clearly.
Was it them?
Did they destroy Great Yan?
Xun.
Stand up.
Let me identify the bodies.
Up there...
are my husband,
my son,
my daughter,
and my kin!
I believe that in this world,
no one is more qualified than I am
to do this!
His Majesty appointed Yan Xun
to identify the traitors.
Do you intend to disobey the decree?
Guards!
Seize the people who defied the decree!
The entire Yan family has perished.
Why is Princess Consort Yan
the only survivor?
His Majesty once issued a decree—
as long as Princess Consort Yan
does not leave Zhenhuang City,
no one is to harm her in the slightest.
Zhuge Huai,
do you intend
to disobey the decree as well?
I...
Stand down.
Mother!
This is my husband,
Yan Shicheng,
the hereditary King of Great Yan!
During the Battle of Baima Pass,
an army of 300,000 Quanrong invaded.
Shicheng led his troops
and departed from Great Yan.
For 7 days and nights, he did not
remove his armor or leave his saddle.
He led the charge
and saved Great Yong from peril.
Your Emperor swore an oath on the spot
that Great Yong and Great Yan
would be ruler and subject for generations,
never to forsake one another.
Most of you
were present at that time.
This is my son.
He was 21 years old.
He joined the army at 13,
started as a lowly foot soldier.
In 8 years,
he repelled the Quanrong invasions
67 times
and achieved countless merits in battle.
On the 14th of April,
at Xunlie Terrace,
he was trampled to death by horses.
This is my daughter!
On the 16th of April,
she rode to save her captured mother.
While passing Weishuihong Lake,
she died amidst the chaos of battle.
They were warriors of Great Yan!
Zhuge Huai,
carry out the execution.
Carry out the execution!
Don't!
Yan Xun!
No!
Please spare my son.
Mother!
Why did you do this?
Father is gone.
Brother is gone too.
All our kin are gone.
Are you leaving me too?
X-Xun.
Promise me.
You must live on.
Even if life is worse than death,
you must live on.
Mother!
♪ The sky is so vast ♪
♪ The dark clouds are gray ♪
♪ The rain is falling ♪
♪ The eagle is flying ♪
♪ In the vast wilderness ♪
♪ The wind blows ♪
♪ I'm fearless of death ♪
♪ And I'll never have regrets ♪
♪ The lonely black eagle ♪
♪ Is flying against the light ♪
♪ Where is my hometown? ♪
Yan Xun! Move!
♪ In the vast world ♪
♪ I have no origin ♪
♪ And no destination ♪
♪ A pair of stubborn wings ♪
♪ Is born to fly ♪
You risked everything
to block that blade for me.
From that moment,
I swore never to fail you.
Chu,
you are my chosen Queen of Great Yan.
Let go!
Chu.
It doesn't matter if you don't remember.
For me, just you waking up
is enough.
I won't force you to remember me
and believe what I say.
I will wait for you
until the day you remember.
Your Majesty.
Drink this,
and you'll get better.
Your Majesty.
Zhuge Yue's body
has been retrieved.
Lady Chu,
we are discussing how to dispose of
the corpse of Great Yong's
chief general, Zhuge Yue.
Do you have any advice?
He was a general of Great Yong?
Yes.
A few months ago,
if he hadn't led his men into Great Yan
to ambush you and His Majesty
at Mount Ximin,
you wouldn't have fallen into
the frozen lake.
How did he die?
Together with you,
he fell into the frozen lake
and died.
This man committed countless crimes.
He was once your fiercest rival.
When you were a slave in Great Yong,
he repeatedly tortured
and oppressed you.
Later, he prevented you and His Majesty
from returning to Great Yan
and clashed with you many times.
This Moon-breaking Sword
was his personal possession.
It once crossed swords with you.
Do you recall this sword?
Moon-breaking Sword?
The Zhuge family has abused and killed
female slaves for generations.
Your sisters, Qi and Ba,
and your brother Linxi
all died at Zhuge Yue's hands.
Countless soldiers
and civilians of Great Yan
also perished
under the Moon-breaking Sword.
After you escaped Qingshan Manor,
you and His Majesty vowed
to end slavery and war,
and to defeat your enemies.
Take a look, Lady Chu.
Can you recognize this villain
from Great Yong?
After all,
you were with him for so many years.
Then burn him.
Let this sword
and this corpse
appease the souls of Great Yan's people.
Lady Chu was once at Qingshan Manor,
spending day and night with Zhuge Yue...
Enough.
Three months ago,
during the battle at the frozen lake,
if Chu and I hadn't
joined forces
against the Yong Army,
this Zhuge Yue,
who was so elusive,
would still be Great Yan's greatest enemy.
Remember.
Chu is a hero who protected our country.
She is also the only Queen of Great Yan.
As for this sinner's corpse,
Great Yan wants no part of it.
Send him back
to the Zhuge family of Great Yong.
Protect the Queen!
Chu?
Chu!
Chu,
how do you feel?
Have you recalled anything?
I feel like I know you.
But I can't remember.
Why did those people want to kill me?
What is going on?
Chu.
Take the medicine first.
Your hand...
Chu!
Do you remember now?
Your hand...
Why is that when I see it,
I feel so sad?
Chu.
I knew our lives
were inseparable long ago.
[Three months ago, Ximeng]
Don't go any further.
Further ahead is Great Yan's territory.
Not until we pass Mount Ximin
will we enter it.
Here,
we can hunt good game.
I have verified it.
This man is indeed General Zhuge Yue
of Great Yong.
Judging by where he was found,
he was carried by the undercurrents
of Qianzhang Lake
and washed up near Mount Ximin.
He is severely injured
and suffering from hypothermia.
It is a miracle he has survived this long.
[King of Ximeng]
But I fear he won't make it.
A dead man is likely of no use.
[Qiu Lin, Left General of Ximeng]
Go.
Throw him back into Qianzhang Lake.
Did I say to let him die?
May I ask,
what use is a dying man?
Sometimes the dead
are more useful than the living,
especially him.
Feed him Bone-Chilling Grass.
News from Great Yan.
Recently,
they have been searching
for his whereabouts.
They want to see him, dead or alive.
There are plenty of death row prisoners
in the dungeon.
Soldiers!
Formation!
Why wouldn't I want to marry Yan Xun?
Great Yong will retreat soon.
His Majesty will then marry her
as the Queen of Great Yan.
As long as you're willing to
put on this wedding robe
and marry me,
I will let her go.