This is exactly it.
This is Huotu water.
It was indeed formulated not long ago.
But this amount
is just enough for one day.
Where did you find this?
If you can guarantee this
for 7 consecutive days,
her eyes will be saved.
I found it by accident.
It's just a 7-day supply.
What's so hard about that?
Qiao,
look up.
Qiao, how do you feel?
Li Ce.
This is Huotu water.
Zhuge Yue. It was sent by Zhuge Yue.
Wait.
This medicine is indeed Huotu water.
But why must you assume
that it was sent by Zhuge Yue?
Couldn't it be me, the peerless,
romantic, and elegant young man,
who found it?
I used this medicine
when I was in Qingshan Manor.
It was formulated by the Zhuge family.
After putting it in the eyes,
you can see the smallest details
and see in darkness
as clearly as in daylight.
The person who sent me the medicine
is Zhuge Yue, right?
Qiao,
this medicine...
Last night,
did you come to my room?
Why would I go to your room?
It wasn't you, as expected.
It was him.
It must have been him.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 5]
I knew it was you.
General Zhuge.
Your martial skill and intellect
truly live up to your reputation.
Everyone knows
you led the Moon Guard of 20
and dared to sneak into Great Yan
to fight Heir Apparent Yant's
massive Black Eagle Army.
But they don't know after you fell into
the extremely cold frozen lake
bordering Ximeng
and have been searched for
by the Yan Army for 3 months,
you actually managed to survive.
Why are you here?
Don't be so cold.
I just don't understand,
so I wanted to ask you on Qiao's behalf.
Since you're not dead,
why do you hide
and refuse to show yourself to her?
I have my own reasons.
You don't need to know.
General Zhuge.
You are a grown man,
yet so indecisive.
If you want to reunite with her,
just go up to her.
She is waiting for you right now.
If you still want to pretend you are dead,
then stop sneaking around,
visiting her one moment
and sending medicine the next.
Qiao is not stupid.
How could she not sense
you're still alive?
What are you doing?
Am I wrong?
Zhuge Yue.
Are you going to kill me?
What are you going to do?
Let me tell you,
if you kill me,
the consequences will be very serious.
Qiao.
Where is Zhuge Yue?
Where is he?
Zhuge Yue?
He didn't come.
Qiao, I told you
that I asked Song Cheng
to find this medicine for you.
Why don't you believe me?
I know it's you,
Zhuge Yue.
Qiao,
I want you to get better.
Zhuge Yue,
I will definitely wait for you.
It's the 6th day now.
Qiao,
how are you feeling?
I can vaguely see some light and shadows.
That's great!
These past few days,
not only did I have Song Cheng
find Huotu water for you,
but I also had him bring
some medicine
for bone and tendon injuries.
The effect is very good.
I think in another half month,
even if you can't use swords and spears,
moving freely shouldn't be a problem.
Qiao,
I know you don't believe what I say.
But whether it's Great Yong, Great Yan,
or Biantang,
everyone knows Zhuge Yue died
in battle at Qianzhang Lake.
If he's not dead,
why won't he come to see you?
I think,
after you finish
your last day of medicine,
just come back to Biantang with me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll stay right here.
Qiao,
your eyes need 14 days to recover.
The situation in Great Yan
is unstable right now.
It's safest for you to go back
to Biantang with me.
If Great Yan shuts down
due to internal strife,
then
we won't be able to leave
even if we want to.
Li Ce,
I appreciate your kindness.
When my arms get better
and I can move freely,
it'll be fine
for me to stay here alone.
Qiao.
Li Ce,
thank you.
But you don't need to persuade me anymore.
Your Highness,
the situation in Great Yan
is unstable right now.
Cheng Yuan is killing people everywhere.
The various tribes in Great Yan
could rebel at any time.
I'm afraid it's not suitable
for us to stay here for long.
I know everything you're saying.
But Qiao doesn't want to go with me.
Your Highness,
you're the Crown Prince of Biantang.
This affects Biantang.
Song Cheng.
Go hire a few more people.
They need to be strong.
And ropes and wooden sticks.
And knockout incense.
Knockout incense?
Get the carriage
and luggage ready as well.
Tomorrow morning,
after Qiao finishes
her 7th bottle of Huotu water,
we'll take her back to Biantang by force.
She still can't see clearly now,
and her limbs haven't recovered yet.
We'll knock her out
and tie her up if we have to.
Knock her out?
That's General Chu.
Are we able
to beat her?
You're right.
No, no.
That's Qiao.
How about this?
Change ropes to silk.
And buy the best knockout incense.
If that doesn't work,
just mix it in my favorite ambergris.
It smells good.
Prepare the biggest carriage too.
Let's tie her up properly.
What are you waiting for? Go!
Yes, yes.
Right.
Remember to buy Qiao's favorite snacks.
Don't let her starve on the way.
Yes.
I'll go arrange it right away.
I will buy Qiao's favorite
snacks.
You...
I'll do it myself.
Heir Apparent,
Fourth Young Master Zhuge
sent some medicine.
He said when Miss Chu
lived in Qingshan Manor,
♪ On the water ♪
she always used it.
♪ Countless ♪
Zhuge Yue?
♪ Ripples rise ♪
Is he here?
The Fourth Young Master
sent Yue Qi to deliver it.
♪ Through the mortal world ♪
♪ With meetings and goodbyes ♪
I don't want his medicine.
He must be trying to poison me.
♪ How unfair fate is ♪
♪ It gave all the memories back to you ♪
♪ Yet left me ♪
Sending you poison
in this freezing weather?
♪ Stuck right here ♪
You really take yourself too seriously.
Sending medicine to a servant like me
in this freezing weather?
♪ Rain falls down ♪
♪ Lingering thoughts ♪
It must be hard for you
♪ Awake once more ♪
to take so much trouble.
Sharp-tongued.
♪ Let the wind shape ♪
I think you've fully recovered
from your illness.
♪ Another me ♪
♪ How can I escape ♪
♪ All the reflections that hold you? ♪
♪ Behind the illusions
of the moon in water ♪
♪ I wait to sink deep ♪
♪ May fortune smile on all below ♪
♪ Just to hear when you'll come home ♪
♪ Braving schemes alone ♪
♪ Treading through thorns ♪
♪ Searching for your name ♪
♪ Till storms rise again ♪
♪ Not a single regret remains ♪
♪ Melt the ice ♪
♪ That fate has wrought ♪
♪ Let the night ♪
♪ Forever glow ♪
Who are you?
Who exactly are you?
Why did you bring me Huotu water?
Qi.
Are you Yue Qi?
Yue Qi, why won't you speak?
Did you become mute
from your injuries at the frozen lake?
What about Zhuge Yue?
Where is Zhuge Yue?
Impossible.
You're lying to me.
He's not dead.
He clearly saved me from the frozen lake.
Why didn't the Moon Guard look for him?
Why didn't you look for him?
Go find him!
Find him!
Find him! Find him!
♪ The dust in the world ♪
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
You are Zhuge Yue,
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
not Yue Qi.
♪ And not be scared? ♪
♪ A slight ripple ♪
♪ Floating life hangs by a thread ♪
This was left behind
when you saved me,
♪ The more pulled, the softer it gets ♪
right?
♪ Who dares to say forever? ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
I am Yue Qi.
♪ Grudges and grace
were never meant to be ♪
Zhuge Yue
♪ Why must you take and demand so much? ♪
is dead.
♪ Go weaving ♪
♪ Grand and glorious excuses ♪
♪ We once beheld ♪
♪ A mirage on earth ♪
♪ Beauty never ♪
♪ Lasts for long ♪
♪ No matter how a jade is carved ♪
♪ It's just a stone ♪
♪ It will eventually disappear ♪
Zhuge Yue has a scar on his left hand.
It is crescent-shaped.
You are not him.
You are not Zhuge Yue.
The medicine I gave you is a 10-day dose.
It's enough for you to go back
and save your woman.
If you don't return
as promised in 10 days,
I'll let you know
what a living hell is.
Once you take it,
the scar on your body will heal.
All traces of who you used to be
will be erased.
From now on, Zhuge Yue will no longer
exist in this world.
You will only be my shadow,
my slave.
Your Highness,
you must make a decision quickly.
The Black Eagle Army of Great Yan
is searching this area right now.
If you don't take Miss Chu away,
we won't be able to retreat unscathed.
How about this?
I will count to 3,
and we charge in together.
Understand?
Understood.
One.
Two.
Three.
Your Highness.
Are you sure Miss Chu's martial arts
haven't returned yet?
Not sure.
But
I'm sure,
certain, and positive
that her eyes haven't recovered.
Let's play it by ear.
-Play it by ear.
One.
Two.
Three.
Qiao.
Whose is this?
I... I...
Li Ce,
I'll go back to Biantang with you.
Your Highness,
right now, inside the city of Great Yan,
people are searching
for Miss Chu everywhere.
Why are the borders of Great Yan
guarded so poorly?
Could there be some changes
in the city of Great Yan?
Hurry out of the city.
Don't stop.
Yes.
[Itinerant Court, Great Yan]
His Majesty is unconscious.
Cheng Yuan blocked the news,
and we can't find out anything!
Could it be that the worst has happened?
[Huo Sang,
Elder of the Baichuan Tribe of Great Yan]
The worst has happened?
[Tu Bo,
Elder of the Hongchuan Tribe of Great Yan]
I'm afraid he won't wake up.
Elders, don't be too anxious.
Let's wait for news of His Majesty.
If His Majesty really doesn't wake up,
[Katuo,
Chief of the Jinhui Tribe of Great Yan]
there is someone
who can take over his position.
You mean...
[Elder of the Lanchuan Tribe of Great Yan]
the Snowy Region Tribe?
In terms of kinship,
General Huan
is His Majesty's cousin after all.
The Yan family all died
at the hands of the Yong people,
leaving only His Majesty.
His Majesty is not married yet.
If something happens,
Huan Huan taking over the position
of King of Great Yan
would be perfectly reasonable.
How can
a little girl inherit the throne?
But this little girl
has made more military achievements
than all of us combined.
Plus, with the prestige
of the Snowy Region Tribe,
I'm afraid that when the time comes,
even Hongchuan and Pale,
tribes with deep foundations,
can hardly turn the tide.
Chief of the Jinhui Tribe's words
are indeed reasonable.
In terms of military achievements,
we are far behind the Snowy Region Tribe.
But Chief of the Jinhui Tribe,
you are also a young hero.
Why let your own tribe
be subordinate to others?
Elder Pale, you truly understand me.
Naturally, I won't let Jinhui
be subordinate to anyone else.
Lady Helian.
I have brought someone
to you, General Cheng.
[Wunan Goddess]
Can your medicine
really cure His Majesty's illness?
When will His Majesty wake up?
This medicine is definitely effective.
Please trust me, My Lord.
I am also confused
about your doubts.
Or there's a possibility...
that His Majesty is the true ruler
blessed by the gods of Great Yan.
If you want His Majesty to wake up,
my medicine alone is not enough.
It also needs...
the will of the gods.
Men of our tribe,
for hundreds of years, our Jinhui Tribe
has always been the cheetahs
of the grasslands.
Warriors,
tell me,
what is a cheetah?
The king!
The king of the grasslands!
For centuries,
we've pledged our loyalty
to the Black Eagles of the grasslands
and served the Yan family as kings.
But what did the Yan family do?
What have they brought to the grasslands?
Yan Shicheng
let his emotions dictate his actions,
ruining the lives
of over a dozen of his own kin
and plunging Great Yan into peril.
And Yan Xun,
for his own selfish desires,
ambushed the Yong Army at Mount Ximin,
leaving tens of thousands of Yan Army
soldiers dead at Meilin Pass.
And for a Yong woman,
he disregarded the safety of Great Yan.
How can such a Black Eagle
be King?
-Not fit to be King! Not fit to be King!
Warriors!
Follow me
to capture Great Yan
and kill Yan Xun!
-Capture Great Yan! Kill Yan Xun!
Urgent report!
Here.
General Huan.
Katuo has rebelled
with 30,000 Jinhui soldiers.
They're approaching the Great Yan camp!
Of the 13 tribes of Great Yan,
7 have already started
mobilizing their troops.
What?
Katuo has rebelled?
Huan,
you can't get involved.
Together with General Cheng,
we only have 10,000 Black Eagle soldiers,
who are responsible
for guarding the Capital of Great Yan.
Unless they attack the capital,
[An Luo, Snowy Region Tribe of Great Yan]
we can't intervene.
General Huan!
The rebels are only 20 li
from the Great Yan camp.
They will arrive soon!
Please give your orders, General Huan.
I will ask General Shiyan for help.
We are kin of the Yan family.
I'll use the loyalty
of my Snowy Region Tribe
and our prestige in Great Yan
to take charge of the military
on behalf of His Majesty.
Huan,
you're going to command the whole army?
Yes.
If I don't,
Great Yan will immediately
fall into a civil war.
They're attacking.
Soldiers!
You are the Black Eagle Army,
the Great Yan Army,
the strongest warriors
defending Great Yan!
Now someone is rebelling
and trying to destroy
the unity of Great Yan.
What should we do?
Defend Great Yan to the death!
-Defend Great Yan to the death!
From now on,
I'll take charge of the entire army
on behalf of King Yan Xun!
Soldiers,
follow me to fight the rebels
and defend Great Yan!
-Fight the rebels! Defend Great Yan!
-Defend Great Yan!
[Border of Biantang, Great Yong]
Chun'er.
The situation is turbulent now,
and I don't know what will happen.
I must focus on dealing with it.
So I can't keep you here any longer.
This guard
will escort you back to Great Yong.
Take good care of yourself
and don't cause any more trouble.
Che.
This lake is so blue
and so clean.
Do you still remember?
When we were in Zhenhuang City,
every Double Third Festival,
we would go for a picnic in the suburbs.
The Luo River
that flows through Zhenhuang City
is also so clear
and blue.
Chun'er,
let's go.
Chun'er!
Save her!
[Tomb of Li Ru, Prince of Chang]
[Li Yan, Prince of Luo, Biantang]
Your Highness!
Someone fell into the water!
Qiao.
It's been a few days
since you finished the Huotu water.
Are your eyes feeling any better?
Can you see anything?
Like,
my handsome figure.
Right.
You are blindfolded,
so you shouldn't be able to see anything.
Never mind.
I'll just wait until the 14th day.
Qiao,
I specifically asked Song Cheng
to buy you
these delicious snacks in town.
Great Yan is a poor place.
The food and drinks
are not as good as Biantang's.
You must be hungry. Have a taste.
Qiao,
we've arrived at a town.
There's a lantern show.
Let's go take a look.
No need.
Qiao,
don't be sad.
If you ask me,
Zhuge Yue might not be dead.
Think about it.
He's highly skilled in martial arts
and very cunning.
He's always killing others.
How could he die?
No way.
He must be alive.
Really.
Is it possible
that he was saved by a foreign weirdo,
and under that weirdo's pressure,
he doesn't dare to acknowledge you,
afraid of bringing you danger,
so he's been hiding from you?
You know,
foreigners
must have some weird fetishes...
What's wrong?
Get off the carriage.
Let's watch the lantern show.
Let's go.
Careful.
Come.
Qiao,
this is the lantern show.
It's very lively.
They sell lanterns ahead.
Let me take you to have a look.
Watch your step.
Lanterns.
♪ Through the mortal world ♪
♪ With meetings and goodbyes ♪
Sir and Madam,
take a look at my lanterns.
We're here. They sell lanterns here.
♪ How unfair fate is ♪
Sir,
♪ It gave all the memories back to you ♪
do you have rabbit lanterns?
♪ Yet left me ♪
The more you care about
worldly possessions,
♪ Stuck right here ♪
the more they will hinder your actions.
If a person has no attachments,
♪ Rain falls down ♪
what is the point
of being like a block of wood?
♪ Lingering thoughts ♪
If one day,
♪ Awake once more ♪
the enemy uses what you care about
to confuse your mind and take your life,
♪ Let the wind shape ♪
and you implicate others when you die,
♪ Another me ♪
then you will know
whether being a block of wood
is good or bad.
♪ How can I escape ♪
♪ All the reflections that hold you? ♪
♪ Behind the illusions
of the moon in water ♪
♪ I wait to sink deep ♪
♪ May fortune smile on all below ♪
♪ Just to hear when you'll come home ♪
Didn't you say
that having attachments
would hinder your actions?
♪ Braving schemes alone ♪
It's just a lantern.
♪ Treading through thorns ♪
♪ Searching for your name ♪
You know so little of the world.
You would just keep thinking about it
if I hadn't bought it for you.
♪ Till storms rise again ♪
♪ Not a single regret remains ♪
♪ Melt the ice ♪
♪ That fate has wrought ♪
♪ Let the night ♪
♪ Forever glow ♪
[Tangjing, Biantang]
Let me see.
Stop!
Go ahead.
Who is in the carriage?
Why?
You want to search my carriage too?
Your Highness, I pay my respects to you.
Great Yan has been in turmoil recently.
To prevent it from affecting Biantang,
our superiors ordered
that all personnel entering the city
must be strictly searched.
Since it is your duty,
I won't blame you.
Well,
I have an exotic beauty in my carriage
that I brought back from my travels.
Why don't you get in and check
if she is a spy from Great Yan?
I wouldn't dare.
Please enter the city, Your Highness.
Chu Qiao?
We have lost our way.
If we keep going,
none of us will make it back alive.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Zhuge Yue!
Your Majesty, you mean
that the woman's identity is suspicious.
You've been with me for 3 days.
Why don't you ask who I am?
Zhuge Yue.
I saw you.