[Tangjing, Capital of Biantang]
Your Majesty.
Beauties.
-Your Majesty.
-Your Majesty, come here.
Come here, Your Majesty.
-I'm right here.
-Where are you?
Catch me.
I'll surely catch you.
Come here.
Over here.
[Li Jiao, Biantang Emperor]
You won't catch me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
-Your Majesty.
-Hurry up.
Come here,
beauties.
You run really fast.
Your Majesty, I'm here.
-Your Majesty.
-Come here, Your Majesty.
Come here.
-Come and catch me.
-Come here.
Your Majesty.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 6]
[Biantang Empress]
Spare us, Your Majesty!
-Spare us, Your Majesty!
-Spare us!
It's not your fault.
You couldn't disobey the Emperor's orders.
Chief Fang,
let them leave.
The floor is too cold.
Kneeling too long will harm their health.
Yes,
Your Majesty.
Get up now.
-Thank you, Your Majesty.
Physician,
how is His Majesty?
Your Majesty,
His Majesty has liver qi stagnation,
poor blood circulation,
and cold invasion,
which caused sudden hematemesis.
Is there a cure?
Yes,
but His Majesty needs to drink less wine
and rest more,
so he can recover quickly.
Go and arrange the medicinal diet.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Did you hear, Your Majesty?
The physician said
it's not a big problem.
It's probably related
to the cold weather recently.
Just rest, Your Majesty.
Do not overthink or overwork yourself.
All these years,
you've shielded me from so much,
running back and forth
between the imperial court and the harem.
It's been really hard for you.
Your Majesty, to share your burdens
is my blessing.
Hardships are not worth mentioning.
It's been hard for you.
His Majesty's health
is getting worse day by day.
He vomited blood again today.
Then what do you plan to do, Your Majesty?
The two beauties you sent to His Majesty
are very good.
He fell in love at first sight.
Continue to select some beautiful women
and send them into the palace,
just to make His Majesty happy.
I understand.
[Zhan Ziyu, Empress's Male Favorite]
Your Majesty,
there is another thing.
His Highness has returned from Great Yan.
And
he brought a woman
of unknown origin with him.
Who is she?
I do not know yet,
but it is better to be careful.
After all, the Crown Prince
is growing more powerful by the day.
If he develops
disloyal thoughts towards you,
that would not be good.
Then you will act on my behalf
to find out her identity.
Yes.
You have accompanied me for 3 days.
Why don't you ask who I am
and why I wanted to jump into the lake?
In this vast world,
everyone has their own sorrows.
If you don't want to say, I won't ask.
You remind me of someone.
That person
must be very important to you.
Yes.
Very important.
But he never wants to see me again,
and I can't forget him.
Then can you temporarily
treat me as that person,
until you truly forget him
and are no longer in pain?
Can I?
Can I forget him?
As long as you are willing,
I can always accompany you.
[Crown Prince's Mansion, Biantang]
Come.
Careful.
Here, hold this.
Li Ce.
This is the Crown Prince's Mansion?
Why does it feel so weird?
Qiao,
I can't explain it in one sentence.
I'll explain it to you later.
Follow me first.
Hurry.
Come in first.
Qiao,
these are all the beautiful clothes
I brought back from my travels.
So revealing.
Unbearable to look at.
These clothes don't even cover the body.
I can't wear them.
Qiao,
I didn't mean that.
It's an emergency.
I'll explain it to you later, okay?
Come.
Your Highness,
it's bad.
We just entered the mansion,
and Her Majesty already knows.
Someone from the palace has arrived,
asking you to enter the palace
immediately to pay your respects.
I've been away for months,
but Mother
is as well-informed as ever.
It doesn't matter.
I will go right now.
Okay.
Here, Qiao.
Your Highness.
Remember to change your clothes.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I'm Zhan Ziyu, Grand Minister of Rites,
acting on Her Majesty's oral decree.
His Highness has been traveling
for a long time.
Her Majesty misses him very much.
She personally sent us
to present His Highness
with 10 pieces of deer skin glue,
5 boxes of Baiyi incense,
and 5 wild ginsengs,
to condition His Highness's body.
These items are all personally
bestowed by Her Majesty.
You must deliver them to His Highness
and place them properly inside the hall.
If there is any mistake,
you will not be forgiven.
-Yes.
Who is in there?
Your Highness,
this person looks a bit unfamiliar.
You are from Fengyi Palace?
Why have I never seen you
at Her Majesty's place?
Your Highness,
I am a subordinate of Lord Zhan.
Your Highness, Your Highness!
I have a stomachache.
I need to return to the mansion.
Catch the assassin!
An assassin has indeed infiltrated
the Crown Prince's Mansion
to harm His Highness.
Arrest this assassin!
Who are you?
What are you doing?
This is the Crown Prince's Mansion.
I am the Crown Prince's person.
The Crown Prince's person?
I often visit the Crown Prince's Mansion.
Why have I never met you?
The Crown Prince went north for a tour.
It is not surprising
that he brought back a woman.
And who are you?
Does the Crown Prince need to report
where he goes and what he does to you?
In that case,
please enter the palace
and explain the whole story
to Her Majesty with the Crown Prince.
Take her!
She is not an assassin.
She is Princess Fu.
Your Highness, didn't you enter
the palace to pay respects to Her Majesty?
Why are you here?
I just returned to Tangjing today.
I suddenly had a stomachache
and feared being disrespectful
to my mother.
So I turned back halfway.
Unexpectedly, I ran into you
having a misunderstanding
with Princess Fu.
Princess Fu?
Lord Zhan,
this woman is not the assassin
you speak of,
but the daughter of the Prince of Pingnan
I found after going through
many hardships,
Princess Fu.
Seven years ago,
the Prince of Pingnan
went to war with his family
and died in battle.
Princess Fu was separated
from them ever since,
and there was no news of her.
My trip to Great Yan this time
was exactly because
I heard of Princess Fu's whereabouts,
and I went specifically to bring her back.
At that time, Lord Zhan, you
hadn't yet entered
the palace to serve Her Majesty,
so you know very little about this matter.
Why don't you
go ask my mother?
She'll naturally
clear your doubts.
Your Highness, given what you said,
I will return to the palace
and ask Her Majesty for clarification.
Excuse me.
Let's go.
How is he?
Wake up, wake up.
He's dying.
General Cheng.
We have lost our way.
If we keep going,
we probably won't be able to hold on,
and none of us will make it back alive.
Are you sure it's just ahead?
It's just ahead.
The Altar of Fire
at the top of Mount Hei is right ahead.
As long as we place
His Majesty on the Altar of Fire,
His Majesty will be protected
by the gods of Great Yan
and will surely come back to life.
Keep moving forward.
Yes.
This is the place.
This is the Altar of Fire.
His Majesty will be saved.
-His Majesty!
Who was that eunuch just now?
How dare he be so bossy
in the Crown Prince's Mansion?
Zhan Ziyu is not a eunuch.
He is the Grand Minister of Rites,
a close minister to my mother.
Most of the things he does
are my mother's ideas.
Your mother?
Your Highness.
-Your Highness.
You're all here.
Why didn't you tell me you were back?
Your Highness,
did you forget about me?
Of course not.
Then look at this.
This is the sachet I made for you
when you were away.
Smell it.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you must be tired.
Let's go inside and sit down.
-Your Highness.
-Here.
This is the shawl I made for you
when you were away.
I designed it myself.
You can't buy it outside.
I also made one for myself.
We can wear them together later.
Beauty.
Why are you crying?
I saw that your face
was not as rosy as before.
You must have been exhausted in Great Yan.
It broke my heart to see you like this.
Who is she?
-Who is she?
-Your Highness.
She... she...
She is...
Who are you?
Tell us the truth.
She's a vixen.
-Little vixen.
-Your Highness.
Since you're unfaithful
and have a little vixen,
we will let them be.
If we are here,
the little vixen can't be.
If she is here, we won't be.
Your Highness,
you can go be a couple
with the little vixen!
Sisters,
let's go.
[Minglu,
Chief Maid of the Crown Prince's Mansion]
By the way,
where is Lady Ziming?
Why haven't I seen her since I returned?
-Lady Ziming?
Your Highness,
she hasn't seen you for days.
She worried too much
and suffered a heart illness.
A heart illness?
I see.
She must be missing me.
Tell your lady
that I will go see her tonight.
This is the room prepared for you.
Before His Highness returned,
he had sent someone to arrange this.
But it was prepared in a hurry.
I will come to tidy it up tomorrow.
Please thank the Crown Prince for me.
I have always preferred things
to be simple.
This is enough.
May I ask how I should address you?
I am the chief maid of this mansion.
If you need anything, Princess,
just tell the maids,
and I will prepare it.
If not,
you won't need to address me normally.
What Princess Fu?
Princess Fu has been dead for a long time.
Seven years ago,
the Prince of Pingnan went against me
and publicly opposed my involvement
in state affairs at court.
So I had His Majesty send him
to fight on the southern border,
and he sacrificed
his life for the country.
Princess Fu
and Princess Consort of Pingnan
also went to the southern border with him.
They have long been dead,
leaving no trace.
Could it be that the woman
is not Princess Fu?
Then why did the Crown Prince...
The Crown Prince is a womanizer.
It's not surprising
that he would just find any woman.
But you said this woman
knows martial arts,
and the Crown Prince
even defied me for her.
That is somewhat unexpected.
Your Majesty, do you mean
that the woman's identity is suspicious?
His Majesty's health
won't last for many more days.
Once he dies,
whether Li Ce remains
the Crown Prince or is deposed
will be entirely up to me.
At this critical juncture,
no matter who this woman is,
she is of utmost importance.
If she is just a romantic affair,
we will report it to the Emperor
and make it known
to the whole imperial court.
If there really is a hidden agenda,
don't blame me
for not showing mercy
to my own flesh and blood.
I understand.
I will keep a close eye on
the Crown Prince's Mansion for you.
It's getting cold again.
You once promised me
that you'd watch the snow
with me every year.
[Spirit Tablet
of the Late Crown Prince Maocheng]
The snow is about to fall,
but you're not by my side.
It is you, the Emperor,
who broke your promise
and killed Crown Prince Maocheng.
Since you are so heartless,
don't blame me for being cruel.
Princess Fu.
It's so late.
Crown Prince, shouldn't you be going
to that sick lady's place?
What are you talking about, Princess Fu?
I have always loved you the most.
I will stay in your room tonight.
Ouch!
Princess,
what are you doing?
Let me ask you,
who is Princess Fu?
Why did you say I am her?
Careful.
Walls have ears.
Stop being so mysterious.
Fu,
don't be angry.
They...
They were all rewarded by my mother
while you were away.
Aren't you back now?
What's going on?
I'll make a long story short.
I am
a useless Crown Prince with no power.
Although there are many beauties
in this mansion,
they were all given to me by my mother.
Normally,
their duty
is not only to entertain me
and make me indulge in luxury
and sensual pleasures
but also to report my every word and deed
to my mother.
As for Fu,
she was the princess
of the Prince of Pingnan
and someone I used to like.
Now,
she is no longer alive.
You do look a bit like her.
I borrowed her identity for you
to protect you as much as possible.
In that case,
I misunderstood you.
Since you are pretending
to be Princess Fu,
from now on,
I will have to stay here for the night.
You have no idea.
What I fear the most
is being with them at night.
But
you're here now.
What do you mean?
Being with you—
Princess, Princess!
Be gentle!
Princess, it hurts!
It hurts!
Let me do it.
It's getting late.
Are we still hitting the road?
Lord Zhao finally found Chu Qiao.
We must travel overnight
to pass this news to Lord Muhe.
We can't delay.
Sir,
the bill.
Who are you?
What do you want?
If you dare tell what you know
to the Muhe family,
I'll make sure you never speak again.
Zhuge Yue. Zhuge Yue.
Zhuge Yue.
Zhuge Yue, where are you going?
Don't go.
Zhuge Yue, don't go.
Zhuge Yue. Zhuge Yue.
Where have you gone?
Come back.
Zhuge Yue.
Zhuge Yue!
Fu.
What's wrong?
Was I just
talking in my sleep?
Just now,
you kept calling Zhuge Yue's name.
I was afraid someone would hear,
so I woke you up.
What did you dream about?
Nothing.
Ever since I woke up at the frozen lake,
my dreams have been mostly the same.
Who is it?
Qiao.
You are indeed unmatched in martial arts
and dashingly cool.
Shut up.
This hidden weapon is poisonous.
What happened?
In this mansion,
someone wants my life.
Hansha Darts...
They're the hidden weapon
of the Muhe family of Great Yong.
I'm afraid
they didn't come for you.
[Zuiyue Restaurant]
Guests.
Remember,
sometimes
hearing is more real than seeing.
When you can't see,
you can actually find what you want.
Great,
[Zhao Kuo, Envoy of Great Yong]
you delivered yourself to me.
Chu Qiao,
I knew you were still alive.
I just didn't expect
that after hiding
in the Crown Prince's Mansion,
you would dare to come meet me alone.
If I hadn't shown up,
would you really have spared me?
You are right.
Back then, you and Yan Xun joined forces
to kill Young Master Muhe Xifeng
and took the opportunity
to bring down the Wei family.
Guess who in Great Yong
wants you dead more, the Muhe family
or the Wei family?
It's a pity that your worthless life
isn't enough to repay Young Master Muhe.
I will kill you first
and then kill that scoundrel Yan Xun!
Aren't you the most capable general
in Great Yan?
Aren't you the invincible leader
of the Xiuli Army?
I will send you to hell right now!
Xing.
Xing, wake up.
♪ On the water ♪
♪ Countless ♪
♪ Ripples rise ♪
♪ Through the mortal world ♪
Zhuge Yue.
♪ With meetings and goodbyes ♪
♪ How unfair fate is ♪
I've seen you.
♪ It gave all the memories back to you ♪
Zhuge Yue,
♪ Yet left me ♪
I've seen you.
♪ Stuck right here ♪
♪ Rain falls down ♪
♪ Lingering thoughts ♪
♪ Awake once more ♪
♪ Let the wind shape ♪
♪ Another me ♪
♪ How can I escape ♪
♪ All the reflections that hold you? ♪
♪ Behind the illusions
of the moon in water ♪
Zhuge Yue.
I've finally seen you.
♪ I wait to sink deep ♪
Today is exactly the 14th day.
♪ May fortune smile on all below ♪
The Huotu water you gave me worked.
♪ Just to hear when you'll come home ♪
I know you are still alive,
♪ Braving schemes alone ♪
and I also know you sent the Huotu water.
♪ Treading through thorns ♪
Zhuge Yue,
♪ Searching for your name ♪
you've been alive all along.
♪ Till storms rise again ♪
But why have you been hiding from me?
♪ Not a single regret remains ♪
You risked getting hurt to kill Zhao Kuo
♪ Melt the ice ♪
♪ That fate has wrought ♪
and used your internal energy
to hold your breath,
making me think you were dying.
♪ Let the night ♪
Was it just to draw me out?
Yes.
♪ Forever glow ♪
Everyone said you were dead,
but I knew you were alive.
I could feel you by my side.
If it weren't for you protecting me,
Li Ce and I
wouldn't have made it
to Biantang so smoothly.
Xing.
Do you know
the Xiuli Army died in battle,
and Miss Zhong was also
killed by Cheng Yuan?
I know.
Do you know
I almost thought
that I got Zhong Yu,
the Xiuli Army,
and the person I care about most killed?
Do you still remember
the day I left for Great Yan?
You told me
you needed me.
Now,
Zhuge Yue,
can you stay for me?
General Huan, you're tired
from putting down the rebellion.
Go back and rest.
Are you sure it was a woman
who entered your room?
-As the King commands!
I am already living like a ghost.
What does it matter if I die?
She looks a bit like...
the escaped slave
Great Yan and Great Yong are hunting down,
Chu Qiao.