Your Majesty!
-Your Majesty!
General Huan,
we found no trace of His Majesty.
Your Majesty!
General Huan!
[Rebirth]
[Episode 4]
It's hypothermia.
Qianzhang Lake has been frozen for years.
The cold has invaded his internal organs.
Ordinary people
cannot withstand hypothermia.
Summon the imperial physician!
Yes!
Lock down the itinerant court!
Search the area around Qianzhang Lake!
Find Chu Qiao for me—
no matter whether dead or alive!
-Yes!
You've been checking his pulse
for an hour.
How is he?
G-General Cheng.
Although His Majesty's wound is not fatal,
it is close to the heart.
Coupled with falling into the lake
which caused the extreme cold
to invade his organs,
all his internal organs have...
Are you saying he can't be saved?
He can.
But he needs the protection of the gods.
I am only a mortal.
The medicine I practice
can only alleviate pain.
But I cannot...
alter fate.
[Ximeng, the border of Great Yan]
This is the border
between Ximeng and Great Yan.
They can't return
to Great Yan or Great Yong.
They must be hiding in this area.
Search carefully.
If we can't bring this person back,
we will all die.
[Ximeng Lingyue Clan's
Queen of Lingyue]
-Yes!
That cave ahead.
You few, follow me.
The rest of you, block the cave.
If you find anyone,
don't let them escape.
-Yes!
Don't move.
Take me to the King of Ximeng.
It's been 3 days.
There's still no news of His Majesty.
We need to go and see
what exactly is going on.
-We want to see His Majesty!
General Cheng has ordered that
His Majesty is unwell
and needs to rest and recover.
General Cheng?
General Cheng is nothing.
Get out of the way!
You can't enter!
You can't go in!
Step aside!
We want to see His Majesty!
You can't enter.
Lord Tumu, let it go.
General Cheng's men
are guarding the bedchamber.
Going there now
won't do you any good.
Are we supposed to just wait?
A country cannot go a day without a king.
We need to know
whether His Majesty is in danger or not!
Now, all the imperial doctors
have been locked in the bedchamber
by Cheng Yuan,
not allowed to leave.
What exactly are they hiding from us?
There are too many ears here.
You must speak carefully, my lord.
What am I afraid of?
Do you know
that in recent days,
Cheng Yuan led his men
to destroy several strongholds
of the Universal Harmony Guild?
He mobilized his Black Eagle Army
to the surroundings
of the Capital of Great Yan.
Are you saying
Cheng Yuan has brought his troops
to the Capital of Great Yan?
General Cheng used the excuse
of providing protection,
saying he was worried about chaos
occurring in the capital.
I think the first person to cause trouble
in the capital
would be Cheng Yuan.
You exaggerate, My Lord.
Lord Tumu must be talking about me.
Well...
Lord Huo Sang.
General Shi.
Lord Tumu.
You guys are in high spirits.
May I ask why you are trespassing
on the royal palace?
I should be asking you that, Lord Cheng.
You deployed troops to seal off
the itinerant court without authorization,
and confined His Majesty.
What are you up to?
His Majesty is safe and sound.
He'll attend the court soon.
Word came out of the court yesterday
that His Majesty is ill—
His Majesty just caught a cold.
He is resting in his bedchamber.
He'll recover soon.
To prevent any accident
in the Capital of Great Yan,
I will inform General Huan
to preside over
the capital's security matters with me.
From today on,
anyone who spreads rumors
about His Majesty being ill
and dampens public morale
will not be forgiven.
I want the medicine for hypothermia.
The medicine is here.
What do you have in exchange?
Now, what do you have in exchange?
If you hesitate any longer,
the woman in the cave
will lose her only chance to live.
I'll trade my life for it.
This is a secret poison of Ximeng.
You'll become
a living dead if you eat it.
Be it General Zhuge of Great Yong
or the manager
of Great Yong's Qingshan Manor—
they are all dead.
I've been dead for a long time.
Didn't you want to walk for them?
Stand up.
Keep walking!
Young Master Huai.
Young Master Huai, please forgive Xiaoliu.
-Young Master Huai, please spare her.
-Go!
Young Master Huai.
Are you walking or not?
If you don't, I'll beat her to death.
Stop beating!
I'll walk. I'll walk.
Zhuge Yue?
What are you doing?
You,
what's your name?
This is the wound medicine
Young Master Yue rewarded you with.
Use it quickly.
♪ The dust in the world ♪
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
♪ And not be scared? ♪
♪ A slight ripple ♪
♪ We face ♪
♪ The heavy thunderstorm together ♪
♪ Even with extreme pain ♪
♪ We don't even wince ♪
♪ No matter how a jade is carved ♪
♪ It's just a stone ♪
♪ It will eventually disappear ♪
Stay in Qingshan Manor.
From now on,
your name is Xing.
♪ We mock karma ♪
♪ For being unfair ♪
♪ Why is life ♪
♪ Often filled with regrets? ♪
Xing.
Here.
♪ The snow falls ♪
Take the medicine.
♪ With fate ♪
♪ It will eventually ♪
♪ Fall before ♪
♪ The dawn ♪
♪ As a foreigner ♪
♪ Don't look, don't ask, and don't speak ♪
♪ Wander ♪
♪ With no resentment at all ♪
♪ The lock in my heart ♪
♪ Put the memories ♪
♪ In the silence of the night ♪
♪ Look ♪
♪ The mortal world has forgotten me ♪
♪ I wish ♪
♪ You'll forget me ♪
Zhuge Yue, don't go.
Xing.
Don't leave me alone.
Zhuge Yue.
I won't let you go again.
This is Blood on Snow.
It's refined from a flower
unique to Ximeng.
Once taken,
one will be dependent on it constantly.
I gave you a 10-day dose,
enough for you to go back
and save your woman.
But after 10 days,
if you don't return as promised,
I'll let you know
what a living hell is.
The King of Ximeng promised me 10 days.
But you've already come in such a hurry
when only 7 days have passed?
It takes 3 days
to get from here to Ximeng City.
Only with our escort
can we ensure
you won't suffer from Blood on Snow
and that you survive intact.
With your poor martial arts,
you say you can escort me?
Besides, I'm already a walking corpse.
You're no match for me.
I won't make things difficult for you.
I'll go with you.
Stop.
-Go.
Go.
Take a look!
Your noodles.
Enjoy your meal.
Sir.
I'd like to ask you something.
Go ahead.
It's chaotic out there.
There are so many soldiers too.
What happened?
You...
You don't know yet?
There's been a big chaos
in Great Yan recently.
What happened?
We commoners
don't know exactly what's going on.
But in recent days,
many places in Great Yan's towns
have been surrounded and suppressed
by the Black Eagle Army.
It's said they are arresting
rebels of the Universal Harmony Guild.
I heard
that the Universal Harmony Guild
laid an ambush on Mount Ximin
with the intention of rebelling,
and everyone was killed.
Was this an order from the King of Yan?
No.
It was General Cheng Yuan.
Don't you know?
His Majesty is sick.
The imperial doctors
in the palace can't cure him.
They are looking for civilian doctors
all over Great Yan to enter the palace
to treat His Majesty.
Go, hurry up!
Go!
It looks like
this is another rebel
from the Universal Harmony Guild.
Can this person survive hanging like this?
What do you mean survive?
She's from the Universal Harmony Guild.
They won't let her live.
With people of the Universal Harmony Guild
all dead,
life in Great Yan
will be even harder in the future.
I heard that not only
the Universal Harmony Guild,
but also the Xiuli Army dying out
at Meilin Pass
was General Cheng's doing.
It was 5,000 Xiuli soldiers
against 100,000 Yong soldiers.
They were abandoned.
How could they survive?
Their corpses
were thrown into the mass grave,
with no one to care for them.
He Xiao...
Commander Chen.
Where are you?
He Xiao!
Did I do something wrong?
Come out!
He Xiao, Commander Chen!
I want you alive!
I expected that
the Queen is a person
who values friendship.
Even at the cost of your own life,
you would come to save
your former comrades.
Therefore,
I have been waiting here for a long time.
General Cheng and I were also comrades.
Unfortunately,
now we can only be enemies.
Go after them!
Miss Zhong!
Miss Zhong.
Hang in there.
Go, leave me.
Let's jump into the river.
Kill them!
Chu Qiao.
Today is your death day.
Miss Zhong!
Chu Qiao.
You must die.
For you,
Yan Xun repeatedly abandoned Great Yan.
If you don't die,
the hatred of the people of Great Yan
and Yan Xun's hatred
will never be avenged.
Live on!
Zhong Yu!
Miss Zhong.
Zhong Yu, where are you?
Zhong Yu!
General,
we still haven't found Chu Qiao.
She is crippled now.
She can't run far.
Assemble the nearby Black Eagle Army.
Search all villages along the valley.
Even if you have to search every inch,
you must find her.
Understood.
[Arrest]
Come take a look, everyone.
If you have seen this woman,
report it immediately.
There is a hefty reward.
Sir,
what happened now?
Don't you know?
I just came from the east.
It seems they are
catching the rebels
of the Universal Harmony Guild.
They have been catching them
for so many days,
and they still haven't caught them all?
Who knows?
Gentlemen.
Here are your noodles.
There are 2 more days.
I will be back in 2 days.
Follow him closely.
Yes.
Have mercy.
Please give me some food.
Listen up, everyone.
Starting today,
anyone leaving the city gates
must be inspected.
Make things easy for us,
and don't cause trouble.
Search them!
Look at the people over here.
Have you seen this woman?
N-N-No.
Have you seen her?
I haven't seen her.
Stop there.
Turn around.
I said turn around.
Can't you hear me?
[Crown Prince of Biantang,
Li Ce]
You stinky beggar.
You ran away after dirtying my clothes.
I'm so unlucky.
Why did I have to come to
this barbaric place
full of beggars?
Come with me.
See how I'll teach you a lesson.
Looking at his clothes,
he's from Biantang.
He's neither masculine nor feminine—
smelling like fragrance powder.
He's wearing a royal tablet.
Could it be...
Keep checking.
You, stop.
Stinky beggar,
how dare you dirty my clothes.
See how I'll teach you a lesson.
Get on!
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Get in.
Qiao.
Long time no see.
To be honest,
my travel out this time
felt different from the past.
I felt refreshed along the way
and that good things are coming.
I just arrived in Great Yan,
and among the flowers,
I met you.
Tell me,
would you call this
fate bringing us together again?
What's wrong with
this Crown Prince of Biantang?
He said men stink
and insisted on having beautiful women
to welcome him.
How...
How did th-this dead tree bloom?
A dead tree blooming—
that's an ominous sign.
It's an ominous sign.
This is so unlucky.
Shut up, all of you.
A dead tree blooming
is a rare sight in a century.
It means that only those with perseverance
can bloom like a dead tree
in desperate situations.
Zhao Che is quite sensible,
arranging such
a cute welcoming envoy for me.
Welcome, Your Highness.
Please follow me into the city.
Beauty, come up
and sit in the carriage with me,
then I will follow you into the city.
Go.
Your Highness!
There is no absolute beauty in history;
one pleasing to the eye
is a beautiful woman.
Your Highness!
How dare you!
How dare you
hit the Crown Prince of Biantang!
That's even better.
Chu Qiao.
How dare you!
Kneel down.
Why are you so fierce?
Do you know who she is?
She is my future wife.
I have seen many beautiful women,
but it's my first time seeing
such a fierce and violent one.
Beauty, how old are you this year?
What month were you born in?
How many people are there in your family?
I am 21 this year,
already at the age of marriage.
Beauty, marry me
and be my bride.
Your Highness!
Doctor,
how are Qiao's injuries?
Young Master,
this lady
has two deep cuts on her right arm.
The one by the elbow is treatable,
but the one on her arm
has hit her veins and tendons.
Even if reconnected,
it's hard to say
whether she can practice martial arts
in the future.
Besides...
Besides what?
It is a little too late
to treat this lady's eyes.
I am afraid
it'll be hard to restore her sight.
Unless...
Unless what?
Can you finish
what you have to say in one go?
Unless you have a potion
called Huotu water.
What water?
Huotu water.
Huotu water?
What's so difficult?
I will send someone to find it.
This medicine
is made from a top-secret prescription.
Few people know about it.
The medicinal materials needed to make it
are also very precious.
Not only that,
the patient needs
to use it for 7 days,
and it must be
freshly prepared every day.
Stop using it after 7 days,
and wait another 7 days,
and then her eyes
will recover on their own.
Thank you, Young Master.
Qiao,
don't worry.
Whatever water, fire, earth, gold, wood—
Biantang is rich in materials.
We have everything.
Come back with me.
I will definitely cure your eyes.
Li Ce,
did you see Zhuge Yue?
Zhuge Yue?
This belongs to him.
He saved me.
Qiao,
do you have a conscience?
I was the one who saved you.
I picked you up from the roadside,
brought you to the inn,
and got a doctor to treat you.
Yet here you are,
talking about Zhuge Yue nonstop.
Without him,
I would have died in the frozen lake.
Without me,
you would have been taken
by Great Yan's soldiers.
If you were caught by them,
you'd wish you were rather dead.
Death by a thousand cuts, cut in half,
skinned, buried alive...
Qiao,
don't overthink.
Curing your eyes is the key.
Great Yan is bitterly cold,
and the doctors' skills are limited.
Come back to Biantang with me.
I'll get the best imperial doctor for you.
I'm not leaving.
Why?
I'm going to wait for Zhuge Yue here.
You...
Zhuge Yue.
Zhuge Yue, Zhuge Yue, Zhuge Yue.
Qiao.
You haven't changed at all.
Once you make up your mind,
you're still sd stubborn.
But,
I like you this way.
♪ We mock karma ♪
♪ For being unfair ♪
♪ Why is life ♪
♪ Often filled with regrets? ♪
♪ The snow falls ♪
♪ With fate ♪
♪ It will eventually ♪
♪ Fall before ♪
♪ The dawn ♪
♪ As a foreigner ♪
♪ Don't look, don't ask, and don't speak ♪
♪ Wander ♪
♪ With no resentment at all ♪
♪ The lock in my heart ♪
♪ Put the memories ♪
♪ In the silence of the night ♪
♪ Look ♪
♪ The mortal world has forgotten me ♪
♪ I wish ♪
♪ You'll forget me ♪
Li Ce.
Is that you?
Could you get me a glass of water?
What's wrong?
Li Ce.
You talk so much during the day.
Why do you say nothing at night?
Also,
what are you doing in my room
in the middle of the night?
Li Ce?
I know it's you,
Zhuge Yue.
You are a grown man,
yet so indecisive.
If you want to reunite with her,
just go up to her.
Qiao is not stupid.
How could she not sense
you're still alive?
It is already the 6th day.
How are you feeling?
Who exactly are you?
Why are you giving me Huotu water?
Zhuge Yue
is dead.