No matter what,
you did save my life once.
In return,
I'll leave your body whole.
I'll give you a dignified death.
Chu!
Yan Xun.
If you keep this up,
she'll suffer more than just
swallowing some cold water.
♪ May fortune smile on all below ♪
♪ Just to hear when you'll come home ♪
♪ Melt the ice ♪
♪ That fate has wrought ♪
♪ Let the night ♪
♪ Forever glow ♪
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 3]
Chu.
Are you okay?
Yan Xun.
I'm Chu.
Chu.
Don't be afraid.
I'm fine.
Your Highness.
Kill Yan Xun now.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Report!
Your Highness.
The main force of the Yan Army
is outside our camp,
saying they're here
to welcome the King of Great Yan.
Your Highness,
we can't hesitate any longer.
If we do, we'll lose our chance.
Your Highness,
their men are already at our doorstep.
If they don't see the King of Great Yan,
they will charge in.
Kill Yan Xun!
-Kill Yan Xun! Kill Yan Xun!
Your Highness, we can't let them go!
-Kill Yan Xun!
Leave.
You can't let them leave!
Kill Chu Qiao for me!
Zhao Che.
Whatever I want,
you always find a way to get it for me.
Now I just want Chu Qiao dead!
Will you kill Chu Qiao for me?
Guards, take the Princess away.
Chu Qiao, I'll kill you!
Chun'er!
Enough!
Che,
if you kill Chu Qiao,
you'll be a hero of Great Yong.
Even if it's just for yourself,
you can't let her leave alive!
Let them go.
Yan Xun!
As long as I'm alive,
I'll try to kill Chu Qiao
and haunt you forever!
Forgive my rudeness,
but what Princess Chun'er said
actually makes sense.
If those two return alive,
they'll always be a threat to Great Yong.
This war has gone on too long.
If we kill Yan Xun,
who knows when this score
will ever be settled?
The soldiers and people of Great Yong
can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry.
You risked your life to protect me,
yet I still doubted you.
Chu.
Do you remember me now?
When you blocked that blade for me today,
I seemed to recall some images.
Did this happen before?
Yan Xun.
Here, drink some water.
We'll plan our next move carefully,
okay?
What are you doing here?
I came to see
how the former Heir Apparent of Great Yan
[Muhe Xifeng,
Son of the Muhe Family of Great Yong]
became the prisoner he is today.
Yan Xun!
Chu!
It is just as well that you are here.
You cut off my fingers that day.
Today,
I will make you pay back a hundredfold.
Hold her down!
Let me go! Let me go!
Stop!
Paying back debts
is perfectly justified.
I will pay for her!
Muhe Xifeng,
we are both men.
I will pay what she owes you!
I want to pay myself.
I don't want you to do that for me!
Since you want to pay for her,
do it yourself.
Chu.
You said your life isn't worth much,
but to me,
it is more important than anything.
Don't!
Back then,
the Emperor of Great Yong
framed my father for rebellion
and executed my entire clan.
On the Jiuyou Platform,
to protect me,
you got this scar on your back.
I swore then
that I would never let you get hurt again.
No matter how many blades I block for you,
I am willing.
Yan Xun,
I don't remember
any of these things you say
and this scar.
The past
is in the past.
As long as
you're by my side now.
When Chu returned
to the Capital of Great Yan last time,
she was intercepted
by the Universal Harmony Guild on the way.
And within 2 days,
Zhao Chun'er appeared.
I have always been puzzled.
After Chu woke up,
she never left the camp.
Who exactly
leaked the news,
or deliberately
released the information
to attract them?
Your Majesty, are you suspecting
that it was my doing?
I don't need to suspect.
Do you think
I don't know what you did?
I have followed you since I was 13.
I owe you my life, Your Majesty.
Whatever I do
is for you.
It is all out of loyalty to you.
If you want to kill me,
then go ahead.
Do you think I dare not?
Of course you do, Your Majesty.
But even if you kill me,
I will not change my view.
You, Chu Qiao, and the Great Yan soldiers
have many past entanglements.
If you make her the Queen of Great Yan,
it will surely cause trouble
in the future,
and other tribes will not accept it.
If you still care about Great Yan's
blood feud with Great Yong
and the late King of Great Yan's remains
not yet cold,
you must not marry Chu Qiao
as the Queen of Great Yan.
Leave!
Leave now!
General Cheng,
this is for you.
It can remove rot and regenerate flesh.
If it works well,
it won't leave a scar.
Lady Helian,
you dare visit me at a time like this?
Aren't you afraid His Majesty
will consider us co-conspirators
and punish us together?
Not only do I dare to visit you, General,
but I am also here to thank you.
We plotted this together.
Yet you, General,
did not expose me
before His Majesty.
Based on this alone,
it shows that you are
a trustworthy partner.
Is this your thank-you gift?
Of course not.
Since it is a thank-you,
I'll naturally help you
achieve your wish.
You still want to move against Chu Qiao?
I won't do it myself.
But those in Great Yan
who can't tolerate her
are not limited to my Helian Tribe.
His Majesty can ignore other tribes,
but what about the Snowy Region Tribe?
Guards!
What is burning in this censer?
General Huan.
Why is it you?
Did you light this?
This incense is for soothing the nerves.
When His Majesty is on campaign,
he often tosses and turns at night,
unable to sleep.
So I'll have this ready for His Majesty.
I eat well and sleep soundly.
I don't need this junk.
Lady Helian,
you'd be better off caring for
the wounded soldiers in the army.
They need you
more than I do.
General Huan, you are of noble character.
But this time,
I have come precisely for the soldiers.
I recall we aren't particularly close.
Is there something
you need to ask of me?
His Majesty
loves General Chu Qiao
to the point of obsession.
For her sake,
disregarding the consequences,
he ambushed Great Yong's General,
Zhuge Yue,
triggering the battle between Great Yan
and Great Yong at Meilin Pass.
How many of our Black Eagle Army soldiers
fell dead at the foot of Mount Ximin?
And now, just as the Yong Army
has retreated,
he ignores the opposition
of the Great Yan tribes
and wants to return to the capital
to marry Chu Qiao as his Queen.
Chu Qiao?
When I was in the Snowy Region
of Great Yan,
I heard of her deeds.
She is a general too, isn't she?
But her battles
are not as famous as her other affairs.
General Huan,
my Helian Tribe is weak and powerless.
We dare not criticize
His Majesty's actions.
But surely you know
how the elders
of the other Great Yan tribes
view His Majesty.
His Majesty is obsessed with beauty
and neglects state affairs,
which may lead to
the downfall of Great Yan.
I imagine
you and the Snowy Region Tribe
would not want, for the sake of a woman,
to ruin the legacy
built by the late King of Great Yan.
I don't know if Chu Qiao is a curse,
but I can see you are up to no good.
You came here
just to provoke me
into stopping His Majesty
from marrying that Chu Qiao.
What is your motive?
Whether it is provocation,
you can judge for yourself.
I have delivered my message.
I shall take my leave.
Chu.
We're almost at the Capital of Great Yan.
[Capital of Great Yan]
King Yan Xun has returned!
Great Yong has withdrawn its troops!
No more war! No more war!
-No more war!
Wonderful!
Your Majesty,
the wedding is coming up soon.
According to the Great Yan custom,
before the wedding,
the Queen must embroider
a sash for the King.
On the wedding day,
His Majesty must wear the sash
and go with you to the Ancestral Temple
outside the capital
to pay respects to the ancestors.
In the capital,
where are the best clothing shops?
[Huajin Ready-Made Clothing Shop]
Your Majesty,
this sash is against the rules.
Sir,
I'll take this sash.
here is the money.
Is this the sash you gave me?
It's wonderful.
I will wear it all the time,
until our wedding day
when we pay respects to the ancestors.
This sash
isn't actually that precious.
Chu,
I have a gift for you too.
Chu.
I prepared this especially for you.
After we get married,
this place will be your chamber
and our home.
It's so magnificent.
I'm afraid
I won't get used to living here.
Chu,
♪ The dust in the world ♪
I promised before
that I would bring you back to Great Yan.
Now I have finally fulfilled that promise.
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
You have no home
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
and no family,
so this is your home,
♪ And not be scared? ♪
♪ A slight ripple ♪
and I am
♪ Floating life hangs by a thread ♪
your family.
♪ The more pulled, the softer it gets ♪
Chu,
♪ Who dares to say forever? ♪
in the past,
♪ Let it be ♪
we were imprisoned
in the Yingge Courtyard,
living in fear day and night.
♪ Grudges and grace
were never meant to be ♪
Later,
we marched to war,
braving the elements.
♪ Why must you take and demand so much? ♪
At that time,
I silently vowed
♪ Go weaving ♪
♪ Grand and glorious excuses ♪
that one day, I would definitely give you
the best home possible,
so you would never have to
live that kind of life again.
♪ We once beheld ♪
♪ A mirage on earth ♪
From now on,
you'll be the Queen of Great Yan,
♪ Beauty never ♪
and our children
♪ Lasts for long ♪
will be the Heir Apparent of Great Yan.
♪ No matter how a jade is carved ♪
♪ It's just a stone ♪
♪ It will eventually disappear ♪
Your Majesty,
it's time for Her Majesty's medicine.
The Queen is already asleep.
Give it to her tomorrow.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Chu,
I'm doing this for your own good.
I hope that in the future,
you can always sleep peacefully,
free from all troubles.
Her Majesty,
His Majesty instructed
that you should not overwork yourself.
♪ Facing the wind, I tread through frost ♪
♪ Measuring rivers and hills,
hooves rise light ♪
♪ The horizon lies far ahead ♪
♪ Swaying gently ♪
♪ Through pine mists, past 1,000 hills ♪
♪ Wrapped in the vast moonlight ♪
♪ Having drunk the surging waves ♪
♪ I care not how far the road ♪
♪ Strong wine to the wild plains ♪
♪ Beyond the pass,
sand blows like arrows ♪
♪ I ride and whip my steed ♪
♪ Chasing 10,000 miles of cloud and mist ♪
♪ Mountains and rivers fade behind ♪
You can do it!
♪ The wind crowns me ♪
♪ Your eyes glow with flame ♪
♪ Strong wind breaks the lute strings ♪
♪ Playing for 5,000 years ♪
♪ I ride my horse toward the south ♪
♪ Endless spring beneath my hooves ♪
♪ Hoofbeats fade away ♪
♪ Rolling over peaks and ridges ♪
♪ A single neigh echoes
between heaven and earth ♪
♪ Treading on the clear wind ♪
♪ The realm unfolds like a scroll ♪
♪ Chasing the bright moon ♪
♪ My spirit swallows
mountains and rivers ♪
-Great!
What can you achieve
fighting a dead wooden stake?
So, it is you, General Huan.
I've heard a lot about you.
The long blades of Great Yan
are not used like that.
Great Yan warriors only attack;
they never evade.
Your grip is weak,
and your internal energy is unstable.
These are fatal flaws
in your blade skills.
Since you are a general,
you should have real skills.
Otherwise, you'd better be a good Queen
and stay out of
military and state affairs.
I just heard you haven't fully recovered
from a serious illness.
My victory just now wasn't fair.
When you're healed,
we'll spar again.
General Huan,
keep your voice down.
We don't know each other.
Why are you giving me a hard time?
I know that most of the generals
and tribes in Great Yan
don't want me to marry Yan Xun.
Some even want me dead.
But let me give you a friendly warning.
Don't let people with ulterior motives
use you.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Even if I stay out of your business,
those elders of the tribes in Great Yan
will make sure you and Yan Xun
have no peace.
General Huan,
I don't want Great Yan
to fall apart because of me,
nor do I want Yan Xun
to be dragged into trouble on my account.
I can give up
being the Queen of Great Yan.
Ever since I woke up from the frozen lake,
I've felt like there's something
I have forgotten.
I often dream of the frozen lake.
I want to go there and take a look,
but I haven't had the chance.
I know Yan Xun loves me very much,
but I don't want him to deviate
from his path because of me.
General Huan, if you
could help me leave this place,
for me,
for Yan Xun,
and for the entire Great Yan,
it would be the best choice.
You're asking me
to help you betray Yan Xun?
General Huan,
please have some tea.
regarding the villa we just saw,
are you satisfied?
Great Yan has just stabilized,
and funds are tight.
Building this itinerant court
must have cost the treasury a fortune.
His Majesty's wedding is approaching.
To welcome the Queen,
it is necessary.
Halt!
Greetings, General Huan,
Lord Helian.
Why are you sneaking around?
Nothing.
Open the box.
General Huan,
this is medicine for Lady Chu.
I'm afraid I can't—
Open it.
Zhigu Herb,
a secret medicine
of the Great Yan military.
I just found it in the medicine
she prepared for Chu Qiao.
What is going on?
I don't know.
I was just delivering medicine
to Lady Chu.
I don't know what Zhigu Herb is.
Su is a veteran servant in the palace.
I trust she wouldn't harm Chu.
Zhigu Herb
is a controlled military substance.
How could a mere female official
possess it?
Who are you working for?
Huan Huan.
You have been leading troops for days.
You must be exhausted.
You should get some rest.
In 3 days,
Chu and I will be married.
The tribal elders will be coming.
You can catch up with them then,
and celebrate our wedding together.
Zhigu Herb is used for interrogation.
It is used to break a captive's will.
Those who consume it
will lose their minds.
General Huan.
You have said
too much.
Your Majesty,
when my father was alive,
he swore loyalty
to the late King of Great Yan
and told me the duty
of the Snowy Region Tribe
is to protect Great Yan.
Your Majesty,
when you returned to Great Yan,
I was the first
to raise troops in your support.
For the sake of the Snowy Region Tribe's
generations of loyalty,
please forgive my offense.
We agreed to enter the palace
this morning together,
but it is already noon.
Elder Gelin still hasn't shown up.
Could it be
that he's changed his mind?
I doubt it.
Regarding the opposition
to His Majesty marrying Chu Qiao,
Elder Gelin
has always been the most vocal.
He wouldn't back out
at the last minute, would he?
Elder! Elder!
We just received news.
Did something happen?
Something happened to Elder Gelin.
Last night, on his way into the city,
he died.
Your Majesty.
It is time
to change and head to
the Ancestral Temple.
Assassins! Protect His Majesty!
Chu.
Chu!
Your Majesty!
Chu.
We have been through so much.
I thought it was all over,
and that this was our new beginning.
My condolences, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
The Queen is not dead.
Without my permission,
who dares let her die?
-Your Majesty.
Find better doctors for Chu.
Has he confessed?
He'd rather die than talk.
Speak.
I'll talk. I'll talk.
It was...
It was... It was Cheng Yuan.
It was Lord Cheng Yuan.
You lie!
I know most of Great Yan's
generals and tribes
don't want me to marry Yan Xun.
Some even want me dead.
I'm sorry.
I... I...
[To General Huan]
Chu.
Guards!
Your Majesty.
Where is the Queen?
Where is she?
Pass on my order.
Blockade all roads.
Do not harm Chu in the slightest.
Bring her back to me!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Seeing these words is like seeing me.
By the time you read this letter,
General Huan,
I have likely met with misfortune.
I heard that you always
care for your soldiers.
After the Snowy Region soldiers
died in the borderlands,
you would spare no effort
to fulfill the last wishes
they left behind.
I know
there must be many people
who want to stop my wedding with Yan Xun,
so I wrote this letter to you in advance.
Yan Xun and I
traveled from Great Yong to Great Yan,
facing many hardships.
Although I do not fully remember the past,
I still regard him
as the one closest to me.
Therefore,
if my departure
can keep him from further trouble,
then my wish is fulfilled.
However,
there is one thing I can't let go of.
I know Yan Xun has deep affection for me.
He will surely bury me
with the honors of the Queen of Great Yan.
This matter, for Great Yan and me,
is of no great benefit.
You and I have only met once,
but I felt like we were old friends.
If you are reading this letter,
could you please take my body
back to the frozen lake?
I have always felt
that my lost memories are there.
I want to be buried
with those past memories.
After we leave Zhenhuang City,
you can follow me.
I will take you back to Great Yan.
I will protect you.
Okay.
Promise me then,
you'll take me to eat something good
when we get out.
As long as you can name it,
I'll find it for you.
My name is Chu Qiao.
I'm only telling you.
Then from now on,
I'll call you Chu,
okay?
Because our paths crossed briefly,
I've brought you here
to fulfill your last wish.
Though I don't know
what you went through before,
I hope your spirit can rest in peace.
Farewell.
I knew you would come, Your Majesty.
General Huan, why are you doing this?
I am just acting on behalf of Miss Chu
to fulfill her last wish.
Why did you betray me?
Because I misjudged you, Your Majesty.
I grew up with you.
I thought you were the one
who would protect Great Yan with me.
But you put Zhigu Herb in her medicine
to deliberately make her forget her past.
I don't know
what your purpose is,
and I don't want to know.
The King in my heart
should be open-hearted
and upright.
I will never support a King like this.
I am the Chief of the Snowy Region Tribe,
and I will certainly obey
the oath of my tribe
to be loyal to Great Yan for generations.
If the King of Great Yan wants me dead,
I will obey and die.
Do it, Your Majesty.
Chu.
Let's go home.
Why?
I want to avenge Zhuge Yue
and the Xiuli Army!
You've been lying to me all along.
You remember everything,
don't you?
The Universal Harmony Guild.
Your Majesty, run!
I've been having you watched.
When did you
notify the people
of the Universal Harmony Guild?
When I bought
that wedding sash for you.
Sir,
I'll take this sash.
[Troops ambush the frozen lake
on King of Great Yan's wedding day]
That shop
is a stronghold
of the Universal Harmony Guild?
You've never forgotten Zhuge Yue,
have you?
That's right.
I've been lying to you.
At the Great Yong Granary,
when you blocked that blade for me,
I remembered everything.
I remembered that I was
the leader of the Xiuli Army,
going through thick and thin
with you in Great Yong.
In those years
with the Universal Harmony Guild,
we shared the same ideals.
You said there would be no war
and no oppression in Great Yan,
and that you would give me
a grassland where I could ride freely.
But I also remember
how you were blinded by power
and betrayed your oath.
You used me
to slaughter the Xiuli Army,
lure Zhuge Yue to the frozen lake,
and kill him.
How many people
have lost their homes and families
because of you?
Your Majesty, run!
The ice is about to break!
Black Eagle Army.
By His Majesty's order,
kill them all and leave no survivors!
Fire!
Actually, I knew all along you were lying.
I just wanted to take a gamble,
betting that you wouldn't have the heart
to kill me.
But now,
I see that I've lost that bet.
The assassins at the wedding
confessed long ago.
I knew about your plan all along.
Using silver needles
to seal acupoints to fake death
is what Zhuge Yue taught you, right?
Chu.
Come back with me.
Let's start over.
Let's go back.
Your Majesty!
Chu.
♪ The dust in the world ♪
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
♪ And not be scared? ♪
♪ A slight ripple ♪
♪ We face ♪
♪ The heavy thunderstorm together ♪
♪ Even with extreme pain ♪
♪ We don't even wince ♪
♪ No matter how a jade is carved ♪
♪ It's just a stone ♪
♪ It will eventually disappear ♪
I'll trade my life for it.
Search the area around Qianzhang Lake!
Dead or alive,
find Chu Qiao for me!
-Yes!
Zhuge Yue, don't go.
Xing.
You're no match for me.
I won't make things difficult for you.
I'll go with you.
Chu Qiao,
you must die.