EPISODE 11
You're getting off work late.
There's a shoot tomorrow,
so I had to prepare before I left.
-Excuse me, Chair Kim.
-What?
When might you be available?
Why do you ask?
I think it's time for a new profile photo.
You've been in the media a lot these days.
We can talk about that some other time!
The exit passcode is different.
Seol-ah.
We need to get out of here.
That's right.
This is where you belong.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
When will the job be finished?
Hurry up.
Get it done before the insurance company
or the police find it.
Are you okay?
Did you find
what you were looking for?
They were all there.
The Taemyung pieces,
the ones Chair Kim had switched out,
and even my father's painting.
Every family photo I had
was lost in the fire,
but the last memory of my family
was locked inside that vault.
I'll never forgive Chair Kim.
I'll make her pay for what she did.
I'll be by your side
the whole way.
Enjoy the auction.
Is everything ready?
SEARCH AND SEIZURE WARRANT
ARREST WARRANT
Untitled by Lee Soo-dam
has been sold to a floor bidder
for 400 million won.
Congratulations.
This unpublished masterpiece
is said to be the final work
by Artist Song Hwan-ju.
Its estimated value
exceeds seven billion won,
and it's expected to surpass
the artist's most famous work,
Cheong-myeong.
However,
I will not be putting it up
for auction today.
The reason is that it's not authentic.
-What?
-It's not authentic?
This artwork was submitted
through unofficial channels
-What is she saying?
-under the orders of Chair Kim Sun-ae
at Royal Auction.
I questioned its authenticity
and sent it
for professional authentication.
-The results showed
-What is she doing?
-the use of an industrial synthetic resin
-Ms. Han!
-rather than the natural glue
-What the hell are you doing?
Artist Song typically used
in their collage works.
ART AUTHENTICATION REPORT: FORGERY
Even the signature is different.
SIGNATURE COMPARISON ANALYSIS
FORGERY / GENUINE
The character for "hwan," which means
"to shine," in the artist's name
is incorrectly written,
using the "child" radical
instead of the correct "fire" radical.
You idiot!
The authentication agency has confirmed
that this piece is a complete forgery.
Get her. Drag her down.
Yes, ma'am.
That crazy…
We've also obtained evidence
that the Taemyung pieces lost in the fire
were also forgeries.
Hey, get her out of here!
What are you doing?
Damn it! No photos!
Then where are the authentic pieces?
As you can see,
she switched them out and stashed them
in her secret storage vault.
Inside is her collection,
all gathered through embezzlement,
confiscation, and swapping.
Hey!
How did you obtain this video?
When did you start preparing
to expose this?
Chair Kim!
Is there additional evidence
that Chair Kim Sun-ae
committed this crime?
Even Han Jin-woo,
the artist who painted this work
and was regarded
as a prodigy in the art world,
was reduced to a forger
because of Chair Kim.
I stand here today
to restore the honor of an artist
who passed away in disgrace.
Even at this moment,
another forgery
is likely being created somewhere
under Chair Kim's orders.
Therefore, I urge the police
to conduct a thorough investigation.
Hey.
Do you think people will believe
a manipulated video?
Ms. Kim Sun-ae.
You're being arrested under a warrant
for embezzlement, fraud, and violating
the Act on Regulation and Punishment
of Criminal Proceeds Concealment.
-The police seem to believe it.
-Chair Kim.
No, don't.
I didn't do anything wrong. How dare you?
You're making a mistake!
What's all this?
Man, an art gallery
doesn't hold a candle to this place.
Just how much did she get away with?
We've already collected evidence
from your suite.
What?
Who do you think you are, going in there?
Don't you dare touch a thing!
Not a single thing!
Don't touch a thing! It's all mine!
Don't touch anything!
Don't lay a finger on anything!
-It's all mine!
-Come on!
Don't you dare touch anything!
Hey, Han Seol-ah!
You!
Han Seol-ah!
Let go of me!
They'll lock down the site
and control access.
There are so many high-value pieces
that they have to seal the vault door
until they can be moved
to a secure location.
We need to compare the documents
you submitted against the evidence.
Could you conduct an initial review
before the professional authentication?
You won't find this painting
in the documents.
The original artist's name
was Han Jin-woo.
He was my father.
This piece can be returned, right?
Help Seol-ah get it back.
Okay.
What's this?
It's still wrapped.
It's the Stiller.
The painting that's worth
over 15 billion won?
Did she switch this out too?
It's the original piece that was
on display in the exhibition hall.
Does that mean a forgery of this piece
is being created too?
-Woo-seok.
-I'll call you later.
Are you still at the company?
We need to talk.
Everyone out of the workshop.
Just get out. I'll handle the rest.
Just do as I say, you bastards!
What the hell?
Why haven't you left yet?
Who is it?
It's been a while,
Ju Hyun-su.
Damn.
You were the SIU investigator
after the Taemyung pieces?
There's nowhere to run now, you bastard.
Get ready to rot in prison.
You have nothing on me
if I burn all the evidence.
Do you want to die too, you bastard?!
Goddamn it.
That was a confession, right?
-Damn you.
-That you killed Woo-hee.
My life got screwed because of that bitch!
I wouldn't have messed with her
if I'd known her brother was a cop.
Shut the hell up, you asshole!
She didn't care about riding in a truck
and begged to ride along on my trips.
She was starved for affection
and so needy.
I said shut the hell up,
you son of a bitch!
Get up.
She was still young,
but said we should get married
so she wouldn't be a burden on you.
Did you know that?
It's your fault she died.
No.
That's not true!
You're wrong!
You asshole!
-Die, you son of a bitch!
-Woo-seok!
-Hey, Cha Woo-seok!
Stop!
-Stop!
-Woo-seok, stop.
Stop.
Please stop.
Come on.
Let's go.
It's over now.
You can let it go.
It was me.
I was the one who got Woo-hee killed.
It was all me.
Remember what you told me?
You said it wasn't my fault.
I'm going to say it back to you.
It wasn't your fault, Woo-seok.
You…
always did your best.
Please don't get hurt.
You're the only family I have left.
It's your fault she died.
Name?
Obviously, Ju Hyun-su.
STATEMENT
Date of birth?
Hey, you think you can pull that
right-to-remain-silent crap on me?
Damn it.
This is Cha Woo-hee's case file
that I've kept for six years.
When Cha Woo-seok was raging and pleading
that you were the one
who killed his sister,
I just scoffed at him.
I told him he was just being emotional
because the victim was his sister.
There's no way a guy
who's already killed someone
has only been making forgeries
all this time.
Tell me, you bastard!
What else did Chair Kim make you do?
You killed Paek Jun-beom, didn't you?
No! That wasn't me!
Then who did you kill?
Did you kill Cha Woo-hee?
Did you kill Kim Yun-ji?
Shit.
What's all this?
I wanted to make you something to eat.
You don't have to do that.
I know it's hard for you
to be around fire.
It's an induction stove,
so I think I can manage.
You really don't have to.
Should I wash this first?
Go get some rest.
You've been through a lot today.
I'm not good at cooking,
especially when someone is watching me.
CARROT
GREEN ONION
ADD THE BEEF
I can't guarantee it'll taste good.
I've never cooked porridge before.
I thought it'd go down easier
than just rice.
Thank you.
It looks great.
It's good.
I often thought about the meal
you made for me.
After the interrogation,
when everything inside me fell apart,
the meal that you made me
helped me get back on my feet.
And then you said
you didn't want to see me again.
I was afraid.
I thought you might get hurt
if you stayed by my side.
Are you not afraid anymore?
I still am.
But I want to give it a try
because you told me
not to run away,
not to push you away,
and to stay by your side and protect you.
I think I know how you feel right now.
But still,
let's keep living.
I won't say things will get better.
Because…
we have to live with this pain
for the rest of our lives.
But let's get through it together.
You should eat.
It's really good.
We ran forensics on Chair Kim's computer
and found chat records with Kim Yun-ji
on the company messenger.
I think you should take a look.
ASSOCIATE AUCTIONEER KIM YUN-JI
About the painting my father bought,
did you personally bring it in
from New York?
Why do you ask?
Don't you think you crossed the line?
I introduced that painting to him
in good faith.
Come to my suite.
Let's talk in person.
Funny, isn't it?
The head of the NTS investigation bureau
has a daughter who's an auctioneer,
yet has a forgery hanging in his house.
What kind of nonsense is this?
I sent it
for external authentication twice,
but the results were the same.
I wonder what will happen
when my father finds out.
Are you threatening me?
I'm suggesting
we try to solve the problem.
What do you want?
The main podium.
In other words, get rid of Ms. Han?
Chair Kim probably felt a lot of pressure.
She would've been hit
with multiple tax evasion charges.
This could've been the motive
for killing Kim Yun-ji.
The Taemyung paintings
that went up in flames
turned up in your secret storage vault,
and you claim ignorance?
My client stored the paintings
upon the client's request.
The issue here is Taemyung's mismanagement
and insurance handling,
not any criminal conduct by my client.
Then let's talk about this.
The Stiller is worth over 10 billion won,
and you took advantage
of the owner's death to take it.
It's the same thing.
My client merely kept the painting
safely in the vault
until the inheritance process
was completed.
That's standard practice.
Then why did she make a forgery?
Why go through the trouble?
Your lackey, Ju Hyun-su,
has been arrested.
There's no point in holding out,
Ms. Kim Sun-ae.
I don't like your tone.
It's very rude.
Listen, Detective.
Did you know who you were dealing with
when you brought me in?
Well, you can't undo a mistake
that's already been made.
Your future in the force
could be an easy road or a difficult one.
This is a critical moment for you.
Don't you get it?
Worry about yourself.
Insurance fraud, embezzlement,
dealing in forgeries,
and the cherry on top.
Murder for hire.
You've got some nerve, don't you?
Your lack of gratitude is impressive.
How dare you stab Chair Kim in the back?
What are you really up to?
Is the plan to take over her position
while she's not here?
That's probably what you want to do.
How dare you accuse me of that?
Hey.
I'm not like you.
I'm doing everything I can
to handle the situation from my position.
I have to take responsibility
for what I've done, don't I?
Fine.
I don't know how long you'll last,
but good luck with that.
Chair Kim will be back soon enough.
The remaining auctions
will fall through, right?
These are all the client complaints
we received this morning.
Most of these
are consignment cancellation requests.
This is so annoying.
Give me the list.
I'll personally call the clients
to persuade them.
Ms. Han, I didn't know
you'd come in today.
Are you okay?
I owe you all an apology.
As someone who understands
how deeply you care about Royal Auction,
I'm truly sorry
for causing this situation.
But you did the right thing.
We actually think
this turned out for the better.
We were unknowingly helping Chair Kim
carry out fraud,
so it's a relief
that everything's come to light.
The paintings are safely stored.
How can I trust you after all the talk
of forgery and embezzlement?
I promise to take full responsibility--
I won't stand for this.
I want my artwork back immediately!
-I'll visit you in person.
-I don't care about compensation.
I'll never do business
with you people again!
KIM YEONG-EUN (VVIP)
AFTERNOON CHAMBER MUSIC (BY ELINA)
Ms. Han.
It's about Artist Han Jin-woo.
You said he was family, right?
Yeah.
He was my father.
I didn't know you carried
such a painful memory.
I'm sorry I couldn't do more
to be of support.
Thank you for saying that.
I came to work prepared
for people to chew me out,
but you've been so kind.
I can't imagine
how hard it must've been for you.
Things will only get harder for everyone
from here on out.
We'll do whatever it takes.
We're ready for anything.
I thought you were the only one
who really cared.
But it turns out,
Han Seol-ah really cares too.
It gives me chills just imagining
what could've happened if we'd been late.
Make Ju Hyun-su pay
for what he did.
The captain is even more furious
about that than I am.
I think he feels really guilty.
Have that bastard and Chair Kim
confessed yet?
We'll make them confess.
But do you really think
Chair Kim would kill someone
over a painting?
She's the only suspect
who has a clear motive to kill.
She might not have done it herself,
but she could've hired Ju Hyun-su
to do it.
He was out of the country for a long time,
and there's no reason for Chair Kim
to go after Han Seol-ah's men.
I have my suspicions about Do Eun-hyuk,
but his alibi is solid.
CCTV footage shows that Do Eun-hyuk
was at his studio in Cheongun
at the time of Paek Jun-beom's murder.
I want to see it.
Don't ask for official records.
And I want the records
of Paek Jun-beom stalking Han Seol-ah
that were seized from his house,
along with the photos taken in Cheongun.
Please.
Cell tower records show that Do Eun-hyuk
was at his studio in Cheongun
at the time of Paek Jun-beom's murder.
Now I understand
why you trusted Cha Woo-seok.
I never imagined someone like Chair Kim
could get arrested.
That's when it hit me
that you joined hands with Cha Woo-seok
because it wasn't something
I could help you with.
That wasn't why.
There was something we had to do,
and when things overlapped along the way,
we combined our efforts.
That makes your relationship
even more special.
Maybe it was fate.
What do you think of him?
You've got a good eye for people.
He's the kind of person
who belongs in the center of the frame.
He's confident and straightforward.
But I'm the opposite.
I'm someone who fits better
outside the frame.
I've acted like it wasn't true
all this time,
but now I'm sure of it.
Why would you think that?
People end up living…
the way their hands have been trained.
Anyway, you've been through a lot
to get this far.
I'm sure it'll all work out.
And I hope you can get back
Mr. Han's painting.
I still feel uneasy.
Chair Kim isn't the type of person
to take things lying down.
Don't worry.
It'll all work out the way you want.
Ms. Han.
Chair Kim is here.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
She's not a flight risk
and has health issues?
It's always the same thing.
You've got to be kidding me.
She brought in another top law firm,
and sure enough,
they kept her out of custody.
Take a seat.
What were you thinking all this time
while working here?
Have you been living
with such bitter determination
just to take me down
and get revenge for your father?
I learned it all from you.
My father painted theater signs.
I just helped him paint at first,
but then I wanted to become a real artist,
so I became an apprentice.
That's when I saw your father and realized
that even a prodigy like him
can starve to death in this industry.
Is that why you had him paint forgeries?
I gave him a chance to earn a living
so your family wouldn't go hungry.
Hey.
How is it my fault that naive man
went into debt to repay everything?
Do you think that justifies
causing someone's death?
I didn't cause it! It was his choice!
I was the one who called 119
when your house caught on fire.
I was the one who saved your life!
You should've left me to die!
Then I wouldn't be in so much pain.
I had to grovel before you like a dog
and constantly force a smile
for living at the price
of my parents' lives.
Even if you manage to get out of this,
I'll hunt you down to the very end.
What else can you possibly do?
All the judges and prosecutors
are in my pocket.
A dog might get away
with biting its owner once,
but do it again,
and it'll be beaten to death.
I'll have to go for the neck, then.
You think you'll get a chance to do that?
It'll be your neck on the line.
I guess
we'll just have to wait and see…
whose neck is on the line.
Ju Hyun-su will be out soon.
Take care of that bastard quietly first.
If you don't,
I'll make sure she finds out
about the secret
you're so desperate to keep from her.
BOOKKEEPING LEDGER
And even if it costs me my life, Llorona
I will not stop loving you
…Llorona…
Ah, woe is me, Llorona, Llorona
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
Everything is too perfect.
Where are you going?
To see Chair Kim.
Did she ask to see you?
No.
I'm telling her that I'm quitting.
I wanted to take responsibility
and make things right
regarding the last auction,
-but Chair Kim--
-She'd never let that slide.
Let's go together.
I'm quitting too.
I told you not to do that.
Don't get it wrong.
I want to focus on my own work now
and get back in the water.
The security guard said
he heard music playing
into the early hours.
The first to discover her
were Han Seol-ah and Do Eun-hyuk.
-Any signs of foul play?
-Not yet.
There's a suicide note on her laptop,
but it's not enough
to rule this a suicide.
The CCTVs near the suite don't work.
Well, she had to move the paintings
into the storage vault secretly.
And now her death
has become a secret too.
HAN SEOL-AH
Your call cannot be connected.
This isn't the outcome I was hoping for.
Chair Kim would never commit suicide.
When I saw her the day before,
she showed no signs of guilt
and was self-assured.
I think someone went through
the chair's suite.
And it's strange that she left
the suicide note on her laptop,
considering that she still keeps
handwritten ledgers.
Does that mean Chair Kim was also…
It's all connected.
I feel like
this is all the work of one person.
This isn't over
until we catch the killer.
Are you okay?
You'll hurt yourself. I'll do it.
Dear Seol-ah,
I hope the day you read this never comes.
A woman came to see me
and told me some strange things about you.
To be honest, I was swayed by her words.
This is Seung-jae's handwriting.
He left a clue about the culprit.
Are you okay?
Seol-ah.
INSURANCE APPLICATION FORM
INSURANCE AGENT: KIM MI-SUK
This is your parents'
life insurance application form.
Look at the agent's name.
I think it might be someone you know.
INSURANCE AGENT: KIM MI-SUK
These are photos
from Paek Jun-beom's house.
I hadn't looked closely before,
but Kim Yun-ji was in some of them.
So she was in Cheongun
the day before Seung-jae died.
She stayed until the next morning.
This photo
was taken by the river that day.
Kim Yun-ji was a witness.
She knew who killed Seung-jae.
And that's why she was killed.
Can this be used as evidence?
It's not enough,
but they'll show up in front of me soon
because I'm Han Seol-ah's man
who knows their secret.
If we use this opportunity to--
No.
I won't use you as bait.
I'm the only one who can approach them
without raising suspicion.
-I'll do it.
-It's too dangerous.
Even Chair Kim is dead.
What's dangerous
is always feeling on edge
and shaking in fear.
I won't live like that anymore.
Then let's go together.
We'll get caught if we do.
You need to confirm something too, right?
Then at least tell me your route.
I'll also keep you updated
whenever I'm on the move.
Be careful.
I have my suspicions about Do Eun-hyuk,
but his alibi is solid.
Records show that Do Eun-hyuk
was at his studio in Cheongun
at the time of Paek Jun-beom's murder.
CHEONGUN STUDIO
RECOMMENDED ROUTE
16 MINUTES
If I drive as fast as possible…
BOOKKEEPING LEDGER
DO EUN-HYUK
If there's no traffic,
it's possible to get to the studio
from Paek Jun-beom's villa in 15 minutes.
PHOTO EQUIPMENT PURCHASE
LIVING EXPENSES
DO EUN-HYE PRIVATE TUTORING EXPENSES
EQUIPMENT PURCHASE
LICENSE CERTIFICATION
DO EUN-HYE TUITION
DARKROOM & LARGE TANK INSTALLATION
SOUNDPROOFING WORK
I'm going to Cheongun.
CHA WOO-SEOK
Don't worry.
It'll all work out the way you want.
Do Eun-hyuk.
If you love Han Seol-ah…
you die.
I didn't gain anything.
Watch out!
I only lost.
If the culprit thinks I'm your man,
I'll either die…
or find out who the real culprit is.
What if you really die?
I don't care.
Go ahead and use me.
This isn't over
until we catch the killer.
They'll show up in front of me soon
because I'm Han Seol-ah's man
who knows their secret.
Subtitle: Jenny Kim