STILL SHINING
Tae-seo, is that you?
Yes, it's me.
If you're done crying, let's go home.
Get some rest
so you can go back to Seoul and work.
Come on!
Okay!
STILL SHINING
MART
You can just say whatever comes to mind.
Like when you have some makgeolli
and go out on a stroll together.
Okay.
I know what your grandma likes.
The pale pink skirt
Flutters in the spring breeze
Biting the ribbon of my blouse again today
Along the village shrine road
Where butterflies flit to and fro
When flowers bloomed
We laughed together
When flowers fell
We cried together
Yet with that earnest promise
The spring days
Are gone
Oh my gosh!
You put the photos on the outside
so it's easy to tell.
Great job.
But I like that one.
OIDO STATION, SNOW, WINTER
Me too.
Wow, you did a really good job.
Great job on these!
Do you want it?
You can wear those.
Check what I've done so far.
It really does feel like
it's being embraced.
It feels warm.
That one's mine.
I've oiled it.
It needs to dry.
So you're all done.
You said after waiting a day
for oiling, that's it.
The third and final moment of waiting.
I'll wrap this up for you.
I'll help you.
I can do it by myself.
KTC RAILWAY LAWS AND REGULATIONS
You're juggling five balls at once.
Of course you'd be overwhelmed.
Why five?
Your job, your side gig,
preparing to change jobs,
family issues, and relationship issues.
Isn't that how everyone lives?
You sure you're doing well?
What is it that you want to know?
I heard things aren't going well
with your girlfriend.
Hyeong-seok said
after he broke up, so did you.
Did you know?
The number of people you've dated
doesn't always match
the number you've broken up with.
The number of breakups is usually lower.
Breaking up with someone
is a memorable experience.
Even with my friends,
they've dated several people,
but they only ever talk about one breakup.
I guess you have to remember the breakup
for it to count as a real relationship.
HUI-SEO
Hold on.
-Hey, Hui-seo.
-Hey, Tae-seo.
Can you come to the hospital today?
Well, I am off today. What's up?
This morning,
the corner of Grandma's mouth twitched.
You know,
it's like how Grandma always smirks
when she sees me.
Anyway, it moved.
What did the doctor say?
No, it's not what the doctor said.
I saw it myself.
So what do you expect me to come and do?
She might wake up, so…
Fine.
I'll tell Grandpa to go home,
and I'll stay here myself.
Go home. I'll be there.
I'm getting a call.
It's A-sol.
Hi, Hui-seo.
If I come down today,
can I get
that red carpet treatment you mentioned?
I'm seeing Tae-seo today to get my frame,
so I might suggest we go together.
I've had so much work lately.
You know I like
to blow off steam by driving.
Yeah, exactly.
You know a place like that?
That sounds delicious.
Okay. Bye.
I'll drive, so you can get
some sleep on the way.
I can go by myself.
Don't you have work tomorrow?
-I do.
-Then you have to come back anyway.
If we leave now, eat,
see your grandma, and come back,
it'll be perfect timing.
Always with bloodshot eyes
from lack of sleep,
the study center's Seat One guy
doesn't seem like
the type to easily fall for someone.
And even when he does like someone,
he doesn't seem like
the type to break up easily.
So how did he break up
the very first time?
This is based on the people around me,
but how your first breakup happens
has a bigger impact than your first love.
I'm curious.
When and how did Seat One guy break up?
How did he feel?
Not that he'd tell me.
Stunned.
What was that?
Then what about the second time?
No second time? Just the one?
The same person.
Wake me up at the first rest stop.
Okay.
Hello?
Yes, I'm Yeon Tae-seo's brother,
Yeon Hui-seo.
Okay, I'll come now.
I'll be right there.
Okay, bye.
Hey, guys!
Thank you!
Damn it, why isn't he picking up?
A-sol, is my brother with you?
-Yes.
-My brother.
Hey, Tae-seo. Wake up.
Yeah, Hui-seo. I'm on my way.
Tae-seo.
They said Grandma woke up.
I just got a call from the hospital.
I told you, didn't I?
Hurry up and get there.
-Okay, I'll go straight there.
-Okay.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, get up.
Get up! They said Grandma's awake.
What?
-Hurry and get up.
-Okay.
Gosh! Oh, goodness.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Grandpa, will you be able to drive?
I have to.
I just woke up,
so my legs have no strength.
-What about your hands?
-What?
Can you grip like this?
My hands?
Like this?
Your helmet's on okay, right?
-Hold tight!
-Okay.
You can't let go.
But…
you've never ridden
past the post office before.
Will you be okay?
I have to be.
Grandma found the strength too.
-Just a second.
-Yes, Doctor.
Why do things seem so serious?
Before passing away,
she might've regained
some momentary consciousness.
Like terminal lucidity.
Her breathing is stabilizing…
Her hand.
What?
Her index finger twitched.
It's twitching.
She really is awake.
Please explain to the patient's family.
Her condition is stable,
so please go put on
your isolation gowns first.
Dad, have you been to the hospital?
How are you feeling?
So…
I'll…
find a way to manage by myself for a year.
You said you'd come back
to work next year.
Make sure you keep your promise.
Okay, bye.
Yeah. She really pulled through.
Apparently, it was no easy thing.
Anyway, thanks. Bye.
I've called the village chief,
so everyone will know.
Call everyone on your way home.
Everyone's well wishes
helped make this happen.
Okay.
Right?
I told you she would wake up soon.
No, you don't have to come, Hyang-gi.
You can visit
when she moves to a regular room.
No, I should be thanking you.
I'll drive.
Can you manage?
Yeah.
Hey…
You insisted that we come.
Thank you.
Grandma…
woke up.
I went and sang to her,
and the next day,
she woke up just like that.
Well, you're really good at singing.
Aren't you coming back here?
Want me to submit another request
to tear down your house?
No, don't.
Gosh.
If you came back
and Hui-seo's family came back,
wouldn't that be so nice?
Make sure you eat properly.
Don't skip your meals.
Okay.
Make sure you eat too, Granny.
Bye.
That's great.
He can go back home
and back to the way he was living.
After work,
he'll run across Dongjak Bridge,
ride a public rental bicycle up the hill,
and continue his woodwork.
Hello!
He'll see his friend every now and then.
Thanks.
Oh, you're here.
Gosh, I'm really craving
some rolled omelets.
Okay, I'll make you some.
The simple,
peaceful…
and precious routine of Yeon Tae-seo.
Tae-seo.
Hey.
Did you already get off work?
No, I went to eat dinner
and came right back.
-Did you bring my frame?
-Yeah, since I was coming anyway.
I probably won't see you much from now on.
Where's your car?
I'll load it in for you.
It's in the parking lot over there.
It must've been hard getting here by taxi.
I took the bus.
You should've called me.
It would've been easier
if I picked it up myself.
No, it's fine.
-Where should I put these?
-I'll take them.
Okay.
How long will it take?
It won't take long.
So you'll finish everything today
and never see me again?
I'm strapped for time since I'm trying
to change jobs while working.
I don't get it.
You were preparing to change jobs
before your grandma woke up.
And she's awake now.
Everything's still the same, so why?
I was going to do it anyway.
It's better to do it now
when I've made up my mind.
Are you done now?
That was quick.
By the way,
it'll dry faster with some air,
so leave the window open later.
Okay.
I don't know if I'll get to see you, but…
Thanks.
For what?
Not now. Tell me when we say goodbye.
Let's grab a drink with Hyeong-seok
after I finish preparing my job switch.
No, not that.
Let's do this instead.
If you want to thank me, do me one favor.
What is it?
I already said it.
I want us to break up.
This isn't some roundabout way
of saying we should date.
I've never been
in a proper relationship before,
so I've never really
broken up with anyone either.
I don't want my first-ever parting
to be with my family.
I want my first goodbye to be a warm one.
There's no such thing as a warm breakup.
That's what I want.
I want my first goodbye to be just that.
That's why I'm asking you.
We weren't…
We weren't even dating though.
Think of it like this.
You're here just to oil the desk,
but I'm dating you right now.
I'm dating and breaking up with you
all on my own.
This actually makes a lot of sense.
I had feelings for you…
Well, it was a mix of feelings,
like sympathy and so on.
But anyway, after ten years,
I went to commission a frame
and just happened to reunite with you.
That was a big part of it.
So after getting all excited on my own
and wondering if it was a thing or not,
I'm breaking up with you.
Do you seriously think
this makes any sense?
Don't overthink it. Just…
think of it as doing me a favor.
So,
how do you want to break up then?
You only need to do one thing.
On the day we break up,
we'll hold hands, face each other,
and say what we had been thankful for.
With warmth.
That's the first breakup
I've always wanted.
And after we break up?
After we break up,
we won't see each other ever again.
That's why we're saying goodbye.
You were going to stop seeing me
after today anyway.
If my first goodbye is a warm one,
any goodbye that comes after that,
even if it's with family,
won't feel so scary anymore.
And if it's with the guy from Seat One,
it'll be special.
And I'd be grateful.
-You're not going?
-You haven't given me an answer.
I'll do it.
It's not even that difficult.
How about after you finish your test,
around the second week of December?
But not December 8th.
I don't think breaking up
on a Monday is a good idea.
I'll pick the place.
The place we broke up…
Where did you…
break up with me?
WONMA EATERY
-Hello.
-Hey.
He's dying over there.
Everyone goes through breakups.
Let's finish this bottle and go home.
He never spills anything.
He just mopes on his own.
Come on, you need
to talk about it to move on.
Will talking about it
really help me move on?
Then I will.
Go ahead. We're listening.
Sir, this won't take long.
So I…
I…
He keeps things to himself.
He's not the type to talk it out.
He won't say a word
because it'll remind him.
I…
went to see her.
-At dawn.
-At dawn?
At dawn.
That doesn't sound like a good time.
And?
Someone came out, and…
she tells me…
not to…
I can't stop thinking about it.
-It's killing me.
-Who came out?
Hey, do you even have to ask?
He's going to have it rough for a while.
Honestly, stop being a fool
and go buy some spring onions.
No way…
Another guy came out?
Hey! And you just came back?
God, I'm going to lose my mind.
What's wrong with her? She's unbelievable.
She seemed perfectly decent enough,
but she's a crazy…
Shut your mouth.
You don't even know her.
God, you idiot.
Give me a drink.
All right. Drink up then.
Get a hold of yourself.
-Are you done drinking?
-Yes, thank you so much.
-Yeah, take good care of him.
-I will.
I'll go get my car. Stay put.
Eun-a.
I was always so jealous
when Seoul would hold fireworks festivals.
It's right there.
That way.
It's that way.
So that's Yeouido.
It's fine now, but I'll have to come back
when it gets colder.
When you've set a date,
get the original faucets and handles out.
I'll come by when I have time
and restore everything.
Thanks.
At the village chief's house.
-Really?
-Yes.
-No wonder why you seem familiar.
-Right?
There she is.
Goodness.
Mom's here!
I told them I was your mom.
That's why they handed
this place over so easily.
I made a scene, saying I'd kill them all
if they messed with my daughter.
You were in Korea this whole time?
It costs a lot of money and time
to come here.
Taking care of your situation came first.
Then, I met some people. It was fun.
Hey, a lot of those people
made it big thanks to me.
They made it big on their own,
not because of you.
You can sleep here if you want.
God, I'm starving. Got anything to eat?
I want to try some of your cooking.
Let's go.
Eun-a.
I'm going to check out your room.
Go ahead.
You made it all so quickly.
I just steamed what I'd made before.
It's delicious.
You're a good cook.
Why are you all curled up like that?
You're the owner.
Don't start.
You look pitiful. I don't like it.
Sit with your legs crossed.
You'll lose your luck eating like that.
I'm not eating.
That there…
I didn't have any soup, so it's corn tea.
It's nice and toasty.
Did you roast the corn yourself?
Pack me a bunch when I go.
So I can make it at home.
It reminds me of Seon-gyu.
Want me to steam some corn for you?
Gosh, Eun-a.
You should've given me those first.
I was actually here before I went
to Gangneung and met your dad.
The village chief's house.
I stayed there.
I was gathering information in Tongyeong.
Then, I was supposed to go to Gangneung.
But I just loved it here.
There was plenty to work with too.
I really didn't want to go to Gangneung.
But in that town,
a man from Seoul
was living with his daughter
as he made vegan dishes
with local vegetables he'd dig up.
And that daughter
kept calling our local coordinator.
"What time are you coming?
What should we prepare?"
Apparently, she was really excited
about all of us coming.
She was going to leave school early
in time for our arrival.
Honestly,
she was a funny one.
Her name was Mo Eun-a,
and she was eagerly waiting for us.
That's why I went.
And going there…
was the best decision I ever made.
I can't come back to Korea anymore.
I'm getting married.
Just kidding.
What's wrong with you?
My mom talks about you every day.
I guess she loved it when you were around.
She said when you left,
you told her you'd come back.
Day and night, she'd…
Don't use expressions like that.
"Lose your luck." "Day and night."
It's obvious you just
picked them up somewhere.
My mom's dying.
You fool.
We're all dying as we grow old.
There's an obvious limit to life.
MO SEON-GYU
Did you pack the corn tea for me?
Can you also pack me one of those baskets?
My mom would love it.
Two sets of chopsticks and spoons too.
For me and my mom.
I like the Korean ones.
It's made of brass. Brass is better.
I'll ship them to you.
I was going to give them away anyway.
What else?
The nameplate.
No.
Eun-a, are you asleep?
Do you want to…
come to Hawaii with me?
Eat the corn right away.
I guess the last thing I eat in Korea
will be Mo Eun-a's steamed corn.
How meaningful.
I'm going to eat it at Incheon Airport.
You should go. It's time.
Smile.
I'm going to show it to my mom.
Smile. Make it cute.
-I'm 30.
-It's a beautiful age.
Give me a pretty smile.
I've done everything I needed to do here.
Take care.
I'll miss you.
Can I go too?
Can I also…
go where you and your mom
will be?
Let's go right now.
Pack your bags.
You don't even have any guests.
Can I really go?
Of course.
Come with me.
I need to wrap things up here first.
I really…
wasn't going to say this,
but your room at my mom's house
is exactly the way you left it.
Don't you dare not come.
What about your passport?
You need to check right away.
If it's expired, get it reissued.
When I go,
I'll bring Dad's nameplate as well.
NOTICE OF CLOSURE AND FREE GIVEAWAY
Thank you to all the guests
who have loved and supported Byeonnwi.
Goodbye.
Bye.
We had a great stay.
Thank you. Let's go.
Byeonnwi will be accepting reservations
up until December.
We'll be giving away
our furniture and decorative items.
If you are interested,
please check the attached photos
and let us know.
Thank you.
Ga-on's excited.
Make good use of it, Ga-on.
That chair is my little brother.
Really? The chair must be happy.
It's all been cleared out already?
I allowed plenty of time on purpose,
but the giveaway happened really quickly.
We're sad about it,
so we all wanted to keep
at least something that came from here.
What about your stuff?
I'm sure you have a lot.
I've already shipped them.
So you're really leaving.
You two were my last guests.
Thank you for coming.
Mom. A photo.
Should we take a photo?
-How about a photo?
-Shall we?
Let's take it here.
We'll take a selfie.
Here we go.
Cheese. One, two, three.
MO SEON-GYU
-Mr. Yeon Tae-seo.
-Yes?
You already have experience
working as a subway operator.
Is there any special reason why you want
to change jobs and be a rail operator?
What did you find challenging
about your previous job?
It's not that I found it challenging.
I wasn't in a situation
where I could do that job, but…
I wanted to become
a Sea Train driver back then.
I guess it looked kind of cool.
That's nice.
It was the first job I chose
simply because I wanted to do it.
It was very rewarding.
It helped me feel like
I was finally self-reliant.
I'd like to go beyond the city
and operate different types of trains
across a wider range of terrain.
-Hello.
I heard you're changing jobs.
No, not yet.
I made it
to the final round of interviews,
but I ended up rambling.
I'm sure you'll get it.
Since you're quitting,
this will be a good way to say goodbye.
Here.
What is it?
I took it while I was taking
night photos at Oido Station.
It came out pretty well.
Thank you.
All right then.
Tae-seo.
This is the right place.
This place is what's real.
Eun-a.
For you, that's the right place, isn't it?
Good job.
For me…
this is the right place too.
Please let us both
achieve our goals today.
You're right,
and I'm right too.
But then,
why did we end up like this?
Can I help you?
The guesthouse that was here…
It's closed now.
Then what about Eun-a…
I mean, where is the owner?
She went home.
I heard she's going to her mom's.
When my mom was pregnant with me,
she'd always crave these noodles.
I'm sure she's doing well somewhere.
Somewhere that has nothing to do with me.
Maybe it's not a good idea
to go looking like this.
He said he was visiting Gangneung,
so he should be back soon.
Was getting a perm a bit over the top?
I have to get out later though.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
What?
Don't tell me you forgot.
Well, I just… Where should we go?
-Did you pick a place?
-That hurts.
Sorry, I'm a little…
out of it today.
Let's do this another day.
Why put it off?
Let's get it over with.
What I said
about my first breakup
wasn't a joke.
It's important to me.
I know.
Let's turn on just the lamp.
If it's too bright,
reality's going to hit hard.
I'll give you some water.
Let's just do it.
Come sit.
Sorry.
Today, I…
What about today?
Today,
I'm feeling really pathetic.
We all have days like that.
I felt like that earlier.
Pathetic and embarrassed.
Well, what did you do?
What kind of pathetic
are we talking about?
I was the one who broke it off,
but I couldn't accept it.
I've heard enough.
Let's hurry and do this.
You're…
breaking up with me because I'm pathetic.
Once we break up,
we won't see each other ever again.
You'd know this better than me.
We're holding hands,
we're facing each other,
and now, with warmth…
Thank you.
The study center's Seat One guy
was the most unfortunate person I knew.
He was so pitiful
that I couldn't even dare to like him.
I was so sure back then when I was young
that your misfortune would last forever.
But you found your way and flourished.
You also found love,
went through a breakup,
and you didn't let misfortune
weigh you down.
You proved my preconceptions wrong
and lived a good life, so I'm grateful.
Also,
thank you for showing me a miracle.
The moment your grandma's finger twitched,
I witnessed a miracle.
I won't ever forget it.
Whenever things get tough,
I'll remember it.
The finger twitch
of Seat One guy's grandma.
I can't do this.
I can't do this today. Sorry.
I can't handle seeing your back.
At the study center,
all I saw was your back.
On our way back
after your grandma woke up,
I saw your back
when you got out of the car,
and I managed to hold it all in even then.
Let's go out for real.
No, I mean…
I mean…
Just until the end of the year.
We can go out
and break up around Christmas.
Hold on.
Before Christmas would be better.
I'm busy at the end of the year.
Maybe on the 23rd or the 24th.
Or just do it today.
You just had to say you couldn't do it…
Never mind. Sorry.
Let's do that.
It won't even be that difficult.
That place where your mom is.
What's it like?
Over there,
the things I couldn't give you
and the things you could never
be fulfilled by in this world
can all be fulfilled, right?
When I was crushed by misfortune,
moving without purpose
and just simply breathing…
you came to me so casually
and gave me what the world
could never fulfill, Eun-a.
I'll forever be
grateful.
I'm going to go.
I'll take you home.
No, it's fine. You'll be coming back here.
It's just a quick trip
to go there and back.
Did you take your medicine?
Yeah.
I'm just sore
because the tension wore off.
I'm fine.
It looks like this will all be over soon.
Grandpa.
-So…
-Yeah?
About me changing jobs…
I didn't get it.
You took a test and failed?
Yes.
I can take it again next year.
I'm off to the hospital now.
Okay.
Mo Eun-a.
STILL SHINING
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee