For the past few years,
our rookies haven't performed well.
As a result,
the Dreams have the oldest starting lineup
of all 12 teams.
I am entirely responsible for that outcome.
Who holds the authority
to decide who gets drafted?
Getting right to it, aren't you?
So you plan to investigate our scouting team?
Everyone has two sides to them.
Naive trust is dangerous.
But so is excessive doubt.
Understood.
[High schools]
I see we've selected rather obscure players.
Sorry? I'm not following.
Yeah! We have specialists who...
You two, settle down.
GM, our reliable scouts nationwide
have gathered this intel for us.
Yes, our colleagues work tirelessly to...
Why was our first draft pick in 2020
an obscure player,
when the baseball Koshien that year
was canceled due to COVID?
Our picks for rookies have suffered since.
Luck is a part of the draft.
Yes, luck plays a major role.
- That's enough.
- But sir!
Then I'll show him.
Stop, you're no better.
What's that supposed to mean?
Have we been unlucky for six years straight?
I believe that may not entirely be the case.
Hold on a minute.
Kikuchi, stop it.
I can't sit, and let him run his mouth, sir.
Just let me say this.
Mr. Kurokawa is not at fault.
Mr. Kurokawa, why aren't you
standing up for yourself?
We were trying to draft Yuma Arihara.
Arihara...
- The Vikings' shortstop, right?
- That's right.
But then?
Osanai, one of our amateur scouts
at the time,
insisted on drafting Satozaki
from Gifu Daini.
No, in the end, I also agreed to it.
That wasn't Osanai's fault.
No, no, no, no, no.
This Osanai.
Where is he now?
Beats me.
Scouts are supposed to be team players,
darn it.
Osanai! Where'd you go?
Our GM's looking for you, Osanai.
Quit grandstanding!
Show yourself already, Osanai!
We're getting impatient, you rascal.
It's my fault I can't wrangle
my own subordinates.
No, no. You're not at fault, sir.
Don't come and defend me.
You're only making things awkward.
It's counterproductive.
Oh, geez! My apologies! I spoke out of line.
The floor is yours.
Let's revisit this matter another day.
Understood. I will go see Osanai myself.
If there's any wrongdoing, I'll be fired.
If there's any wrongdoing, you will be.
GM!
Why were you badgering him?
Who?
Mr. Kurokawa.
The 2020 draft was six years ago.
Why are you pursuing accountability, now?
Why not?
The 2020 draft
was not under your jurisdiction.
It is so we do not repeat our mistakes.
I commend you for bringing back Sawada.
- President Makita.
- Yes?
Do you trust our Scouting Director,
Mr. Kurokawa?
Of course I do. We've been
working together for years now.
- Is that your only reason?
- Huh?
Your trust is baseless.
You've confirmed nothing for yourself.
You're speaking so coldly again.
We've been through thick and thin together.
Then you're satisfied with uncertainty.
GM, wouldn't you be hurt if we doubted you?
Doesn't seem like it.
I'd rather work with someone who doubts me,
than an observer who only knows trust.
Where does that steel-like confidence
of yours come from?
Shift's over!
Alright everyone,
it's welcome party time!
Party!
That's right, party!
The night is still young! Party!
Could you not start weird chants?
Just get ready already.
But, Prez.
Coaches and staff
rarely grab drinks together!
Right, Mr. Kurokawa?
He's right.
Where's the GM?
He's meeting us there.
Yikes, let's go.
Huh? Wait a minute! Wait up!
Long hallway, eh?
Everyone, please take off your slippers.
- We know.
- Okay!
- It's a tatami room.
- Right.
- Welcome.
- Who wouldn't take off their slippers?
Careful, there's a step here.
Guess he's not here yet.
- Try contacting him.
- Yes, ma'am.
That won't be necessary.
- Whoa!
- You were early?
We were scheduled for 7PM, no?
- Yikes.
- We're so sorry.
We're late because of your stupid chant.
No, it was because you were slow!
It was your fault!
- It was yours!
- No, yours!
Please, let me enjoy my drinks
in peace tonight!
Quit it with the lover's quarrel.
Look, see? You two are holding up the line.
- We're so sorry.
- Real sorry, folks.
- Guide them in.
- Right this way.
Testing, testing.
Alright everyone, your attention, please.
I'd like to invite the GM up
to give a few words.
GM, if you'd please.
Let's hear it for the GM!
That's our GM!
Again, I am Sakurazaki, the GM.
I fully respect your ways
and method of operations.
However, I believe change is necessary.
I acquired Sawada in place of Kudo.
I will do whatever is necessary for the team.
I will not hesitate to cut off anything,
or anyone, who causes the team harm.
Here's to our success, as a team.
Give it up for our GM!
Thank you GM, for the riveting greeting.
Yes! That's our GM!
Sounded more like a declaration of war to me.
Yes. He's putting
quite a bit of pressure on us.
How annoying.
Hey, are you really okay with that?
Mr. Kurokawa, he's approaching.
Sure, Mom.
I'll call you back.
Yeah. Take care.
Are you alright, Mr. Kurokawa?
Someone, help! His knee!
- I think he broke something!
- No, no.
Quit exaggerating, I'm fine.
And he has me locked on.
Sir, leave this to me.
Was there something you needed?
Right, I thought so. I kept the seat warm.
Here, it's all yours.
Here, have a drink.
Thank you.
Now that trade.
That was just brilliant.
Do you have any requests for me?
Requests, eh?
Hold a drinking party every month.
Nice one, Mr. Kurokawa.
Since Toyohashi is famous for its chikuwa,
I suggest we get oden every month.
We could go bar hopping.
A foodie tour doesn't sound bad at all.
I'm just kidding.
You asked for requests, was it? Let's see...
Ah, I do have one.
Pro scouts cover 12 teams
and independent leagues.
Amateurs cover middle school
to university leagues.
Our job is to observe the play styles
and personalities of promising players.
- That's right.
- Idiot!
You're very dedicated to your work.
You didn't need to get involved...
When a scout is fired or transferred,
it's a rule to hand over
all their materials to their successor.
We love clear-cut rules!
Absolutely!
But the instincts I've developed
can't be passed on.
I see.
So you're saying personnel changes
are unnecessary for scouts.
Well, that's one way to put it.
I'll carefully consider
if those words were advice...
or an attempt at abusing your authority.
GM.
Isn't that going too far?
Now, now, let's lighten up and have a drink!
Anyone wants tequila?
- Just come back.
- Ow, ow, ow!
Yes, I understand! I'm sorry.
- Hey!
- Please, just not the suspenders.
Evening, folks. What a party this is.
Please, there's no need.
Relax.
Oh?
Was I interrupting?
No, no, of course not!
Your presence is more than welcome, sir.
I'll get you both a plate and chopsticks.
I'm fine, thank you.
I only came to settle the bill,
but I simply had to join in the fun.
May I sit right over here?
Sir, if you'd like--
Watch out!
I'm terribly sorry.
- Please, go ahead.
- Move it!
Pardon my interruption.
Mr. Kurokawa is a very responsible person.
When he was an active player,
I was actually a fan.
I'm honored, sir.
A decorated athlete,
who is now Scouting Director.
There is a slight disjoint there, no?
I often think that myself.
- There he goes
- Kurokawa's history,
and his title of Scouting Director.
They are slightly disjointed.
My words exactly.
Now would you please can it?
As you wish, sir!
I offered him the position of manager.
However, he insisted his role
as Scouting Director was crucial,
and shot me clean down.
A truly moving story, is that not?
I think I'll have a drink.
- Come, bring him a cold one.
- Oh, it's fine.
- Miyahara, please.
- Beer!
Well then, I bid you all a good night.
May I ask one question?
The manager was here with us today.
What about it?
He may have overheard your offer to Kurokawa.
Is that so?
I understand.
How could you say that to the President!
I thought he ought to know.
Must be nice, being able to speak your mind.
Prez.
My heart just clenched.
Yeah.
I brushed it aside earlier,
but I can't help but think back to it.
Was the GM lecturing me?
No, no. For a mere GM to lecture you?
Unthinkable.
What kind of person is he?
Erm...
What do you mean by that, sir?
I'm asking if he will obey me.
That is, well...
Some individuals hold no power,
yet they have conviction.
I find these sorts of individuals...
to be absolutely detestable.
The conviction these people hold
can, and will be broken.
I cannot wait to see it happen.
Today,
I'll be reuniting with a teacher
who I haven't seen since graduating.
- I'm home!
- Oh, welcome back.
Your adorable, exhausted sister is back.
- Where's dinner?
- I didn't cook.
Just be quiet for a moment.
This is where it gets good.
You're not working, so at least make dinner.
I'm looking for work.
I want a job where I can maximize my charm.
I've heard that before.
Please, just be quiet for a moment.
See, watch.
- She's reuniting with her mentor.
- Mrs. Tanaka!
- See? See?
- Long time no see.
- How have you been?
- I've been doing well.
I'm so happy to see you!
Oh, no!
Do you remember Mr. Yamashita
from junior high?
Oh, I remember him. Why?
He was my favorite teacher.
Huh? Why?
- I was always playing around, right?
- Yeah.
Well, Mr. Yamashita set me straight.
He said, "you're underestimating yourself".
So then you changed your ways
and studied diligently?
Yup.
Hey. How was that funny?
Well, here's the thing.
Mom actually asked the teacher
to encourage you.
What?
- Seriously?
- Dead serious.
Why?
To give you the motivation you needed.
For real?
My respect for Mr. Yamashita just shattered.
Really? I highly doubt it.
I didn't want to hear that secret.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ms. Tanaka, I greatly treasure
your presence in my life.
He insisted his role
as Scouting Director was crucial,
and shot me clean down.
Your trust is baseless.
You've confirmed nothing for yourself.
You're still here?
- I'm working overtime.
- Are you done?
Now I am!
Okay, then make a list of players drafted
in the last six years,
grouped by their high school.
I, Itsuki Miyahara,
hear your request loud and clear, ma'am.
Why are you being so dramatic?
I'm happy you rely on me.
I'm not relying on you,
I'm giving you an order.
Oh, come on.
Just do it already.
[List of drafts by school, 2020-2025]
And sent!
Thank you.
That's it?
No hugs for your capable junior?
- No pushing him against a wall?
- Hey.
No pulling down my suspenders with a snap?
Be quiet.
What's wrong?
[Scouting Director]
What are you doing?
- Be quiet.
- Huh?
You're still around?
Good evening.
We're working overtime...
I see. Good work.
- I'll get that.
- Sure.
Yes, hello?
What? The police?
Huh?
Tanigaki got into a fight.
That was close, wasn't it?
Even if someone insults the Dreams,
fighting is not allowed.
Please be very careful.
I apologize.
If you do the same thing again, you're fired.
Yes, ma'am.
You should be careful.
When Prez gets angry,
she turns into a real demon.
- Don't say anything unnecessary!
- Ow! That hurts!
- Back to the office we go.
- Ma'am, please!
- Not in front of the police station!
- Pipe down.
Hey.
How are your parents?
They're fine.
Give them my regards.
You know the players' parents?
Yeah.
Even if a player's short,
they could hit a growth spurt
if their parents are tall, you know?
When scouting players,
what do you prioritize most?
- That's gotta be...
- I wasn't asking you.
Physicality is number one.
Right, I thought so!
If there are no issues there,
then it's all about character and motivation.
That's our Scouting Director!
I see...
But, Tanigaki, the rehabilitating Okajima,
and the now retired, unsuccessful Kurata
were all physically weak.
Prez?
I trust your eye, Mr. Kurokawa.
But there are some players
I simply don't know why you chose.
I understand scouting can come
with certain temptations, as well.
Makita.
Yes.
What do you think you're doing?
I admit, I'm incompetent.
But I won't tolerate being suspected.
Stop the car.
Is it just me,
or does it feel stuffy in here?
Hey, I know.
Why don't we all sing the Dreams' team song?
Let's sing! Come on!
After me, folks!
Okay!
Go!
Great!
Nice, nice!
Nice catch!
Alright, he's getting in the groove.
- How's this?
- Looking good.
Who are you?
What is that?
Well...
Were you passing through the neighborhood?
Yes, something like that.
Are you knowledgeable about baseball?
No. Not really.
Do you know how many seconds it takes
to run from home to first?
About six seconds?
For a right-handed batter, 4.3 seconds.
For a left-handed batter, 4.0 seconds.
That's enough to tell you
which kids will go pro.
Know why?
Because they're fast?
Well, it's partly because they're athletic.
But kids who sprint to first
always succeed as pros.
Because they're the real hard workers.
Alright! You guys got this!
He's losing his grip strength.
Change the pitcher.
You can't keep him in.
He'll injure his shoulder!
I know, I understand.
- You clearly don't.
- Let's calm down.
I mean, aren't you the manager here?
We have our reasons.
A player's career is on the line!
Let's calm down.
- Protect the player!
- Now, now.
- Sir, here.
- It's no big deal.
Thank you very much. You really helped me.
I'm so grateful it went well.
- Heading back?
- Yes.
- Keep it up.
- I will.
Thank you.
Take care, sir.
Good work.
Wait, you're still here?
Who exactly are you?
I'm the GM of the Dreams. Sakurazaki.
I called you yesterday.
Huh? Our GM? Seriously?
- Yes.
- You should have said so.
Oh, no, please don't get the wrong idea.
This isn't a bribe or anything.
May I see it?
Yes.
[Draft News]
[Mystery of the First Round Tanigaki Pick]
[Bribing the scouts?]
How are your parents?
They're fine.
Mom asked the teacher to encourage you.
Even though it's the off-season,
you're always practicing until it's late.
I have to make up for what I'm lacking.
A player chosen first in the draft
couldn't be "lacking".
The Draft Lottery is coming up again.
Bad rumors about you are spreading.
Tanigaki.
How much did you give Mr. Kurokawa?
I only know about baseball.
Anything else is...
Please, tell me the truth.
I won't cause you any trouble.
You're already causing me enough trouble.
Please leave!
Are you prepared?
If I tell you everything,
both my career and Mr. Kurokawa's
will be put in jeopardy.
Can you be held responsible for that?
I had lent him money
to get his injury treated.
Many players are poor,
and come from single parent households.
Even so, monetary transactions
are a violation of the rules.
Yes, I am aware.
May I ask about the 2020 Draft?
Pardon?
Why was Satozaki your first round pick?
Six years ago,
I was scouting Gifu Daini High School,
an obscure team that made it
to the prefectural finals.
But the tournament was canceled due to COVID.
I couldn't give up.
I went to see them.
The players weren't discouraged.
They were practicing.
With Koshien unfortunately canceled,
I now realize we can never take
our games of baseball for granted.
It's an odd feeling, really.
But I will continue to play baseball,
with this thought in my heart.
I knew his humility
and passion for baseball...
would surely bear fruit in the pros.
That's why I went against
the Scouting Director's objections,
and had the team draft him first.
He was released after only three years.
If he hadn't been injured...
Being too soft-hearted...
never benefits the team.
Indeed.
I admit I was wrong.
My father was a huge baseball fan,
and it was his dream for me to go pro.
So, from the signing bonus...
I thought it would be a one-time thing,
but he still demands a cut.
What brought you to that field today?
There's a pitcher at that university
who pitched well as a reliever
even as a freshman.
I came to check on his status.
Are you preparing for the upcoming draft?
Yes.
A right-handed sidearm pitcher is valuable.
His throws are speedy,
but his control is unstable.
It might take time for him
to succeed as a pro.
Our team currently needs players
who can show results, now.
I believe it's best we pass on drafting him.
[Scouting Director]
What?
What's wrong?
What would you do, if I did something
to tarnish the team's name?
Huh? Something, like what?
Like taking bribes from a player.
Holy cow, a bribe?
How much did you get?
- It was a hypothetical!
- Ow!
Can you stop hitting me
for every little thing?
But what would you do if it were true?
I would trust your choice, ma'am.
Why?
Because I know you, Prez.
I haven't been at your side for nothing.
Don't trust me too much.
If you're ever suspicious, doubt me.
Believe, only after seeing the truth
for yourself.
Am I clear?
Sorry, I don't really get it.
How can he be out, when drafts are coming up?
Hello? Where are you right now?
I'm in Korea.
Korea?
I believe you called earlier?
I have a report regarding Mr. Kurokawa.
First, I'd like to ask you for a favor.
Sorry, a favor?
I'm the one who's been trying to call you...
[2026 Draft]
This year's a bad crop,
so let's call it at round three,
and head out for drinks.
Excellent idea, sir.
Let's get this over with.
I'll go ahead and make a reservation.
You're a bit too eager, aren't you?
- Sorry, sorry.
- Bars aren't even open yet.
I got ahead of myself.
How about we first decide
between meat or fish?
I'll take a vote.
Prez, where have you been?
What?
What's wrong?
There's something I'd like to discuss.
If it's about changing a pick,
you're too late.
Scouting Director Kurokawa.
You are suspected of scouting bribery.
Huh?
You.
What are you talking about?
That's right, what are you talking about?
Acting like a detective or something.
Since 2020, the Dreams have scouted
a total of 24 high school students
under your direction.
Among them, 12 students were drafted
from Seitoku Sports,
Toei Tech, and Tomohama Academy.
Half of our 24 were from these three schools.
Yeah. And what of it?
The coach of Seitoku Sports
was your upperclassman.
Yeah, from high school.
And the coach of Toei Tech?
Was an upperclassman in college.
Is there a problem with that?
What about the coach from Tomohama Academy?
How am I connected to him?
Answer me.
The mountaineering club.
You're still around?
Good work.
[Mountaineering Club 8th Anniversary]
Bingo. You got it.
I still don't see the issue here.
We're close, so I get insider intel.
It's inevitable I'll pick from their schools.
Only one player you received intel about
has performed well.
The others are late bloomers.
Give them a few years.
The Dreams need athletes
who can make plays, now.
The team must have told you this already.
Fine, call me incompetent, why don't you?
Yeah, let's go with that.
Didn't you make an under-the-table deal?
Hey.
Don't test me, Makita!
Where's the evidence, huh?
If you've got evidence, show it here!
Accusing me with nothing to show?
What's wrong with you?
He's right, Prez.
[I cannot go after all. I'm sorry.]
I'm sorry.
It's getting stuffy in here.
What're you going to do about that, huh?
I've never been so humiliated
in my entire career.
Forget the draft.
You guys figure the rest of it out.
No, no, no.
Sir, we need you!
Direct your complaints at that woman.
President Makita.
If this draft fails,
you'll be held responsible.
You've upset our Scouting Chief.
What're you going to do about that?
This man has something to tell you all.
Mr. Kurokawa, it's been a while.
I'm Arihara, from the Vikings.
In 2020,
on the condition of a first-round pick,
I gave Mr. Kurokawa 5 million yen.
Oh my god, it's true!
However, the Vikings won
the luck of the draw.
Watch it, Arihara.
This is a recording of our deal.
He clearly promises me a pick,
and states I won't get my money back.
Are you out of your mind?
This is obviously nonsense.
I don't mind playing this recording now.
Your career will be over!
Welcome.
How do you know about our deal?
The day after the draft,
Mr. Kurokawa was seen
visiting your high school.
It was captured on video.
Why did Mr. Kurokawa come to see you?
Wasn't it because he couldn't pick you?
When you won Rookie of the Year,
could you earnestly be proud
of your accomplishments?
Are you telling me
to get it all off my chest?
You can't turn over a new leaf
if you continue to hide your wrongdoings.
Your brother also plays baseball
in high school, yes?
Are you going to teach him your ways?
This way of joining a team?
Scouting Director Kurokawa.
Please return the 5 million yen to Arihara.
You...
are fired.
- What?
- Fired?
This is tyranny! Tyranny!
Absolute tyranny, I say!
He's right. Firing the Scouting Director
right before the draft...
It's simply going too far!
Osanai.
You.
Where have you been all this time?
I'm appointing Mr. Osanai...
as the new Scouting Director.
[2026 Professional Baseball Draft]
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for waiting.
The 2026 Professional Baseball Draft
shall now commence.
Please welcome in the 12 teams.
The Toyohashi Yaoshima Dreams!
The Chiba Ocean Waves!
The Yokohama Mardline Vikings!
The Tokyo Smile Pelicans!
Kansai Electric Railway Octopathy!
Please pick many players who will be popular!
Please!
Let's all send them our prayers!
Oh, no, what should I do?
Why are you the most nervous one here?
- Sit down.
- I know, I know it's weird.
But I have the right to be nervous too.
Stop it, your nerves are rubbing off on me.
How about we take deep breaths together?
You shoot down all my suggestions.
Mind if I join your breathing exercises?
Sure.
Please sit.
- No standing?
- All teams have been seated.
It's starting.
We will now read out the first-round picks.
First Draft Pick.
Toyohashi Yaoshima.
Yuki Tanaka.
Pitcher, Midoriyama University.
First Draft Pick.
Yokohama Mardline.
Yuki Tanaka.
Pitcher, Midoriyama Gakuen University.
Tokyo Smile.
Yuki Tanaka.
Pitcher, Midoriyama University.
Wow, six teams have picked Tanaka.
Don't make a fuss.
The GM will draw us Tanaka.
We're counting on you, GM!
Maintaining composure is key.
Representatives from the six teams,
please come to the stage.
The GM will surely make it happen.
We're counting on you.
Please, GM!
Which one?
Which hand will you use to draw?
Right or left?
They say it's good to use
your non-dominant hand.
I see.
Please.
Please come up to the stage.
Toyohashi Yaoshima.
Yokohama Mardline.
Please open your envelopes.
Please, please, please.
Yes!
Alright!
Yuki Tanaka will be signed
to the Tokyo Smiles.
- Huh?
- Why?
Are you serious?
Aw...
Why is he so calm? We lost our first pick!
Boo! Boo! Boo!
What's with that attitude?
I've always had bad luck with lotteries.
Huh?
Why aren't you more disappointed?
Should I be?
Look, here.
- Now, now, now.
- Prez.
Maybe not now.
Ow! Why me?
I needed an outlet.
Ow! What? Why me?
I needed an outlet, too.
There are still plenty of good players.
GM.
First Round Pick.
Toyohashi Yaoshima.
Lim Min Jong.
Pitcher, Busan University
of Information Sciences.
Are there any other players
you're interested in?
Huh?
If not, that's fine.
Yes! There are!
Please take a look at this.
He was the ace of Gifu High at the time.
Lim Min Jong?
Yes.
After the Koshien was canceled in 2020,
he returned to Korea
without ever showcasing his skills.
Can he be chosen in the Japanese draft?
Since he graduated
from a Japanese high school, yes.
They got me.
So they had their eyes on Lim.
And he was their first-round pick.
Korea?
- Know him?
- Can't say I do.
Trying to show off, eh?
That's what a weak team would do.
Lim Min Jong has been confirmed
as the pick for Toyohashi Yaoshima.
Alright!
Ow! Why me again?
Ow!
[Dreams' surprise pick of Lim Min Jong]
[The Birth of a New Ace]
[Lim Min Jong is the Dreams' first pick]
15 years ago,
you faced off against the Vikings.
It was the bottom of the 9th,
two outs, bases loaded.
You were at bat, sir.
You said the umpire's dead ball
was called on a foul.
You said the ball grazed your bat.
Even though we lost the game,
you were absolutely amazing, sir.
Back then, I was still young.
You were the embodiment of justice, sir.
Good work.
What kind of person was he?
He had his own idea of the perfect swing,
and was a sociable person
who could befriend anyone.
Everyone recognized his eye
for evaluating batters.
But he strayed from that path.
To quote someone I know.
"People have two sides to them."
"Look at them both."
Like you do.
Huh?
Was that a compliment?
You just complimented me, right? Right?
Well, you're right.
I do see the good and bad in people.
It's a skill of mine.
Do you recall what I said
after Kudo was traded away?
Why sow unnecessary seeds
when the team has no tomorrow?
I'm simply following my resume.
I asked for a disbandment.
Disbanding wasn't the only thing
on my resume.
Victory first.
Then disbandment.
Do you really think this team can win?
You only acquired Sawada.
Sir.
I will meet your expectations.