[1056 AM Tokai]
This Dreams versus Vikings game
is brought to you from the Dreams' very own
Toyohashi Yaoshima Dome.
The score is 8 to 2.
The Dreams are trailing by 6 runs.
- Good work.
Good work.
[President of Baseball Operations (POBO)]
It's the final game between the Dreams,
who are in last place this season,
and the Vikings, who have already secured
a spot in the Climax Series.
Batting third is Tanigaki.
He previously hit a line drive
to second base.
Well, that was a jammed hit.
The shortstop handles it lightly,
and throws to first.
Bottom of the 6th, two outs,
no runners on base.
The Dreams are down six runs.
Kudo! Kudo! Kudo! Kudo! Kudo!
Batting cleanup, left fielder Kudo.
[Tatsuya Kudo]
Stepping up to plate
with the crowd cheering for him
is Dreams' slugger, Kudo.
Hit it out of the park, Kudo!
His appearance alone has the crowd roaring.
Fans have high hopes for Kudo's swing.
Kudo is 1-for-2 today.
If he gets a hit here,
the dugout will liven up.
Hit it out of the park, Kudo! Kudo! Kudo!
He hit it! Did it go?
The ball is flying far!
It's in! It's in!
The ball goes straight
to the left field stands!
A defiant home run from cleanup hitter Kudo.
This is his 30th home run of the season,
putting him third in the home run race!
What a dazzling hit that was.
Indeed.
He knew it was out of there
the moment he hit it.
He truly is a reliable presence
throughout this team's rough season.
In the bottom of the 6th,
Kudo's solo home run
brings the Dreams to five runs.
[The Kudo Burger: Filling, and satisfying!]
Leading off the 7th for the Vikings,
is their 5th batter, Nomura.
On the mound is the starting pitcher, Kijima.
He has already thrown over 90 pitches.
Hit it out of the park, Nomura!
Oh no, the ball got away!
- It's a dead ball!
- Hey!
Don't hit him over the score!
Yeah, watch it!
Looks like the Vikings' dugout
is getting a bit heated.
Catch it!
Coach! Please change the pitcher already!
Batting 6th, designated hitter, Allen.
Hey!
Why is a useless hitting coach
interfering with a pitching change?
Huh?
Coach, I'll decide when we change pitchers.
Well, I say we change. How about it, Coach?
Stay out of my lane!
What? Then change him already! Hear me?
What?
Coach, please...
Can it!
Now sit your asses back down.
The Dreams can't give up any more runs.
Kijima on the mound.
Can he get out of this jam?
He's hit it! The ball goes to center field!
He comes forward, and the ball has dropped!
That's a clean hit.
Did he misjudge the trajectory of that hit?
I swear that was an out in the making.
Their pitcher must be frustrated.
The count's at three balls.
Kijima's pitching marathon continues.
Kijima's a veteran getting on in the years.
The dugout ought to consider
swapping pitchers.
This one goes right to second base.
And it's a glove fumble!
His throw is way off.
The ball goes to left field!
Wow, I can't believe what I just witnessed.
This is practically a sandlot game.
Nomura scores in the meantime!
The Vikings score another run!
What are you doing? Get it together!
The score is now 9 to 3.
The Vikings are once again up six runs.
Seriously? Damn it...
It's the final game of the season,
and fans are already leaving the stadium.
- Pitcher change.
- Yes, sir.
Your attention, please.
Now pitching for the Dreams, #22 Suzuki.
#22 Suzuki.
I can't blame paying fans for leaving
when their home team is absolutely fumbling.
Dreamers, give it up for our Lucky Sevens!
That guy who got in through connections
is slacking!
I'm so tired.
A mascot shouldn't be giving up!
Woah, hey! Watch it!
Why do I have to wear this thing?
Because our usual guy is out sick.
Well, I'm going to be out sick from the heat.
At least we're not outdoors.
Yeah? You try wearing this.
Come on, no more complaining.
- Move it.
- Hey, careful!
- I'm hydrating!
- Hurry up!
Ms. President! Ms. President!
We've got a problem, ma'am!
What's wrong, Dreams?
Was there a conflict within the team?
How disgraceful. This team is finished.
What do they think they're doing?
- Let's go!
- Huh?
Hurry!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Hey, hey, wait!
- My water! Water!
- Let's go!
Someone! Hey!
Stop it!
Stop fighting!
Please calm down!
Calm down!
Everyone!
Hey! Please calm down!
Calm down!
There are children watching!
Don't disappoint them!
It's the last game of the year.
What are you doing, seriously?
Geez.
- You started it.
- Oh, yeah?
Move it.
The game has ended.
- Thank you.
- Today's score is 14 to 3.
The Vikings have won.
Winning pitcher, Onizuka.
Losing pitcher, Kijima.
Why can't we win?
It's not our fault.
The players are the ones playing the games.
Exactly.
It's not fair to blame us.
Alright everyone, let's drink the night away.
Yeah.
- Kurokawa, you drink too!
- I am, I am.
Maybe our cheapskate owner is to blame?
You may be right.
Next year, let's aim for 5th place!
- 5th place!
- Perfect!
- Excellent.
- Great idea.
Why're you all laughing, huh?
Ma'am, you're drinking too much.
We lost, and you all are laughing.
This is why we're always in last place!
Oh no, the alcohol monster
is about to go on a rampage!
Someone, take her drink away!
Huh? Me?
Okay, Prez. Let's put that down for a second.
Don't touch me, Nepo hire!
Ow!
Now, now, folks. Let's calm down.
Everyone...
What's wrong, GM?
Well, the Dreams this year
only managed 56 wins.
Last year we secured 59 wins.
- So, we had 3 fewer wins.
- That's what it is.
That's true.
I...
have decided to resign as GM!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
I apologize for the delay
in making this decision.
Well then, I'll be taking my leave!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait!
GM, please wait!
- What? What's wrong?
- Scary, scary, scary.
He's fast.
Just wait a minute!
Just a moment.
- More alcohol!
- Ouch.
Alcohol!
Let's drink! Drink, drink, drink!
Slow down, Prez.
No drinking it straight.
She's got a strong grip.
Drink, drink, drink!
This isn't alcohol!
- Were you even listening?
- Ow, ow!
- I said, alcohol.
- I thought water would help.
- Alcohol!
- Ow, ow...
My ear's gonna fall off!
It's gonna rip off!
- Anyone got more alcohol?
- Is my ear still there?
- Let's calm down.
- Where's the alcohol?
Maybe I should quit too...
I know.
I'm not quitting.
How do you plan to utilize
your previous work experience?
I will leverage my experience
as a management consultant
to assign the right people
to the right positions.
As I've been a player, coach, and manager,
I believe in incorporating many opinions
from those directly on the field.
Which of them will be the new GM?
They're both excellent,
so it's a tough choice.
Indeed.
- There's still an applicant left.
- What?
Oh, right.
Come on in.
Excuse me.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Mr. Jun Sakurazaki.
You were a GM for ice hockey, volleyball,
and rugby, correct?
Yes.
And you're currently unemployed?
Have you ever watched a Dreams game?
I've watched my fair share of edited clips.
Ah, those.
If only they weren't so malicious.
Only our losing games get uploaded.
Those sorts of videos
will only continue to increase.
Huh? What do you mean?
For the next decade,
your team may remain in last place.
What?
What are you talking about?
Presumptuous.
Can you back your claim in any way?
What do you know of the Dreams?
Now, now, now...
I know enough.
Oh, really? Then go on, tell us.
- Hey.
- Calm down.
The coaches fight amongst themselves.
Huh?
The manager is looked down upon.
The players are ashamed of their own team.
Team management is outdated,
and relies solely on instinct.
And...
- We've heard enough.
- Hey, now.
- Thank you for your time today.
- Prez.
We'll keep your resume on record.
Keep an ear out for your results.
- Wait!
- Please leave.
The exit is right that way.
Then if you'll excuse me.
You missed a chance to win.
What?
What's with that guy?
He doesn't know a thing about baseball.
He's so annoying!
And what's with the nonchalant face?
Mr. Sakurazaki.
Do the Dreams have any strengths to them?
What is it you want for this team?
I want them to win, of course.
Does everyone see eye-to-eye with you?
Huh?
What do you mean?
I mean nothing more than just that.
What the heck was he talking about?
We're united! We're one team!
Hey, hey!
Our dumplings are burning.
Blame that on the dumplings.
You're always full of sophistry.
Hey, turn off the heat.
He talks big for a baseball amateur.
Sorry, who?
Haven't you been listening?
The guy I interviewed!
You're lashing out at everyone,
so I don't know!
Listen up.
I love the Dreams more than anyone.
I don't care! Rejected!
Why do I have to be interviewed
by my sister?
Well, he's probably wondering
why he was interviewed
by a lady who's never even played baseball.
Damn it.
I win.
No, I win. Did you see that chug just now?
No, but it's my win.
- I win!
- Careful, I'm cooking.
This girl...
So, you're not hiring him?
Of course not!
If I worked with a guy like that,
I'd catch his apathetic face.
Hey.
Don't burn it this time.
Yeah, yeah.
Easy!
Alright, has everyone gathered?
Good morning.
- Morning!
- Sorry I'm late. There was an accident...
I'd like to introduce
a very important person.
Charmed already?
Oh, how embarrassing!
While he may not be an expert in baseball,
he has led many other athletes to victory.
Please welcome our new GM, Jun Sakurazaki.
Hello, everyone.
I am Jun Sakurazaki, the new GM.
I look forward to working with you all.
Welcome, GM!
Our new GM! He's so cool!
Why did you choose him?
He has many victories under his belt.
He's an exceptional man, I'd say.
But that person...
Are you dissatisfied with my decision?
No, it's not that. It's just, he...
He has no team spirit.
He's a necessary asset for the Dreams.
Right?
Yes, sir.
Ouch!
Practicing already?
It's like you want to make a fortune.
Hey, the feeling's mutual, isn't it?
You're the only pitcher who throws
right after the season, Kijima.
I'm challenging myself
to a new breaking ball.
At this age, no less.
You're so ambitious.
Then I'll hit even better,
and make you the winning pitcher, Kijima.
Really now.
I'll keep my expectations low.
Come on in.
Good afternoon, sir.
What do you want?
As an old-timer,
I know everything about our players.
I believe I can help reassess our strengths.
Is that so?
Please give me a moment.
Shohei's batting speed has increased.
We can expect great things next year.
Also, Rui is essential.
He can't hit much, but he's fast.
His defense is improving, too.
I think he'll become a great player.
Let's see, who else...
How about the pitcher, Kijima?
Kijima, huh...
What is it?
Honestly, I don't expect much from him.
His performance is declining,
and our younger guys find him hard to handle.
He's too harsh on them.
I see.
Thank you.
I have a plan of action now.
That's good.
[Pitchers]
- What's with the "thumbs up"?
- Ow, ow, ow!
Can't you learn to be serious for once?
No matter what I do,
you just get mad at me.
The Prez has been irritable lately.
Oh? How so?
You just proved your own point.
Hear ye, hear ye, Ms. President.
Here he comes!
Coming through.
- Now watch me, Ms. President.
- He's here.
Smile!
See? Let's go with a smile!
Lift those corners and smile!
- Yes, perfect!
- Enough with your fake smile, Kikuchi.
We need none of it.
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Ow, ow, ow.
- Mr. Kikuchi!
- I took that with my face.
- Where did Mr. Kikuchi go?
- I'm here.
Huh? I am, aren't I?
- I'm no ghost, right?
- Are you okay?
- You can feel me, right?
- You're being dramatic!
- Ow.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
- Morning.
I will inform you all of some decisions.
If anyone has any objections,
please don't hesitate to speak up.
First.
The manager will remain.
- What?
- No, but...
President Negishi has given his approval.
Mr. Nishida's contract
will be renewed three more years.
- Three years?
- That's long.
It's difficult to win and develop players
with a one-year contract.
Did Mr. Negishi really agree to this?
Yes.
If Mr. Nishida respects the authority he has,
he will become a good manager.
Any objections?
- Well...
- It seems there are none.
Then my second plan of action.
Though our coaches dispute with one another,
all of them will remain.
I object!
That's ridiculous!
You're the one who criticized our infighting.
I don't mind them clashing.
However, I'll have them compete
over their own stats.
Now, now...
Lastly, my third course of action.
Something even President Negishi
initially opposed of.
Kudo will be...
traded away.
Huh?
Now hold on. He's our star player!
I object to everything.
What are you thinking?
Kudo is our cleanup hitter.
Kudo will be traded.
He's an indispensable asset.
- I don't understand.
- GM.
Did Mr. Negishi really agree to that?
He would never.
- He did.
- No!
I have nothing but objections.
In that case...
Do you have an alternative plan?
No, but I still object!
Your objection is denied.
Say what?
Woah, woah, woah!
This isn't a fistfight.
Let's use our words.
Ow!
[The GM's talking about trading you away.]
Kudo, what are your predictions
for strategies seen in the Climax Series?
Great question.
It's a short series,
so teams will use their best pitchers a lot.
I think batters will have
an especially tough time.
I see.
We'll continue with Kudo's predictions
after the commercial break.
- We're in commercials.
- Copy that.
[The GM's talking about trading you away.]
Don't mess with me!
Five seconds. Four, three.
The professional baseball Climax Series
is about to begin.
We're getting predictions
from the Dreams' Kudo and...
I was able to keep batting
because I was with the Dreams.
I can't imagine playing for another team.
Tatsuya Kudo is a slugger for Samurai Japan.
Yes. I know.
It's not about knowing.
I'm trading him.
My dream is to have my number
retired by the Dreams.
Why are you persisting, President Makita?
I can act without your permission, no?
Yes, however...
Are you speaking out
because you think I'm a baseball amateur?
Honestly, yes.
I want to retire with the Dreams.
This trade will happen.
Definitely.
GM Ishikura.
You're jumping the gun.
I mean, talking about trades
before the Japan Series?
The regular season has ended.
Negotiations are fair game.
Now hold on there.
This season's last game just ended.
Let us rest a little!
Listen.
We'll talk trades, later.
Even if I were to trade...
Kudo, our cleanup hitter?
Kudo?
Is that so?
Does he really draw that much resentment?
Yes, a maelstrom of resentment is raging.
He's doing exactly as I expected.
Hey!
Kudo.
Here.
Catch it properly next time.
Hey!
The Dreams are my home.
I've dedicated 11 years of my life
to this team.
And now some baseball amateur
is trying to kick me out.
Hey!
See?
You'd better catch it.
Hey!
Aw, man.
Poor girl.
Hey!
Pick it up.
It's for the repairs.
Good work.
What happened here?
It was Kudo.
Huh?
Erm, the police...
We can't turn over a player
who brings in money.
But...
For the sake of the team,
I will sell him for a high price.
But are you really trading Kudo?
He's our star player.
We don't need a rotten star.
We've been together for so long.
I can't believe he's like that.
Attachments and the likes
are unnecessary to win.
Our staff are no exception to this rule.
Huh? What do you mean?
I mean nothing more than just that.
This is pointless.
Seems I'm being traded away.
Huh? With who?
A Vikings player.
What?
The new GM seems determined to get rid of me.
What's he thinking?
Here's your travel expense.
No, it's fine.
I insist.
No, really.
Please, it's on me.
Look forward to the article.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Prez.
I need to talk to you.
What? So formal.
Are you and the GM close?
What do you mean?
Like, are you two an item?
- Are you an idiot?
- Ow! It hurts!
- Is that all you ever think about?
- Ow, ow...
Ow! Please stop.
Huh? What now?
- I'll keep going until you get it.
- W-Wait, let me explain myself!
Rumors say you two left the office together.
- Says the gossip who spread them.
- Ouch!
Ow! That actually hurts.
- Are you sorry?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Ow!
- You clearly aren't.
Ow, that hurts!
- Feel remorse!
- Yes, I understand.
You're not even listening anymore.
I'm just letting myself get hit!
Pause, pause, pause.
Huh?
What's wrong?
What? PC? A virus?
A scoop! Look at the PC!
[Batter K from Dreams]
[Traded for a Vikings benchwarmer]
Huh? Seriously?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Yes, this is Miyahara.
[They're definitely talking about Kudo]
[Is the GM an amateur?]
Thank you for your cooperation.
- Dreams management, speaking.
- Thank you.
[Under that amateur Sakurazaki,
it's really the end for Dreams]
[Dreams isn't Dreams without Kudo!]
[This Sakurazaki should just quit]
[Critics say "The new GM ought to quit"]
[Voices of betrayal over Dreams trade]
[President of Baseball Operations]
No, there's no such trade discussion.
The article is a hoax.
You're persistent!
Why don't they believe us?
I've had it.
I'm going.
Where to?
To the GM.
Then I'm coming too.
I have a thing or two I want to say myself.
- Then let's all go!
- Yeah, let's go!
Huh? Wait a minute, please.
Well, maybe I'll go too.
Huh? Where's everyone going?
To the GM. We're going to tell him
we're against the trade.
Without me?
Yes. Because you two are, you know...
I stood up to him. Did you forget?
No, ma'am.
I remember your knuckle sandwich
clear as day.
Ow! My eyeball!
We have something to discuss.
Ah, GM.
What is it?
Why are you letting Kudo go?
Are you rallying on his orders?
No.
Then meet me in the meeting space in an hour.
Excuse me.
Yikes. I can practically
taste the bloodlust in here.
Can you blame us?
He's trading our star player for a nobody.
Let's calm down.
It's like you're itching for a throw down.
How so?
There! That knuckle!
Alright then, let's begin.
[Reasons for Letting Kudo Go]
First, he's weak in clutch situations.
Kudo can't hit in clutch situations.
What? No, no, no.
Whose Kudo are you talking about?
What do you know about our Kudo?
Right?
I could laugh at how absurd that sounds.
Looking at his batting average
and home runs,
he seems like a valuable player.
His batting average with runners
in scoring position is a .307.
I don't think he's weak
in clutch situations.
Exactly.
- Don't just sit there.
- Ow!
That's right! What they said!
Kudo has made five game-winning hits.
He's only third on the team.
Despite a .330 batting average,
he has too few game-winning hits.
He can't deliver results in crucial moments.
He's a weak hitter in clutch situations.
Talk back to him!
Huh? Me?
He's not weak in clutch situations!
You see... I'm Kudo's...
Cheerleader!
Oh, God, Buddha, Kudo!
Hit it out of the park!
We don't need reassurance from a cheerleader.
Say something sensible.
Right?
R-Right.
Just calm down for a moment.
- He has his good points...
- Let's hear him out first.
- Sit down, sit down.
- Yes, sir.
Second, his big plays
are relatively low-impact.
Kudo is weak in the heat.
He performs poorly in the summer,
especially at outdoor stadiums.
Summer is a crucial period
for determining standings.
Yet he can't produce results
during these crucial times.
What's the point in hitting home runs
after last place has been determined?
He's really studied baseball.
Yes. And quite thoroughly too...
Prez, say something back!
Where's all that momentum you had?
Just be quiet.
Yes, ma'am.
Third, the new standard for baseballs.
As you all know, starting next season,
we'll be using a rebound foam ball
that doesn't fly as far.
The flight distance is said to drop
by 5 to 10 meters.
If that happens, Kudo's home runs...
will decrease by 16.
He would no longer be a long-ball hitter,
but a mid-range hitter.
In other words,
if the ball doesn't fly as far,
his utility becomes ambiguous.
Fourth, a generational change.
Kudo's career will be short.
But fortunately,
we have many promising players
who can replace him.
[#59 Kotaro Sakakibara]
[Batting average: 0.327 - Home runs: 9]
[#70 Koji Miyamoto]
[Batting average: 0.314 - Home runs: 16]
[#72 Kaito Tokoro]
[Batting average: 0.301 - Home runs: 8]
[#59 Junji Honda]
[Batting average 0.269 - Home runs: 8]
What do you all think?
And fifth.
This is the biggest reason.
[Reason 5: Throws the team in disarray]
Kudo is eroding the team.
Pitchers, gather 'round!
Yes, sir.
- Hurry up!
- Yes, sir.
What are you guys doing, huh?
You good-for-nothings!
Hey! Why'd you let them make a comeback?
Are you underestimating pros?
- Hey!
- Hey, Kudo!
Huh?
Baseball is a team sport!
Pitchers cover for batters
when they can't hit.
We each cover the other. That's how it works.
Keep it to yourself, you bastard!
Sawada pitched for Dreams
until two years ago.
Despite securing 15 wins for the team,
he had to leave the Dreams to protect Kudo.
Sawada didn't say a word
in his own defense, did he?
The reason Kudo clings to the Dreams
is not love.
It's because it's a team he can control.
Kudo is the star of the Dreams.
If the player with the most fans leaves,
tickets and merchandise won't sell.
That's absolutely right!
Go, Hiromi!
- Give it to him!
- Quiet!
Indeed, the presence of a star player
is important.
That is why I'll bring in a player
to replace him.
Huh? There's no one who can replace Kudo!
But there is.
And I believe you all know him well.
This infamous star player...
was forced off the team because of Kudo.
No way...
President Makita,
please have Sawada's uniform ready.
He's coming back?
To the Dreams?
The trade has already been finalized.
Wow! Seriously?
Sawada will be returning to the Dreams.
You know about WAR, yes?
[T/N: "Wins Above Replacement"]
Sawada is top of the league, at a 7.5.
Did the Vikings really let Sawada go?
Yes.
You're offering up Kudo?
But Sawada is a pitcher who represents Japan.
Sawada has a losing record
against the top-ranking Pelicans.
And Kudo's useless in the summer.
He only hits well in autumn.
Isn't a player who hits in autumn
necessary for a team who's always in second?
No, we need a player
who hits well on average.
His batting average
against the Pelicans is...
I know.
A .420 batting average.
As expected.
Moreover, he has great chemistry
with the Pelicans' home stadium.
No, that's...
Anyone against the trade?
Anyone?
Then I'm done here.
Sawada is coming back, huh?
This is going to be busy.
A miracle is happening.
Ow, ow, ow! Hey, that hurts!
Wait, don't tell me.
I get hit even when things are going well?
Why can't it be one or the other?
Why?
Please clear out your locker.
Right now.
I paid for the repairs myself.
Don't get carried away.
It ought to go without saying,
but be polite over there.
I'm a homegrown star,
a candidate for a retired number.
You'll turn the fans against you.
Sawada is returning to pitch for the Dreams.
- Sawada?
- Yes.
He is more deserving of a retired number.
He has real accomplishments,
and is admired by everyone.
He's even a future manager candidate.
You.
Who do you think I am? Huh?
I can crush you anytime!
Next time, it won't just be your car!
Kudo...
Welcome back! We've been waiting!
Thank you!
Sawada is back with the Dreams!
Sawada, who has returned to the Dreams,
is welcomed with glee by the fans.
Great things are expected of him next season.
In 2024, Sawada was traded away...
- Yay!
- What now?
- Alright, alright!
- Huh? What?
Too close.
- Hey, Miyu.
- What, what, what?
Maybe if things go well,
the Dreams might not be last next year!
- Yay!
- I see.
Nothing's started yet, though.
I don't care. Praise me.
What brought on this strange attitude?
Huh? Did you work hard?
Yes, you're great, you're great! Amazing!
I'm home.
What are you doing?
Jun.
If there are any technical terms
you don't understand, just ask.
Don't look through my files
without permission.
Sorry.
[Rookies from 2020~2026]
Well, regarding this trade...
As a comrade, I couldn't help
but support your work.
The Dreams recorded 56 wins this year.
Before that, it was 59 wins.
Don't you think that's too many victories?
Why do you think I hired you?
Because you have a unique resume.
Win, disband.
Win, then disband.
Please follow your resume.
Alright?
Understood.
Good morning.
Everyone from the scouting department,
to my office in 5 minutes.
Yes, sir.
For the past few years,
the performance of our top draft picks
has been disappointing.
It's reasonable to assume
there are some questionable picks.
But many players don't succeed
even among first-round picks.
President Makita is right, you know.
There might be a scout committing fraud.
What?
Now wait a second.
Where's the evidence?
In one hour,
we'll have a meeting for the draft.