- We're seeing big changes in the Dreams,
- Yes.
thanks to their new GM, Sakurazaki.
Yes. Not only did they trade for Sawada,
but they surprised us all with Lim Min Jong.
Sakurazaki is truly proving his worth.
The Dreams may very well qualify
for the Climax Series this year.
- I see.
- I'm home.
However, others suspect
their team's offense has taken a hit
after trading away their best hitter.
- The hole left by Kudo is a large one.
- Right.
But the Dreams have plenty of young athletes.
- I'm home.
- They'll find someone.
Welcome back.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet. Thanks.
Sure.
What?
Jun?
Your accountant exam is next week, right?
Oh...
Yeah.
You feel ready for it?
I guess.
Study hard.
Don't overdo it.
I'm getting mixed messages.
Great work, you all.
Thank you, sir.
- If you'll excuse us.
- Sure.
Isami.
Sir.
I scroll tirelessly every day
to check on my company's reputation.
So what's going on here?
Explain it to me!
Sir.
This would be...
The Dreams!
They're making headlines!
We can't have that happen. Absolutely not!
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
This team rakes in no money.
So what's with all the attention? Huh?
The GM may be acting out now,
but our plan remains unchanged.
All will go as you wish, sir.
So we can crush them?
We can disband the team?
I am working towards that goal.
But sir, the dissolution of a team
is unprecedented in Japanese baseball.
Unprecedented?
I've spent my whole life
doing the unprecedented.
That is why I'm a success.
That is why Yaoshima exists. Am I wrong?
No, sir.
You're a capable man, aren't you?
Well? Aren't you?
Yes, sir.
Of course you are.
We're a family.
A family, I say!
You know what that means, right?
But of course.
- Mr. Mitsuo, it's time.
- What?
It's almost time!
- For what?
- For your dinner, sir!
Oh, you.
Maybe they'll find themselves victorious.
They are dreamers, after all.
Oh?
What's with that face?
Oh, right.
Pops was singing praises about you.
He said you turned out better
than your failure of a father.
Don't be so angry.
Nothing good comes out of arguing with me.
We're cousins. Let's get along, yeah?
I'm going to be
the face of this group someday.
In other words,
you'll become my right
or my left arm, at best.
Let's go out to eat sometime.
I'll treat you.
See you later.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
GM!
I had the weekly "Baseball Continent"
cover our draft and trade extensively.
- Did you give it a watch?
- Yes.
That program's an influential one.
Baseball fans flock towards their coverage.
Not to mention
their cohost is an absolute cutie.
That's why you favor that program?
I'm disillusioned.
What? It's just my opinion!
Don't worry.
You two are cuties, too.
- Creep.
What? Surely that was the right thing to say.
Right?
- Creep!
- Boom chika wow wow!
- Alright, I get it.
- Creeps.
- Yeah!
How are we tackling
the articles criticizing Lim?
Pardon?
Signing on to a Japanese team
instead of a Korean one
seems to have caused a bit of backlash.
Min Jong is still young.
I'm worried the criticism
will cause him mental strain.
[A traitor who sold his soul to Japan]
This is terrible.
We'll deal with it immediately.
Thank you.
The data needed
for annual salary negotiations
will be ready within the week, Ms. President.
Thank you.
Another year, another difficult negotiation.
Why is that?
Management believes
the players are money sinks.
They get stingy when discussing salaries.
This is going to be tough.
Even so, we manage to reach
an agreement every year.
GM!
Worry not, we've got this.
You could stand to worry more.
Ouch! Whoa!
- Aw, my perfect hairdo...
- What hairdo?
GM, I have bad news to add.
Our data analyst, Mikami,
has decided to resign.
What? He was one of our best.
He's taking over his parents' tangerine farm.
Gosh, they all quit so soon.
Aren't you being too hard
on your subordinates?
I'm totally fine.
My boss is a bit punchy, but I'll manage.
You're asking for another hit.
No, no, I'm good. I'm good.
I'll look for a former pro
who can replace Mikami.
How about we do an open recruitment instead?
Open recruitment?
The job primarily deals with numbers.
We should expand past former pros,
and consider hiring statisticians as well.
Have you heard of "Banzai Baseball"?
It's a blog run by an ordinary fan,
who posts about highly analytical topics.
If you're not a former player,
then you can't fully understand the stats.
We haven't even implemented Sabermetrics.
[T/N: the empirical analysis of baseball]
There's no harm in speaking
to an analytical expert.
I can't work with people
who don't know baseball.
Knowledgeable or not,
there are capable individuals out there.
I, too, have no experience with baseball.
He said it himself.
He's throwing himself under the bus.
What an inspirational act of self sacrifice.
I've never been more moved in my life.
Anyone agree?
He sure is the Prince of Nonchalance, huh?
Not all big league coaches
used to be players.
Even the Pelicans have a statistician
lead their data analytics team.
In baseball,
only those with experience
can give an accurate analysis.
Why has every day felt so prickly lately?
Let's advocate for peace.
Do you know why I start my mornings
at the batting range?
No.
It's so the players don't underestimate me.
They are all confident in their abilities.
No matter how correct the analysis is,
they will not listen to the advice
of an inexperienced person.
Experienced or not,
players will listen,
if they're thoroughly convinced.
But these athletes know only of baseball.
Correct the wrongs of your players
before focusing on your own body.
We'll invite both specialists
and former professionals alike to apply.
Yes, sir.
That's all for now.
Let's start our morning assembly.
First on the docket.
Miyahara, our analytics team got back to us.
Yes?
You call on Miyahara often these days.
Certainly not by choice.
You used to get on his case
for getting in with connections.
Where did that anger go, I wonder?
[FY2023 New Hire Interview Room]
Miyahara's up next, huh?
The youngest son from the Aiba Corporation?
Yeah.
I owe a lot to his father.
Likewise.
Excuse me.
Mr. Miyahara.
Mr. Miyahara!
Woah! You startled me.
It's your turn. Please stand.
Hello.
- Huh?
- Hurry up!
- Yes...
- You're making everyone wait.
Huh? What year is it?
Itsuki Miyahara?
Yes, sir!
First, let's hear a bit more about you.
Just know I'll do anything!
I'll work super, duper hard!
I'm ready to put my whole back into it!
It's nice to see you're so energetic.
Motivation and energy
are all I got going for me.
Ask, and I, Itsuki Miyahara, will do it.
Motivation plus energy, equals Miyahara.
I love the Dreams! Go team!
You're a real shining applicant, kid!
Thank you very much.
I also like the hairdo.
You noticed? Thank you!
Ow, ouch!
Ouch, ouch!
Ma'am, what the--
Ow!
Do you want to die?
Wait a minute. What did I do?
Do you understand how everyone else feels
about this interview?
Please, wait. What are you...
An earnest worker is going
to get rejected because of you.
You've got connections.
If you pass, don't bother coming in.
I'll beat the living daylights out of you.
What is with that lady?
Miyahara has returned.
- Welcome back.
- Thanks!
Hey there, connections hire.
What's all this about?
Why did you answer?
I thought you "had no connections".
Oops! Ouch!
Please forgive me.
Sorry, sorry.
But you were rejected,
even with your connections.
Why's that?
I wasn't rejected. I withdrew.
I decided not to rely on connections.
The following year, I passed all on my own.
Boom chika wow wow!
- Surprised?
- Really? I had no idea.
Yup.
Because if I got in through connections,
a certain someone promised she'd beat me up.
Good going, Miyahara!
Woah, hey!
- You rich idiot!
- Hey!
That's what you think of me?
I mean, you're not entirely wrong, but...
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Morning, sir.
Have we received applications
for our data analyst position?
Yes, about ten.
Great. Then we'll hold interviews tomorrow.
What? All ten of them, tomorrow?
Why not?
There are preparations to make, and...
GM?
The least you could do is listen to me!
And he's gone.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
It's tomorrow, right? Your accountant's exam.
Yeah.
I'm going to bed. Good night.
Good night.
Jun.
What's up?
I wanted to talk about baseball.
Has it been fun?
Yeah, it's fun.
And I like playing, but...
Maybe all the practice is making me unsure.
I know I should like it.
But it's starting to wear on me.
Akito.
You can't be whining like that.
Concentrate on the goals in front of you.
You're right.
Do your best.
Okay.
We haven't even implemented Sabermetrics.
Have you heard of "Banzai Baseball"?
["Banzai Baseball", "Blog"]
[Banzai Baseball]
[Pitchers shouldn't play defense]
[Writer - Robinson]
Are you ready for the exam?
Yeah.
There's always the next year.
Take it easy, alright?
Don't worry, I'll pass.
Then we'll use both our salaries
to move Mom closer to us.
Thanks for breakfast.
I'll be heading out first.
Take a taxi to the exam.
I'll call in the next applicant.
Go ahead.
It's kind of nerve-wracking,
having to choose people.
Leave your thoughts for later. Call them in.
Yes, ma'am!
Come on in.
You're currently studying sabermetrics?
Yes.
Then allow me to ask.
What is the numerical metric
used to evaluate a pitcher's ability?
A throw-to-strike ratio measured per inning.
And why is that?
In modern baseball,
it is crucial to strike a batter out
with the least amount of pitches possible.
So speed and type of pitch do not matter?
A pitcher can throw a fastball,
or a disappearing fork,
but it must be a strike.
A steady pitch that consistently strikes out
is far more appealing than anything flashy.
But a professional batter
will easily get used to one type of pitch.
Over the course of a long season,
are you sure that metric alone will work?
I do not know.
I see. Thank you.
Thank you, we'll be in touch.
Great work, team.
Prez, you really showed him your stuff.
You think?
What was the correct answer to that question?
There was no correct answer.
I was testing his analytical skills.
It was a trick question?
You studied up on analytics?
Yes. I referenced some books,
and "Banzai Baseball".
Come on in.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Oh.
Are you alright?
Yes, I'll handle it myself.
Oh, okay.
May I?
- Thank you.
- Okay, here I go.
Heave-ho.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
There we go.
Thank you.
Thank you for having me.
Then let us begin.
May I share some documents first?
I'll pass them out.
- Thank you.
- Sure thing.
Alright.
One for me.
One for you.
[Pitchers shouldn't play defense]
And you, sir.
[Heat changes the ball game]
No way.
Are you Robinson, of "Banzai Baseball"?
Author of "Pitchers shouldn't play defense",
and "AI Pitching Strategies"?
Yes.
What?
Wow!
You don't know him?
No.
He's a very famous writer.
- Right?
- Yes.
I'm Akito Sakurazaki.
Today, I've brought you all summaries
of articles I wrote regarding asset analysis.
This is quite the stack.
Your method of tracking a player's records
is also considered a type of sabermetrics.
It's simply a different interpretation of it.
In baseball,
many elements are not reflected in data.
For example, a player in a slump
could be suffering from heartbreak,
or a family issue.
Can these factors be quantified?
Baseball is the easiest sport
to numerically quantify.
Basketball and soccer heavily rely on a team.
But strikeouts and hits
are both done by a single player.
Not implementing sabermetrics,
is like a doctor telling you
he's not interested in your health.
Sabermetrics is not
an official academic discipline.
Yet if we do not propagate this study,
it will greatly affect
the future of baseball.
Jun.
If I quit baseball,
will you teach me to study?
You're not cut out for studying.
Keep playing baseball.
I have to get back to work.
I have a game today.
Then do your best.
My pelvis has been hurting since yesterday.
If you're afraid of pain, you'll slow down.
Focus on what's in front, and run.
Focus.
Don't be afraid of pain. Do your best.
The results will follow.
I'll call back after the match. Good luck.
The Titans, who are currently undefeated,
have not yet implemented sabermetrics.
That's a common misconception.
Their analytic work
is outsourced to a sabermetrics expert.
What? Seriously?
Titans' analysts wish to remain contractors
because they are paid more this way.
I get that you're good with numbers.
But you have no experience on the field.
Will you be able to survive on the team?
I have experience playing baseball.
Sandlot baseball?
No, Koshien.
If a more proficient
sabermetrics expert has applied,
I suggest hiring them,
even if they're a baseball amateur.
He's so reliable.
Wow, I can practically taste victory already!
Sabermetrics alone won't change the rankings.
However, incorporating statistical analysis
will expand this team's possibilities.
What do you think of the sacrifice bunt?
You're asking so many questions, Mr. Inamura.
According to sabermetrics,
the sacrifice bunt is considered irrational,
yet it is still used in the Japanese league.
What are your thoughts on this?
An out reduces the chance for scoring.
If victory is the priority,
a sacrifice bunt is clearly ineffective.
However, data analysis is like cooking.
Data is like an ingredient.
It's up to the analyst to use
those ingredients in a meaningful manner.
Teams may have a need for bunts,
depending on their strengths or weaknesses.
I can't rule them out entirely.
What would you do?
I've heard that
the Dreams are aiming to win the series.
In that case,
I would forgo sacrifice bunts entirely
to further improve our chances at victory.
Any other questions?
No, none.
GM?
How many centimeters was that?
When you entered this room,
which you could not even overcome alone?
It's about 5 centimeters tall.
Your work will be more difficult
than overcoming a 5 centimeter hump.
GM!
I'm simply telling him the truth.
I like Jackie Robinson.
Hence my pen name online.
The referees were always making decisions
against Jackie Robinson.
There were a lot of dead balls.
Because he was African-American.
But he never gave in
to that sort of adversity.
I won't either.
- Can I ask you one more question?
- What caused your injury?
The cause was...
Don't be afraid of pain. Do your best.
Focus on what's in front, and run.
Concentrate on the goals in front of you.
Time out! Are you okay?
Stretcher!
I was injured during a match.
An analyst watches tons of game footage.
You'll be reminded of your past
every time you watch a match.
Can you bear those painful memories?
I'll be fine.
Will your family allow you to work here?
I wouldn't know.
But I'm okay.
Because I love baseball.
Akito Sakurazaki is my younger brother.
I thought so!
The same surname tipped me off.
You have a spectacular brother.
Please make your choice objectively.
I will not be choosing him.
Huh? Why?
Do you make subjective judgements, GM?
My brother knows I will turn him down.
You didn't have to be so harsh on him.
Yeah, GM.
If it were me, I'd be left crushed.
No one asked for your opinion.
Ouch!
Ouch! Twice?
Fine. Let us make the decision ourselves.
Huh? Are we allowed to decide without the GM?
We'll have to.
I don't get it.
I don't get that GM.
I just don't get him.
Something's up.
I know something's up. I know it.
Something's fishy here.
No, no. It's all too fishy.
Risa.
I get that you want me to ask what's up.
But in that case,
I'd rather you be direct about it.
Then ask me.
Risa.
This GM has made you all... strange.
Exactly, our GM is acting strange.
Are we on the same page here?
He lost his usual cool demeanor.
Is working with your sibling really so bad?
Obviously.
Why? Why? Why?
Too close.
See? If you're too close,
you'll lose sight of your surroundings.
Who cares? I like being close.
Really now.
I wonder what reasons he could have?
Well, for one, it'd get noisy.
You'd also cling to me.
Not to mention your potty-mouth...
- Who are you talking about?
- Huh?
- The GM?
- Who?
Huh?
[Akito Sakurazaki]
[The end to a promising baseball star]
[Injured while running to base]
[Ignoring the pain led to severe injury]
[Tragedy of a promising player]
[Made it all the way to the baseball Koshien]
GM!
After thoroughly investigating our building,
I found eight doors with a threshold
of two centimeters or less.
Totally wheelchair accessible.
We will also install ramps where necessary.
It'd be cheaper
than replacing the doors themselves.
That is none of my business.
Excuse me?
I'm coming in.
- What are you doing?
- I'm not done yet.
Your brother was a star player.
It's all in the past now.
Have you read this?
[Utilizing Sabermetrics - Akito Sakurazaki]
Do you really understand?
I do not feel comfortable
discussing my family with you.
I'm here to talk about potential hires.
Please take a good look at these documents.
[Utilizing Sabermetrics - Akito Sakurazaki]
I believe he overcame the pain,
and found his passion for baseball.
That passion, brought him to us.
Please get out.
I understand your concerns.
But, GM, why won't you recognize his efforts?
This has nothing to do with the Dreams.
I won't hire him because of mere connections.
And we won't choose him
because you two are family.
We will judge him
for his own brilliant abilities,
and the results of his accumulated efforts.
Even if there are doubts,
we've already hired a reliable...
a stupidly honest rich kid working for us.
In any case, please see him for who he is.
Good night.
[New waves brought on by Dreams' Sakurazaki]
[Though he has no baseball experience...]
Welcome back.
How long have you been writing?
A long time now.
You've been lying to me?
I never meant to hide it from you.
I just like baseball.
I wanted to make your life easier.
When I played, it caused me nothing but pain.
But now...
I truly love baseball.
I really do.
I was going to tell you I moved on.
Then why didn't you?
You hated the sport.
How could I tell you I loved it?
That's because...
Because baseball made you...
No.
Deep down, you blame yourself, don't you?
But that happened years ago.
How could a GM not show his brother
a single match of baseball?
That's just strange.
If you hate the sport so much,
why work for a baseball team?
Then who will put food on the table?
I'd do anything for my family.
Stop it.
You keep everything to yourself.
Blame everything on yourself.
Can't you let go?
The one who hasn't moved on...
is you, Jun.
How long are you going to act
like the sacrificial victim?
I'm sick of it!
Let's just be happy together.
Please.
You have to move on.
You don't have to hire me.
Let's enjoy our lives.
But I did this.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Please stop blaming yourself.
Do you know why he is bruised all over?
No.
He was likely punished
over a long period of time.
His ankles were also very swollen.
I can't believe he ran
until his legs gave out.
Why did you simply leave him be?
[Banzai Baseball]
I knew you'd check it out.
Oh, well...
What do you mean, you knew?
I'm simply looking for talented people.
I know.
What are you smirking about?
Oh, nothing.
So, who are we picking?
Great question.
Come on in.
Excuse me.
What's up?
I needed someone else
to bad-mouth him to.
I see.
I certainly know that stubborn fella well.
Which one do you want?
I'll have this one.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I guess I'm still being swung around by him.
Not that I entirely mind, though.
Sawako, were you and my brother
not honest enough with each other?
You don't have to worry about us anymore.
Though I'm able to be a stranger,
it's different between siblings, isn't it?
I told him everything.
For my own sake.
That's for the better.
You and I both need to become happy.
Otherwise, he'll be disheartened forever.
The two of us have been through a lot.
But let's laugh. Good fortune
comes to those who laugh, right?
Right.
One moment.
Hello?
Good afternoon.
This is Risa Makita, from the Dreams.
Hello there.
Akito Sakurazaki.
You are hired.
What? Really?
Thank you!
Congratulations.
When can you start working?
Anytime!
Then I'll see you at the office tomorrow.
Thank you!
Have a good day!
Was that...
Yeah!
Yes!
Congrats! Good fortune did come!
Stubborn as he may be, that guy...
He never betrays anyone.
Yeah.
[General Manager]
[Utilizing Sabermetrics - Akito Sakurazaki]
Due to a change in assessment criteria,
we are joined by the coaches this year
for our annual salary negotiations.
Sakurazaki will take the floor from here.
Yes, sir.
- Huh?
- Sakurazaki?
But...
He's our newcomer.
He's the younger brother of the GM.
Yes.
I'm Akito Sakurazaki.
It's nice to meet you all.
The Dreams have negotiated annual salaries
on the basis of a seniority system,
which gave more to older players,
regardless of their skill.
As a result,
skilled athletes were earning less,
and promising young players
have had to be let go.
See? He's got you there, Inamura.
I won't deny it.
We do treat our older players favorably.
They are the face of our team.
The veterans keep our dugout unified.
Do you get what that means?
He's never played baseball. I doubt he would.
- Sirs.
Look to the future, not the past.
He is a good analyst.
Let's hear it.
Continue.
Yes, sir.
Therefore, in order to avoid
losing any more players,
we will change our evaluation metrics.
Specifically,
we will be referring to WAR,
and Clubhouse Values.
WAR is about quantifying
how much a player contributes to victory.
On the other hand,
Clubhouse Values refers to traits
that are harder to quantify,
like team cohesion, and leadership skills.
Implementing this new metric
will allow us to fairly evaluate
both younger players, and veterans alike.
The salaries of our veterans
will certainly decrease.
However, if we implement this system,
we can renew our contracts
with every player this year.
Negotiating with the veterans
will prove somewhat difficult.
As such, Miyahara and I will handle those.
Yes! We'll have them agreeing in no time.
I'm absolutely raring to go!
He may not be reliable,
but he can handle negotiations.
No, I'm ready. I've got this.
Will you be able to convince our veterans?
I will!
Yes, we will.
Our veterans love the team.
Keep all their teammates signed on,
and they should consider the pay cut.
Is that what you're getting at?
Yes, sir.
You're unexpectedly shrewd, aren't you?
I have no objections.
Then we will begin negotiations
using this new evaluation system.
- Alright.
- Thank you again.
Thank you.
Yes!
So? We can disband the team?
Sir, the dissolution of a team
is unprecedented in Japanese baseball.
Unprecedented?
I've spent my whole life
doing the unprecedented.
That is why I'm a success.
That is why Yaoshima exists. Am I wrong?
What do you think is the best way
to accomplish something unprecedented?
I am not qualified to answer, sir.
I will offer a famous saying instead.
"Rome wasn't built in a day".
To accomplish an unprecedented feat,
you must take it one step at a time.
Tell him to come to my office.
Come in.
Excuse me.
How much was the team offered
to divide amongst their players last year?
2.902 billion yen, sir.
Do you think that's too little?
Yes. Quite so.
Goodness, what a shame.
The team is in for a budget cut.
Romanée-Contini.
You're no wine expert, are you?
Not at all.
A wine lover will be joining us.
Who?
Wait, and you'll find out.
What's this?
It's your assigned annual salary.
What?
How...
I stole the data.
Obviously, I stole it.
That's definitely not allowed.
Whoever wants the data, lookie here!
Ouch...
I'll pass.
If you'll excuse me.
Hey, hey.
Listen to what I've got to say.
Don't be so on edge.
Come, sit.
Just give him five minutes, please.
Sir.
The thing is, I started an agency of my own.
You can leave the salary negotiating to me.
Sir.
I'm a young player.
You won't make a buck off me.
Treat me to a drink, and we'll call it even.
You younger guys are paid too little.
Number 31, Yuto Nara.
Mr. Kurokawa's giving you an opportunity.
You really ought to take it.
Kato, Shirasaki, and Nojima
all signed with me.
That's this season's whole starting line-up.
Don't take the deal, and it's your loss.
I know these Dreams contracts
like the back of my hand.
Nara, join the group.
Are you surprised?
That's not like you.
Is a 30% cut really all that difficult?
It's impossible.
Still...
Negotiating with the players
is one of your jobs.
Right?
We'll take a 10% cut.
30%.
Then 15%.
Are you haggling with me?
You're the one driving us for a bargain, sir.
Please explain to me
why a budget cut is necessary.
Fine, explain I shall.
The reason is simple.
This team sucks at baseball!
They're so bad, it's a waste of money!
Every year, they're last.
Every year, they're in the red!
Need I convince you any further?
We're signing players on
at their lowest salary already.
I cannot accept a 30% cut to our budget.
Well, well. It seems you weren't listening.
I am not speaking my mind here.
I am giving you an order, as the team owner.