What is this?
Where are we going?
- We'll bike around!
- Slow down, slow down!
Jade, will you be
my best friend again?
Hmm... Yes.
- You can't take that back.
- [CHUCKLES]
Whether in danger or not,
no one's leaving
this friendship.
No one leaves.
You want to make it
up to me, right?
I have three wishes.
Okay, sir. Three wishes?
What are they, sir?
I'll think about it.
I hope that before I leave...
our families could reconcile.
I think it's time to bring back
the annual Hotel 88
team building!
- Team building! Team building.
- Sari.
Hey, guys.
Edward.
Thank you for
accommodating us.
No problem, Luna.
How can I say no to you?
Besides, my staff didn't
have a hard time.
Because the coordination on
your end has been excellent.
It was me, sir.
I handled the coordination.
I did a great job, didn't I?
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Oh, you can put
your bags inside.
Come on.
- Wow!
- This is it!
- Did you bring any bags?
- No.
Jade.
- Uh, let me carry that.
- Oh.
- No need. I can manage.
- I've got it.
- I can carry it myself.
- It's okay.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Sure.
[CHESKA]
Aren't you going to help me?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You should be thankful
that you're my brother.
I'm letting you prioritize
your love life.
Psst! Keep your voice down.
Someone might hear you.
I'm just being supportive,
okay?
- Whatever.
- Hey, wait up!
You can do it yourself.
We've owned this
for a long time.
- So, you're welcome here.
- Jade, do you need help?
No, I'm good. I've got it.
- [JADE] Thank you.
- [KIKO] Okay.
[CHESKA] Wait a minute.
Hey! Ouch!
Why are you blocking the way?
Who are you anyway?
You know, I've seen you
at the hotel. Do you work there?
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- I'm Cheska, Kiko's sister.
So, why are you here?
Well, the same goes
for Trixie, right?
She's just Martin's sister,
but she's also here.
Besides, I volunteered
for the team building. Okay?
Tsk.
Give me that.
Stop blocking the way.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
For a moment, I thought he
sincerely wanted to help me.
Thank you!
Martin.
What is it, Luna?
Leon just messaged me
saying he couldn't make it.
He has something
important to do
straight from the airport.
- Okay.
- [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on in. The staff will
take care of your bags.
So you can get changed.
- Oh.
- Thank you.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
What important thing
does Leon have to do?
He didn't tell me.
He just said
he'd go to the site
to do something important.
Come on.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, everybody,
I would like you to meet
our facilitator, Art.
Hello, everyone!
I think it's a perfect day
today to work
on our teams, yeah?
Alright, short intro.
My name is Art.
I've been a facilitator
for many years,
and Trixie has mentioned to me
the background of the hotel.
I've curated today
all the activities
so that each one can learn
from each other.
To build a
stronger communication,
foster better collaboration,
and most importantly,
the most crucial part,
to have fun.
[ART] Right?
- Yeah!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Whoo!
[APPLAUSE]
- Let's go!
- Let's go, guys!
Let's go.
["SALUHAN" BY 1621 PLAYING]
[ART] We will divide you
into two teams.
Team A is Trixie,
Gio,  Luna, Martin,
Sari, and Monette.
And Team B is Cheska,
Justin, Edward, Kiko,
Jade, and Raphie.
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is treasure hunting.
You need clues
to find the location
of prized possessions,
which are puzzle pieces.
Remember:
your clues are intertwined,
like a single motion
of the world.
One is rooted
in the earth,
one flows
with the wind,
and one moves
between the two.
Three clues.
And in order
to find them,
you have to prove
that you can follow
the pace of the game.
It's not just about power,
but about strategy.
[SHOUTS] Are you ready?
- Ready!
- Yes, sir!
[ART] Are you ready?
- Yeah!
- Yes!
Three, two, one...
Go!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
["SALUHAN" CONTINUES]
- [SARI] Let's go, team!
- [MARTIN] Go, go, go!
- [MONETTE] Yeah!
- Sir, sir!
Let's pick this one, sir!
Let's go!
Monette, join me here.
Oh no, sorry.
I'm riding solo.
- [SIGHS]
- [GIGGLES]
[MONETTE] So fun.
I have this all by myself.
- [TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
Come on!
- Seat belt.
- Okay.
Hey, let's get going!
[TENDER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Gio, hurry up!
[ENGINE TURNS ON, RUMBLING]
[TRIXIE] Alright, guys!
Are you ready?
[SQUEALS] Yes!
- [MONETTE] Yeah!
- Ready?
- Yes!
- Ready! Ready!
- [MARTIN] Let's go.
- Ready, sir?
- [TRIXIE] Ready...
Alright!
Get ready...
Get set...
Go!
[ENGINE ROARING]
[SHRIEKS] Ah!
Hey!
[ENGINE REVVING]
Wait! What's happening?!
This is sabotage!
[STAMMERING]
- [ENGINE TURNS ON, REVVING]
- [SCREAMING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
Sir, drive faster!
- Sari, wait! Just wait!
- Come on!
- We need to find the clue!
- Quiet! I'm focusing!
I'm focusing, Sari! Wait!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's so muddy!
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
[TIRES SKID]
- [RAPHIE] Go!
- Raphie, hurry up!
- Look! There it is!
- Come on!
It's our first activity.
Roll those Zorbs
while people are inside,
and then circle
the whole area.
Once you're done,
I'll reveal the clue.
[JADE]
Okay, okay! Game! Game!
So, who's going inside?
- [RAPHIE] I volunteer!
- Choose me!
Kiko, you should do it.
I'll handle the rolling.
Me, really?
You should get inside.
How about that?
We need a fast decision.
We're running out of time!
Choose now,
or we won't finish quickly!
I'll do it!
- No, I'll do it!
[JUSTIN] Wow, now you're racing
to volunteer? Decide already!
[JADE] Justin, I'll do it.
I'll be okay. Promise.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yes!
Trust me.
I'm Dad's brave girl.
I'll handle Jade's ball.
You focus on Raphie's.
- Well, shall we?
- Hurry up!
Make sure you roll them!
Be careful, Jade.
It's hot inside.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Go, hurry!
- Jade and I are ready! Guys?
- Raphie, climb in!
- Come on, come on!
- Ready?
- Go, go! Faster!
- Game!
- Games, games, game!
- Now!
- Go!
- Let's go! Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Justin, hurry up!
- You guys can do it!
- Aah!
This way!
- Keep going!
- Let's do it!
- I'm moving this way!
- Come on!
- Go!
- That's it!
- Sari, wait!
- We need to find the clue!
I'm focusing!
I'm focusing, Sari! Wait!
- Sir, hurry up!
- I know! I know!
- I know, Sari! I'm doing it!
- Sir, step on it!
[ENGINE ROARING]
The clues are waiting for us!
- Sir, sir, sir--
- Aah!
- [SARI SCREAMING]
- [CAR CRASHES]
- [BOTH GROANING]
- [LEAVES RUSTLING]
- Sari...
- Sir, are you okay?
- Ants! So many ants, Sari!
- Aah!
- They're everywhere!
- Sir, what's going on?!
Ants!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Damn it, too many ants!
[ENGINE ROARS]
Hey, hurry up!
We all need to be there
to get the clue!
[MARTIN] Wait!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Wait!
- [ENGINE REVS]
Focus.
Focus, Sari.
- I'll go here!
- There! There!
- There, that's it!
- Go!
Go around.
- You alright, Jade?
- Come on, come on!
- [GRUNTS]
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Wait. Wait a second.
W-Wait a second, Justin.
Be careful, Jade. Oh.
- Be careful!
- I've got it
- Hey!
- Justin... Justin...
- Jade!
I need a second.
- Be careful!
- Are you okay?
I can do it.
Wait, wait, wait.
- Jade?
- Oh, Justin...
Justin...
Wait, wait, wait.
- Justin.
- Jade?
Oh!
[IN DEEP VOICE]
Hi, miss.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
I feel dizzy.
Jade, are you sure
you're okay?
- Yeah.
- Hey!
Here's the clue!
- There it is.
- There's the clue!
- Finally!
- Hurry! Hurry!
Hey! Hurry up, guys!
- Sari, focus!
- Sari, focus on the game!
You guys go ahead, Monette!
[ENGINE REVS]
Focus on the game, Sari.
No, no, no, no, no.
Not yet.
Sari, focus.
Sari!
What are you looking at?
Hey!
Nothing, sir! Nothing!
Sir, sir, let's go!
Focus on the game.
Focus on the game!
Jade, are you sure
you're okay?
I'm okay, Justin.
Don't worry about me.
[EDWARD]
Jade, are you hurt?
I'm okay!
- What's the next clue?
- Read it.
“At the end of the soaked trail,
where each step sinks.”
Hmm?
- What?
- Is this a riddle?
I don't get it.
Is it a person?
"Where each step sinks."
Wait is it quicksand?!
Huh?
But there's no quicksand here.
"Soaked trail."
Hmm?
"Where each step sinks."
Mm!
- In the mud!
- [BOTH GASP]
- Mud cart!
We got it!
- Is that right?
- Yeah!
- Come on! Come on!
- Run!
- Raphie, wait for me!
- Come on!
[ENGINE REVS]
- Sir, hurry up!
- Sari, wait!
- Go!
- Ssh!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Aah!
Gio, drive faster!
Hold your horses.
Wait for me!
[MONETTE EXCLAIMS]
Monette is catching up
to us already!
Maybe I should be driving.
Why are you in such a rush?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WATER SPLASHES]
Gio!
Hey! Pull over!
I told you
I should've driven!
I can drive! Go ride
with Monette if you want!
Fine! Where is she?
I'll ride with her!
Go ahead! Go ahead!
I'll drive!
No, go with Monette!
What?!
Where is Monette?
[ENGINE REVS]
I said I could do it.
I should be driving.
You clearly can't handle it!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- I can!
Are you two fighting?
- Monette...
- I can hear you arguing.
- I'll ride with you.
- What's wrong?
What's the problem?
I'll ride with you.
But...
Come on, Monette.
Let's leave him.
Are you really going
to leave me here?
Come on, Monette!
[ENGINE REVS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS, EXCLAIMS]
Congratulations, guys!
[SARI CLAPS]
I'm fine.
- But I'm done with her.
- Go ahead, sir.
"Hidden in a skin of steel,
I hang above in silence.
Strike me with the guard's hand,
and I awaken."
So...
do we have to
guess what that is?
I guess.
"Hidden in a skin of steel..."
You have to hit it
to wake it up.
The clue is in the can!
Yeah, but where is it?
- Target shooting!
- Ooh!
- Oh!
They figured it out!
- Wow.
- Come on, let's go!
- Let's go, let's go!
[MARTIN] Gio, hurry up!
[RAPHIE] Come on, come on!
Edward, where is it?
Edward?
Lead the way!
- Come on!
- Hurry!
- Over here!
- Jade, are you okay?
I-I'm fine.
I think I just sprained my foot
when I fell on Raphie.
- Come on, hop on.
- What?
- I'll carry you.
- No, I'm okay, Kiko.
Don't be stubborn, Jade.
You're injured.
Just go.
I'm not leaving you here, okay?
Come on.
They've already left us.
- Let's go!
- Hey!
Hey, Edward.
What's wrong?
Oh man...
- Hey, what happened?
- I just sprained my foot,
- but I'm okay.
- Alright, let's go.
- Let's go! Come on!
- Come on!
Hey!
- [CAR ENGINES REVVING]
- [BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE] Justin, slow down!
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [JADE SCREAMS] Aah!
- [CAR CRASHES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[WHEELS GRINDING]
Justin!
You were going too fast!
Get out of the car.
Why?
So it's more light.
You ask so many questions.
[HUFFS] Okay.
[GRUNTS] Hold on. Ouch.
Justin, we might not able
to catch up.
Let's hurry. What happened?
Is it stuck?
Let's try pulling it.
[CAR APPROACHING]
Justin.
Do you need help?
What happened?
[JUSTIN] Let's push it.
- Come on.
- What happened?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
What's wrong?
Keep pushing.
- Ready.
- Three, two, one, go.
- [MEN GRUNTING]
- It's heavy.
I'll be on this side.
Move, move.
Hurry, hurry.
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
Out of the way!
[SCREAMING] Aah!
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [KIKO] Jade!
- [EDWARD] Jade!
Jade!
[RAPHIE]
Sorry! Sorry, Miss Jade!
- It's okay. I'm okay.
- Sorry, Miss Jade.
Justin. [GRUNTS]
Raphie, why are you going
so fast?
I was trying to catch up to you.
Miss Jade, are you okay?
I'm fine. Come on, let's go.
We need to find
the clue, let's go.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- I'm fine, let's go!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Yay!
- Yes!
You guys are awesome. Game!
- Go, go, go, hurry!
- Quick, quick!
[PAPER RUSTLES]
"I'm beneath a metal skin.
I'm up there,
peacefully hanging.
Hit the keeper to wake me up."
- Come on.
- [KIKO] Metal skin?
[JADE] What could that be?
- Up there?
- A can. It's a can.
That's right.
You're good at this, Raphie!
Oh, please. Don't mention it.
I think it's right there
at the target shooting.
- Wow.
- How did you know that?
You're really good
at this, Raphie.
He saw Martin go in there.
- [LAUGHS]
- What now?
- Let's just go. Hurry.
- Let's go!
Hurry up!
Hey, wait for me!
- Okay guys!
- G! G!
- This is your last stop.
- [LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
The mechanics are simple.
One of each member of the team
has to hit the bullseye.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Every member
should be able to try, okay?
- Okay, who goes first?
- I'll do it.
- Let's go, let's go!
- Let's go!
Go, go, go!
I'm going to finish this.
Go, Sir Edward!
["SALUHAN" BY 1621 PLAYING]
[YAWNS]
[ARROW THUDS]
Too bad.
- That's okay. [APPLAUDING]
- It's fine.
Fine, your turn.
Game, game.
Show him, bro. Show him.
[ARROW THUDS]
Too bad.
It really is.
- [EVERYONE CHEERING] Whoo!
- Go guys!
You can do this, sir!
I believe you can do it
in just one shot, sir.
[SARI] Oh my god, sir! I believe
so much in you, sir!
If you can't do it, just say so.
Don't be a show-off.
One try per member.
You want to go first? Try it.
No, thanks.
[SARI] Sir, you haven't hit it,
but I know you'll do great!
Sir, you can do it!
It's just in the palm
of your hands!
You can do it, sir!
Sir, this is for clues.
[CHEERING] Sir!
- You're so good, sir!
- Shh!
Sari, I need to concentrate.
- Go, Justin! [CLAPS]
- There you go!
Go, Justin! Come on, Justin!
You can do it!
- [ARROW THUDS]
- Wow!
That was close, Justin.
- Cheska, can you help me?
- Hold it like this.
[EDWARD] Go, you can do it.
Careful, Jade.
You can do it, Miss Jade!
You can do it.
[LAUGHS]
- Go, you can do it.
- Okay.
- Let's go, Jade!
- [ARROW THUDS]
[KIKO] That was close!
- That was close!
- [APPLAUDS]
Don't be embarrassed.
You'll hit it.
You know what, move to the side.
You might get hit.
- [ARROW THUDS]
- Aah! Sir!
Martin, that's awesome!
[ARROW THUDS]
- You're good!
- Let's go!
- Wow!
You're so good!
- I'm nervous!
- Go Raphie!
- Sister, you can do it.
- There's nothing to lose.
Just give it a try.
You can do it.
- I'm sorry in advance.
- That's your lucky color.
- [APPLAUDING]
- I'm nervous.
There we go.
- [ARROW THUDS]
- Whoa!
[CHEERING, SCREAMING]
Did you see that?!
Guys, congratulations!
- Yey!
Who's going to read this?
["SALUHAN" CONTINUES]
- [PANTING]
- We're almost there.
[PANTING]
[ART] Alright.
Valid effort.
Both groups actually
finished all the tasks.
- Yes! [CLAPPING]
- Whoo!
[ART] I just want to say
congratulations.
It is a tie for both teams!
- What?!
That can't be.
Why not, sir?
Both teams got clues.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
So, what's the treasure?
- You'll know--
- [RAPHIE] At the right time?
Sir, I've heard that line
before. Don't say it.
- [LAUGHING]
- Oh, Raphie...
[KIKO] I think
what Raphie meant is...
he's excited to find out
what we'll get later.
We will discuss further later
during the bonfire.
Oh. Then what will we do
in the meantime, sir?
Good question.
What will you do?
Enjoy! It's your free time!
Guys, spend the whole day
bonding together,
especially with the people
you haven't teamed up yet.
Like they say, carpe diem.
Seize the day!
Make the most of it. Right?
Oh, by the way,
look forward to your
sleeping arrangements.
We already have tents
by the beach.
- Wow.
- Whoa.
- Enjoy.
- Sounds so exciting!
- Thank you.
- [CLAPPING]
[PANTING] Let's have some water.
Who's going to be
my roomate?
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER,
GIGGLING]
It's not always about
finishing the job first
or getting it done.
It's how you do it
and who you do it with.
Are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
Ah! A snake bit me!
So, it's confirmed, mister?
We're unlucky together?
You're going to perform
a ritual.
You already got Uncle Ronald
to agree to a meeting.
But you need a date.
Where am I even going
to find a date like that?
Gio, put me down!
I don't care if people hear us!
Tell me, Luna.
What happened to you?
Do you know him?
Someone's already
looking for him.
Sandro Soliman.
He's my father.
Something smells.
It smells like something dead.