When two people meet bad luck
when they're together,
they are cursed.
If I were you,
I'd have that removed.
I know a way
to get rid of it.
I know something
happened,
because the Luna I met
in Manila
is different from the Luna
I'm with now on this island.
People change, Gio.
Yes, but I know
there's a reason.
And that's what I want to know.
- Sandro Soliman?
- You know him?
Someone is looking for him.
Could it be his family?
Good morning, sir.
How can I help you?
I'd just like to ask
if I could post this.
Oh, sorry, sir, but the
bulletin board
is only for hotel
programs and activities.
Why were you staring at my
brother like that?
Okay. How many fingers
am I holding up?
- [KIKO] Three.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
How about this?
One.
And this?
- Four.
- Wrong!
Oh, no! I think the venom
got into your brain.
- That's not good.
- You didn't let me finish.
Four plus one is five,
so that's five.
[CHUCKLES] You guys are funny.
Stop it, okay?
You're making everyone here
think that we're silly.
Kiko, are you sure you're okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I already got
first aid treatment,
and we went to the clinic
before we went home.
They said it wasn't
poisonous.
- I'm telling you, it's--
- Sari.
Sir, I'm just concerned
about them.
I don't want them
to get bad luck.
Well, I think there's
no harm
if we'd follow what
our elders say.
See? You've brainwashed
the people here.
Martin, it's okay.
I don't believe it either.
But--
[SARI] Okay, okay.
I won't insist anymore.
I'll stop.
[MARTIN] Finally, you're here.
Okay, I think they'll have
a family meeting.
So, girls, let's go?
Come on.
Bye, bro.
You take care, okay?
Oh, here's your fan.
Thank you, I thought you were
going to take it.
Of course not.
But thank you.
I slept well last night.
Don't mention it.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Thank you.
- Okay.
[LEON] Why are you back
just now?
Where have you been?
Is Justin here already?
He arrived a few
minutes ago.
Where have you been, Luna?
I went somewhere
with Gio.
Gio? Where did he take you?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- He asked me to go with him.
- Where?
Justin, enough with the
questions, okay? I'm tired.
I'm tired, too.
You're not the only one.
You two should get
some rest.
Go home, okay?
No need. I'll stay here.
What are you going to do here?
[JUSTIN SCOFFS, CLICKS TONGUE]
I don't get it.
You get upset when
I'm not here,
and when I'm here,
you ask many questions.
What do you really want?
I'm just asking what you're
going to do here, Justin.
Nothing. I'll just hang out
here and look around.
I'll keep an eye
on things.
Suit yourself.
Just remember, don't cause
any trouble, Justin.
I won't. I promise.
You better behave, Justin.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
I think even though we ended
up doing treasure hunting,
the team building
was still a success, right?
Yes, I think it went great.
Even though we were teamed
up with the Almazans,
we were able to play
without any problems.
You know, I guess
it's a step
for us to be reunited
with the Almazans.
What do you think, Gio?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's alright.
Whatever you decide to do
with the Almazans,
I'll be on board.
Are you still going to leave?
For now, no.
Really?
That's good.
Did the team building
change your mind?
[LUNA] I left everything
that happened in the past.
This is who I am now.
This is the Luna I know.
If you can't accept it,
there's nothing I can do
about it.
So enough.
No.
Just think of it as my way
of making it up to you.
That's why I'm still here.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[YELLS]
[SCREAMING]
[YELLING CONTINUES]
[LAMP THUDS]
[PETER SINGING]
Happy birthday to you...
- Happy birthday to you...
- [LUNA] Oh!
- [LUNA CHUCKLING]
- Happy birthday...
Happy birthday...
[LUNA GRUNTS]
Happy birthday to you
- Make a wish.
- 'Kay.
[BLOWS]
Yay! Thank you, babe!
Anything for you.
Something is missing.
Where's my gift?
[CHUCKLING]
I love my gift!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LUNA] Peter...
[WAVES LAPPING]
Hey!
You okay?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Can I have this one?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
What happened?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay.
I'll leave you here for now.
If you don't want to talk,
I won't force you.
I already know.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
She was broken
when we met.
Huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Weren't you guys
too young to be broken?
No, Monette.
We were together
a few years ago.
Huh?
- [DEVICE CHIMES SOFTLY]
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
When she ran away,
I found her in Manila,
and we stayed together there.
Were you guys a couple?
I don't know.
How can you not know?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I was there
when she needed me.
I was there when
she just wanted me around.
Then suddenly,
she left me.
And now...
she acts like I don't exist.
Yikes...
That's called "ghosting".
I guess.
[MONETTE SIGHS SOFTLY]
All I know is...
she treated me like trash.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you still love her?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Looks like it.
You wouldn't be like this
if you didn't still
have feelings for her.
[BOTTLE CLINKS]
[MOUTH CLICKS, SIGHS SHARPLY]
If you still love her,
find the answers
to all your questions.
Then fight for it.
As long as you can,
as long as you want to.
But if you can't anymore...
don't hurt yourself trying.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here's your drink, sir.
Thank you.
The staff here
is very attentive.
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you for
the compliment, sir.
But we need cash.
[CHUCKLES]
You guys are funny.
Thank you.
Maybe your bosses
are kind too,
that's why you treat
guests like this.
[RAPHIE] Oh, our bosses now
are different, sir.
They're kind too,
but Sir Michael..
He was different. Not a
single bad bone in his body.
Rest in peace, Sir Michael.
Yeah, I heard you're
under new management...
since you just reopened.
Why did you close before?
Well, first,
because of the pandemic.
You know,
the whole world shut down,
so we had to as well.
But we reopened, sir.
Except then,
there was a fire.
A fire?
[RAPHIE] Mm. Yes, sir.
But not the whole hotel.
We just had to close again
for renovations.
So it was renovated.
But there aren't any signs
of a fire here.
Your contractor
must be good.
Who handled it?
Oh! I don't know
about that, sir.
My former boss
handled all that.
Oh, okay.
Sir, do you need
anything else?
Uh, no. I'm good.
Thank you... Raphie.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You're welcome, sir.
[CLEARS THROAT] Please sign the
acknowledgment receipt, sir.
And maybe add
your social media?
Just kidding!
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you, sir!
Take care. Enjoy!
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
The hotel was renovated.
Is this what Dad meant
when he said he worked on
a project here in Isla Solara?
Right here at Hotel 88.
[UNEASY MUSIC SWELLS,
THEN FADES]
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
[BOTH CLEAR THROAT]
[EDWARD] Let's eat.
Yes.
[PHONE CHIMES]
"Hi Jade. Where are you?
Are we still meeting
Sari's grandpa today?"
Jade.
Lunch.
One hour.
I don't think
responding to messages
won't take long.
It doesn't matter.
Come on, eat.
I made it so I'm sure...
You're not going to poison me?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
It's delicious.
[EDWARD] Try it.
Well?
It's good.
[BOTH CHUCKLES]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey, Sari!
- Yes, Sir Kiko?
[KIKO] Can you tell
your grandfather that--
Shh!
Shh! Wait.
Stay! Stay there, sir.
[PHONE BUZZES, BEEPS]
[KIKO] H-Hello?
Sir Kiko, let's communicate
this way.
I don't want Sir Martin
to catch us
talking about your
and Miss Jade's curse.
He's just behind me.
Wait a second.
Did I give you my number?
Sir,
you're Sir Martin's brother.
I need to know all of my
boss's emergency contacts.
You're really impressive.
Of course, sir!
[KIKO] Wait. Hang on.
I just wanted to ask you
to tell your grandpa
that we can't meet him today.
Jade hasn't been
responding to my messages.
Oh, sir! You can't delay
a curse.
It might get worse!
What will get worse?
[SARI] Oh! The...
You know, the...
What will get worse?
Uh, sir, the...
uh, my... my...
my head, sir! My head hurts
so bad!
This needs to be cured
immediately, right?
Of course, we have to tend to it
right away!
[SARI] I told you!
This headache of mine
should be cured, sir! [GROANS]
Alright, Gramps.
I'll message you
on how to get
to your destination instead.
Ouch, my head hurts, sir!
[INAUDIBLE]
- [SARI GROANS]
- Huh? I thought you left?
Uh, no, I-- I just took
this call first
but I'm heading out now
I think it's from a scammer.
- Alright then...
- See you, Martin.
- Sari, let's go!
- Yeah?
I'll have Monette
get you some medicine.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[LAUGHS] Jade, you can
take your time, you know?
- We have an hour, right?
- [JADE LAUGHS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
By the way, how is...
how is...
Kiko doing?
Didn't he get bitten
by a-- a snake?
- Was it a snake?
- [JADE CHUCKLES]
He's doing fine. [LAUGHS]
It's like nothing even happened.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, guys! I didn't know
you were here.
- Ah, Uncle, eat with us!
- Dad.
Oh Jade, have a seat.
Enjoy your lunch.
[LAUGHS] Hey, did you cook?
You should come by
more often, please! [LAUGHS]
You know, I don't remember
the last time you cooked, bud.
Dad, I actually
saved some for you.
- You can eat it later.
- [ANDY CHUCKLES]
Alright, alright.
Good to see you.
I hope to see you around
all the time.
See? When he cooks for you
I end up eating some too.
- [JADE CHUCKLES]
- Dad.
Okay, I get it.
I'll leave you two.
I'll eat what you made
later, alright?
- Bye, Uncle!
- Good to see you.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Kiko, don't just stand there!
You might be mistaken
for a bad person!
Dude...
Le-- let's just go home.
Huh?
What about the curse?
Well, Jade didn't say whether
she's coming or not.
It's not like I can do
this alone.
Well, that's a shame.
- Sure you don't want to?
- Nah, let's just go home.
- [JADE] Kiko!
- Oh, there she is!
Kiko! Oh! [PANTING]
Hi Cheska, I'm sorry.
Sorry I'm late.
[PANTING] I had lunch
before going here, sorry.
Is this the place?
- [WHISPERS] Let's go home...
- But I thought--
Well...
[BOTONG] Are you...
my granddaughter's friends?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh...
[STUTTERING] Ye-- Yes, Gramps.
We're Sari's friends.
Are you the one who needs
to have their curse broken?
Oh, not me! I'm not cursed
but they are!
- It's just them!
- Hey! Cheska...
Gramps! Wha-- what are you
gonna do?
- [BLADE SWISHES]
- I'll slash your curse off!
- Wait!
- Don't, please!
[PLANT CRUNCHING]
[BOTONG] You may now
head inside.
Inside!
Go inside, he said.
- Inside.
- [WHISPERS] Sure, go on!
- Dude.
- Cheska!
Yeah, I'm coming!
- You there.
- Me?
- Stay outside.
- Dude!
Huh? Why?!
The curse might transfer to you
once it's broken free from them.
Is that what you want?
Oh, not at all, Gramps.
I'm fine staying outside.
Hey Kiko, take care!
Good luck!
Go!
Alright.
The next time Jade visits,
let me know.
So I can tell the maid
that you'll be in charge
of the cooking.
[SARCASTICALLY] Oh sure, Dad.
Tease me more.
No, I'm serious.
If I only knew, I could've had
the kitchen renovated.
[SCOFFS] Dad,
what are you even on?
It's just a meal.
You say it's just a meal but...
Didn't you have lunch
with her last time too?
It's just what we agreed on.
It's all part of a deal.
What-- What deal?
I saved her, right?
Mm-hmm.
- Do you remember?
- Yes.
She said she wanted
to make it up to me.
Said she wanted to pay back
the kindness I showed her, so...
It's one of the things
I asked from her.
One of the things you asked?
[LAUGHS]
What else did you ask from her?
Coffee for ten minutes.
Look, bud...
Why don't you just
be honest with her?
Dad.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I just wanted to help her.
She's going through a lot
so I just wanted to make sure...
that she's eating well.
[SIGHS] Do you hear yourself?
Not eating well?
Bud.
The Alamzans have
a private chef.
And if I remember correctly,
her sister cooks as well.
And I've also heard
that the chef of Hotel 88
is also excellent
so food is the least
of her worries.
Dad... [SIGHS DEEPLY]
Okay, I won't bother you
anymore.
But,
for whatever it is,
whatever you have going on,
I just want you to know that...
I approve of her.
- Okay?
- [SIGHS IN DISBELIEF]
I approve of her, she's good
she's good
for our family and uh...
most importantly, she's good
for your heart.
'Kay?
[BOTONG HUMMING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUGHS]
Seems like this isn't
your first time.
It's just similar to a facial
treatment at a salon, Kiko.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEON] Roi is the only one
that seems to have a motive.
If only I could
find a connection
with what we did to Sandro...
A folder?
Uncle Mike has a folder?
What's inside it?
And why did he bring it
when he met up with Dad?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Leon.
Hey. Why're you here so early?
I just left my power bank.
I came back to get it.
What's that?
Oh, nothing.
Just some business contracts.
Business contract
that Dad left behind.
Can I see?
Why?
You won't understand it anyway.
Go on ahead,
get your power bank.
Alright.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUSTIN] This isn't
the first time
you're digging though
Dad's things.
What are you up to, Leon?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are we cursed?
The two of you
have to do a ritual.
You shouldn't reveal this
to a single soul!
A leave of absence?!
I just have to take care
of something.
- And that is?
- If the ritual
to remove the curse
becomes a success,
the opposite will happen to you.
There will be a new connection.
You'll just suddenly feel
something in your chest.
Something smells bad.
Like a dead body.
A dead body?