What are we?
It's like we're at
opposite ends of a bridge.
We will cross the bridge...
when we're finally ready
to accept each other.
- Are you ready?
- For a while now.
First, for two months...
you will eat lunch with me.
Aside from lunch,
we'll also have coffee updates.
Jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
Just a friendly advice.
It's fine if our friend has...
a boyfriend.
Do you know someone
named Sandro Soliman?
I think your dad has
mentioned him before
talking about one of
his business ventures
that he was going to enter.
Did this Sandro guy
get in touch with you?
Not really, Uncle.
I don't know him.
I need to know the truth.
The Almazans will lead me
to where you are, Papa.
You seem to be...
You seem to be enjoying
that a lot.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Kiko and I made this together,
so it's just right that...
I enjoy it, right?
Uh.
Jade, there...
- There...
- What is it?
["PANGHABANG IKAW" BY
DARREN ESPANTO PLAYING]
There is...
There's a mosquito!
Oh.
There are mosquitoes here.
- You might get bitten.
- Oh, right.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Sit down.
Don't you want to sit down?
Here.
["PANGHABANG IKAW" CONTINUES]
Start the update.
Update?
We've been together
the whole time, haven't we?
You've seen me all day, so...
what update do you still need?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Well, yeah.
But that's my POV.
I would like to see or know...
what your point of view is.
What's your story? Your update.
Whatever you want.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Well...
Come to think of it,
this day was fun.
I mean, sure.
It's chaotic and
exhausting, but...
I had fun.
I feel like...
I felt more relieved.
Because, in a way,
we were able to get justice
for my father's death.
And then, Mom would have
peace of mind in Spain.
I'm also with my family.
My family and that of Kiko's
won't need to fight anymore.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's always nice
to see you smile, Jade.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHUCKLING]
What?
Ten minute coffee update
is over.
Buh-bye!
Good night, Edward.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHESKA CLEARS THROAT]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Oh.
How great.
Is this tent just yours?
You'll fit in there.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHESKA EXHALES DEEPLY]
My goodness.
Hey, you.
Let's talk.
What's your problem with me?
Why are you so hot-headed?
You've been having an attitude
for a while now.
Because, you have
no concept of personal...
space.
What?
What word did you just say?
Space?
Can you see my space, huh?
Can you see that space?
Cheska, you're just so noisy.
You're so stubborn and dirty.
Girl, I just can't stand people
like that, okay?
Even at the hotel,
you behave like
it's your own home.
Your brother is
only a part-time owner.
[SCOFFS] Well,
what can I do, huh?
That's just how Endayas are.
We easily adapt and
feel at home anywhere.
Just look at my brother, Kiko.
Have you seen him?
He immediately got along
with Gio and your brother Martin
even if they had not seen
each other in a long time.
There, have your space
if that's the issue.
We don't need to talk.
[CHESKA SCOFFS]
Wait a second.
Didn't you even listen
to Art's speech
during the team building?
Didn't he say that
it's who you do it with?
He said that's how
you could do the task.
You didn't even bother
to apply it yourself.
[MOODY MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRIXIE SCOFFS]
You're giving me a headache.
[FAN BLOWS]
[SCOFFS]
[MOODY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here.
I know you're not used
to the heat.
I can't sleep because of you.
You keep going like this.
You'll be like that all night.
Use it!
Thank you!
[CHESKA] You're welcome!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHESKA SNORING]
What kind of person can go
to sleep right away?
She really feels at home.
[SNORING CONTINUES]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[WAVES CRASHING]
- Come with me.
- Oh.
Gio, what is it?
We'll have a talk, Luna.
I don't want to!
You don't want to?
Gio, put me down!
I don't care if people hear us!
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Fine! I'll come with you.
Just let me down.
[GIO] I'll bring you down and
you will come with me.
If you run away,
I'm going to carry you
like a sack of rice.
Do you understand?
Okay, just put me down.
Hop on.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Get in!
[SCOFFS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
["TADHANA" BY SOFRONIO VASQUEZ
PLAYING]
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
Hey, wait!
Where is he going?
[GIO] He's going
to leave us here.
We're just going to talk, right?
He will come back
when I call him.
He won't come back until
you talk properly with me.
Gio!
What, are you going
to start now?
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
What? Just tell me, I'll listen!
Just say it, Luna!
You are childish.
Really, Gio?
Did you have to come
to this point?
I tried talking to you properly,
but you wouldn't.
It is your fault
that we got to this point.
Alright.
What if the boatman leaves?
What if he doesn't come back?
Do you even think, Gio?
You talk a lot,
but keep avoiding my question.
- What happened to you, Luna?
- Nothing!
Nothing happened!
Something happened because
the Luna I knew in Manila
is different from the Luna
I met on this island!
People change, Gio.
I know, but there's a reason.
And that's what I want to know.
You wouldn't change
if nothing happened to you.
Now, tell me, Luna.
What happened to you?
[SOFT, DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
You don't believe that Roi
killed your fathers anymore?
I just wanted to be sure.
It's possible that other people
held a grudge against them.
At the moment, Roi is the
only one who has a motive
and said he was at the
crime scene at the time.
Didn't Dad
or Uncle Michael report
about anything before they died?
Maybe someone tried to kill them
or someone's mad at them?
Nothing.
If they did, we'd have it
included in the investigation.
Maybe...
It's best to talk to your lawyer
about your speculations.
It's possible that Roi
is getting through your head.
Do you need anything else, Leon?
No, sir.
And, Leon...
Wherever your fathers are
right now,
I'm sure they're at peace.
I hope you find that, too.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYS]
I just have to do something.
Can't I just want to change?
Can't I not be Solenn anymore?
You think I'd believe that?
I know you love what you did
back in Manila.
You don't really want
to be here!
That's not me!
You may fool others with that,
but I know who you really are.
Just call a boatman, will you?
This is going nowhere.
- We're not done yet!
- Why?
Because you haven't heard
what you wanted to hear?
That I'm just pretending
right now?
Yes!
Because if you were
pretending then,
you also admit that
what we had wasn't real!
Everything we went through...
You can't just convince yourself
to wake up one day and decide
that it never happened.
I never said it didn't happen.
But that's what
you're showing me now.
That's what you make me feel.
You avoid me, you won't talk
to me unless about work.
Your siblings don't even know
we met back in Manila!
So, I don't understand
why you're acting like that.
You just discarded me.
We were happy, weren't we?
Was that just nothing to you?
[SIGHS]
I've let go of everything that
happened to me in the past.
I'm here now.
This is the Luna I know.
If you can't accept that,
there's nothing I can do.
[SOFT, DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Hey, Leon.
I thought you're going home.
I'm just waiting for my driver
to get the car.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
- [ENGINE REVVS]
- [THUDS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Sandro Soliman?
Do you know him?
Uh... No.
I just read what was written.
Is he a local?
No, just visiting.
His son just
reported him missing.
Alright. Take care.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CELLPHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
[KIKO] Jade!
- Jade.
- Wait!
- Let's go.
- Wait, wait.
I'm just taking pictures.
Maybe I can get
some inspiration
for the kids' painting sessions.
[CELLPHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
Did you sleep early last night?
Yeah. Mm, Edward and I
didn't stay up long either.
He just wanted me
to tell him stories.
We're going home again.
Back to the real world.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, right.
Too bad Leon didn't get
to experience this.
If he were here,
it would've been so much fun.
- For sure.
- [SNAKE HISSING]
[KIKO GROANS]
- Ouch! Jade! It hurts!
- Kiko! Kiko! Kiko!
What happened?! Oh my god!
- I got bitten by a snake!
- You got bitten?! Oh my god!
- Oh my god!
- [GROANS]
You got bitten! Kiko!
- Ouch!
- Oh no! What do I do?
- Jade...
- What should I do?!
- Jade, it hurts!
- Kiko-- Help!
Help! Wait!
Wait, wait. Just breathe.
Hold on.
Calm down, wait! Wait!
- Wait, I saw in movies...
- Ouch! Ouch!
...that when you get bitten
by a snake,
you have to suck
the venom out.
- You're going to suck it out?!
- What?!
I'm not sucking it!
What do you mean suck it?!
- No! I'm not sucking that!
- Jade!
What if the poison
transfers to me?!
Jade, oh my god!
I think I'm going to die!
- No, you're not-- Okay fine!
- Ouch! Ouch!
I'll do it!
I'll do it! Here! Here!
Okay. [BREATHES HEAVILY]
- What?
- Where?
- [KIKO GROANS]
- Hurry! Come on!
- Sit! Sit! Here!
- Ouch! Ouch!
I'll suck it out! Hurry!
Come on!
- Lift it! Hurry.
- Here-- Ouch!
- What happened?
- Art!
He got bitten by a snake!
- Snake?!
- [KIKO GRUNTS]
Wait, what color was the snake?
What? It was like...
Kind of black with brown spots.
Something like that.
- Maybe a wolf snake.
- Huh?!
- [ART] But it's not venomous.
- [KIKO] Ouch! Ouch!
[GROANING CONTINUES]
- [JADE] Kiko?
- Mm?
Do you have a mark on your butt?
- Huh?
Because my grandpa said
if you have a mark on your butt,
it means bad luck.
I don't have a mark on my butt.
Maybe you do!
I only get into accidents
whenever I'm with you.
The time I choked,
when you almost got hit
by a motorcycle, and then this--
[GROANS] Ouch! Ouch!
That's three times?!
Oh, Ms. Jade,
that's a different kind
of bad luck.
Huh? What bad luck?
Sari, what is that now?
Sir, that's a belief
of the elders
here in the province.
When two people are always
unlucky together,
it means they're cursed.
Well, there are certain beliefs
in the provinces.
Oh dear, Ms. Jade.
If I were you,
I'd have that removed.
I know how to remove it.
Do you want to?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WAVES CRASHING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WAVES CRASHING]
[GIO] The bridge...
You said before that we were
on opposite ends of the bridge.
I couldn't cross
the bridge, Gio.
So let's stop.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOAT ROARING]
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEON]
Someone's looking for him.
Could it be his family?
Why are you looking
for my father?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JUSTIN] Why are you looking
at my brother like that?
Sorry, sorry! I didn't see you.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- I didn't mean to.
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
What is it?
Good morning, sir.
How may I help you?
I just wanted to ask a question
at your front desk.
We don't have anyone in
right now.
You can ask me instead.
I work here, too.
I was wondering if I could post
some missing posters here.
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
We only post hotel activities
on the bulletin board.
But I can tell our staff
about it.
If we ever see, uh...
Mr. Sandro?
Sandro Soliman.
My father.
Oh, okay.
I'll tell our staff
to keep an eye out.
Thank you.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Folder? Uncle Mike has a folder?
- I'll stay here.
- What are you gonna do?
Just keep an eye out.
Why did you shut down
the first time?
There was a fire.
There aren't any traces
of a fire anywhere.
Whatever your decision is,
I support it.
If you still love her,
find out the answers
to all your questions.
And use it to fight for her.
Whatever you have going on,
I'm all for it.
But, she's good
for the business.
Most importantly,
she's good for your heart.
Are you...
Are you the ones
who want to break a curse?
- Wait, no!
- No!