Thank you for your cooperation.
I'm glad you can
finally go home now.
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS] Ah!
Sir, how about Bok?
He's dead.
Yes, I did kidnap Jade.
Jade.
But no matter what you do,
you can't pin your fathers'
death on me.
They didn't kill each other.
There's someone else.
Sandro Soliman?
I'm afraid something might
have happened to him.
Are you scared that
your father might be dead?
Maybe it's time to revive
the annual Hotel 88
team building!
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [SARI SCREAMING]
I curated today
all the activities
so everyone can
learn from each other.
Focus, Sari.
- Let me drive, or I'll leave!
- Then leave!
- Move! I'll drive!
- Just leave!
How can you finish
this task faster?
I'll do it.
- No, I'll do it.
Now you both want to do it.
What's your deal?
Justin, I'll do it.
I can do it. I promise.
And most importantly, have fun.
- [CHEERING]
- Let's go!
[CHEERING]
It's a tie for both teams!
Wait, what will we do
now, sir?
Spend the whole day
bonding together,
especially with people you
haven't teamed up with yet.
Seize the day!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mr. Soliman?
Sandro Soliman?
Yes. My father had a meeting
with him.
[LEON] So that's his name.
Sandro.
[CAFE STAFF] Sir, Mr. Soliman's
reservation was made
around a month ago.
Is that so?
Does your guest list say
who else they met with?
[CAFE STAFF] I'm sorry,
but we don't divulge
our guests' information.
Okay. I understand.
Thank you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUAN] He's from Hotel 88.
What was he doing here?
Good morning.
Are you the one
in charge of reservations?
[CAFE STAFF] Yes, sir. Do you
want to make a reservation?
Can you help me?
My father made
a reservation here
under Sandro Soliman.
The other guy also asked
about him earlier.
He wanted to know
who Mr. Soliman
was meeting that day.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUAN] Why are you looking
for my father?
Are you also looking
for the treasure?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANDY] I thought you had
a team building?
I couldn't go there after
taking Mom to the airport.
I had some things to
take care of in Dad's business.
Right, right.
Frida's flight to Spain
was today.
Is she alone or with someone?
My aunt is with her.
Alright, so let me guess.
You and Luna
are now in charge
of managing the businesses
Fred left behind.
That's right, Uncle.
[ANDY CHUCKLES]
You know,
I'm not surprised that...
you took over the businesses
your Fred left behind.
Actually, Luna's a big help.
She's the one managing
the hotel closely.
Alright, that's good.
Speaking of the hotel,
how is it? Any updates?
Well, trying to survive, Uncle.
Of course, it's not as popular
as your hotel right now.
No, no. I wouldn't worry
about it, you know.
Hotel 88 has just reopened.
So just give it
some time and, uh...
it'll pay off big for you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Uncle, I just want to ask you
something.
What is it?
Do you know someone
named Sandro Soliman?
Sandro Soliman...
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Thank you, mister.
- Thank you.
Monette, let me have a taste.
Jeez, Raphie!
Come on, just this once.
Mister, two cups, please.
[MONETTE] Just take
a picture at the hotel.
We have coffee there.
Really? You won't take it out
of my pay?
[MONETTE] Seriously!
Have you seen Sari?
[MONETTE] Sari...
- Uh... There!
- She's over there!
[MARTIN] I see.
Why are you looking
for her, sir?
Do you miss her already?
What?
I just need to double-check
something about work.
Is there anything
you need to do, sir?
- Maybe I can do--
- No.
It should be Sari.
Nevermind. You guys have fun.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[MONETTE] Oh, come on. Just
enjoy your coffee and chill.
- [JUSTIN] Trixie.
- It was so tiring earlier.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh...
It sounds familiar.
I think, uh...
I think I've heard
that name before.
Actually, from your dad.
You only heard it from Dad?
You don't know him personally?
[ANDY] No, no. I don't know him.
Um, I think your dad
mentioned him
while talking about one
of his business ventures
that he was going to do. Then
that name was mentioned.
But after that,
I didn't have any updates
so I didn't know if the business
pushed through or not.
Uh, did this Sandro guy
get in touch with you?
No, Uncle.
I don't know him.
I'm just checking
Dad's business transactions,
just in case I missed something.
You know, you're such
a responsible son.
Anyway,
whatever business
you need to take care of,
I hope you can do it well.
And regarding this Soliman guy,
I hope you find him.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jade.
[EDWARD] Jade, let's go.
Huh? Wait, where are we going?
There's something I need
to tell you.
Uh-- What? Edward!
You brought me here
away from everyone
just to tell me
your three wishes?
Yup.
Okay.
Tell me.
First, for two months...
you'll eat lunch with me.
Wherever you are, wherever I am,
we'll eat together.
Lunch?
Are you aware that eating lunch
with you every day
will ruin my schedule?
Okay. I thought you were serious
about making it up to me.
No, I'm serious.
I'll make it up to you.
But that doesn't mean
that you can control
my schedule like that.
Okay, okay.
Let's do it this way.
The lunch should be planned.
Is that good for you?
Fifteen days.
One month.
One month of one-hour lunches.
Exactly one hour.
Okay.
Deal.
Second.
Coffee update.
What's that?
[EDWARD] In addition to lunch,
we will also
have a coffee update.
Update what?
It can be anything.
Tss.
Can't I just update you
while we're having lunch?
It's different.
Okay?
Okay.
Fifteen days.
One month.
One month, ten minutes.
Deal.
Okay.
What's your third wish?
Secret.
Hey, Edward!
[EDWARD] I still need
to think about it.
Bye, bye.
["PANGHABANG IKAW" BY DARREN]
[JADE] Edward! Wait!
What is the third one?
- [MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
- [MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAND CRUNCHING]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
[GIO] What are we?
[LUNA] We're like a bridge.
What bridge
are you talking about?
- Our status right now.
- Hmm?
We're like at opposite ends
of a bridge.
- [GIGGLES]
- Just like the idiom?
"We'll cross the bridge
when we get there?"
[CHUCKLES]
We will cross the bridge
when we're ready
to accept each other.
Are you ready?
For a while now.
How about you?
Are you ready?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Let's dig in.
- [CHUCKLES]
Mm! It's hot!
Why?
- You're making a mess!
- [GIGGLES]
Watch this.
You have to mix it first.
Mm.
Mm! I said, it's hot!
[GIO] Just eat slowly.
[LUNA] You didn't
blow on it first.
[GIO] Last bite.
["TADHANA" BY
SOFRONIO VASQUEZ PLAYING]
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
[ART] Take the clues,
then place them on the sand.
If you turn them upside down
and then put them together,
you'll see that when you combine
the images of the two groups,
a big image will be formed.
[CALM MUSIC PLAYING]
Hotel 88?
Too bad.
We would've won faster
if we looked at the other side.
Not really.
But it would be easier
to finish the tasks
if you knew exactly
what you're working towards.
It's not always
about finishing the job first
or getting it done.
It's how you do it
and who you do it with.
And that is Hotel 88.
I hope you always remember
that Hotel 88
isn't just about
operating a hotel.
It's also about
continuing as a family.
Justin.
[CALM MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Miss Monette!
- Miss Monette.
- Yes!
[ART] So, everyone okay?
Here's your tentmates.
- [MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GRUNTS]
[WAVES CRASHING]
Are you really fine
with us sharing a tent?
If you're uncomfortable,
we can put this bag between us.
It's like I'm talking
to the wind.
[MUSIC TURNS SOFT]
[GRUNTS]
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SAND CRUNCHING]
Let's talk.
Gio...
What's the problem?
Why are you avoiding me?
We were teammates, right?
Yeah, but you avoided me
like I'm ill or something.
Because we have nothing
to talk about.
We have a lot to talk about.
No, we don't.
Luna.
We need to talk.
Luna...
Gio, I just want to take a rest.
Please?
[TENT ZIPPING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bro, let's just talk next time.
We have a hotel activity,
so I wasn't able to answer
your call.
I'll call you when I get back
to Solara island-- [SCREAMS]
Sari, what the hell?!
Sir, Monette said you were
looking for me earlier?
Yes, but what's that?!
Skincare, sir.
We're here at the beach all day,
so we need to take care
of our skin, sir.
Oh, here!
I have an extra for you.
Sir, what do you want?
- Piggy, sheep, or panda?
- I don't need it.
[SARI] You need this, sir.
So your skin won't get
- irritated--
- I said...
I don't need it.
Not everything
is your business, Sari.
There are boundaries.
You're getting a bit
too comfortable.
[MARTIN] Yes,
we're at a team building.
Yes, this is work-related,
but I hope you learn your place.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry, sir.
I hope you don't forget.
I am still your boss, Sari.
- [GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[SIGHS, MOUTH CLICKS]
Of course he'd get mad.
Monette, he's my boss.
Is it wrong to think that
his skin might get irritated?
Sari, that was already
something personal
that you interfered with.
Is that a bad thing?
It's obvious you have a
happy crush on Sir Martin.
And there's nothing
wrong with that. It's fine.
But maybe he's
no longer comfortable
with how you show
your feelings for him.
I only did that
because I feel inspired
working with Sir Martin.
But of course, you still have
to know your place.
[SIGHS]
Is that really just
a happy crush, or...
are you hoping he'll
eventually like you back?
Oh, come on!
You know, Monette...
I wished to the universe
for the person...
...who would be my soulmate.
That he would come...
...on a day when the sky
is crying.
And that's Sir Martin.
- Oh.
- [CHUCKLES]
You know, Monette,
my parents ended up together
because of a sign.
I saw how happy they were,
until the very last moment
of their lives.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Monette, I want to experience
that too.
I want to feel...
what my parents had before.
[EXHALES]
And I feel like...
there's a reason
why it was Sir Martin
who came on that day, Monette.
So for now...
even if he scolded me...
...he's still my soulmate.
Oh my.
Must be nice.
[WHIMPERS]
Must be nice to love
that purely.
- [CHUCKLES]
- That's the spirit.
[KIKO] There it is.
This is the...
Smo!--
- Smo...
- S-Smos...
[CHUCKLES]
Smo-- S'mores!
- It's s'mores! [CHUCKLES]
- Here.
Goodness.
It's just marshmallows
and crackers.
Oh, come on! It's good.
It's actually my favorite.
Try it.
Come on. Let's cheers.
Cheers.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[EDWARD] Jade.
Coffee update.
Let's go.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE] Really? Right now?
Coffee...
update.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KIKO] Just take it with you.
[JADE] Sorry, Kiko.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WAVES CRASHING]
Hmm... It's like...
You're stretching your neck
by looking over so much.
You'd be a giraffe by the time
we return to the hotel.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you jealous?
Me? Jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
[SCOFFS]
Your nose is growing
just by saying that. [CHUCKLES]
No, I'm not jealous.
Jade and I are fine,
and I'm glad
that we're friends again.
Okay.
So, as a friend,
you don't find it weird
that Jade went with Edward
while you're having
a moment together?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alright, then.
You're fine, as you said.
If you think about it,
it's really okay for our friends
to have boyfriends.
Right?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're probably just hungry.
- Is this good?
- Mm-hm.
For a friend.
[MUSIC TURNS UNSETTLING]
[LEON] I wish you had told me
everything, Dad.
What really happened
that night?
Why did this man
want to kill you?
"Two Businessmen Killed
each other on Kaluguran Island"
It had been more than a month
since Federico Almazan died.
It's been over 5 months since
I last spoke to my father.
Papa is missing
and his colleague is dead?
If Federico's son
is looking for you,
do the Almazans have something
to do with your disappearance?
I need to know the truth.
The Almazans will show me
where you are, Papa.
You don't believe that Roi
killed your fathers anymore?
Do you know him?
Someone is looking for him.
Sandro Soliman. My father.
I was thrilled.
We were able to get justice
for Dad 's death.
And we've made amends
with Kiko's family.
- [SNAKE HISSES]
- [KIKO GROANS]
- Are you really that unlucky?
- I don't think so!
Every time we're together,
something bad happens!
When two people meet bad luck
when they're together,
it's probably a curse.
- Gio, put me down!
- I don't care if they hear us!
Tell me, Luna.
What's going on with you?