- Sir Gio!
- Welcome back, Sir Gio!
You're going back to Manila?
I don't want you to be
in danger because of me.
We won't let you disappear
from our lives.
This family will never separate.
It's impossible that what
happened had nothing to do
with Dad and Uncle Mike's death.
But the man is dead.
I've killed him.
If what Roi says is true...
They didn't kill each other.
There's someone else.
That person is still free...
My siblings could be in danger.
What if I don't leave?
Ma, we already talked
about this, haven't we?
And Mom,
this might help you, too.
Like, you originally planned.
But it's like... I feel like
I can't leave you anymore.
Mom, I have something for you.
Wow!
- It's beautiful!
- You'll be able to use this
when it's winter in Spain.
- It looks good on you.
- Thank you, thank you.
Mom, you're not going
to leave us.
We will not allow you
to not come back.
But of course, you can stay
as long as you like.
What if we just all go there?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Mom, we're not kids anymore
that you need to bring
with you everywhere.
Besides, Leon and I
need to manage
the businesses that Dad left.
But you have to heal.
After your dad's death,
you immediately took over
the hotel.
- And the incident with Roi--
- Mom, Mom.
We promise,
we're going to be okay.
Hmm?
As long as we're together,
we're going to be fine.
[JADE] Plus...
You should put yourself
first now, Mom.
You've been taking care of us
all your life.
Time to prioritize yourself now.
Besides, we're going to be
there. We will visit you.
And...
I can go home whenever I want.
Come here, you kids.
[CHUCKLING]
- Mm.
- We'll miss you, Mom.
What good have
I done in the world
to have such loving children.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Your father raised you right.
Thank you for...
for understanding me.
I love you so much.
[SMOOCHES] I love you, Ma.
Hmm...
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir, I'm glad you have
a strong case against Roi.
Mrs. Almazan's statement saying
that Roi was at the crime scene
when the crime happened
was a huge help.
Almazans' lawyers are already
on the move
to file a murder case
against Roi.
Two counts of murder.
Our lawyers will also
coordinate with them
to file a case against Roi
for killing our father.
File all the applicable cases
against him.
Murder, kidnapping of Jade...
He even harmed Aunt Frida
and Leon.
Include what he did
to Kiko in his house.
That way, he'll be
in prison for life.
Ma'am, sir, thank you.
Thank you for helping us out
in Roi and Bong's case.
We're just doing our job.
[MONETTE] Sir.
Here's the key for the pickup
- and the speedboat's ready.
- Oh, thank you.
Looks like you're
going somewhere.
You should ride with us.
We're going to the city.
But finish your coffee first.
Hello, Papa.
Are you surprised
that we are here?
We're still complete, look.
Pa.
Roi is in jail.
The guy who killed you
and Uncle Fred.
I hope you and Uncle
are at peace now.
Have a shot there from heaven.
I hope Papa can still see us.
That we didn't sell the hotel,
and the three of us
are managing it.
Grandma said...
that they're never truly gone.
Just like Mama.
She still watches over me.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I do hope Papa
can see us from up there.
He might give us some
advice about what to do.
Advice about what?
What we should do
with the Almazans.
I mean, yes, we worked together
on everything that happened.
But...
[SIGHS]
Now that the truth
has come out...
It turns out that our fathers
didn't kill each other.
We were wrong
to judge each other.
But we can't go
back to the hotel
and act like everything's
okay now, right?
What?
We're suddenly chummy now?
Didn't they say anything bad
about us?
But we have to figure out a way
that won't affect things
because of our relationship.
So the hotel can thrive.
In other words...
We need to be
in good terms with them?
We need...
to actually be friends
with them.
Just like Papa and Uncle Fred.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Here's your key.
Please assist her, Pamela.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
You should be proud.
The number of
hotel guests increased
thanks to the music fest.
[RAPHIE]
Do you have reservations?
Your project is a success.
- [RAPHIE] Your keys. Enjoy!
- [HOTEL GUEST] Thank you!
How are you feeling?
- Kiko mentioned--
- I'm okay.
How's Jade?
We told her
not to work for now
because we know that what
happened to her was traumatic.
The Bok guy.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- [RAPHIE] How sweet!
A guest booked our hotel
for a debut celebration!
- Birthday?
- Oh, I love that!
- What do we need?
- A lot of energy.
Is it a party?
I'll take care of it.
Go on, ask them.
[RAPHIE] Okay.
- [GIO] Debut date.
- [RAPHIE] I'm excited.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Right?
Ah, excuse me.
Here's your drink, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- I'll get your main in a bit.
- Ah, okay.
- Thank you.
[THUDS]
Sorry, I didn't see you.
- Are you okay?
- It's fine.
[RAPHIE] Sir, sir, sir!
I'll handle that.
I'm really sorry.
- Raphie.
- [RAPHIE] Sir?
Give our guest any drink
he wants.
- On the house.
- Okay.
Which is on the house?
Oh, the guest's drink spilled,
Sir Leon.
Justin?
I already said I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's fine.
I'll go now.
[CHESKA] A knife?
Why does he have a knife?
Let's go, back to work.
Justin.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[FRIDA] I went here
to again personally apologize
for Roi's actions.
The lawyers are taking care
of everything.
It's okay.
[MARTIN STAMMERING]
I mean...
It's not okay that Papa died.
However, you don't have
to apologize
for your driver's actions.
My brother's right.
You are a victim, too.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
A lot has changed.
I remember
when you were all little,
just running around here.
Everyone was happy.
We didn't have problems.
They said you're going to leave?
[FRIDA SIGHS]
That's one of the reasons
why I'm here now.
I hope that before I leave...
Our families could reconcile.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know that with everything
that happened to us,
what I'm asking for
is not easy.
But...
I'm sure this is what
your fathers would have wanted.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KIKO SIGHS]
That's also what my brothers
and I want.
We just don't know
where to start.
[MONETTE] This calls
for a team building!
[LUNA] Are you saying
something, Miss Monette?
I think it's time to bring back
the annual Hotel 88
team building!
I love it!
The team building will revive
the hearts of the employees
who are losing
their interest in work.
[SARI SIGHS]
If you say so.
You are in charge
of the logistics.
I've also spoken to Trixie,
and she knows a facilitator
who will help the organizers
for the whole program.
[SARI] Okay, sir!
I'll also help Miss Trixie
on the things she needs to do.
I also know of a possible venue!
Ohh! Go, Team Hotel 88!
[MARTIN EXHALES DEEPLY]
I'm entrusting you with that.
I don't want any foolishness,
and I don't want a repeat
of the music fest,
where you brought
our siblings everywhere
without asking for permission.
Understood?
No foolishness,
you're entrusting this to me,
and don't repeat what I did
at the music festival.
Got it, copy all, check!
Copy, noted. On everything!
- [GASPS] And!
- And? There's more?
And have fun!
I need to make sure
we all have fun.
- Team building! Team building.
- Sari.
Team building, team building.
[SARI GIGGLES]
[SARI] Team building!
Jade!
- [JADE] Kiko! Hey.
- [KIKO CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Seems like we haven't talked
in a long time.
- Yeah.
- How are you?
Are you fine now?
- You don't feel sick anymore?
- I'm fine now. Why?
Ah, Jade.
- Come!
- [JADE] Where?
[KIKO] Sir, can I borrow this?
- Huh? But--
- Thank you.
What is this?
Where-- Where are we going?
- We'll bike around!
- [JADE CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Hop on.
- Do you know how to ride this?
- Of course!
- [JADE GIGGLES]
[JADE] Hey.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
[JADE] Kiko, wait.
Where are we going, anyway?
- Just hold on!
- [GIGGLES] Drive slow, okay?
[JADE CHUCKLING]
- Woo!
- [JADE] Woo! Woo!
- [KIKO] Woo!
Slow down, slow down!
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN CONTINUES]
[KIKO] Hold on.
Hold on!
- [LAUGHTER]
- [JADE] Go slow!
[JADE LAUGHING] Kiko!
We're wobbling.
- [KIKO] Woo!
- [JADE] Woo!
[LAUGHTER]
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN CONTINUES]
- [JADE] Woo!
- [KIKO] Wow!
[KIKO] Just hold on.
- Hold on!
- [JADE LAUGHING] Go slowly!
[JADE GIGGLING]
[KIKO] Come.
Wait.
- [KIKO GRUNTS]
- [JADE CHUCKLES]
[CHUCKLING]
[KIKO] What do you think?
You still okay?
Is it okay that you suddenly
made me ride a bike?
Why? Didn't you have fun?
Of course, I did! That's why...
- Matsa...
- Love.
Love. Matsalove. (Thank you)
[JADE CHUCKLES]
Jade.
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't lost consciousness,
I could've saved you from Roi.
I'm the one
who should apologize.
For what?
If I didn't involve you
in my search for the truth,
then you wouldn't have gotten
caught up in what Roi did.
Jade, it's honestly a good thing
you pulled me in this,
rather than you being all alone.
I wish he would've taken me
instead of you.
What? That can't be.
But it was really dangerous
what happened to you.
Even if you were
inside that drum,
it still would be dangerous.
That's nothing to me. It's fine.
Just not my friends.
Especially you.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're my best friend,
especially when we were young.
Only when we were young?
What about now?
Why?
Is it still possible?
You said a lot has changed.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
Then propose first.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] Propose?
Yes.
[KIKO CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- [KIKO GRUNTS]
- [JADE GIGGLES]
Jade.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN CONTINUES]
Will you be my...
...best friend again?
[JADE CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Hmm...
- Really?
- Yes.
- You can't take that back.
- [JADE CHUCKLES]
Whether in danger or not,
no one's leaving
this friendship.
No one leaves.
Promise.
- [HANDS CLAP]
- [JADE CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN CONTINUES]
No one's leaving.
Ah. Let's go! Let's leave.
- [SMACKS]
- I thought no one's leaving?
We're leaving right away?
It's true! We're leaving,
we're going home.
- Don't you want to?
- Fine, fine. Let's go.
- Am I driving the bike?
- Sure, if you can.
[JADE CHUCKLING]
- [JADE] Come on.
- [KIKO] Wait.
[JADE] You should drive instead.
- [KIKO] Excuse me...
- [JADE] I think you're heavy.
- [KIKO] I'm heavy?
- [JADE] You should drive.
Come on.
- [KIKO] Let's go!
- [JADE CHUCKLING]
- [KIKO] Come on.
- [JADE] Can you even drive?
- [KIKO] Of course!
- [JADE GIGGLING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Bud, Jade's calling.
Edward.
Edward, aren't you gonna
answer it?
Dad, I'm busy. Just let it be.
Alright. Whatever you say.
Anyway, um...
Join me for dinner
when you're done.
[EDWARD] Okay.
[PHONE RINGING CONTINUES]
Is Sir Edward not answering
your calls?
Yeah. He might still be
at the meeting.
But don't worry. I'll talk
to him for the venue
- of our team building.
- [SQUEALS]
Thank you, Ms. Jade! [SIGHS]
The resort that Sir Edward owns
is the only one that satisfies
the location requirements
of the facilitator.
If we don't give it our all,
we might not be able
to secure it. [LAUGHS]
Are you the organizer
of the event?
Ms. Trixie is the one
coordinating
with the facilitator.
Cheska volunteered
to help out as well.
So you'll be able
to join us, huh?
[GIGGLES]
Yes I will, Ms. Jade.
I just really need to secure
this venue
then we'll be able to proceed
with the team building!
- [CHUCKLING]
- Consider it done.
You're such an angel, Ms. Jade!
I'll have your wings cut off
so you'll never go back
to heaven.
The world needs angels like you.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
- I'll go then, Ms. Jade.
- See you, Sari.
Thank you!
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
- [JADE] Where are you?
- [PHONE CHIMES]
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE] Edward!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[JADE] Ah.
- Edward.
- What are you doing here?
Can I talk to you?
Uh... You weren't answering
my calls so...
I'm busy.
What is it about?
Um...
Luna was requesting
if it's possible
to hold our team building
at Mystic Sports.
Can you tell your associates
to reserve it to us?
That's it?
Uh...
Lu-- Luna said that you are
invited to join us!
You're part
of the promotions anyway
and because of the success
of the music festival too.
You'll join us, right?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Will...
Will Kiko be there too?
Uh...
Mm-hmm.
He'll be coming
along with his siblings.
All the core staff
of Hotel 88 will come.
Okay. Is that all?
'Cause I still...
I still got things to do.
Edward, wait.
I still haven't
thanked you properly.
Thank you for saving me.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll make it up to you
next time.
Promise.
Next time?
Can't you do it all the time?
[LAUGHS IN DISBELIEF]
[LAUGHING] What do you mean?
Why are you laughing?
I thought you'll make it
up to me.
You can't laugh.
Sorry.
You want to make it
up to me, right?
I have three wishes.
Okay, sir. Three wishes?
What are they, sir?
I'll think about it.
If you don't tell them
to me right now I might...
I might change my mind.
[LAUGHS]
Just like how
you changed your mind
during prom?
[BITTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Huh?
Edward...
It's alright, Jade.
I'm already used
to your broken promises.
[BITTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FRIDA] Just give me an update.
Always.
And Luna, you can take it easy
every now and then.
I'll do my best to do so, Ma.
[LAUGHING]
Justin, please be a good boy.
Don't make me worry, alright?
And call me if you need
someone to talk to.
I will always be
your good boy, Mom.
- [FRIDA CHUCKLES]
- Bye bye.
Bye.
Jade.
Take care of your heart.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Take care, Mom. Alright?
Yes.
[JADE LAUGHS]
I love you all so much.
I'll miss you all
but I'll be back soon.
Can I get a hug?
[LAUGHTER]
[JADE] Group hug!
[ALL GIGGLING] Mhm!
[FRIDA BREATHES DEEPLY]
[FRIDA] I have to go.
- Bye, Mom.
- I'll see you soon!
- [GIGGLES]
- Bye, Mom!
Bye!
Tell them that I'll send Mom
and Aunt Yayo to the airport
so go on ahead
to the team building.
[JADE, LUNA] Okay, Leon.
Be careful.
Bye, Mom!
We love you!
[VAN DOOR SLIDES CLOSE]
[CAR ENGINE STARTING]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[VAN DOOR SLIDING OPEN]
[STAFF, SARI] Mystical day!
Welcome to Mystic Sports!
[RAPHIE] So this is what
being welcomed feels like!
[INDISTINCT EXCITED CHATTERING]
[JEEP ENGINE REVVING]
[CHESKA] I'll bring these.
- [RAPHIE] Let me handle it!
- [CHESKA] It's okay!
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[HANDLEBAR STRETCHES]
[JEEP DOORS OPEN]
[JEEP DOORS CLOSE]
[STAFF, SARI] Mystical day!
Welcome to Mystic Sports.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHIMING, CLINKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEON] Soliman?
"Meeting with Mr. Soliman:
Cafe Lumi in Belina."
[LEON] Who is that?
Dad didn't mention
he had a new business partner.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAMERA CLICKS]
[LEON] Who did Dad meet
one week before he died?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HENRI] Sandro Soliman?
Yes, sir.
My father told me that...
he's working on a
new project on Solara Island.
So I'm here to look for him.
A project on Solara Island?
I'm not aware of
any construction there.
What kind of project was it?
He didn't mention it to me.
Shouldn't he have told you that?
Papa always travels for work.
Most of the time,
he doesn't get to tell me where.
But, sir,
no matter where
Papa ends up,
he always lets me know
he's okay.
So now that I can't reach him,
I'm scared that...
I'm scared that something
might have happened to him.
Are you scared that
your father might be dead?
Yes, sir.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[HENRI SIGHS]
Alright, come on.
Dela Paz will assist you.
We'll contact you as soon as
we get a lead on your father.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did your father mention
a place before he went missing?
He had a meeting
in the town of Belina.
Oh.
That's a different town.
Did you ask around there?
Not yet, ma'am.
A new restaurant just
opened there, Cafe Lumi.
Maybe that's the project
your father worked on.
Go check it out.
Sign here.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is treasure hunting!
- Are you ready?!
- Yes!
We will divide you
into two teams.
- Get ready! Get set! Go!
- Yes!
[ENGINE REVVING]
Sir! Sir! Aah!
Get it off!
Focus, Sari.
I need...
- Help.
- Jade.
- Move!
- [SCREAMS]