At the start, you had my heart, oh
You are my everything
Attracted to my light, poor thing
Ugh, boring!
I can't retain, don't say my name
'Cause I'm your only claim to fame
I'm too smart, too hard
Too busy, too pretty
To get caught up in…
Uh, Kitty Song-Covey. I'm on the list.
Afraid not.
No, I have to be. That's my boyfriend.
Uh-huh, I'm sure it is.
I'm not lying.
Min Ho!
Look, sorry, I can't let you in.
Especially not in that.
All the boys wanna see me
All the girls wanna be me
It ain't surprising
I'm hypnotizing
I get them so excited with a kiss
Hey. You were having a nightmare.
Yeah, I guess I was.
I love interpreting bad dreams.
Were you falling from the sky?
Naked in front of a class?
Ooh. Losing all your teeth?
Min Ho and Eunice
were making out in front of me.
Okay, it gets really dark
inside that bubbly brain of yours.
Well, last night, Min Ho said
he was going out with Marius,
but then I saw him
sneaking off with Eunice.
And they were hugging.
And not like a hello-goodbye hug.
It lingered.
Kitty, there's no way.
He's her manager. They work together.
And people hug all the time.
And besides, Min Ho's a great guy,
and he is obsessed with you.
Just trust him.
You're right. I know you're right.
Oh my God! It's Yisoo.
Like, the actual Yisoo.
She wants me to meet her at the office,
like, right now. Right now.
- Gotta hurry! Okay…
- It's Chuseok.
Don't you have, like, time off the clock?
You don't get to be a fashion legend
by taking holidays off.
Oh my God, this is amazing.
I didn't even know she knew my name.
I've never even met her before.
Well, I'm very glad she sees you,
but you are gonna make it
to Dae's dad's restaurant, right?
My imo-halmoni's coming from Bukjeon.
This might be my last chance to have
traditional Chuseok with friends and fam.
Yes, of course.
I will not miss Dae's grand opening.
Save me a seat, okay?
Kitty, don't spiral.
Go talk to your boyfriend.
HAVE A GREAT CHUSEOK
- Kitty! Hey, hey.
- Morning! You're glowing.
Oh, well, that's probably
my 13-step Korean skincare routine,
or the fact that
Jin and I said "I love you" last night.
Stop! Tell me everything!
Okay. If you must know,
I usually start with a cleansing oil.
- Then I'll go in with salicylic--
- Q?
I don't know.
We didn't plan it or anything.
We just kind of blurted it out.
That is so romantic.
Wait, so this means you got over
your little episode of Q's Anatomy
in the summer with Marius?
Oh, yeah. Water under the bridge.
Marius is ancient history.
Although he did tell me last night that
I was the reason he came back to KISS.
I know. Intense.
Damn, does that change anything?
If it did, would I be introducing Jin
to Dr. Candelaria?
Wait, whoa! Your love life is,
like, popping off right now.
I know. I'm kind of nervous.
I never introduced my mom
to my boyfriends.
She's always got high standards.
Well, I'm sure when she sees
how in love you two are,
she'll be nothing but supportive.
I hope so. God, look at us.
Happy, mature relationships.
Yes! You and me both!
See you later.
What am I going to say?
Keep it cool, Kitty.
"Where were you last night?"
Oh my God!
So sorry, Eunice.
Didn't mean to… do that.
Just set you right here.
My God, that is lifelike.
Okay, this is actually weirder
than my nightmare.
Are you stalking me, Covey?
I'm actually looking
for the Eunice Museum.
Ha-ha, very funny. Hey.
Um, how was it with Marius last night?
Yeah, about that, um…
I didn't actually end up
going out with him.
Because you were with Eunice?
I saw you two from my window.
Okay, the truth is…
I didn't want you
to figure out our secret.
I was getting her opinion
on whether or not you'd like…
this.
Happy Chuseok, Covey.
- The gift is actually inside the box.
- Right. No, no. Of course.
It's beautiful.
I'm sorry for the white lie.
You're just such a hard person
to surprise.
I don't know what to say.
I think of Chuseok
as an anniversary for us.
It's when I started
having feelings for you.
So…
What are you doing here?
Oh, I, um…
I need your help.
Jiwon texted me and said
that Imo-Halmoni canceled on tonight.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah. At the very least,
I want to call her and say happy Chuseok.
And my Korean is getting better, but…
All right, say no more.
Remember? Soon Ja-nim adores me.
Thank you.
Yisoo, it's such an honor to meet you.
Well, everyone has already left
for the Chuseok holiday.
To be honest, I'd usually give this task
to a more experienced person.
Oh, well. Desperate times.
I can handle anything.
Just leave it to me.
Good.
Ah.
Koko's sitter canceled.
I'll be back in three days.
But Koko has separation anxiety,
so don't ever leave him alone.
Keep giving him verbal affirmation.
Oh, and never make direct eye contact.
Oh, and he's vegan. Mm!
Aren't you a little angel, Koko? Mwah!
Do well!
Impress me. And who knows?
Maybe one day
you'll become my second assistant.
Koko, Mommy's leaving! Be good.
Bye!
What are you doing? Bring down my bag.
Chop-chop!
Uh…
Oh my God!
You came.
- Welcome to BoDaeGa.
- Thank you.
I thought of the name.
It's mine, my brother's
and my mom's put together.
Wow, Bora, you've grown so much!
What happened?
Yuri! Welcome!
Hello, Mr. Kim. Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's because of your family
we were able to open. I feel a little…
Oh, there’s really no reason
to feel any way.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Yes!
- I'll do it. Stay here and talk.
- Huh?
- Ah.
You got a dog?
It's my boss's.
I had to bring him
because he can't be left alone.
How could you bring a dog here
when we just passed a health inspection?
We could be shut down.
Sorry. I didn't think of that. I'll go.
No, Dae, you can't uninvite her!
And he's so cute!
Don't make eye contact.
Okay, fine.
Just promise me
you'll keep him out of sight.
Of course. Of course.
- I said, "I'll do it myself."
- Mom, don't.
I snapped that ankle back into place
with my hands
in the middle of a Thai jungle.
I'll never forget that guy's scream.
- I'll never forget that story.
- This bitch is sick.
My injury was more of a sprain.
Luckily, I didn't need surgery
because I'm also a screamer.
Huh.
Marius!
Dr. Candelaria!
I didn't know you were coming for Chuseok.
Oh, you must join us. Sit.
When Quincy first came to KISS,
he was so homesick until he met this one.
They were inseparable.
It was such a relief, especially after all
the trouble Q had at elementary school.
- Mom, please stop.
- He had to wear an eye patch.
I mean, his dad used to say,
"He really puts the 'lazy'
in the 'lazy eye.'"
- I'm sure it was very cute.
- It was not.
Well, actually, I have a photo.
- Check this.
- Oh no, we don't have to…
Look at that.
- Okay, there it is.
- Bam.
So good.
I'm sorry.
Look at this place. It's perfect.
It has to be. My dad sank
most of the settlement money into this.
Well, this is gonna be a huge success.
You have nothing to worry about.
Thanks.
Min Ho! Is Eunice coming?
Ah, she's going to be spending
the holiday with her family.
- Um, is everyone here?
- Actually, we're waiting on one more.
We are?
I don't think I can handle another setup
with Professor Vegemite.
No, no. I think you're gonna like
tonight's surprise a lot more.
Ta-da! Happy Chuseok!
I convinced her to come after all.
Halmoni…
You wouldn't come home to me,
so I had to come to you.
Hello.
Yes, yes.
Let's go.
What is going on?
The reason I said Halmoni couldn't come
is because I didn't invite her.
What? Why not?
She didn't approve of me moving to Seoul.
We had a huge fight before I left
for KISS, and we haven't spoken since.
Sorry I didn't tell you.
I didn't want you to worry.
Min Ho, why don't you tell my imo-halmoni
what a great teacher Jiwon is,
and how all the students love her.
As a teacher, Jiwon is so popular!
Mm.
If she had stayed in Bukjeon,
she'd have been an even better teacher!
Don't they have kids there?
It would've been great
to have you back at home
and see your face during the holidays.
If I went home,
I knew you'd want me to see him.
Who?
Chung-hee? The guy she's been wanting me
to marry since I was seven
because she's always trying
to control my life.
So, Quincy, you haven't told me
how you did on your midterms.
- All A's, except AP Chem, B+.
- That's like an A.
"Like an A" is not an A.
Does it really matter?
He already has a track scholarship to USC.
Track is not exactly a major.
He needs to start thinking
more practically.
He's from Bukjeon,
and he has a good family,
lots of money, and so much land!
I mean, that's great bone structure.
What? He could have a career in modeling.
I mean, why rule out any possibilities?
Why didn't you wait to see
if any Ivies were interested?
She's got a point. You know,
I think it's smart
to keep your options open.
Well, I think a full ride to USC
is an incredible accomplishment.
Halmoni,
I don't care how accomplished he is.
Chung-Hee and I are nothing!
Marius, what are your plans
for the summer?
Well, I'll be interning
at my dad's company.
You know, he's always talking about
handing it over to me someday. So…
Must be nice.
Well, finally someone
around here has a decent life plan.
I mean, you can't get into medical school
just by running fast.
Okay, all due respect,
Q was the first person
in our entire class to get into college.
- Jin, stop.
- No!
Your son is amazing
and one of the kindest people I know.
Oh my God, is Jin sexy?
I am beyond proud of him.
And you should be too.
I thought you'd get tired
of Seoul in a month,
then come back home where you belong.
I have to live my life,
not the life you want for me.
My goodness.
This mandu is delicious.
Yummy.
Sorry to interrupt.
Hope you're enjoying your food.
Opening a restaurant with my dad
was my mom's dream,
but she never thought we could afford it.
And now we can.
But really, it's our love for her
that made everything possible.
She always believed in us, no matter what.
What better way to honor her
than gathering us all here together?
My mom would be so proud.
Happy Chuseok!
Mom would be so proud of you, Dad.
I will do my best.
At least someone's mom
would be proud of them. Must be nice!
Jiwon, I'm so sorry. This is all my fault.
No, it's not. Uh…
Halmoni's not gonna be happy
unless I follow her exact plans
for my life.
I'm gonna go now.
No, uh, wait. What if I talk to her?
Like, matchmaker to matchmaker.
Kitty, you of all people
know how stubborn she is.
She didn't speak to her own sister
for 50 years.
This isn't your problem to solve.
Well, so much for checking off
a traditional family Chuseok
from my Sunset List.
In my experience,
this is how they usually end.
You still get to cross it off your list.
Well, at least I got to spend it with you.
Min Ho!
Are you okay?
No, they followed me
all the way from my parents' house.
That was insane. I'm gonna call my dad,
tell him we need security.
Eunice, are you okay?
Mm.
Oh my God, it's really you?
Can I get a picture with you?
Yeah. Of course.
- Kitty, would you mind?
- Of course.
Oh, I love your necklace. Where's it from?
- Uh, Min Ho got it for me.
- Oh, he's the best, isn't he?
It's happening. My unofficial
Eunice merch has gone viral on TikTok.
And I'm already sold out of these.
- Wow.
- Welcome to the Eunice K-Popalypse.
Ooh. Yuri, can I get a photo
of Koko with the plushie?
I'd love to create a frenzy.
Fine, but his fee is crazy high.
Girl…
Wait. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Oh my God, the dog is gone.
What?
Oh my God.
Ugh. You're so fired.
No, I cannot screw this up
for Dae and his dad. I promised.
- This night's so important for them.
- Breathe.
He has to be here somewhere.
- You check the back, I'll check in here.
- Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Koko! Koko! Koko! Koko!
I tried to talk to my parents about it,
but I couldn't.
Honestly, I couldn't speak.
I have no idea how to begin to tell them.
I'm so scared
they'll be disappointed in me.
What am I going to do? I'm so scared.
No.
Listen carefully.
You're not alone, okay?
I'm responsible too.
But listen.
You can't tell anyone about this.
If anyone finds out, we're done!
It's okay.
Oh my God.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Wait. Did anyone
in the restaurant see him?
No. I lured him out
from under that table with this.
Oh no. You've given this gremlin
a taste for flesh?
I am so sorry.
Honestly, thank you so much.
I owe you big time.
If you ever need anything,
I'm your first call.
Good to know. 'Cause I'm pretty sure
you're still my emergency contact, so…
Um, will you excuse me just one second?
We need to talk.
- When did you get a dog?
- Nice necklace.
Okay, I just overheard
the weirdest conversation…
Are you okay, Eunice?
Yeah.
Why wouldn't I be?
Okay, I think you were right all along.
Min Ho and Eunice
are definitely hiding something.
I know. He said she helped pick
this necklace. She didn't recognize it.
He said whatever it is, it's big enough
that it could end Eunice's career.
Oh no. Koko, don't eat that.
Oh no. No. Ew. Ugh.
Wait. Is this a…
A… pregnancy test.
A positive one.
What exactly did you hear them say?
See you back at the dorm.
Mm-hmm.
Kitty, you all right?
Is Eunice pregnant?
- How did you know?
- It doesn't matter. Is it true?
Yes.
When did it happen? Over the summer?
I don't know. When we were in Paris.
Look, okay, no one knows, all right?
Eunice's career would be over.
My… career would be over.
I saw you two hugging last night,
and it didn't look just friendly.
Kitty, what--
And supposedly she helped
pick out this necklace?
She's never even seen it before.
Yes, I lied about--
Yes, you did lie!
You said you didn't hook up last summer,
and I believed you!
- I didn't!
- I trusted you, Min Ho!
You got our friend pregnant?
Friend pregnant?
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Kitty!
Hey, want a mocktail?
You okay? What happened?
Min Ho said that he didn't hook up with
anyone last summer, but he was lying.
And not just about that.
I don't know if I can get over this.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know if I could either.
How'd you get over
what happened with Q and Marius?
- I mean, it's not the same, but…
- What are you talking about?
- Never mind.
- Kitty?
No, Jin, wait! I…
What happened between you and Marius?
- What do you mean?
- Kitty told me something happened.
- Okay, it's not a big deal.
- Tell me what happened, Q.
Jin, please, not right now.
Tell me!
It was before you came to USC,
and it was stupid. It was just a photo.
You know what they say.
A picture's worth a thousand words.
Jin, wait! Wait, don't--
Oh my God.
Oh! Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Are you okay? Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Jin! What is wrong with you?
He only sent me one picture!
You?
Quin…
Jin. Jin, wait.
Jin, wait. Can we please just talk?
I thought that you told him.
I didn't think I had
to worry about you bringing it up!
- I didn't think it'd be a big deal if--
- Kitty, just stay away from me!
So, I guess Marius was
more than just your roommate?
I don't even know why I sent that pic.
Jin loves me,
and I love him.
Marius has been playing games
since the day we met.
Well, my doctorate
isn't in psychology, but…
maybe there's a reason
why you're attracted to people
who don't treat you so well.
You know, I failed my, uh, chem final,
first year of college.
Yeah. I stayed in bed all week.
You never told me that.
The pressure got to me.
Being pre-med,
being my immigrant parents' only child.
I mean, they never told me
they were proud of me.
I guess they were afraid
I would stop trying.
I don't always show it,
but, um, for the record,
your whole life,
I've never not been proud of you.
Even tonight?
Even tonight.
And I am so sorry
if I made you feel otherwise.
But Jin…
Jin cares more about you
than what I think of him.
And that's…
That's the kind of love you deserve.
Come here.
So, you think Min Ho and Eunice hooked up?
- He said it happened in Paris.
- That's impossible.
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you this.
I know how you feel about her,
so I felt like you deserved to know.
No, I mean,
it's, like, literally impossible.
I was with Eunice
the whole time she was in Paris.
What? What are you talking about?
When the settlement came through,
my dad gave me some
to spend on whatever I wanted.
So I bought a plane ticket
and surprised Eunice.
And Min Ho doesn't know that. Nobody does.
Did you sleep with her?
I'm sorry. It's not my business, but…
Right now, this is important.
Yes, I did.
But after we came back to school,
she started acting
like it never even happened.
Oh my God.
Min Ho is protecting her.
Protecting her? From what?
I'm sorry. I can't tell you.
But I do think you need to talk to Eunice.
I don't know.
She's too much of a big star now.
People saw one paparazzi photo
of her coming into this place,
and now we're booked out for a month.
Wow, that's great news
for you and your dad.
But regarding Eunice…
sometimes things are
more complicated than they seem.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
Honestly, after Paris…
I stopped having my period.
Min Ho thinks I was with Tae-Oh,
but obviously I was only with you.
If you're saying
what I think you're saying,
let's do this together.
We can even get married if we need to.
No, Dae, it's not like that.
I'm not pregnant.
Are you sure?
Mm.
For a while, I thought that I was.
But that wasn't the case.
When I came home tonight,
I started my period.
I guess I was so stressed.
The paparazzi always following me,
fans always wanting something from me…
Honestly, I was so scared.
I felt like I couldn't breathe.
Dae, I just
want to go back
to the way things used to be.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
I got everything so wrong.
Why did you not just tell me the truth?
Because I gave Eunice my word.
I didn't expect my own girlfriend
would believe the worst of me.
I know.
I think that I spent my whole summer
watching you with all these fancy people,
and doing these fancy things,
and it made me question if I would
ever really fit… in your big, fancy world.
So I got in my head.
Like you did with Gigi.
Like you did with Marius.
You know, I get it now.
It's not that you don't trust me.
It's that you've never trusted me.
No, no, that's not true--
I've done everything…
to show you how I feel about you.
I've given you every reason
for you to believe in me.
But the problem isn't me, it's you.
We're done.
No, I…
Min Ho…
Please record your message.
LJ. I need to talk to you.
I've messed everything up.
I don't know what to do.
It's killing me
Fear is holding me down
But I wanna be sure
I will burst through the crowd
Screaming for this man
If I got this with you