[somber music playing]
[door opens]
Covey.
- What are you doing here?
- I need to tell you something.
Wait, me first.
I understand why you shut me down
when I tried talking to you about Stella.
So when you accused me
of just being jealous, I--
- Okay...
- [dreamy music playing]
You were right.
- About what part?
- All of it.
[sighs]
Stella is some kind of evil mastermind,
and she never really liked me.
Min Ho...
And I was in denial about Stella because
I was trying to convince myself
that I was over you,
but the truth is, I'm not.
And I know you said
it can never work out, but
do you still feel that way?
I don't know.
Yes, you do, Covey.
[tender music swells]
- Kitty!
- [yelps]
[panting]
What were you dreaming about?
[nervously] Calculus.
[whimsical music playing]
Wow.
- Didn't know you were that into math.
- [quietly] Yeah.
[inhales sharply]
- [door closes]
- I don't even take calculus.
[bright music plays]
- [school bell rings]
- [music fades]
[Q] Yeah, I've said it before
and I'll say it again,
sex dreams mean something.
It was not a sex dream, you little weirdo.
Only because Stella woke you up.
Babe, we've been here before.
Okay? You had a sex dream about Yuri
last semester. Remember?
Also not a sex dream. [scoffs]
I don't know.
It's kind of giving repression.
I'm not repressing anything.
I mean, I told you about it. Did I not?
[sighs] Things with Min Ho and I are just...
They're complicated right now.
So you don't have
any feelings for him, like, at all?
I... just miss him.
I mean, he's barely said two words to me
since I talked to him about Stella.
Probably should've waited till I had proof
before I showed him that video,
but I wanted to be there for him the way
he's been there for me all semester.
God, I wish
I never gave Stella his number.
[growls playfully]
[both laugh]
[Kitty] Isn't it kinda late
for prom-posals?
The Cherry Blossom Ball
is literally on Saturday.
Yeah. That's what I'm saying.
But have you decided yet
if you're gonna go?
[Kitty] Yeah, solo.
What about you and Jin?
I know he's kind of
being bratty about regionals.
He apologized.
And he said he's really proud of me.
I'm really glad.
I want things to work out with you two.
Me too.
What's with the face?
- ["Next to You" playing]
- ♪ Wanna be next to you ♪
♪ Do what others do... ♪
[Kitty giggles]
[laughs] What?
Q, I'm doing everything in my power
to heal up and ditch the scooter
so I can slow dance with you.
Go to the ball with me?
Yeah.
[romantic pop music swells]
- I helped him organize--
- You're ruining it.
[quietly] Sorry.
[squeals]
[both chuckle]
["Cherish" by Aimers playing]
♪ Yeah ♪
[Kitty] When Dae and I were long-distance,
I went to plenty of school dances solo.
So why does this one feel so hard?
Maybe it's because the semester's
almost over and I'm leaving soon.
Or... maybe...
- ♪ Let's cherish ♪
- ♪ Cherish ♪
[song continues in Korean]
- ♪ Let's cherish ♪
- ♪ Cherish ♪
- Min Ho!
- [music cuts out]
[giggles]
Stella, will you be my--
Yes! Yes! A thousand times, yes! [giggles]
[chuckles softly]
[whimsical music playing]
These are so pretty. [chuckles]
[quietly] I'm not jealous.
I'm not jealous. I'm not jealous.
- [cell phone vibrates]
- [gasps]
[Kitty] Right. Forget romance.
I've got a family to reunite
before the year's over.
[Jiwon] I'm gonna be real with you, Kitty.
I've heard some pretty bad stuff
about your side of the family.
Like what?
Halmoni said that your halmoni
was the little sister
who did whatever she wanted.
She ran off with
some terrible boy to America
and left my halmoni alone
to take care of their parents.
That cannot be true.
My halaboji is a total sweetheart.
What did your halmoni say, then?
She didn't... say anything.
I didn't know that your side of the family
existed until a few months ago.
[scoffs]
But, Simon, your dad,
wrote to my mom about the feud.
And they worked together to end it
up until my mom died.
She passed away when I was three.
I had no idea.
- Both my parents are gone.
- [somber music playing]
Car accident when I was ten.
Halmoni raised me after that.
I guess there were a lot of secrets.
[waitress speaking Korean]
[speaks Korean]
- [Kitty] Thank you.
- [scoffs]
I wish I'd known about you.
But now we do.
And we could finish
what our parents started?
I just need another chance
with your halmoni.
Well, I take her to the market
every Saturday.
[Moon] Come on, Joon Ho.
Don't raise your voice.
You need to rest your vocal chords.
No, I told you. That's not possible.
Oy.
- Hey.
- [grunts]
What's up, Team Dae?
Your co-manager's here.
Less than two weeks till the contest.
How we feeling?
Actually, pretty good.
Oh, and did either of you get an email
from Mr. Moon's assistant?
About submitting final choreo
for approval? Already taken care of.
Thank you, Kitty.
Exciting news! My superstar son,
Joon Ho, will be performing this summer,
and I have decided that the winner
of my contest will be his opening act.
[students murmur]
[Moon] In the biz, we call it synergy.
Oh my goodness! That's amazing.
With that in mind,
today we'll be focusing on media training.
It only takes one awkward pause
on a gotcha question to be #canceled.
Sample questions are here.
I'm the king of awkward pauses.
Don't worry about it.
You've got this, and we've got you.
Thanks.
I'll grab the sample questions.
We got this, don't we?
[whimsical music playing]
[quietly] Yes, Kitty, we do.
Um... [sighs]
Uh, sorry. What was the question?
Where did you learn to sing?
Mm.
I didn't.
Okay.
Next question.
What's your relationship status?
Well... Eunice said yes
to my prom-posal, so--
[Min Ho] Obviously. You're a catch.
But you might want to keep this vague.
Fans like to think that you're single.
Oh.
[pensive music playing]
- [Moon] You're a star, Eunice. Great job.
- [Eunice] Thank you.
- [sighs]
- [school bell rings]
Min Ho, you cannot still be mad at me
for showing you that video of Stella.
That wasn't Stella.
And yes, you were way out of line.
Or I'm right,
and you're in a fake relationship
and your family is in danger.
You sound absolutely mad.
You know that, right?
Listen, until you can admit
you're wrong about Stella,
you and I have nothing to talk about.
[somber music playing]
- [Stella] Can I talk to you?
- Always.
I'm thinking about
entering the singing contest.
What? Seriously?
But you don't even like singing.
You had a meltdown over karaoke
at my dad's place.
That was just stage fright.
And this will be the perfect opportunity
to help me get over it.
[sighs] But the contestant deadline
passed weeks ago.
I know. But I'm hoping you could ask
your dad to make an exception for me?
Um...
I'll even record an audition video
so you can show him.
Doing a huge summer tour
with your family would be such a gift.
But you can totally say no.
I would never ever want to put you
in an awkward position with your dad.
Well, I mean, I doubt I'd even be
speaking to him if it weren't for you, so...
All right. Consider it done.
Thank you. [giggles]
[tense music playing]
[in Korean] We're not going
to all of these stores, are we?
We could, why?
I have school work to do.
[in English] Dae,
you're up against Eunice.
Okay? Your outfit needs to slay.
Plus, it's on me.
[in Korean] Hello.
Hey, I found my outfit.
Hey, are you kidding?
This is important.
We have to make you look cool.
Thanks for going out of your way
to help me.
It's better to have something
to distract myself from the breakup.
Are you going to the ball tonight?
I haven't decided yet.
If you decide to go, I think it'll be okay
if you come with me and Eunice.
Thanks, but I don't think
she'd be okay with it.
Isn't it weird having your girlfriend
as your rival?
Well, it's a little weird, but...
I really like Eunice.
Congrats.
Even though it's a bit unexpected.
But we're not as different as I thought.
Did you know she only pretends to be rich?
[Yuri] Hey, that's for right now.
With her level of ambition,
she will be rich for sure.
What do you mean?
You know I like Eunice, right?
But you have to win this for your dad.
So don't forget that your girlfriend
is also your main competition.
All right?
["Noiza" playing]
[upbeat pop music continues]
[in English] Oh, hey, Min Ho.
Hello.
[energetic pop music fades]
What's that?
Oh, it's for Jin.
Before the dance tonight,
I thought he might want some of
my lola's special Filipino healing broth.
It's got calamansi, coconut vinegar,
bagoong, pickled green papaya, natto oil--
Oy, that's potent.
- Okay.
- [coughs]
Jin must really like you
to drink all that.
[scoffs]
Oh, that might be him.
He's coming over early to get ready.
No, it's Kitty. She's on her way to meet
Soon Ja and Jiwon at Gwangiang Market.
- Oh.
- I'm surprised she managed all that.
Her great-aunt wasn't exactly welcoming.
Seeing as how this is more like an ambush,
let's keep our fingers crossed.
Like how she ambushed me
at the track meet?
Tell her it's a bad idea.
Or... you could.
Look, I know Kitty's
Stella conspiracies are out there,
but she's just looking out for you.
I don't need Kitty looking out for me.
Or pitying me.
[exhales slowly]
- [sighs]
- It's just humiliating, okay?
Like how she rejected me on the plane.
Do you know how that felt?
After I put myself out there?
It's not something I do.
What do you feel for her now?
- [gloomy music playing]
- [sighs]
I moved on. With Stella.
Where are you going?
You didn't answer my question!
- ["Over and Over" playing]
- ♪ But I still gotta let you know ♪
- [song continues in Korean]
- [excited chatter]
♪ Over and over ♪
[song continues in Korean]
[in Korean] Oh, those tomatoes look good.
How much are those?
8,000 won. It says so right there.
Oh, goodness! Your tomatoes
don't even look that good.
6,000 won! 6,000 won!
Come on, sell me these ones at a discount.
[whimsical music playing]
[in English] Hey,
just let me get that for you.
[in Korean] What are you doing here?
You think I can't buy a tomato?
Hey, I have money!
Who are you to come all the way
down here to humiliate me?
This is hilarious. Just give me 7,000 won.
What 7,000 won...
This grandma is a vegetable expert.
Please give it to her for 6,000 won.
[in English] What are you doing?
Making sure you don't mess this up.
[in Korean] No.
5,000 won is enough. 5,000 won, here.
5,000 won is enough, right?
You heard her, right?
Please give it to her for 5,000 won.
Thank you.
No... But why are you helping her?
Ah, she's lacking a lot,
but she has some strengths.
Her Korean's a mess! I can't listen to it.
Oh no, it's more than a mess.
But she's been trying.
[great-aunt] Hmm.
[chuckles]
Hey, I need you to hold this!
- [in English] She says hold the bag.
- Oh, yeah.
[in Korean] Let's go buy some vegetables.
[gentle music playing]
[Jiwon] Look, Grandma!
[in English] "Love, Simon."
[in Korean] Dad reached out
to Aunt Eve first.
They bought plane tickets to Korea.
Even Great-Aunt Young Ja.
[gasps]
My sister...
was going to come home?
[gasps, sobs]
[Jiwon] Grandma. What's wrong?
Young Ja was our family's youngest.
She was outspoken and rebellious.
But because I was the older sister,
I always felt responsible
and took care of her.
Except... once...
Back then, I told my mother and father
Young Ja was sneaking around...
with your grandfather.
They disowned her.
I thought that was right at the time.
Because she was supposed to marry a boy
my parents had already chosen for her.
She was meant to stay in Bukjeon.
My sister left because I betrayed her.
From then on, we lost touch.
[sniffles]
All this time,
I thought Young Ja had forgotten about me.
Oh, Grandma,
but you see it wasn't like that.
Now that you know the truth,
would you like to see her?
[shakily] Mm-hmm.
[in English] I'll explain later,
but do you think you can convince
your halmoni to give mine one more chance?
[sighs]
Yes, I... I'll find a way.
- [sighs, chuckles]
- [grandmother crying]
[whimsical music playing]
[Kitty] Stella?
- [Juliana] Hey.
- Hey, Juliana.
You said you saw Stella
coming out of an Internet cafe
on the same day MoonLeaks dropped, right?
Yeah, uh, PC Bang. Why?
Because she's there again,
and I'm about to catch her red-handed.
Okay, good luck.
[Kitty clears throat] Stella?
Kitty? What are you doing here?
[Kitty] More like,
what are you doing here?
I'm about to Zoom with the Pepper Pike
Youth Group from my church.
Why not do that from the dorm?
'Cause I know you and Juliana
make fun of me
for being a homeschooled church girl.
Don't you both call me the Ohio Weirdo?
I know you're lying.
Fine.
So for Pepper Pike Youth Group retreat,
we're gonna go to the church in the...
- [mutes audio]
- What did you think I was doing?
Nothing. I...
Never mind.
[Kitty] Oh my God,
do I have this all wrong?
Hey, guys.
Esther! What a blessed surprise
to have you pop in.
I actually go by Stella now. See ya.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Moon sighs] I don't know, Min Ho.
[Min Ho] You just watched her video.
She's got a great voice.
[Moon] Yeah, but
with only a week to prepare...
[Min Ho] She'll pull it off.
I believe in her.
[Moon] All right, I trust your judgment.
She's in.
[Min Ho] Thank you.
- ["Illusion" by Dua Lipa playing]
- ♪ I've been known to miss a red flag ♪
♪ I've been known to put
My lover on a pedestal... ♪
[excited chatter]
- Shall we?
- [Yuri] Yes.
But I'm only gonna stay here
15 minutes, tops.
[giggles] I'm glad you're here.
[Eunice gasps]
[Yuri] Whoa!
♪ I could do this dance all night ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ What you doin'? ♪
♪ Don't know who you think
That you're confusin'♪
♪ I be like, "Ooh, it's amusin' ♪
♪ You think I'm gonna fall
For an illusion... ♪
Hey, you doing okay?
Just looking for Min Ho.
I wanna thank him
for helping me with my family stuff.
I also owe him an apology.
I think I was wrong about Stella.
Q, come on.
Come dance with us.
That's sweet, but go have fun.
I'm gonna go get a weird mocktail.
[chuckles] Okay.
- [sighs]
- ["Got Me Started" playing]
♪ He's got the personality ♪
♪ Not even gravity
Could ever hold him down ♪
It's a good song, right?
♪ He's got the sexuality of a man... ♪
[groans]
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Ugh, I wanted
to do better than this for you.
I think lola's healing broth is a placebo.
- [both chuckle]
- Stop. You are perfect.
[sighs]
[both] Oh.
- [Yuri] Go ahead.
- Uh, no, you can have it.
I don't even know what these are.
Blossomitas.
Did you just say "blossomitas"?
Yeah, Mihee and Madison
worked really hard on curating the menu.
[sighs, chuckles]
You look really nice, Yuri.
Thank you. You too.
[quietly] Thanks.
[inhales sharply]
["B2b" by Charli xcx playing]
♪ I don't wanna go back, back to ♪
♪ Back to, back to, back to, back to you ♪
♪ I don't wanna fall right back to us ♪
♪ Maybe you should run right back to her
I don't wanna go back, back to ♪
♪ Back to, back to, back to, back to you
I don't wanna go back... ♪
- [Mihee] Kimchi! [laughs]
- [snaps photo]
[Mihee] Aw, you guys.
Who'd ever think you two
are in a K-Pop battle to the death, right?
[chuckles]
So what are you guys gonna say
if any reporters ask
if you guys are dating?
- I have a boy... friend.
- I am single.
Kidding! [laughs awkwardly]
Let's just...
I'm sorry. I just assumed that--
You make a lot of assumptions about me.
Dae, of course I want to win.
But not enough to lie.
You lie to everyone about being rich.
That's... That is different.
Yeah, 'cause I didn't judge you for it
the way you're judging me right now.
Maybe we are too different.
- ["Picture You" by Chappell Roan playing]
- [scoffs] Cool.
Now I don't have to feel bad
when I mop the floor with you.
♪ Every night ♪
♪ Both lips on the mirror ♪
♪ It's ritualistic ♪
♪ Counting lipstick stains ♪
♪ Where you should be ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I need you around ♪
♪ I'm getting close now ♪
♪ Do you picture me like I picture you? ♪
♪ Am I in the frame
From your point of view? ♪
♪ Do you feel the same? ♪
- [chimes ringing]
- ♪ I'm too scared to say ♪
♪ Half of the things I do ♪
♪ When I picture you... ♪
- There you are. Where's Stella?
- [chuckles]
I'm not sure.
She's supposed to meet me here.
Something about a hair appointment
that went long.
[Q] Hmm. [clicks tongue]
Well, while you're waiting,
I know someone who could use a dance.
The semester's almost over,
which means she goes back to Portland.
For good, this time.
♪ I need you around ♪
♪ I'm getting close now ♪
♪ Do you picture me like I picture you... ♪
[Min Ho] Covey.
You look...
pathetic.
- [chuckles]
- Hmm.
- You too.
- [Min Ho scoffs]
Come on, let's dance.
What? Why would we do that?
Because we're at a dance, silly.
And I know you love this song.
I remember you singing this off-key
in the shower once.
[Min Ho sighs]
Thank you for today.
I got through to my great-aunt
because of you.
I know you would have done it without me.
I also have something else
I need to tell you.
I was wrong about Stella.
[softly] I am so sorry.
- [scoffs]
- [Kitty] Also...
I miss you.
♪ Half of the things I do ♪
- ♪ When I picture you ♪
- [Stella] Min Ho!
[dramatic music swells]
- ["Secrets in Your Head" playing]
- ♪ How many silhouettes on the wall? ♪
♪ How many stars are forgotten and fall? ♪
♪ Caught in all the lies again ♪
♪ Running circles 'round your head ♪
♪ How many shadows are trying to see? ♪
♪ All that you bury and hide underneath ♪
♪ Caught in all the lies again
Running circles... ♪
You don't mind if I dance
with my boyfriend, do you, Kitty?
No, of course not. [chuckles nervously]
♪ Oh, oh... ♪
- Hey.
- [softly] Hey.
[Min Ho clears throat]
You surprised?
You look different.
I hope that's a compliment.
I figured, if I'm gonna be
in the competition,
I should try a new look.
♪ Don't close your eyes... ♪
[Stella] Min Ho?
- ♪ Secrets in your head ♪
- [song fades]
[crying] But beauty
is supposed to come from within!
Why are you staring at me like that?
♪ In a moment... ♪
Beauty is supposed to come from within.
- ["Secrets in Your Head" fades out]
- What did you say?
[tense music playing]
Nothing. Uh...
- Excuse me.
- I wouldn't make a scene if I were you.
Not with the dirt I've got.
So Kitty was right.
You used me, to get what?
Revenge on my dad?
Can you blame me?
He's a monster.
My original plan
was to destroy his empire.
But when I heard about the tour
with Joon Ho, I had an epiphany.
You know what they say.
If you can't beat them, join them, right?
- Your dad's gonna make me a star.
- [Min Ho chuckles]
And you're gonna help.
Now, why would I do that?
'Cause if you don't,
I'll make sure the world finds out
that your dad is shipping off
a poor, poor backup dancer
that Joon Ho knocked up.
How--
I've got lots of insurance policies
to make sure things go my way.
Like the evidence I planted
on Kitty's laptop
to frame her for MoonLeaks.
You dare touch Kitty--
Hopefully, I won't have to.
But that's up to you.
[tense music swells]
Now keep dancing. And make it look good.
["Drama" by Aespa playing]
[Kitty] I still don't trust Stella.
But I also can't trust myself.
'Cause I am jealous.
I have fallen for Min Ho.
A little bit.
Or a lot.
♪ I bring, I bring
All the dra-ma-ma-ma-ma ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ I bring dra-ma-ma-ma-ma ♪
♪ With my girls in the back ♪
- ♪ Girls in the back ♪
- ♪ Drama ♪
♪ Dra-ma-ma-ma-ma
I break trau-ma-ma-ma-ma ♪
♪ With my world in the back ♪
[song continues in Korean]
♪ Dra-ma-ma-ma-ma ♪
♪ Break that trau-ma-ma-ma-ma ♪
♪ With my girls in the back
Girls in the back, yeah ♪
♪ I break trau-ma-ma-ma-ma ♪
♪ Trau-ma-ma-ma-ma ♪
♪ With my world in the back ♪
[song continues in Korean]
[dramatic pop song ends]