"My world got so much bigger
because of you and because of Simon."
[sighs] Jina has to know
something about Simon.
Why else would my mom
mention him in her letter?
I mean,
Yuri emailed her mom to ask, right?
Yeah, but Jina's at some wellness retreat
and doesn't have any service.
[sighs] It is killing me to be this close
to finding the guy
that my mom was so in love with
that she moved here
against her parents' wishes.
I always thought
my mom was this perfect daughter.
Those are the only stories
that I ever heard.
[sighs] I guess when someone passes,
you kind of forget their flaws.
Well, this is the first time that
my mom actually feels like a real person.
[Q chuckles]
I have to find Simon.
He can tell me things about her
that nobody else can.
[laughter and indistinct chatter outside]
I guess Yuri and Juliana
are still in their honeymoon phase, huh?
They're always tickle-fighting.
I tear them apart for curfew so the RA
doesn't figure out they're a couple.
Doesn't that bother you?
Oh, not at all!
Their squeals of joy
act as a helpful reminder
for me to stay focused on my goals.
It'll get rid of this silly crush--
- [alarm chimes]
- Thank God. [sighs]
Okay, you guys, break it up!
Ten minutes until curfew check!
- [Yuri and Juliana] Thanks, Kitty!
- [bright music playing]
I love the smell of your shampoo.
What is it? Like, jasmine?
Ooh, yes.
You're really gonna subject yourself
to an entire semester of that?
You know what they say.
What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, right?
Right. [takes a deep breath]
Something's telling me
this is just killing you, though. So...
[clicks tongue]
- Good night.
- Night.
[Yuri] Kitty!
You're always hiding out in your room.
Come hang out with us.
Yeah, come distract us.
Otherwise, an RA
might walk in and catch us making out.
- [Yuri] Oh!
- [chuckles] Uh, sure.
Well, we have to remember,
no making out unless we're
in the bedroom with the doors closed.
Suddenly, I'm just feeling so, so sleepy.
- Right? Come on.
- [Yuri] Oh, okay.
- [whispers] Sorry.
- Uh, actually, Yuri, quick question.
Yeah? What's up?
Um, have you heard anything
from Jina about my mom's letter?
Oh, sorry. Nothing yet.
Really? Nothing?
I mean, the wellness retreat
is supposed to be off the grid.
Right. Well, maybe if you give me the name
of the retreat, I could try and call them?
[Juliana] Babe! You comin'?
Yep, in a second. [inhales sharply]
- What about you? You going to bed?
- Soon.
I'm gonna wait for Stella to get home.
She's on her big date with Min Ho.
[Yuri] You're always matchmaking
other people.
When are you gonna find
someone you wanna be with?
- [exhales]
- [Yuri] Well, don't worry, Kitty.
We will find you someone.
- ["Fireworks" by Aimers playing]
- ♪ Fireworks ♪
[gentle chimes ringing]
♪ Every time I close my eyes... ♪
Good night.
[Yuri] I'm comin'.
[Kitty] Q's right.
This is definitely going to kill me.
[groans]
- [pop music fades]
- Wow, Korean horror movies are intense!
My parents would definitely think
that was the work of the devil.
You barely watched it.
You spent most of the film
with your head buried in my chest.
[laughs] Is that why you picked it?
Min Ho, are you trying to corrupt me?
Um...
[whimsical music playing]
[Min Ho] I'm just not that into Stella.
[Kitty] Wait, really?
Yeah. I mean, she's cute.
Don't get me wrong.
But maybe she's a bit too... nice?
Is this where you're the playboy
wanting to corrupt the good girl,
and you're just mad
because you're not getting anywhere?
Please give me a little credit.
[sighs] I just think she's boring.
And why are you so focused
on my love life anyway, Covey?
[imitating accent] I'm not.
I actually miss
the two of you bickering like this.
How am I the only one
who's irritated by her?
It's Kitty's fault that we're cleaning
this building for my dad's vanity project.
Guys, there could be
way worse punishments.
Like your dad forcing everyone
to take one of his arts electives.
Except for me. Your boy got an exemption.
The star of KISS's track team needs
to focus on getting gold at regionals.
I'm taking Entertainment Management.
Kind of sounds interesting.
Me too. It's the only one
without singing or dancing.
I signed up for Advanced Voice.
You sing? How did I not know this?
We were long-distance, and it's weird
to serenade someone over the phone.
I think we should hear something.
Now, like, here?
- No, next year.
- Yes.
- I wanna hear it.
- Yes. Now.
♪ Demons'll charm you ♪
♪ With a smile ♪
♪ For a while ♪
♪ But in time ♪
This is a punishment for secretly
living with Ms. Covey last semester.
No fun!
Okay, kids, you're dismissed.
My cleaning crew will take care of it.
Wait. You can't overrule me
on student matters.
Renovations must begin today
to stay on schedule,
unless you also want my donation delayed.
Students, you're dismissed.
For today.
- [footsteps fade]
- [group chuckles]
I've never seen anyone talk
to Professor Lee like that.
- I mean, he kind of ate. [laughs]
- [giggles] Mr. Moon forever!
[laughs] Oh.
You have an amazing voice.
- I would've loved being serenaded by you.
- Thanks.
But... now we can be karaoke buddies.
[softly] Bye.
[cheeky music playing]
[music fades out]
- [whistle blows]
- [Q grunts]
[Dae sighs]
[exhales]
How was that, Dae?
Was I faster off the block?
Looked kinda slow to me.
- [tense music playing]
- [Dae sighs]
I hate Jin.
You know he used to steal
my lunch money in grade school?
And Min Ho's hair products?
- Yeah, he's a toxic alpha male.
- [Jin] Hey, Q?
Remember how Coach Alex said
to picture something amazing
waiting for us at the finish line?
Bet I can guess what you're imagining.
Is it... a rainbow unicorn?
And you're picturing what?
A cheeseburger... with boobs?
No. You crying like a little baby
after I beat you tomorrow
and take the spot at regionals.
There's no way he's taking my spot.
- Hey.
- [music fades]
You okay?
Yeah, I was just thinking about Kitty,
how she called me "buddy" earlier today.
I hate that this kind of thing
still takes over my brain.
I get it.
It takes a while to get over someone.
Is there anything we can do
to speed it up? [sighs]
I was gonna take tonight
to rest before tomorrow's race, but, uh...
I think I know a way
we both can clear our heads.
Hi. Could you connect me
to Jina Lim's room?
She's a guest at your resort.
Oh. My mistake. She must be staying
at another property. Thank you.
Hey. Do you know who our teacher is?
I'm just glad I won't have to perform.
I'm still scarred from playing
the donkey in my church's Nativity play.
But I'm guessing with your dad,
you'll have a record deal,
blockbuster movie out soon?
Yeah, not my thing.
- [energetic music playing]
- Good afternoon.
Oh my gosh.
And congratulations.
Out of all the new arts courses
offered at KISS,
you lucky few
have stumbled into a masterclass.
But I have some news for you.
Being a successful manager...
isn't something one can teach.
Then why is this a class?
[Moon] It comes down to trusting your gut.
And today, you will determine
who will earn a spot in Advanced Voice,
and who will get their mic cords cut.
Uh, Mr. Moon, I don't know enough
about singing to be an effective--
Knowledge is overrated.
My strongest opinions
are on things I know almost nothing about.
[Praveena chuckles]
And that's my dad.
[Moon] Let's bring in
the aspiring singers.
♪ Being close and being clever ♪
♪ Ain't like being true ♪
[Moon] Okay, next.
[singing in Korean]
♪ Super shy, super shy ♪
♪ But wait a minute
While I make you mine ♪
♪ Make you mine ♪
[singing in Korean]
♪ You're on my mind ♪
[shudders]
[tense music playing]
[footsteps fade]
[belting out operatic vocals]
[out of tune] ♪ I'm staying ♪
♪ And you, and you, and you ♪
♪ You're gonna love me ♪
Dae Kim received unanimous approval.
Though Min Ho did note
he was a bit pitchy.
Dude, seriously?
I agree. In fact, Min Ho and I had
identical feedback for each singer.
Stella, you were
the only student who voted for Mihee.
- Why?
- I didn't want to hurt her feelings.
It's hurtful to let someone with no talent
believe they have what it takes.
My son is right.
Those who feel the urge
to sugarcoat the truth
will never make it in this business.
[bell rings]
[Min Ho] Okay.
Hey, it's just the first day.
It's not that. It's Min Ho.
It feels like he's lost interest in me.
[sighs] I was stupid to think
I ever had a chance with a playboy.
No. I... I mean, yes, he is a playboy,
but he's also a good guy.
If it doesn't work out between you two,
that's his loss. Just be yourself.
See you later.
[upbeat pop music playing]
[Praveena] Kitty Cat.
Hi.
Praveena. Don't tell me
you forgot my name.
Oh, of course not. Don't tell me
that you forgot. We're old friends.
[laughs] That's right.
Thank you
for reminding me of our origin story.
So there's this great DJ playing tonight
at this teen queer club in Itaewon.
Do you want to go?
Like, with you?
Yes. Unless you don't date girls.
No. No, I do. [chuckles]
I... I want to.
Um... would love to go with you.
Great.
Thank you! Thank you, thank you.
I got into Advanced Voice.
- You did?
- Yeah.
Well, I thought I blew my audition,
but your dad said
your critique inspired him to keep me.
[clicks tongue]
Did he?
- [intense music playing]
- [Moon] Hmm.
[Min Ho] Dad.
Oh, Min Ho, my star student.
Come look at these plans. I keep telling
my architect to make my name bigger.
So, I just ran into Mihee.
Ah, the proverbial lamb to our slaughter.
She'll be put to good use
in my lecture for Monday's class.
The topic is on how to run
a successful reality competition show.
And audiences tune in for blood.
So you put Mihee into Advanced Voice
so I can give her my feedback
to humiliate her?
You see? You're such a natural at this.
I don't know, Dad. This is...
You remind me of me
when I was an ambitious young man.
Only slightly less handsome.
Weirdly enough, that's probably
the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
[Moon] I mean it.
I'm not getting any younger. I'm 42 now.
Dad, you're 52.
The point is, someday,
I want to pass on the family business,
and I hope you have my killer instinct.
[reflective music playing]
[Kitty] Min Ho!
Stella was embarrassed when
you threw her under the bus in class.
- I know you wanna impress your dad, but--
- Yeah, but why wouldn't I?
He's a successful, good-looking man
who can charm anyone
into doing what he wants.
He's got killer instincts.
And maybe I do too.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but the point is,
if you don't like Stella,
please just let her down easy.
I told her you were a good guy,
so don't make me out to be a liar.
See you later.
[energetic music playing]
Yes, I'm trying to reach Jina Lim.
She's a guest at...
She is? Actually? Yes.
Please put me through. Thank you.
Hi, Principal Lim.
Jina. It's Kitty.
Did Yuri email you
about why I was hoping to talk to you?
[music fades]
No?
Oh.
Oh, she must have forgotten.
Well, I was hoping to talk to you
because I... have something to ask you.
Holy shit.
So Simon wasn't your mom's boyfriend?
No, he was her cousin.
He's my grandma's sister's son.
I'm not searching for my mom's first love.
I'm searching for... my family.
Kitty, that's incredible and so exciting.
It is, because here's the thing.
My grandma doesn't have a sister.
Wait, what?
She's an only child,
or so she always claimed,
and I'm sure what my mom believed,
until cousin Simon tracked her down.
Let's assume my mom confronted my grandma
about her secret family in Korea.
And Halmoni stonewalled her,
the same way that she stonewalled me.
That would explain why my grandma
did not want my mom to come to Korea.
Okay, this is giving major K-drama.
Like, all the tropes.
But maybe your grandma had a reason
as to why she kept this a secret.
Maybe. [sighs]
[gentle music playing]
But my mom still believed that
even against my grandma's wishes,
coming here to meet Simon
and the rest of her family
was the right move.
So I'm just gonna trust her.
[alarm chimes]
Oh my God, I have to go.
I have to run by the library,
then get ready for my date.
Okay, go, go, go. Go. Wait, what?
A date? With who?
- [Juliana] You look hot in that dress.
- [Yuri] Aw.
Wait, that's Kitty.
Hey, I want to ask her
to come with us tonight.
Why? So she can annoyingly ask you
about Jina every five seconds?
She's a really good friend.
A really good friend
who obviously has a thing for you.
Stop. Kitty!
Hi.
So, since you've had
your great bi-awakening,
I was wondering if you wanna come
to this place called Sugar Bar
with us tonight?
Oh. In Itaewon?
I'm actually already going.
This girl Praveena invited me.
- Oh.
- Praveena?
Wow, yeah.
Praveena and I, we were
in Korean class together last year.
Her parents are, like, CIA or something.
She's, like, really cool.
Good job, Kitty.
Uh, give me one second.
- I'm gonna ask my lab partner something.
- Okay.
Praveena sounds... really cool. [chuckles]
Still no word from your mom, huh?
Yeah, sorry.
I know you want that Simon info.
Yeah, well, Jina's totally
and completely unreachable, right?
Yeah.
I know Jina's not off the grid.
I talked to her today, Yuri.
And she said that you never even
emailed her about my mom's letter.
What is going on?
[gentle music playing]
Okay. Don't be mad.
The truth is, I'm not really talking
to my mom right now
because of the way
she's been treating me since I came out.
What? I thought she was supportive.
She was.
So when she told me
not to tell my grandparents
because it would "kill them,"
I was cool with it.
But then, every time she called,
she would add another person
to the list of people
she doesn't want to know about me,
so I...
stopped talking to her.
Yuri, I am so sorry.
Juliana gets triggered
by mom drama anyways,
so it's all for the best.
Really.
- [crowd cheering]
- [club music playing]
You brought me to a gay club
to help me get over Kitty?
Straight girls come here so they don't
get hit on by cishet meatheads, all right?
Let's, uh...
Let's find you some girl to flirt with.
But the only girl
I've ever flirted with is Kitty.
How am I gonna know
which ones are straight?
Usually, the fingernails.
Hetero spotted, 12 o'clock.
Follow my lead.
Hi! My name's Q.
This is my super-straight bestie, Dae.
And he just came to support me tonight.
Talk about an ally. Yeah, right?
[Dae chuckles]
Um, hello, ladies.
Are you here
to support a gay friend as well?
Or just avoiding straight... men?
[girls giggle]
You talk like AI.
[group chuckles]
[Dae] Hey, Q. Where are you going?
["Next to Mexico" by La Felix playing]
[Q] This is a new low, even for you.
Showing up the night before our track meet
to, what, psych me out?
Really, Q?
You can't think of any other reason
that I might be here?
[Q scoffs]
Hold up, you've been giving me shit
for years, and you're gay?
Dance with me.
I guess, uh,
a little extra cardio couldn't hurt.
[dance music intensifies]
- Wow. It's crowded.
- Wow.
[Kitty gasps]
Kitty!
- Hi!
- [Praveena] Hi!
Hi, Juliana, Yuri.
I knew you two were dating.
I figured you would. It's that spy gene.
Yeah, are your parents
actually in the CIA?
And if so, should that not be a secret?
They are in the State Department, which is
exactly what people in the CIA always say.
[giggles] This place is amazing.
Isn't it?
Hey. You want to get mocktails? Come on.
Wow, I can't believe how packed it is.
I mean, I don't even recognize...
Dae?
Hi, what are you doing here?
[nervously] Hi. I'm here with Q,
who I haven't seen for an hour.
- You want to sit?
- Oh.
You want to dance? [chuckles]
Uh, find me later.
Hello?
[in Korean] It's obvious
that you like her...
Why don't you leave and not waste my time?
She's just my ex!
I am trying to get over her.
What happened was...
She came to Korea to be with me...
at the time I was fake-dating
this other girl.
I know it's my fault,
but my ex-girlfriend fell in love
with that girl!
Sorry.
I'm boring you. I'll leave.
[in English] Are you kidding?
[in Korean] It's totally juicy!
Tell me everything right now!
[in English] So,
I heard you're a matchmaker.
- Wow, you really do have a spy gene.
- [both laugh]
[upbeat dance music playing]
So what's more important
when matching up a particular couple?
Timing or chemistry?
[chuckles]
Kitty?
[speaking inaudibly]
That's why you didn't wanna sit
with them at the assembly.
You're into Yuri.
Let me explain.
This is feeling complicated.
No, it's not. I had a crush on Yuri,
and now we're just friends.
Sorry. I'm... I'm just worried about her.
I never want to get in the way
of you being there for a friend,
but this is clearly not our night,
so... I think I'm gonna go.
[sighs] See you around, Kitty Cat.
["Show Me How You Do It"
- by Aiden.
- J playing]
- Hey.
- Kitty, hey.
Sorry to interrupt. Can we talk?
Uh, can you give me a minute?
- Thirty seconds. I'm timing you.
- [chuckles]
Who is that?
It's just some guy I hate
on my track team.
What are you doing here?
Are you on your date?
I'll tell you about that later.
I know I need to mind my own business,
but Yuri's in this big fight with her mom.
She's not honest with Juliana
about how it's hurting her.
What do you think I should do?
Fine. Just go have fun.
Thank you.
♪ Show me how you dance... ♪
[Kitty] Sorry. Excuse me. Sorry.
- Where's Yuri?
- Bathroom.
You know what's weird?
She's been looking forward to tonight,
but ever since she ran into you,
she's just been... upset about something.
I found out that
Yuri's been lying to me about her mom,
and I confronted her about it today.
Right. So Yuri's pissed at you
for not minding your business.
Uh, maybe, but she's also clearly hurting,
and I think avoiding Jina
is making her feel worse.
Yuri was so happy when she came out
and had her mom's support.
Support that her mom
pretty much snatched away.
Yes, but I'm sure
Jina doesn't see it that way.
I bet she thinks she's protecting Yuri,
which I know is wrong and messed up,
but I don't know.
I feel like if Yuri talked to her,
Jina would step up and do better.
So Jina deserves a free pass?
No, absolutely not,
but this is about what Yuri needs.
It is.
And Yuri said that
she did not want to talk to Jina.
And I'm following her lead,
and if you were a real friend,
you would do that too.
Hey.
Sorry, I'm just... I'm just in a weird mood.
No, no, no. You're okay.
I get it. You're thinking about your mom.
How did you know that?
Because I know you.
Look, she's trying to be protective,
and it's messed up, for sure,
but maybe if you try to open up
and tell her your feelings, she'd step up.
- Bye, Dae. It was nice talking to you.
- [Dae] Bye.
[girl giggles]
Looks like you had fun.
You too. With Praveena.
So, you're finally over Yuri?
I'm... trying.
[softly] Bye.
[Kitty] I am trying to get over Yuri.
She has a girlfriend.
A girlfriend who doesn't want me
in their business.
So, why am I giving up
a chance with someone new?
[sighs]
[Moon] Mihee dropped Advanced Voice.
- You tipped her off, didn't you?
- [scoffs] Well--
You went around my back
just to protect her feelings.
[scoffs]
I don't know why I thought
you had what it takes to be a manager.
I gave you a chance
to step up and impress me,
and instead, you threw it away
for some loser who can't even sing.
Don't talk to him like that.
This is a private conversation
between father and son.
Well, you're a crappy father.
Min Ho does have
what it takes to be a manager,
more than you do with this tired
Simon Cowell routine from 2002.
For a man who claims
to have his finger on the pulse,
you should know
that bullying is so over, Mr. Moon.
It's really a miracle
you haven't been cancelled.
You certainly have a lot to say,
don't you?
Uh...
I'm... I'm sorry.
No, wait. Wait.
Where did that come from?
I know everyone just thinks I'm so sweet,
but when I see someone being mistreated,
I just... explode.
Plus, the press makes your dad out
to seem like this great father.
Yeah, well,
don't believe everything you read.
By the way, I've never had someone
who'd stand up for me that way,
so thank you.
I hope I didn't make things worse.
- I mean, I really insulted him.
- [sighs]
Don't worry about it.
In fact, I think you impressed him.
Yeah, I bet he thinks
you're a real badass now.
I know I do.
[tender music playing]
Can I be honest with you?
I love it when people underestimate me.
It's like having this dirty little secret,
'cause they have no idea
what I'm capable of.
Well, I definitely underestimated you.
Looks like you're in big trouble.
[tender music swells]
- [music fades]
- [birds singing]
[Q] "Don't hate the player,
hate the game."
[gasps]
Oh my God.
That bitch turned off my alarms.
- [sighs]
- [tense music playing]
[guy] K-I...
[crowd] S-S!
[guy] We're team...
- [crowd] KISS!
- [all] Go, KISS!
Kitty! Guess what?
I just talked to my mom,
and she apologized for being
an overprotective weirdo,
and she said
if I want to come out publicly,
she will support me.
[chuckles] Oh my God, that is amazing!
It was Juliana's idea to call her.
[crowd cheering]
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you.
Congrats!
Mm!
[sighs]
This is crazy. Where is Q?
I have no idea, but that is the guy
he was all over last night at the club.
[Dae] Q ditched me for Jin?
But he's Q's rival, and he's a big jerk.
Yeah, well, looks like
Q might have gotten played.
Runners, please take your marks
for the 100-meter dash qualifying.
The winner will represent KISS...
We have to do something!
- Take this.
- [guy] Okay!
What are you doing?
Can I borrow this
for one second? Just real quick.
Let me. Thank you so much.
That's great. Okay.
♪ We've got spirit, yes, we do
We've got spirit, how about you? ♪
- What?
- Kitty, get off the track!
[grunts]
- [feedback squeals]
- [crowd murmuring]
- [Dae sighs]
- Kitty!
Kitty! You all right?
Stella, get help.
I'm trying to cause a diversion, dummy!
I'm here! I'm here!
- [crowd cheers]
- [man] Let's go!
I'm here!
[man] Runners, take your marks!
- Morning! Did you get my note?
- Shut up.
[crowd cheering]
You got it! You got this!
[man] Get set!
[starting pistol fires]
[runners panting]
Let's go!
- Come on!
- Yeah!
[crowd cheers]
[gloomy music playing]
[cheering dies down]
I can't believe it. [scoffs]
Duped again by a cheater.
The universe telling me
to swear off boys this semester.
And I'd wish I'd changed rooms
when I had the chance.
Now I'm stuck watching
Yuri and Juliana make out all the time.
[Lee] Excuse me?
[Kitty gasps]
I said I'm always watching
Yuri and Juliana put on their makeup.
- Juliana, Yuri.
- No.
A word.
Ms. Covey has just informed me
of your relationship.
The honeymoon is over.
One of you must move out.
- ["Crazy Like You" by CHUNG HA playing]
- ♪ You make me crazy ♪
♪ Like you ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm crazy like you ♪
[singing in Korean]
♪ I'd rather be crazy like you ♪
[song continues in Korean]
♪ You make me crazy like you ♪
♪ Just like you know that you do ♪
♪ Twisted me just like it's true ♪
♪ Pushed me and pulled me ♪
♪ Until I was crazy like you ♪
♪ Crazy like you ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm crazy like you ♪
[balloons expanding]