Dae, what is this?
What?
Where did you get...?
When did you start dating Han Yuri?
Did Kitty dump you?
What happened? Tell me.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, Dae Heon.
I was going to drive you to campus,
but I need to go see
President Han right now.
- Okay.
- Dad,
that's not what's important right now.
Dae is going viral right now.
Hmm?
"Dae Heon Kim, humble boyfriend
of hotel heiress Yuri Han,
saves tarnished corporate image
of Han Hotel Group."
"Acquisition of Miller Hospitality
back on track."
Hey, are you doing all right?
Is there something I should know?
Don't worry.
- Everything will be fine.
- All right.
I'm going now.
Watch out for cars.
- Okay.
- Have a good day.
Dae.
Can we play before leaving?
No, we're already late.
Go get ready.
Fine.
- Have you packed your schoolbag?
- Yeah!
Good job.
Bora...
what happened to your sneakers?
I'm probably going through
a growth spurt. It's okay.
How is this okay?
It's going to look weird, but...
Hold your foot up.
You can wear this for a while.
Nobody would notice this.
It's fine. I already get
made fun of in school, anyway.
What?!
Let's go.
I'd move the barrette up a little higher.
Thanks.
Come in, come in.
Okay, that can go there.
And that one here, please.
- What are you doing here?
- You hired movers?
- Kitty, you're still here.
- Yes, she is.
I'm going to call Campus Police
and have her forcefully removed.
- Do not call Campus Police.
- Dae, we need to talk. Now.
- All right, where to begin?
- I'm late. I need to change.
I saw you on TV this morning.
That was quite the performance.
- I'm sure you have questions.
- Yeah, for starters, I...
What...?
Um...
Uh, for starters, I'd like to know
why you chased me down in pajamas,
begged me not to leave,
and then almost kissed me.
- Kitty.
- And I would've kissed you back,
if you hadn't been kidnapped
by your other girlfriend's family,
by the way.
I can explain.
Great.
Why don't we start with the lies?
Lies? Plural?
You have two girlfriends, right?
Or is that a double-double lie?
And why would you pretend
to be rich all these years?
- What else are you lying about?
- I never lied.
Oh, but you FaceTimed me from a fancy car
and just left out the fact
that your dad is the chauffeur?
Do you not know me well enough
to know I wouldn't care about that?
I was embarrassed.
Here's this beautiful girl
on a fancy family vacation,
and she's interested in me.
And about Yuri...
Hey, so we gotta go now,
or we're gonna be late.
I'm leaving this open.
Dae, now.
I'll find you later where we can be alone,
and I promise
I can explain everything.
Looking forward to that.
Are you texting Dae?
Yes.
- Ask him if he signed the NDA yet.
- No.
It's already weird enough.
You and Daddy made this
a whole business thing.
Fine.
Are you almost ready to go?
Just give me a minute.
Okay, open up.
Oh, my God.
You're so talented, it's painful.
- Could've been better. I could've blended.
- Are you kidding me?
This song is dope. What is it?
It's the DJ I was telling you about.
Oh, the one that's DJing on New Year's?
Mm-hm. So we can go
see him together in Iceland.
Mm... Us dancing together
under the northern lights?
- Mm-hm.
- Can't wait.
Me too.
Yuri! We're gonna be late.
Coming!
Dae Heon Kim. Did you sign the NDA?
Behind us, be careful. Paparazzi.
My mom is having me tailed right now.
This was easier than I thought.
All right. Let's go.
Smile.
Kitty's figured out too much.
I have to tell her the truth.
- You can't.
- I know, but I have a conscience.
I might be fake dating you and lying
to the press, but I have integrity.
No, Dae Heon Kim,
you literally can't tell her.
Or do you want to get sued?
Whatever. Just answer me this,
who is "Baby"?
- None of your business.
- Fine.
Don't tell me if you don't want to.
I'll just tell your dad's lawyer about it.
Check your phone.
It's Juliana.
I'm with Juliana.
What does that mean?
You're with Juliana?
She was supposed to be
at the welcome party.
But she didn't come.
All her social media's been deleted.
And her phone's been disconnected too.
I think her parents sent her away
because of me.
I might never see her again.
Hop on.
What are you doing?
We can't be late
on our first day of school.
Trust me, and hop on.
Thank you.
- It has to be fake.
- Huh?
Don't you think?
When people are performative like that?
I'm Kitty Song Covey.
It's nice to meet you.
Hey, you're the Portland Stalker.
It's fine. It's just Day 1.
I'm gonna listen to Mom's favorite song...
...and focus on the fact
that she went here,
and forget about boy drama.
Today is gonna be great.
♪ Welcome to your life ♪
♪ There's no turning back ♪
♪ Even while we sleep... ♪
Thanks for earlier.
No problem.
I know I can't stop you from telling Kitty
that we're in a fake relationship.
But she has to keep the secret.
I get it, and so will Kitty.
She's never told anyone
any of my secrets before.
But she can't know about the real reason
why we're faking this either.
I know. That will never happen.
If she asks about the real reason,
I'll make something else up.
Ugh, this is stressing me out.
Oh! Did you finish my summer homework
for Professor Lee's class?
You know this is part of
me paying your tuition, right?
No offense,
but I hope we get to break up soon.
You and me both, kid.
Oh!
Ow! What the hell?
- Juliana? Oh, my God, you're here.
- Hi.
Just for a second.
Listen,
my parents are sending me to Oakham.
- No.
- I know. At least it's not a nunnery.
This is all my fault.
- I should have been more careful.
- Stop. No, no, no. It's not.
What am I supposed to do here without you?
Everything here sucks.
You still have me,
even if we can't talk for a while.
But we didn't get to do
the things we planned,
New Year's Eve, northern lights,
holding hands in public places.
We were finally gonna get to be ourselves.
And we still can,
because you are a genius.
Using Dae to distract our parents?
That press made its way
to my mom's favorite morning show,
and she's already shipping it too.
- That's only a temporary fix.
- That's all we need.
Stay the fake, shiny "it couple"
so my parents forget about the rumors,
and then I'll be with you,
kissing you at midnight in Iceland.
- How?
- No idea.
But if you promise me
that you'll be there,
I promise you I'll be there too.
Go. This is your first day.
You can't be late,
because Principal Lim will flay you.
Go.
I spotted it immediately.
The phrasing,
the traditional sentence structure.
Yuri is usually more colloquial.
Can you prove her tutor wrote it?
Well... no.
Then this discussion is over.
- What?
- You have the face of a lost person.
- I'm looking for Literature.
- Sure. Up there to the right.
Great. Thank you.
Professor Lee, Professor Lee.
It's so nice to see you.
You're in my third period class?
No, we've actually met.
At the faculty luncheon?
- I'm a new teacher here.
- Right.
Great.
Many students come to me
with a lack of exposure to anything
but the basics of the Western canon.
We have to get lunch together.
Expect that to change here.
I'll see you all tomorrow.
Dae, you and Yuri are adorable.
Do you guys have other classes together?
Um, I'm not sure.
He knew my school schedule
when I was thousands of miles away.
Fakey McFakersons.
Dae, wait!
Miss Song Covey, before you go.
After looking over your test scores,
I've forwarded your name
to the tutoring office.
Oh, great. I used to tutor kids
back at Adler High in Portland.
- I started taking AP classes as a soph...
- Not to be a tutor.
To be tutored.
You're well below the level of your peers,
and the work only gets more challenging.
Oh.
Report to the library after school.
They'll you assign a tutor.
- I'm sure that there...
- You can go.
Is the Portland Stalker
half or just white?
Oh, my God. She got a cupcake on her tray.
Didn't she get enough last night?
Hey! What's up, guys?
- Hey, you're the Portland...
- Portland Stalker, yeah.
I earned a serial killer name on Day 1.
I really shouldn't be talking to you.
I gotta stay on Team Dae.
Does Team Dae know that he and I
have been together for years,
and this whole Yuri thing
is weird and probably fake?
Weird, yes. But fake?
Come on, life ain't a K-drama.
You saw the heat crackling
between us this morning, right?
We were seconds away from kissing.
Maybe he's torn and confused.
He's not confused. He's miserable.
I know what I'm talking about, trust me.
My sister, Lara Jean, was in a fake
relationship with her boyfriend, Peter.
Kind of my fault, then it turned real,
and they're still together.
But that's not gonna happen
with Yuri and Dae.
I know.
I'm a matchmaker.
- Okay, I still don't...
- You like him.
Florian?
No, no.
He was just yawning,
then you yawned,
and yawns are contagious, so...
He's an elitist.
He thinks not liking Marvel movies
is a personality.
Sure.
Well, you're hot, he's hot,
let's move on it.
Sorry. God, I forgot I wasn't in Portland,
and I should not assume that you're gay,
or that you're out, or assume anything.
I am out.
Don't get me wrong, compared to the US,
Seoul isn't exactly gay-friendly...
but I have family in Iran
and the Philippines,
so I basically spend every vacation
in Hetero Cosplay Summer Camp.
And besides, even if I was interested,
Florian wouldn't be.
He hates athletes,
and my thighs are tree trunks.
Come on, let me help you.
Thank you, but no thank you.
- I'll see you guys later.
- Peace, man.
Are you smiling?
Smile properly.
- I said, smile.
- Ow!
Smile.
I've gotta go.
What did I do now?
Professor Lee suspects
Dae wrote your summer reading essay.
He's my tutor. He just helped.
I want your credit card.
What does this have to do
with my credit card?
No money, no access to trouble.
We've let you run wild for too long.
Jetting off to the DJ festivals,
your face in the tabloids
that Juliana employs.
Juliana's gone.
Whatever. Just tell me what I need to do
to get my credit card back.
What's so important
that you need to buy this minute?
Nothing.
Just...
You promised I could go
to that New Year's festival in Iceland.
We can revisit Iceland
when and if your behavior improves.
So if this festival
is that important to you,
don't mess up.
Yuri...
this is for your well-being too.
Dae!
Bora! What was the shoe brand you said
all your friends at school had?
FILA Disruptors.
I'll buy them for you.
I make a lot of money now.
Really? You're the best.
I'll call you again soon. Bye.
Bye.
Yes!
- Congrats, Kitty. Right on time.
- Thank you.
I'm starting to figure this place out.
Can you please get out of my life?
Trust me, I don't wanna be
next to you either.
You need to go home.
Dae has made his position clear.
The longer you stay,
the more pathetic you look.
No pimply-faced playboy
tells me about my relationship.
I haven't had a blocked pore
in four years.
Oh, well, it looks like
one's coming in right here.
Are you supposed to be in this class?
Professor Finnerty,
I want a new lab partner.
Portland Stalker is in remedial classes.
No.
That's not true, and don't you dare
call me that name again.
You mean "Portland Stalker"?
That's the unfortunate thing
about nicknames.
They tend to stick.
I suppose that's true...
Poopy Baby.
- What did you just call me?
- You heard me.
It's him.
Okay, okay. That's fine.
Everybody can pick
their own lab partners, but quickly.
Chemistry doesn't do itself.
Hi there.
Hey, Eunice.
Min Ho just said
he wants you to be his new lab partner.
- Um, what are you doing?
- My thing.
Hello.
Hi. It's Florian, right?
Oui. Hi.
I should probably apologize in advance.
It seems as if
the American educational system
isn't as exceptional
as I was led to believe.
I totally understand if you decide
to do all the labs for us.
I would never forgive myself
if you failed this class because of me.
What anguish.
Anyone sitting here?
- Hi.
- Hey.
Now this is chemistry.
What's up?
Hi. I'm here for tutoring.
Katherine Song Covey.
Yes. Wait right here.
I bet Mom stood here.
So much history.
Mom.
You found your place here, Mom.
Hopefully, I will too.
I wonder if one of these debate dudes
could have been your mystery boyfriend.
Katherine?
This is your tutor, Dae.
Dae, this is Katherine,
a student from America.
Hello.
Hi.
♪ Mommy, Daddy, cheer up! ♪
♪ Mommy, Daddy, I love you! ♪
Oh, my God. Min Ho is the Poopy Baby?
Yeah, Kitty let it slip in chem.
How does she know?
I guess Dae told her.
I gotta go.
Yuri!
Can you go over this part again?
- I don't really get it.
- Yeah.
If you want to do this,
you can't go right over to here.
- You should always do 30.
- Right.
Finally, she left.
- There's so much I want to say.
- Me too.
If it makes it any easier,
I know what you were trying to tell me.
- Okay, great, because...
- Dae, there you are.
Have you heard?
Someone outed Min Ho as the Poopy Baby,
- and now it's all over school.
- What?
He told a close friend
he thought he could trust,
and that person blabbed
to the whole school.
I guess you got to be careful
who you share your secrets with.
Bye, baby.
NDA.
Well, that was something.
I mean, your girlfriend is intense.
I can't believe you told Min Ho
about Poopy Baby.
Sorry, but Min Ho was being such a jerk,
and if it was a big secret,
you shouldn't have told me.
Yeah, I definitely shouldn't have.
Dae, I'm sorry.
This isn't gonna work.
What?
What isn't gonna work?
Me and you.
I'm sorry.
Why'd you tell me to stay this morning
if you were gonna break up with me?
Because I still care about you.
You are my best friend.
I'll stop by the tutoring office tomorrow
and tell them to assign a new tutor.
- But, Dae...
- I'm sorry.
I really am.
But I'm with Yuri now.
But it isn't real, right?
It is real.
He was wearing it this whole time?
He kept this close to his heart.
So why is he breaking mine now?
Sorry.
I thought you were Dae.
Yeah, I heard.
You doing okay?
Nope.
But I'm not going to cry,
because I cannot have
puffy eyes for this photo.
It's a Covey family tradition
that my mom started,
and I'm here for her.
Here, I'll take it.
Thanks.
So Florian followed me on Instagram today.
- Really?
- Oh, shoot.
This fell out.
Aw, baby bracelet.
- I didn't know you were born in Korea.
- I wasn't.
That's my mom's name.
In Korean.
August 12th, 1993.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, Kitty, what?
I think...
I think my mom had a baby here.
♪ I know it's over ♪
♪ You don't even have to say ♪
♪ You pull me under ♪
♪ Underneath your skin ♪
♪ Deeper than the dark ♪