[bright pop music playing]
[monitor beeping]
[in Korean] Dad,
you heard the doctors, right?
There's still a long way to go,
but you've already improved a lot.
What a relief.
I can't walk.
I can't work.
I can't take care of you two.
Oh, and my youngest, Bora...
I told you not to worry about that.
Bora is doing fine at Auntie's house.
Don't worry about all those things.
I'm already looking for a part-time job.
No, no. You can't do
a part-time job, okay?
If you really want to help me,
you focus on your studies.
You can't let your grades fall
because of me.
[knocking on door]
[in English] Hi.
Sorry, are we interrupting?
- Not at all.
- Oh, hi.
[in Korean] Hello.
- Hello.
- [Kim] You came!
Mr. Kim, you look very good.
[in English] We come bearing gifts.
[Kim] Oh.
Oh, thank you.
[Dae] He's made so much progress
in the last two weeks.
[in Korean] Hey, Min Ho.
I have a favor to ask you.
If you ever hear Dae
talking nonsense about
a part-time job,
you have to put a stop to it!
Of course, don't worry.
I'll be sure to grab him if I hear of it.
[Kim] That's right.
I feel better that Dae has
such a loyal and good friend like you.
[chuckles]
Thank you, sir.
[in English] I think
she needs to check his vitals.
We'll wait outside. Do you need anything?
[gentle piano music playing]
I thought things were
getting better with Dae.
Well, at least
he's tolerating your presence now.
- [Q] Mm-mm.
- I suppose.
Any updates on cousin Jiwon?
I've basically given up on that.
I mean, you saw how mad they were.
[Q] Ugh.
- What's up?
- Just...
Jin's really stressed about the race
because his dad's gonna come watch.
I don't know. I wish I could help him.
What if you did something romantic
for him, just to take his mind off of it?
Hmm. That's actually
a pretty good idea, Kitty.
[Yuri] Hey, guys.
[Q] Hey, Yuri.
Kitty, can we talk?
Um...
- We're gonna go get some snacks.
- It's my intermittent fasting this week.
Read the room.
You haven't been answering
any of my texts, calls, DMs.
Hmm. Don't you just hate
when that happens?
[Yuri] Kitty, I'm so sorry I shut you out
while I was trying to get Juliana back.
I just really miss our friendship.
[cell phone vibrating]
I have somewhere I need to be.
Say bye to Mr. Kim for me, please.
["I Like Me Better" by Lauv playing]
[Kitty] I'm still really confused
about how to move forward with Yuri.
And other things too, like,
is my roommate Stella
the evil mastermind behind MoonLeaks?
Luckily, when times are tough...
- Peter!
- There she is!
...there's nothing like
a friendly face from home.
[both laugh]
I'm so happy you're here.
Come on.
- ♪ I like me better when I'm with you ♪
- [song fades]
Who knew people outside the States
cared about lacrosse?
[chuckles] Okay.
I'm not interrupting some weird
pre-tournament team ritual or anything?
No, I'm all yours.
Yay. I want to show you my dorm.
Hell yeah.
I can see why you like it here.
God, it must be so crazy that you get
to walk in your mom's footsteps, huh?
It's surreal, in the best way.
You know, speaking of your mom, I am
under strict orders to hand-deliver these.
Lara Jean found them at your grandma's.
They're letters Simon sent to your mom.
Are you kidding me?
Oh my God!
I'm sure you're dying to rip into 'em,
so I figure...
No. I am, trust me,
but I can do this later.
I promised to help with a surprise for LJ,
which, by the way,
what kind of surprise are we talking?
It's not a ring, Kitty.
We are 22 years old.
- I don't know!
- Yeesh.
Hey.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Oh, you must be Peter.
- Yes.
- I'm Juliana.
One of my roommates.
Yeah. Maybe don't swing by the dorm,
unless you're trying
to introduce him to the Ohio weirdo.
- It's nice meeting you though.
- You too.
[whimsical music playing]
Okay, Lara Jean told me
you had beef with Juliana,
but she was acting super chill.
Well, we have a common enemy now.
But I did still kiss
her girlfriend. [chuckles]
Ex-girlfriend.
Wait. Does that mean
there's a chance you and Yuri--
No. No chance. And I wouldn't want
a chance, given the way she treated me.
Okay, so Yuri's out. We're canceling Yuri.
What about the guy on the plane?
No, he's dating our other roommate,
the Ohio weirdo, Stella.
Anyway, let's go. This way.
I wanna know why you guys are calling
a human being "the Ohio weirdo."
I think she's using Min Ho
to bring down his famous dad.
[Kitty] See, she snuck into his office,
and then...
Never mind. You'll think I'm insane.
- [Peter] Oh no, you're definitely insane.
- ["Where We Go" playing]
[song continues in Korean]
♪ I feel like I know it ♪
♪ Baby, when I look at you ♪
♪ I'm in love ♪
- [song continues in Korean]
- [Peter chuckles]
- Isn't it great?
- Yes.
Ah. I want everything.
Okay, so which of these do you think
your sister is gonna like...
Never mind. What? I'm gonna get 'em all.
You are such a simp for LJ.
Hey, I am not a... Oh yes! Look at these.
- Oh yeah, she's going to love these.
- [Kitty giggles]
Covey?
Min Ho.
- [whispers] The guy from the plane?
- Stop talking.
- What are you doing here?
- Stella. She loves this place.
- Peter Kavinsky.
- [clears throat] All right, mate?
- Yeah.
- [Kitty] This is Lara Jean's boyfriend.
- My sister.
- [Min Ho] I know.
I was subject to your monologues
for an entire semester, remember?
I heard about your travel too.
- [Peter] Hmm.
- In great detail, actually, from Covey.
You're here for what?
A ping-pong tournament?
- [chuckles] Lacrosse.
- [under breath] Yeah, same thing.
Uh, those sparkly pens are super sick.
Where did you find those?
Thanks. It's actually
right by the sparkly stickers.
[Peter] Mm.
- Thanks, bro.
- No worries, mate. [clears throat]
Covey.
[Kitty sighs]
You know, I think
he totally likes you still.
- Whoa. Whoa, no. Nope.
- He's calling you by your last name.
- That's not a thing, Peter.
- He remembers every word you've ever said.
But he still pretends to be annoyed
when you talk too much. Classic.
He has a girlfriend who he's very into.
Did you see the sparkly pens?
But I'm telling you,
she's up to something.
Only I can't prove it without
looking like a freak and butting in.
Okay, well, look, if he is your friend,
then you should look out for him.
[quietly] Yeah.
Also, since when do you care
about looking like a freak?
All right. I gotta get going.
But I do have a free window
this Saturday before we leave for Tokyo.
With enough time to try
a sweet potato latte
from our coffee truck?
Can't say no to that.
Or a Covey sister.
Yay.
Can I also have this one?
- Excellent choice.
- Thank you.
[in Korean] Hello.
[sighs]
[bright music playing]
[Kitty] "Dear Eve, Hello from Korea."
"Happy Lunar New Year 1994."
"Sorry your mom's still mad at you."
"I feel somewhat responsible
for dragging you into this family feud."
Jeez, Grandma, way to hold a grudge.
"Dear Eve,
Dan sounds cool for a white guy,
and you seem head over heels."
"Did you hear your old friend Gina
has a new boyfriend too?"
"Sun-jin Han, total player,
and I'm pretty sure
she's not his only girlfriend."
"I can't believe you convinced
your mother to go back to Korea."
"Remember back in the '90s
when she didn't speak to you
for six months because of this?"
"Now I just have to get my mom on board."
Wait, what?
"And I'm so happy
you're bringing your youngest."
"How cool that Kitty will have her first
passport stamp at three years old."
"Jiwon can't wait
to play with her cousin."
Oh my God.
[cell phone vibrating]
Kitty?
[Kitty] I'm still feeling weird about us,
but I just had to tell you.
My sister's boyfriend gave me a bunch
of letters from Simon to my mom.
It turns out they were
writing each other for years.
And I found out my mom
convinced my grandma
to reunite with her sister
when I was little.
She was gonna bring me
to Korea too, but she...
But she died before...
Before we could go.
I was meant to be part of their reunion.
Oh, Kitty.
Only no, because I'm stuck.
My great-aunt won't let me in the house,
and my cousin Jiwon
has ghosted me on Instagram, so...
Well, what can I do to help?
[somber music playing]
I don't...
I don't really know how you can.
But thanks for listening.
[call disconnects]
[sighs deeply]
Luckily for you, this non-pop quiz
is worth only 5% of your final grade.
The earlier you start reviewing
for the final, the better.
That bloke bought you a pen?
What's his name? Pete?
Peter. And... yeah.
I'm sure Stella also loved her pen.
And is using it to write up
her next diabolical plan.
Did you guys go on
some hot date last night?
She barely made it home for curfew check.
None of your business, Covey. [scoffs]
[school bell rings]
[indistinct chatter]
Um, Professor Lee, are there
any TA positions available?
I could really use the money.
Unfortunately, in light of
the MoonLeaks scandal,
the school's been under a lot of heat.
We're bracing for potential budget cuts.
I... I understand. Thank you.
[sighs]
Speaking of MoonLeaks, Min Ho!
Can you please let your father know
that a PR crisis
is not a reason to call off
weeks of classes?
Will do.
[under breath] I don't believe you.
[Min Ho] Dae.
I heard you ask Lee for a job.
I promised your dad
I wouldn't let you do that.
- If you need money, I can always--
- [Moon] Dae!
Yes, sir.
[chuckles] "Sir"?
Can you believe this kid?
Could you excuse us for a minute?
[tense music playing]
[Min Ho] Dae, seriously!
Where have you been?
Handling MoonLeaks.
I fired several executives, and I had
everyone else sign an iron-clad NDA.
It's behind us.
I hope it didn't have
any negative effect on you.
Oh, not at all.
I've only been pestered by hundreds
of people on every social media platform,
dying to know if you're a sociopath.
- [scoffs]
- Or if you have hair plugs.
Well, I'm about to change
the conversation.
Tonight, I am gathering my best students
to discuss the future
of the Moon Arts Program.
Dad, it's Friday, Bulgeum.
I obviously have plans with my girlfriend.
Oh. She's invited, of course.
I promise, it will be worth it.
Fine. I'll be there.
Thanks for doing this. I...
I know this has been hard for you.
It could have been you running tomorrow.
If I had only known then
how I was gonna feel
about you now, I wouldn't have--
It's okay.
Really.
Something I've been meaning to ask you...
Since my dad is going to be at regionals,
would you want to meet him?
The Mr. Olympics?
I would love that.
[tender music playing]
Okay, I should probably
do a couple more sprints.
Or... want to race?
Oh, it's so on.
- The loser has to do 100 burpees.
- [both laugh]
What's the matter? Can't keep up?
[laughs]
[groans]
Shit, shit, shit. Are you okay?
Just rolled my ankle. I'm fine.
- That did not sound fine. You need--
- I said I'm fine!
See? Just need to sleep it off.
[jazz music playing]
Whoa! Such a vibe!
What?
Do you think he's gonna have to sell
all that crap when his empire tanks?
- Dude!
- [Madison] What?
Welcome, welcome. My best students
in Entertainment Management.
And the star of
my Acting for K Drama class.
- What?
- Come on in. Come on in, please.
- Thank you.
- Come on in.
For the host.
Oh. Oh, a gift.
[softly] Yeah.
Oh.
Thank you, son.
I know the perfect place for it.
You're welcome, Dad.
[sighs] I'm very touched.
Excuse me.
That's... odd.
Is it me, or did he just exhibit
a genuine human emotion?
You should probably go check on him.
[Min Ho] Dad?
Is everything all right?
[sighs]
What have I done with my life, Min Ho?
I barely know my own kids
except as commodities.
And you. I want to be in your life.
Then you might've shown up at Seollal.
Your brother's in trouble. He needs me.
[somber music playing]
Joon Ho got a girl pregnant.
Some backup dancer.
- That's why you missed the ski cabin.
- [sighs] Yeah. Stress is getting to him.
He's having panic attacks,
and he's even talking about quitting.
You can't tell anyone.
[sighs] I won't.
I know it's terrible timing
with the MoonLeaks scandal.
If I lose my biggest star,
it's over, and I'll have nothing.
That's not true, Dad.
I made mistakes, and it means a lot
that you showed up for me tonight.
Kitty? You're kind of staring.
Oh no. I was just admiring your makeup.
I've never been good at contour.
[Stella] Hmm.
Where did you get your nose done?
Excuse me?
Oh no, don't misunderstand.
It's really nice.
Uh... [chuckles]
God gave me this nose.
Sorry!
- My bad. [chuckles]
- [door opens, closes]
She's totally lying.
I know a rhinoplasty when I see one.
- Interesting.
- Wanna know who else at school has one?
I'm... I'm good, for now.
Okay.
Pretty nice place, huh?
[Stella] Seriously.
There are no skyscrapers in Pepper Pike.
[Kitty sighs]
- Hello, darling.
- Hi.
You were right, as usual.
I'm glad I went over to talk to him.
She was right about what?
[clapping] Everyone, dinner is served.
[Min Ho and Stella exhale]
[tense music playing]
[knocking on door]
[crickets chirping]
[in Korean] Yes?
Hello. I know you don't know me,
but my name is--
[in English] Yuri Han.
I follow you on Insta.
I loved your last "Get Ready With Me."
Oh. That's the same bag.
Oh. [chuckles]
Great. Then maybe
you'll listen to what I have to say
and stop ghosting my friend Kitty.
All right.
So I hope everyone enjoyed the meal.
And I have an announcement.
As you know, my big showcase
is coming up soon, but--
[gasps] Oh no. Has it been canceled
because of MoonLeaks?
Oh, of course not.
We are going even bigger.
And no one will remember MoonLeaks
after what I am planning.
Our showcase will now be filmed
at one of Seoul's grand palaces
and streamed around the world.
We are turning this into
a massive reality competition show.
You know,
I've had many shows over the years.
International Star Challenge
with Young Moon,
Land Amongst the Stars with Young Moon,
and my highest rated of all,
Rising Stars with Young Moon.
[coughs] Sorry.
It's okay. So, we'll have
a special performance by Joon Ho.
And the winner
will get a recording contract
with Moon Star Entertainment.
- [gasps]
- No way.
Now, this competition
will be for solo artists only.
A K-pop duo is a no-go.
Sorry, you two. You'll have to split up.
Now, let's eat dessert, and then I have
the best karaoke setup in all of Seoul.
Oh, dear Lord. [sighs]
♪ I thank God every day
That I woke up feeling this way ♪
♪ If I was you, I'd wanna be me too ♪
♪ I'd wanna be me too
I'd wanna be me too ♪
♪ If I was you, I'd wanna be me too ♪
♪ I'd wanna... ♪
[in Korean] What's wrong?
What's the problem?
The hospital contacted me
and said the Han Group
is not paying my dad's medical bills.
I'll ask my dad.
[Dae] Forget it.
How can you,
knowing your dad's company is in trouble?
Then I'll take some from my savings.
This is more important.
[in English] Is this you trying
to buy my forgiveness?
No.
Maybe.
[gentle music playing]
[chuckles]
- Is that a cheeky little smile I see?
- [Dae] Shut up.
[in Korean] Anyway, I can't take
that much money from you.
[in English] And I know
that you regret what you did.
I do. [sighs]
There's nothing between me and Covey.
Yeah.
[audience cheers]
[Madison] ♪ I'd wanna be me too ♪
[chuckles, exclaims]
[audience applauds]
[Min Ho] Ah, that record deal
my dad's offering!
If you do well,
that could help pay off
your dad's hospital bills.
- [in English] If you win, that is.
- [softly] Yeah.
You know what? Never mind.
You will win, with my help.
Come on, Dae. One last duet?
[in Korean] I'm going to try
to win that record deal.
Me too.
Are you confident?
[in English]
♪ Don't go breaking my heart ♪
♪ I couldn't if I tried ♪
[Kitty] ♪ Hey, hey! ♪
["I Will Survive" playing]
[Kitty] That's weird.
Who hates karaoke this much?
Stella! Why don't you come up here?
We could do a duet.
- Oh, that's... that's okay.
- [audience cheers]
No, girl, didn't you sing
in your church choir?
Come on. Don't be shy. Come on.
I need some water. [sighs]
♪ Go on now, go
Walk out the door ♪
["I Will Survive" fades out]
[Kitty] First,
Stella does a literal spit take
when Moon mentions
one of his old reality shows.
Then she freaks out at karaoke.
Two huge red flags.
- Rising Stars with Young Moon.
- [tense music playing]
[Kitty] Mm.
Pepper Pike, Ohio.
[yawns]
Oh. My. God.
[tense music fades]
Are you sure you're okay?
For the last time, yes.
Jin! Mate, what's wrong?
- Did you tell him?
- No, why would I?
What have you done?
You're clearly injured.
I can see it plain as day. Your ankle.
Coach, I'm fine. I can run.
Jin, I'm sorry. You're out.
- [scoffs]
- [Alex] Q? You're in.
I need you to go to the lockers and grab
your spikes before the bus gets here.
[sighs]
You heard him. Go.
["ASSA" by Cignature playing]
♪ Clap ♪
♪ I don't care anymore ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
[song continues in Korean]
[sighs]
Jiwon just DMed me. She wants to meet up.
Aww. That is so amazing.
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you.
[Mihee] Wait, guys, look. That's Q.
I didn't know he was running.
[Kitty] Q? Where's Jin?
[announcer] Runners, on your marks!
Get set!
[crowd cheering]
- [starting gun fires]
- [announcer] Go!
Drive! Come on, Q!
- Let's go!
- Let's get it!
Let's go!
[announcer] KISS in first place!
[cheering]
Yeah!
[speaks indistinctly]
[pop song ends]
Min Ho, wait up!
[sighs] I need to talk to you.
- [quietly] Come on.
- What are you doing?
Stella is not who you think she is.
[Stella on video] ♪ Amazing Grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch ♪
♪ Like me ♪
♪ I once was-- ♪
- Why are you showing me this?
- [Kitty] Keep watching.
- ♪ I see ♪
- [applause]
[Moon] Wow.
Esther from Ohio,
I have goosebumps all over.
[Esther] Thank you, Mr. Moon.
That means everything coming from you.
Unfortunately, to be a real star, you need
the look, which you just don't have.
Pass.
- [buzzer sounds]
- [sobbing]
But beauty is
supposed to come from within.
- [sobs]
- That girl is Stella!
What are you talking about?
It says her name is Esther Shim.
Yeah, from Pepper Pike, Ohio,
who grew up singing in the church.
- You're insane.
- No, listen to me.
This became a meme. It was a viral video.
But beauty is
supposed to come from within!
[sobs mockingly]
♪ Amazing Grace... ♪
It's her.
Yeah, she changed her name and changed
her face, but that's Stella's voice.
Look, I feel bad for her.
I mean, she was a middle schooler
who got bullied by the entire internet,
but now it's her motive--
Motive?
Stella leaked my letter as a distraction
so she could sneak into your dad's office
to find dirt on him.
And then MoonLeaks dropped.
I'm telling you,
she wants revenge on your dad
and she's using
your fake relationship as a cover.
First of all,
she's on good terms with my dad.
She even got me a gift for him.
You have no idea how happy that made him
or what it means to me
to have a better relationship with him.
And second of all,
not everyone is in a fake relationship.
- No, not everyone. Stella.
- Enough!
It was bad enough you broke my heart.
You trying to break up my relationship?
I... broke your heart?
Why do you think I jumped into
a rebound relationship with Stella?
And now that I'm past all that
and actually really care about her,
you try to tear us apart because what?
Are you jealous or something?
You're my friend.
I wanna look out for you.
Well, don't!
[Peter] Maybe Min Ho just needs
time to process.
It's a lot to handle.
[Kitty] I've never seen him
so angry before.
When am I gonna learn
to just mind my own business?
All I do is ruin things
for myself and for other people.
Hey, that is not true.
Remember when you mailed out
Lara Jean's love letters?
You not minding your business
landed me the love of my life.
Kitty, you have this killer instinct.
It is literally your superpower.
So stop second-guessing yourself.
Who cares if Min Ho wasn't ready
to hear what you had to say?
It doesn't mean you're wrong.
Thank you, Peter.
- You are Kitty Song Fricking Covey.
- [chuckles]
Don't you forget it.
- You're the best.
- Mm.
[Kitty] I'm so glad you came.
Me too.
[sighs] Do you like your latte?
I do.
That's good.
[intense hip-hop music playing]
[Moon] Joon Ho got a girl pregnant.
Some backup dancer.
The stress is getting to him,
and he's having panic attacks,
and he's even talking about quitting.
You can't tell anyone.
[Min Ho sighs] I won't.
It's terrible timing
with the MoonLeaks scandal.
[Moon] Oh.
Oh, thank you, son.
[Min Ho] Dad, is everything all right?
[Moon] What have I done
with my life, Min Ho?
I barely know my own kids,
except as commodities.
If I lose my biggest star,
it's over, and I'll have nothing.
[chuckles softly]
♪ I'm in the places you dread ♪
♪ I'm at the edge of your bed ♪
♪ I'm at the back of your head ♪
♪ With my sledgehammer
With me up in my coffin ♪
♪ In the dark of your closet
I don't get down too often ♪
♪ I swear I'm coming out of the blue ♪
♪ And when we take on, they lose ♪
♪ No matter the choice that they choose
So beware ♪
♪ With my sledgehammer
With me up in my coffin ♪
♪ In the dark of your closet
I don't get down too often ♪
♪ See, I am the voice inside ♪
♪ It's you and I
You and that silence ♪
♪ I am a raging fire
No playing nice ♪
♪ Today I choose violence ♪
♪ Now ♪
[dark pop song ends]
[balloons expanding]