[energetic music playing]
[Kitty] It's crazy to think
how much can change in a year.
[speaks Korean]
[Kitty] When I first came to KISS,
I'd never felt more like an outsider.
I almost left the first night.
But soon, this place
started to feel like home.
My friends became family,
and then amazingly,
I found my actual family.
Now that my scholarship is almost over
and I'm about to head home,
I have one last thing I have to do.
This is for you.
One hazelnut latte.
- Thank you.
- [phone ringing]
[Kitty] I think this is her.
[gasps]
Please tell me you have good news.
Halmoni said she'd do it!
[both squeal]
- [gasps] Is that Jiwon?
- [Kitty] Oh, yes. Sorry.
- This is our cousin Jiwon!
- Hi, Margot.
Does this mean we get to meet in person?
Yes. I can't wait.
This is crazy. How did you convince
Halmoni to say yes?
Actually, Halaboji did that.
He told her to imagine
if her granddaughters had
a falling out that lasted this long.
And he reminded her that
this is what her daughter wanted too.
She gave me the go-ahead. I've only got
a couple weeks before my new job starts,
so I'm gonna go so I can look for flights.
- Okay, thank you! I love you!
- Bye.
- I love you.
[call disconnects]
Kitty! You're getting
your KISS happy ending.
[somber music playing]
I always thought
there was a vibe between you two.
Oh no, he's super happy with Stella.
Kitty, we're family.
You can tell me the truth.
[sighs]
Fine. Recently, I have had...
feelings, but it doesn't matter.
It's too late.
You sure about that?
'Cause I would have said the same thing
about our grandmas' reunion.
I can't believe
this is actually happening.
[squealing] I know!
[bright music playing]
[Q] Seriously?
Jin wants me to do
another Gilded Age rewatch.
What's the problem?
I thought you loved that show.
I do.
It's like Downton Abbey,
but with crazier hats.
I just worry that Jin's falling into
this depression since he can't run,
hence the constant binge-watching.
To top it off, I keep getting these emails
from recruiters at D1 schools.
Like, I just got invited
to USC's track program for the summer.
- [Dae] What?
- What?
- That's amazing. Congrats.
- [chuckles] Thank you.
That's incredible, Q.
I know.
I just worry
it'll make Jin feel even worse.
No, he's gonna be happy for you.
He adores you.
- True.
- I mean, I am adorable.
[chuckles]
Okay, just tell us
what you're dying to say right now.
Oh, is it that obvious?
- Yeah.
- Okay, well--
[door unlocks]
[tense music playing]
- Hey, guys. Good timing.
- Hey.
Uh, so, the news is,
Halmoni said yes to the sister reunion.
Margot is literally
booking flights as we speak.
- [Q] Oh my--
- Covey, that's great news.
What a blessing. You must be thrilled.
[Kitty] Yeah, thanks, Stella.
Min Ho, you better put on a fresh shirt.
We're having dinner with his dad.
Yeah. [clears throat]
Big show tomorrow.
See you guys later?
Yeah.
[door opens]
She didn't even take off her shoes.
And Min Ho passed over
his usual collagen water
for one of your synthetic energy drinks.
Not to kick a man while he's down,
but his skin is giving major
Edward Cullen vibes, and not in a hot way.
Something's off.
Do you think Stella--
No. I was wrong, remember?
[sighs]
[energetic pop music playing]
[Yuri] Okay, what do we think?
Is this giving "I am totally worthy of you
forgiving me and loving me forever"?
[cell phone vibrates]
- It's Mom.
- Shouldn't you answer it?
Nope. She's gonna want
to talk about Dario again.
This massage therapist she's dating.
- Oh.
- Uh...
- [in Korean] Excuse me?
- [clerk] Yes?
I'll take everything from here to here.
And I'll take what I'm wearing right now.
[cell phone chimes]
[in English] Ugh. It's my dad.
He's been extra crabby
in the lead-up to tonight's concert.
He's probably butt-hurt.
Seeing these kids
living out their pop star dreams
just reminds him he never made it
as a rock star, you know?
So that's why he's been playing
a bunch of sad songs on his guitar.
Oh my God.
Juliana just hearted my Insta story.
I think she might be ready
to get back together.
[Alex] Hmm. I...
What? We had this moment
at the dance last week. Okay?
[clerk in Korean] Miss?
This card has been declined.
Ah, my mom pauses my cards
to get my attention.
Then, please hold these for later.
Yes.
[in English] Okay, I'll go change.
The concert's starting soon.
[upbeat pop music playing]
[excited chatter]
Hey. I got your text. What's going on?
Hey, it's Stella. She's competing tonight,
and Min Ho's helping her.
What? That's impossible.
Well, she was last up
during the tech rehearsal,
and Moon introduced her
as his big underdog story.
This explains his weird behavior
and the synthetic energy drinks,
and the less-than-glowing skin.
This is not Min Ho's fault.
What do you mean? Min Ho knew all along.
How could he do this to us?
Stella's been fake-dating him this entire
time as part of a plan to take down Moon.
- [tense music playing]
- What? What are you talking about?
It's like she has him trapped somehow.
Well, if Min Ho's trapped,
we have to help him.
You have to get ready for the show.
Watch out for Stella. I'll handle this.
[sighs]
Whoa. Kitty, what are you doing here?
What is going on with you?
Stella has you trapped somehow,
doesn't she?
Okay, you were right.
Stella's a complete psycho.
She found out that
Joon Ho got his backup dancer pregnant
and threatened to release the story
to the press unless she wins this contest.
Damn, ten points for Slytherin.
What does your dad think?
You haven't told him. Min Ho!
Well, how do you expect
this conversation will go?
"Hi, Dad. It's a good thing
that I finally earned your respect,
because remember that girlfriend
I convinced you to let in the contest?"
"She's blackmailing us
and planning to ruin your entire empire."
"Cheers, thank you, bye!"
I know I have to, okay? It's just...
I feel pathetic.
None of this is your fault,
but you cannot let her win this thing.
I mean, imagine what she'll do to you
and your family if she gets famous.
I feel like a proper idiot.
Hey, look at me.
I am not afraid of some freak
dressed in sheep's clothing.
If she wants to mess with my friends,
I will drop-kick that bitch faster than
she can say, "Have a blessed day."
All right, Covey. Calm down.
Let's go.
[energetic music playing]
[in Korean] Enjoy the show.
Thank you for coming.
It's an honor
to have the school board here.
[Stella sobs]
[in English] But beauty is supposed
to come from within.
[Moon] So, Stella was behind MoonLeaks?
Why are you just telling me this now?
Stella bugged your office.
She found out Joon Ho knocked up
that gold-digging backup dancer
and threatened to release the story
unless she wins.
For the last time,
Eunji's not a gold digger.
[Moon] Joon Ho, don't start this again.
I told you, I love her.
I want to marry her.
- No, hold on.
- Wait, you love this girl?
Who are you?
Kitty Song Covey. [giggles]
Your skin is everything.
I know.
[chuckles]
What about your career? Your fans?
You're just gonna walk away from
everything that we have worked for?
Not being with Eunji?
Not being in my kid's life?
That would be the real mistake.
And I think out of everyone,
you would understand.
Right, Dad?
Or should I say...
[in Korean] Granddad?
[in English] You told me
you want to do better as a dad.
So prove it.
[gentle music playing]
You're right.
And of course,
I'll support you if that's what you want.
And this might also be
the best way to get out of this mess.
Joon Ho, listen up. I have an idea.
[announcer] Is everyone ready
to shoot for the moon tonight?
[crowd cheering]
Good evening, Seoul!
[energetic dance music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[Madison] Okay, so Eunice is up first,
then Andre, Sophie, then Dae.
Hi. Here you go.
And a drink for you.
[in Korean] Hey. Don't forget to breathe.
[in English] Yeah.
Hey, guys. Don't forget to hydrate.
Thank you. Did you bring these yourself?
[Stella] I sure did.
- [Eunice] You look so cute today.
- [Stella] Thank you.
- I love the whole color. It looks--
- [Dae grunts]
Sorry.
[in Korean] What's wrong?
[in English] Welcome
to Moon's Young Talent Showcase,
featuring a special visit
from Korea's favorite son.
But first, you will meet
handpicked trainees
from my Moon Arts program
as they shoot for the moon, and...
Land amongst the stars!
[crowd cheers]
Eunice, you're up. Come on.
Break a leg, Eunice.
- [Eunice] Thank you.
- [Stella giggles]
Dae, we need to go get you dressed.
[announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
Eunice Kang!
Here, stay hydrated.
- [chuckles]
- Thank you.
[singing in Korean]
Oh my God, did her heel just break?
She's working through it.
[guy cheers]
That had to be Stella.
This is sabotage.
She's taking down the competition.
[Min Ho] Where's Dae?
He's on in 15 minutes.
What's going on here?
I'm screwed. All my dancers
are sick to their stomachs.
[Yuri] Plus, Stella messed with
his music track and his visuals.
Okay, don't panic. We've got this.
[continues singing in Korean]
Here's the plan. Dae's music
and visuals have been sabotaged.
Min Ho you're gonna access
the sound system and fix that.
The rest of us
are gonna be Dae's dance crew.
We've all seen him rehearse--
I'm down.
- We can't leave Dae hanging.
- Yeah, I'm down.
Me too.
What are you talking about?
[sighs]
- [Kitty] Oh!
- Okay, what is happening right now?
- There's something I need to tell you.
- Miss Covey.
For future reference, a peremptory text
demanding your head of school, quote,
"haul ass" to urgently meet you?
Not appropriate.
Sorry, but Dae's music track is missing,
and we need your, uh, sick guitar skills.
That's preposterous.
The school board is here!
Please? Dae's doing this for his family.
Dad, music has always been your dream.
You have to go out there and save the day.
[Lee grunts]
I think that's a yes!
Okay, team, let's do this thing.
- Come on. Let's do it.
- Okay.
So you're healed.
You've just been faking.
Straight talk?
After I got over being jealous of you,
I've been feeling kind of liberated.
For the first time ever,
I'm eating what I want,
not having to wake up at 4:00 a.m.,
and binge-watching Gilded Age
with my hot boyfriend.
I think I might wanna give up running
for good.
Maybe find a whole new passion.
But I didn't wanna tell you because--
Because our entire relationship
is based on competition and sport.
Look, while we're being honest,
I have something to tell you too.
I got accepted into
USC's summer training program.
That's huge. I'm so proud of you.
Okay, let's go kill it.
Yeah.
[announcer] And now,
for our next contestant, Dae Kim!
[audience cheering]
[playing laid-back tune]
♪ Weight of the world on your shoulders ♪
♪ I'll kiss your waist
And ease your mind ♪
♪ I must be favored to know you ♪
♪ I take my eyes and dream ♪
[music distorts]
♪ The world's looking bright ♪
♪ It's working right ♪
- ♪ Think I met you in another life ♪
- [sighs]
So, what do you think?
- What the hell?
- [Min Ho] Didn't you hear?
Dae's backup dancers
all came down with something.
♪ Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday
Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday ♪
Thursday, Friday... ♪
They may have saved his ass, but I'm next,
and I'll blow the roof off this place.
♪ Loving you for seven days a week ♪
♪ Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday
Thursday, Friday ♪
♪ Saturday, Sunday ♪
♪ Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday ♪
♪ Thursday, Friday, seven days a week ♪
♪ Every hour, every minute, every second ♪
♪ And now that you're mine ♪
♪ I'll be loving you seven days a week ♪
[crowd cheering]
[friends exclaim]
Amazing!
[gentle music playing]
There she is.
Stella, your performance is canceled.
No, this is my moment!
Not anymore.
[announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
your favorite son, Joon Ho!
[crowd goes wild]
If I don't get to perform,
I'm gonna destroy your family.
[Joon Ho] There's a special announcement
I'd like to make tonight.
I wanna introduce you to someone
very special in my life.
Eunji, would you come out here, please?
[crowd exclaims]
[Joon Ho] My whole life,
my fans have been my family.
But now, I'm ready to be a father...
[audience] Aww!
And hopefully a husband.
Eunji...
will you marry me?
[Eunji giggles]
Yes.
[sighs]
[Kitty] There goes
your blackmail material.
[tender music playing]
[entrancing pop music playing]
♪ Daddy says I'm number one ♪
♪ His prize boy, one and done ♪
♪ I'm his favorite son
I'm his number one... ♪
I am putting you on the next plane
back to Ohio.
[sighs] But I also want you to know,
I am sorry I was cruel to you.
I've done things over the years
I'm not so proud of.
And I'd like to think
I'm a better person now.
I know that
the most important thing is my family.
And I hope you have people
who care about you like that back home.
You're gonna need them.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
[Min Ho] Was any of it real?
[somber music playing]
No.
Not at first.
But then, you were different
than I thought you were going to be.
I liked you.
For real.
Only...
I could tell your heart
was never fully in it anyways.
[chimes jingle]
Congratulations, brother.
[Joon Ho] Thank you.
I know I haven't been the best brother,
but I want that to change.
Yeah, I'd like that.
[Moon] My two favorite sons.
Oh, favorite sons. Oh, finally.
[Joon Ho] Congratulations.
[crowd cheering]
[Moon] From five outstanding contestants,
all but Dae and Eunice
have been eliminated.
It was a tough call for the judges,
but a decision has been made.
The winner is...
[suspenseful music playing]
...Eunice Kang!
[gasps]
Oh my God!
Thank you!
[Moon] This summer,
Eunice will open for Joon Ho
on his worldwide "Sugar Daddy" tour.
[Dae] Congratulations. You deserve it.
Thank you so much!
[gasps] Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you so much! Thank you!
We tried.
Thanks for being such a great friend.
- We're all here for you, you know.
- Yeah.
[Praveena] Jules.
Hey.
Oh, I'm sorry Dae didn't win,
but you were brilliant out there.
You think so?
- Yeah.
- You want me to teach you?
[Praveena] Yeah, how about tonight?
Yuri! Hey, Yuri, wait.
[gloomy music playing]
[Juliana] Uh, I'm sorry.
Praveena and I, we got to talking
at the dance, and it was...
I should have told you.
You still mean a lot to me.
I hope that we could be friends.
I would love that.
[Kim gasps]
[in Korean] Dae!
- [chuckles]
- [Min Ho] Ah.
I'm so proud of you.
[sighs]
I wanted to win. We need the money.
Truthfully,
I didn't know how things would turn out,
so I didn't tell you.
A lawyer called.
There will be a class action lawsuit
against the Han Group.
From now on, we're going to be fine.
Don't worry.
[Alex sighs]
[in English] Yuri, I'm sorry.
[tearfully] She was supposed
to want me back.
- And now she's dating--
- Wait.
I thought Jina finally got a hold of you.
[sniffles] Wait, what happened?
It wasn't a mistake that
your credit cards were getting declined.
Your father's assets were frozen after
a development in a class action lawsuit.
[scoffs]
[Yuri] So, I'm broke.
[somber music playing]
[Min ho] Anyone else would have given up
on me. You really came through today.
[cell phone vibrates]
[phone unlocks]
Oh no.
What's wrong?
Margot and Halmoni were headed here
to reunite with Soon Ja,
but the flight got canceled.
Margot has a small window
before she goes Scotland for her job--
Covey! Calm down.
Why should I?
Because you know someone
whose dad owns a private jet.
[Kitty] Seriously?
[romantic music playing]
[sighs]
[Min Ho clears throat]
So, um, let me see what I can do about it.
Cool.
[jet engines roar]
[hopeful music playing]
[Kitty] Halmoni, you've got this.
[gasps]
[in Korean] Oh my, oh my goodness.
Sister?
[sobs]
[sniffles]
For 50 years,
I've thought about what I'd say
if I saw you again.
However,
seeing you now,
my heart is overwhelmed.
I'm deeply sorry.
[sighs]
[sniffles]
Sister, sister.
[both sobbing]
Sister.
Come with me. Come.
[uplifting music playing]
[both chuckle]
[door opens]
[chimes ring]
[chuckles]
[great-aunt] We want
to perform a jesa ritual for Eve.
I regret I didn't do it when she died...
Sister, I wanted to give this to you.
Thank you.
[in English] You did this.
I know how important sisters are.
People always say I'm the most like Mom,
but really, you are.
You bring people together.
She'd be so proud of you.
When I first came to Korea, I just wanted
to learn more about who Mom was.
But I have learned so much about myself.
I mean, this place, it's become just as
much a part of me as it was a part of her.
Now that I have all of this,
the last thing I want to do is leave.
Maybe you don't have to.
Hi, it's so nice to meet you!
[great-aunt in Korean]
Come on over, have some tea.
[pop music playing]
[Kitty in English] Staying at KISS
wouldn't be as simple
as Margot made it sound,
but for all the ways
I've changed this semester,
I'm still the girl who goes after
what she wants with everything she's got.
So, as soon as finals were over...
Well, I have good news.
Thanks to the renewed interest
from donors after the concert,
we've granted your request
to renew your heritage scholarship.
- [gasps]
- We'll see you next year, Ms. Covey.
Oh my God, thank you!
Can I give you a hug?
[tense music playing]
No, not a hugger. Right.
A high five?
I'll take it.
[Q] So?
Have you told Min Ho
the news about you staying?
Not yet.
Oh, come on. Don't play blasé.
He flew your grandmother
and your sister across the ocean.
You basically saved his family.
You two clearly have
some epic thing going on here.
I don't know if I would say "epic."
[pensive music playing]
I am just...
terrified. [sighs]
What if he doesn't feel
the same way anymore?
Plus, Stella really screwed him up.
[sighs]
Isn't it just
too complicated?
I think that's a question
only you can answer.
But if there is something
you want to tell him,
I happen to know he takes long walks
in the sculpture garden
around this time every day.
So, it's true.
Covey, what are you doing here?
Q told me you've been walking out here.
Just trying to clear my head before I go.
Go? Go where?
I'm leaving tonight, with Joon Ho
and my dad, on their big summer tour.
Oh, wow. Q did not tell me that.
Well, it was really
a last-minute decision.
I figure it will give me a chance
to bleach Stella from my brain.
I'm swearing off all relationships.
I think I was better off as a playboy.
Wait. Why were you looking for me?
Oh.
Right.
Um...
I just wanted to tell you...
[expectant music playing]
I'm coming back next year.
That's great, Covey.
[Kitty sighs]
Um...
The car should be here any minute now.
I should probably get going.
Um...
Have a great trip.
Thanks.
See you next year?
[softly] Yeah.
[bright, hopeful music playing]
[heart beating loudly]
[chimes ringing]
[dramatic string music rises]
[Kitty] Maybe it's not our time.
Not yet.
Or maybe...
Wait!
Can I join you?
["Changes" playing]
♪ Can I grow old ♪
♪ Like someone new? ♪
♪ Like someone special to you ♪
♪ Can I grow old ♪
♪ Like someone new? ♪
♪ Like someone special to you ♪
♪ Can I grow old ♪
♪ Like someone new? ♪
♪ Like someone special to you ♪
[uplifting pop song fades]