♪ I just can't let you go ♪
♪ No, I just can't let you go ♪
♪ I'm seeing smoke signals ♪
What is happening?
Q! I have something to tell you.
- Get up!
- Q!
Did you drink my collagen water?
Or was it you?
What? No.
My collagen water
is meant to keep my skin dewy.
Not rehydrate people
who can't handle their liquor.
My God, why are you screaming?
It's the middle of the night
and I'm still drunk.
No, it's not. It's 8:00 in the morning.
And thanks to some idiot,
my party dynasty has come
to an untimely end, so,
yeah, I am in a mood.
Are you in a mood to make me coffee?
Yes, but I will deeply resent you.
- I can live with that.
- Okay, Q, can I ask you something?
Yes, I drank his collagen water.
Not that.
Then no, I'm too tired for your questions.
You kept me up all night.
- I could hear you through the wall.
- I was loud? How?
Was I talking in my sleep?
Because people say all kinds
of crazy things in their sleep.
Like this one time,
I asked LJ to make me a BLT with mayo,
but I hate mayo.
No, no, you were not talking.
You were snoring.
Because I was drunk
and drunk people do tons of things
they don't normally do, like snore.
And have really weird dreams.
You had a sex dream. Was it about Dae?
- No.
- Oh, not Dae.
No. I didn't say that I had a sex dream.
Okay. You didn't have to. Spill.
It doesn't even matter,
dreams don't mean anything.
She's right. They don't mean anything.
You can have a sex dream about
someone you're repulsed by in real life.
Yes, exactly. Thank you, Min Ho.
Min Ho could have a sex dream
about, like, me.
- You had a sex dream about Kitty.
- No, I didn't.
If I did have a sex dream about Kitty,
it'd be a sex nightmare.
- Oh, my God.
- I'm not hearing a denial.
It doesn't matter,
dreams don't mean anything.
- Exactly, I hate mayo.
- And I hate Kitty!
Thank you.
Sex dreams mean something.
Resident advisor.
- Uh...
- Using master key.
Well, I hope last night was worth it
because you're all in big trouble.
Saturday detention?
Come on.
You and your friends are lucky
that's the extent of it.
Do you know how embarrassing
this is for me?
For the school?
Have you checked your phone?
What? I wasn't even drinking last night.
That doesn't matter.
The narrative is out there.
And it's not just the school.
This puts your father's business at risk,
after we worked so hard
to rehabilitate the family image.
We need to arrange a photo-op
for you and Dae.
Maybe church tomorrow?
Oh. It's unwise of you
to have an attitude about this
if you want your credit card back.
I'm sorry, you're right.
I'll do whatever you want.
So, what does this mean for Iceland?
You have some nerve
even asking me about that right now.
What now?
Hey, I'm not having a
great morning. Can we talk after...?
Let's break up.
Dae, I'm sorry about the necklace.
But right now is really not the...
Whatever! It has nothing to do with me.
We both still need this.
I need to see Juliana. And you...
No, I'm fine. I've saved some money,
and I don't want to lose Kitty
because of you.
Why?
Why did you take it?
Because I was jealous.
- What?
- Because I thought I might lose you.
During Chuseok,
I felt like we became real friends.
But when I saw Kitty's necklace,
I thought you might want
to go back to her.
- Then you'd be done with me.
- Friends?
- Is that something a real friend would do?
- I know. I made a mistake.
And I'll make it right, okay?
I'll see you in detention.
I'm dying, come here!
Yes, just leave the food on the bed!
Hi, I'm looking for Kitty...
your roommate?
Oh, yeah, she's not here.
Hasn't been here in weeks.
I have no idea where she's been sleeping.
I do.
Ugh. This sucks.
I wanted to work out and then chill.
Then work out again.
- I was going to study anyway.
- Really?
Yeah, finals are coming up,
and with my scholarship
I need to keep my grades up.
I need to study too.
Nerds.
Hey, some of us have divorcing parents
ready for any slip-up
to demand us moving home.
And adorable little distractions
we keep making out with
when we should be finishing our papers.
Indeed, Florian.
Your paper on the war-inspired poetry
of Chinua Achebe was superb.
Really?
If only you hadn't turned it in
a day late.
Phones, gentleman.
Flo, are you falling behind because of me?
A little,
but don't worry about Professor Lee.
- I'm his fave.
- Attention, students.
Your precious digital appendages
will be returned when detention is over.
Eight hours from now.
You have your friend, Ms. Song Covey
to thank for that.
That's right.
She was kind enough
to alert me to last night's shenanigans.
It was you?
This could be fun, though.
Like The Breakfast Club, right?
Hey, babe.
Last night was memorable.
Why are you even in here?
You didn't get caught at the party.
Hmm.
How did you not get caught?
Please, I've snuck out of every window
of every boarding school
from here to Antarctica.
Ms. Miller,
this is not a time for socializing.
Hey, did you talk to Yuri?
Yuri? Why would I talk to Yuri?
I really barely know her.
I don't want to talk to Yuri
or do anything else with her.
Hey - you - that necklace...
Weren't you going to return it to Kitty?
Why are you wearing it?
What are you going to do about it?
- What?
- You can't break up with me.
Or I'll tell on Kitty for living with you
in the boys' dorm.
And that would get her expelled
from school.
- Yuri Han...
- No, I get it.
You, Min Ho, Q,
all saving sweet innocent Kitty
from the big bad Yuri.
You only said you're my friend
because you wanted something from me.
- Yuri. I'm sorry...
- For what? For not telling me?
For making me feel bad?
Or getting caught lying?
Why do you have my necklace?
- You gave it to her?
- No, I didn't.
- She stole it before I even got it.
- Dae. Ladies.
Take your seats, please.
Professor Lee, I need to discuss...
Where did you get my necklace?
What? That's my necklace.
It was my mom's.
Oh.
My mistake.
Now I can see that it's not mine.
Will you excuse me?
First, she pretends
she doesn't know mom
and now she thinks mom's necklace is hers?
All of you, in your seats.
Now.
Are you all right?
Of course.
I recognize that necklace.
You and Eve Song got them together.
Why didn't you tell me
Kitty was Eve's daughter?
Why would I have?
Does it matter?
Should not have had that coffee.
Attention, students.
Apparently, I am needed
in the gymnasium briefly.
He has to poop.
Definitely.
Madison Miller,
you've proven yourself trustworthy.
You are in charge while I'm gone.
Please make sure
everyone is quietly studying.
Yes, sir.
You heard him. Eyes down.
Kidding. Do whatever.
But be careful, if you're going to vape,
crack a window.
You, keep watch by the door
and warn us when Lee's coming back.
What? Haven't any of you
ever gotten stuck in a Saturday detention
and kept the party going
when your teacher leaves the room?
Oh, y'all are so cute.
Okay. Poker game will start
in the World History Section,
make-outs move in back by the rare books.
I like an organized chaos.
Go.
Come with me to the yearbooks.
Why?
Please?
You, me, rare books.
Let's go.
Wait, what?
Look, I know you've been living with Dae
and you know I stole your mom's necklace,
but can we please put a pin in our drama?
I need to know why my mom loses her shit
whenever anything about your mom comes up.
Yeah, I do too.
That first day
I introduced myself to your mom,
she acted like she barely knew my mom,
but if you look at the photo album,
there are so many photos of them together.
And, did you know they were roommates?
- They were?
- Yes.
Did she say something weird happened
between them?
No, just that they weren't close.
But maybe she was lying about that.
And that's why we need to find
more photos of our moms.
I need to know what she's hiding.
To understand her better?
No, to destroy her.
Damn, that's terrifying.
But I'm in.
Okay, we need to find 1993.
That's the only year
that's missing.
Maybe someone just put it back
in the wrong spot?
Or maybe my mom got rid of it.
This morning was so weird.
She thought that my necklace was hers.
Maybe they both had one
and wore them like friendship necklaces.
Then something happened
to make them not friends.
Yes, like... Professor Lee.
Maybe he came between them.
Random, but I'm listening.
I love love triangles.
Uh, what are you two doing here?
We were gonna go make out.
We're official.
I proposed.
But this seems fun too.
I saw some very intense body language
between your mom and Lee this morning.
- They did go to KISS at the same time.
- Yeah, I know.
It all makes sense.
Jina was in love with Lee,
but Lee ended up choosing Eve in the end.
Tragic.
Why are we assuming he chose Eve?
Maybe he chose my mom
and Eve was the tragic one.
Regardless, we need to find this yearbook.
My mom might have one in her office.
I know she's stuck in a board meeting
right now.
The sooner I find what her secret is,
the sooner I can use it against her.
So are you with me or what?
I'm with you.
Check the shelves, I'll check her desk.
Okay.
Oh, my God, here's my file.
I can't believe this.
She has my mom's obituary.
Look.
Wow, I guess my mom's
an even better liar than I am.
She's hiding something big.
But what?
I have an idea.
He's coming.
Oh, assume your positions.
Shh!
Thank you, Ms. Miller.
It looks like
you kept everything under control.
My pleasure.
Lunch time. Write down your orders.
Get them back to me
as quickly as possible.
Feel free to stretch your legs,
your arms, whatever needs stretching.
We have one hour and one hour only.
- What do you wanna eat?
- I don't know.
How can I think about food right now?
I'm going crazy worrying
about what Yuri and Kitty are up to.
Whatever it is,
it's not your business, dude.
Kitty wants to learn about her mom.
She didn't just come here to stalk you.
You're right.
I'll guess I'll just order their lunch.
All right.
Mm-mm. No, she likes the tuna gimbap
without mayo.
What, are you an expert on Kitty?
Yeah, I'm living with her,
thanks to someone.
I also wish I didn't know this much
about the girl who ruined my party.
I know what
you're gonna order.
What? No, you don't.
We've never shared a meal.
The bulgogi gimbap, extra kimchi.
Students, roll call before lunch.
Hey, they're not here yet.
He's going to catch them.
I got this.
No, you cannot have your phone back.
I don't need a phone.
I'm in the library.
I am surrounded by knowledge
and I couldn't help
but notice you're reading Gilgamesh.
I'm obsessed with Sumerian epic poetry.
And you have
the Benjamin Foster translation.
I... I die.
- Florian.
- Yes?
You never cease to amaze.
I have a wonderful picture book
depicting the original,
ancient cuneiform tablets.
I would love to see that.
Well, I would never hold back
on sharing a book with a keen student.
I'll go get it.
It's just in my home office.
Ms. Miller, you're in charge.
Oh.
Thank you so much, Professor Lee.
So we're official, boyfriend.
You're so cute I could vomit.
Oh.
Um, hello?
Q, can you hear me?
Kitty?
Where are you?
I'm on Professor Lee's
landline in his house.
Thank God he did not take your watch.
Wait, did you memorize my number?
Lee was in the same class as our moms
so he might have the yearbook
we're trying to find.
Kitty.
I'll be back soon. Cover for us.
What?
The cuneiform.
- What? Right.
- He went home.
♪ All for freedom and for pleasure... ♪
Oh, my God. Go, go, go.
Oh, my God, it's Lee.
What is he doing here?
This way.
♪ ...rule the world ♪
♪ I can't stand this indecision ♪
♪ Married with a lack of vision ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♪ A lack of vision ♪
That was my mom's favorite song.
My mom loves that song too.
Look. Look.
It's 1993.
There they are...
wearing the necklaces.
- Like BFFs.
- Mm-hm.
At least your mom looks cute.
My mom looks like
she just gained the junior 30.
Hello, I just fat-shamed.
You're supposed to call me out now.
Oh, wow. I got this so wrong.
I get it.
You do?
I should have
given it to you this morning.
Or never taken it in the first place.
We should get back to the library
before Professor Lee.
Yes, I know a shortcut.
Oh, my God.
♪ Beep, beep ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ I see that I'm icy
Go rising, up, up ♪
Icy but I'm on fire... ♪
Shh!
♪ I see that I'm icy ♪
Enjoy.
Students, roll call.
- Kon.
- Here.
- Mihee.
- Min Ho.
- Here.
- David.
- Florian.
- Yeah, here.
- Eunice.
- Here.
- Leo.
- I'm here.
Do something.
- Jiyung.
- Here.
Watch this.
Professor Lee?
I have an emergency.
Yes?
Well, it's personal.
Ms. Miller would like to inquire
if any of the girls here...
Any of the women... Women here,
have any lady supplies she can borrow.
- Have.
- I've got tampons.
I have pads.
Amaze-balls.
Thank you.
Amaze-balls. Thank you.
Why did you take the necklace?
Because I'm an idiot.
But I'm not going to be anymore.
Hey, can I borrow your Apple watch?
I have a really important
phone call to make.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Gasp!
Your sex dream was about Yuri, wasn't it?
Mm-hm.
Look who's the matchmaker now.
- It's me.
- I know.
Okay. Yeah.
I hope this day
has allowed all of you to understand
the consequences of your actions.
Underage drinking is a serious offense,
it is never a good decision,
understand?
Weird day.
You think?
I'm glad you're okay.
I was really worried about you last night,
as your teacher and as your half-brother.
Yeah, about that.
I have something to show you.
Look, this is May 1993.
And that's my mom,
clearly not pregnant, but Jina...
Oh, my God.
Principal Lim.
Principal Lim...
could be my mother.
Hey, the paparazzi's here.
I know.
I called them.
With Q's Apple watch.
Why?
You will see.
What's going on?
I'm so sick of this.
You're obviously still in love with Kitty.
Don't even try to deny it.
Sorry.
You're free now.
♪ "Think easy" she said ♪
♪ "Forever young and so wild ♪
♪ Or pull a gun and then fire it" ♪
♪ "It's easy" she said... ♪
What are you doing?
What I should have done
the minute you got here.
♪ We still got walls
On those sides, maybe ♪
♪ I wanna know how to climb ♪
♪ We're blind, blind ♪
♪ How'd we get air all this time ♪
♪ These things ♪
♪ I never thought when you were mine ♪
♪ We used to break it together ♪
Dreams are just dreams.
But this, this is real.
And it's really happening.
♪ I don't wanna miss anything
When I'm dreaming ♪
♪ We used to break it together ♪
♪ We used to dive
In our highest feelings ♪
♪ Are we growing older together? ♪
♪ I don't wanna miss anything
When I'm dreaming ♪
♪ About when we were dazed and confused ♪