[energetic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, sorry.
Yeah. You've been saying that a lot.
[Kitty] Things have been pretty tense
since I let it slip to Professor Lee
that Yuri and Juliana are dating.
Like I said, I swear
I didn't know Lee was standing there.
It was a total accident.
So you're ruining lives without trying?
- I really am sorry.
- [message alert chimes]
[clicks tongue] I've never seen
such deep regret.
Oh. No, this is Praveena.
[sighs] I was so worried that
I messed things up the night at the club.
You were ignoring her
'cause you were obsessing over Yuri?
That was because she was upset,
to be fair.
And something you totally solved.
Yeah, with your advice.
Who even remembers the details?
I think Praveena
could still be my first kiss.
First girl kiss. Right?
I have some work
that I gotta get done before class.
No, I can shut up. Don't leave.
You can finish your cereal.
[Juliana] Kitty, I have to go.
[whimsical music playing]
[under breath] Cool.
- [door closes]
- [sighs]
[bright music plays]
[music fades]
[in Korean] I can't believe
you have to work this weekend.
It's Seollal.
Our ancestors won't mind
that we had tteokguk a day early.
- [sighs]
- [Mr. Kim chuckles]
- [yawns]
- I'm just worried about you.
- You just work all the time.
- [sighs]
I'm the dad and you're worrying about me?
When did you get so grown up?
You're all grown up!
- ["Camellia Lady" playing]
- Ahh, this song is so good!
This is a bit of an old song,
but it's one of your mother's favorites.
You're right. Her favorite song.
[bittersweet ballad continues]
[singing along in Korean]
You're really good at singing, huh?
It's such a relief
you take after your mom.
[Dae chuckles]
- I'm taking off.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Okay. I'll be home later.
- Okay.
[Dae sighs]
Hey, Dae Kim!
Hey.
How is it living back home?
Oh, well. My room's
a bit smaller, but it's fine.
Your dad didn't say anything
about living with your mom?
Oh, he was furious and said
I was taking my mom's side.
[in English] I do miss living
in the dorms, though.
I miss Juliana, and I miss... Kitty!
Hey!
[Dae] Hey.
[Juliana] Yuri!
Uh, we can talk later.
- [Dae] Bye!
- [Yuri] 'Kay. Bye, Kitty.
- Baby, I missed you so much.
- [Juliana] Mm.
At least we don't have to hide
that we're dating anymore.
[Yuri] Mm.
One silver lining
of us not living together.
- [sighs] Thank God.
- [chuckles]
[energetic music playing]
So, how's my favorite student doing?
A bit early for blatant nepotism, Dad.
I was talking
to your girlfriend, the shark.
[sighs] Sorry about that. Again.
It's okay. I loved it.
So, have you decided
about the ski cabin for the long weekend?
Just you and me, one-on-one on the slopes?
You used to love
when I took you skiing as a kid.
That was Joon Ho, not me.
Anyways, Stella and I have plans
this weekend.
Well, it would be a shame
to let this house go to waste. Again.
Your dad's not doing
a Seollal get-together with the family?
All my siblings are spending
the holidays with their moms.
Joon Ho is on tour,
meaning I'm his last resort.
It sounds like he's putting in the effort.
You never know.
This could be a chance to--
Torture myself? Forget it.
All right. Come on.
Let's get this assembly over with.
[energetic music playing]
As part of our Lunar New Year celebration,
you'll see traditional decorations
around our school,
including bokjori.
Now, we have Ms. Miller,
one of the students
on the Festival Planning Committee,
to tell you all about it.
A bokjori is a tool
to sift dirt from rice,
and for Seollal, it represents
good fortune in the new year.
Thank you, Ms. Miller.
As always, your knowledge
of Korean culture is very admirable.
[in Korean] It's my honor.
- [students murmur]
- [in English] Exactly.
[girls laugh]
We'll also have our yearly opening
of the time capsule
of the graduating class 40 years prior.
These time capsules are a pillar
of KISS's ongoing commitment
to preserving our school's history.
Or KISS-tory, if you will.
- [student coughs]
- Um... [clears throat]
And documenting the experiences
of our heritage scholarship students.
Oh, that's my mom's scholarship.
Unfortunately, we will not be doing
our own capsule this year,
as that time and budget has been allocated
to less academic pursuits.
Which is where I come in,
just in time, before you all fall asleep.
[students laugh]
In the spirit of Seollal,
I have a gift for you.
To celebrate the new arts center,
I am hosting a student talent showcase
at the end of the semester.
- [exclaims]
- [students murmur]
And the winner... will receive a cash prize!
[students gasp]
[triumphant music plays]
Dae, you have to enter the contest.
You have the voice of an angel.
My family could use the money.
But singing is just, like, my hobby.
I got you, bro. I'll coach you.
Manager-performer dream team, baby.
- And I won't even take commission.
- [chuckles]
But do you think I could actually win?
Yeah.
Okay, then. Let's do it.
Alex!
Kitty!
My mom must've put something
in that time capsule for the scholarship.
It might tell me more
about my Korean family.
Right, but they're not gonna open
your mom's time capsule
for several more years.
Okay, well, maybe you can make
an exception for me?
I wish, but Dad's in charge
of the time capsules.
[Kitty] So that's a no-go.
Yeah. I've gotta go prep class.
I'll see you soon, okay?
Okay.
[exhales]
How's living with Kitty?
[clicks tongue] Chill, I guess.
She's all googly-eyed for Praveena,
which would be kinda cute if I wasn't
so annoyed that she blew our cover,
which I know
wasn't on purpose, but... [sighs]
For what it's worth,
I actually like living with my mom again.
We've had a lot of good talks.
You were so right
that I needed to reach out to her.
Uh...
What?
I need to tell you something.
It was actually Kitty's idea for you
to reach out to your mom, not mine.
Wait, what?
She just knew exactly what you needed.
And I guess that made me insecure,
so I recycled her idea as my own,
and I'm... really sorry.
[gentle music playing]
I don't care whose idea it was.
You're not mad?
No, of course not. [chuckles softly]
Okay.
So you're just gonna march in there
and ask for the time capsule?
Yeah.
You must get your cockiness
from your white side.
[both chuckle]
Oh look, there's your girl.
- Hey, Kitty. Q.
- [Kitty] Hey.
What's up, Prav? Might I say,
your bangs are banging today.
[sighs] Thank you literally so much.
Are you guys heading to the gym?
No, the archives building.
I'm hoping they let me open the capsule
from when my mom was here.
Unlikely. I was an aide
in the archives last semester.
You need clearance
for access to the time capsules,
so if you want it,
you're gonna have to steal it.
Uh, Kitty, friendly reminder
that you have priors.
I got you. I know the old lady
that guards the archives building.
It'll be a breeze to get past her.
How's tomorrow night at nine?
It's a date.
Cool.
- See you guys later.
- [Q] Bye.
Q! Did you mess with my lucky sneakers?
They're filled with glue.
- [tense music playing]
- Oh.
Jin, I think you're projecting.
See, I would never do anything
to jeopardize a teammate like that.
Careful. You have
no idea how low I can go.
Actually, I do.
And, uh... it's a lot lower than that.
[Jin sighs]
[tense music fades out]
[gentle music playing]
Hey. What are you still doing here?
- Hanging out with Juliana?
- I'm headed home.
What's up with you?
You look freakishly perky.
Well, I may or may not
be planning a small heist
to steal the time capsule
from our moms' class.
What? Like, how do you come up with
these ideas?
This one was Praveena's, actually.
We're kinda doing it together.
I'm jealous.
What?
I just mean, that's how we bonded
last year, you know?
Do you want to come? I mean,
I could always use another set of eyes.
And crash your date? No, thanks.
But I will catch the next one.
[upbeat music playing]
Hey, you all right?
What is Eunice doing here?
I think your best shot to win the contest
is performing a pop duet.
To win with this crowd,
you need the three S's.
Sex appeal, spandex, smoke machine,
and... choreo.
That's actually three S's and a C.
Plus, I don't want to dance.
It's okay. Choreo's simple, see?
One, two, and three, four.
- And five, six, seven, eight, and one.
- Whoa. Whoa. [sighs]
[Eunice] Right?
Simple.
[sighs]
- ["Colors" by Aimers playing]
- Three, four, and five.
- Six... No. No.
- [Dae] No.
- It's like this.
- [Dae] Okay.
- One, two, three, four.
- [Eunice] One, two, three...
No! Not that much.
[panting]
- And one--
- One, two...
- Okay.
- [Dae] What?
No.
One, two, and three.
- [Dae sighs]
- No. It's giving flamingo!
- [song ends]
- This isn't gonna work.
It is not my fault that you can't handle
a little constructive criticism.
[Stella] Okay.
Why don't you tell them
your brilliant idea?
Well, I thought of the cherry on top
for your performance.
When the song ends, you spin around,
bend her back, and lay one on her.
What do you mean, "lay one on her"?
What I mean is...
- [Stella sighs]
- [Eunice gasps]
Oh.
Perfect!
Absolutely not.
My boy's right.
Your instinct is so spot on, son.
[cheeky music playing]
All right, I won't distract you.
I just wanted to say Baek Jong Won said
he'll be happy to cook a dinner
at the cabin this weekend.
I know you love his ramyun.
The famous chef?
[Moon] Yeah. He's just a family friend.
Think about it. [clicks tongue]
[music fades]
[sighs] Your dad's really trying.
Where were we?
I... was just about to leave.
Hm.
Sorry. I can't do this. [sighs]
Dae.
[Eunice] Yo.
[Min Ho] Dae!
[Q grunts]
[groans] What?
[sighs]
You. How did you even manage
to shrink polyester?
- Turnabout's fair play, Quincy.
- Fair play?
- [Jin] Mm.
- [Q] You took my spot at regionals.
I don't know what you think this is,
but I don't want to do it anymore.
I thought this was flirting.
Well, I'm not interested. [sighs]
[gloomy music playing]
Oh, mate.
You're gonna have to change.
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh great. You brought the muscle.
I'm the muscle?
Don't get too excited.
We just need someone
tall enough to reach the high shelf.
And Dae and Q were busy, so...
Okay. Huddle up. Here's the plan.
I'll distract the old lady.
[gasps]
[in Korean] It's been a long time!
Mrs. Park! Are your grandkids doing well?
They're doing well.
I got the girls matching hanboks.
- Yes! Let's see!
- Hmm. Where did I put it?
Let's see here.
[inhales sharply] Oh.
[in English] Why are we going
through all this?
Because I have
a whole other side of my family
that my mom came here to find.
So if this time capsule has
a clue on how I can track them down,
I have to have it.
[whispers] How touching.
Personally, I'd love to erase
the existence of half my family.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but did your dad not fund an entire
arts program to spend time with you?
That's his move. Big, shallow gesture
to make up for not being there.
Like inviting me
to a ski cabin for Seollal.
Well, do you want to fix things with him?
I guess so, but, uh...
One-on-one time
with him is always stressful.
It'd be different if there were
a bunch of family members around,
like there's supposed to be on Seollal.
Or even just very loud
and chatty people like yourself.
- [Kitty] Mm.
- As a buffer.
[takes a deep breath]
What if we did that?
Use me as your buffer?
Well, you and the guys.
I mean, it'd be more fun
than hanging out here for the holiday.
And we'll have your back
if your dad's being difficult.
["Keeping the Fire" playing]
[Praveena, shouting] Professor Lee,
I can assure you I know aisle 12!
- This is aisle 12! Move!
- [Praveena] Like the back of my hand!
[Lee] Why are you shouting?
I am perfectly capable
of hearing you as well.
[Praveena] Okay.
- I'm not as old as you think.
- I don't think you're old!
- [Lee] My goodness.
- [Praveena] Uh...
- Here it is.
- Ah.
Festival decorations.
Great job finding that!
[loudly] Uh, I guess we'll go now!
[Lee] You should try out
for the musical next year.
- [Praveena] You think?
- [Lee] That projection.
[intense pop song ends]
[both sigh in relief]
[door closes]
Praveena just saved our asses.
I mean, it's only our second date.
[chuckles]
"Date"? [scoffs]
She's sweet-talking an old lady
whilst you're in close quarters
with the hottest guy in school.
[softly] Okay.
I'm just saying. It's not much of a date.
[inhales sharply]
Why don't you bring her skiing?
- That's kind of a big step.
- [Min Ho sighs]
Oh my God, I think that's it.
[energetic music playing]
[Min Ho] I think you might be right.
Well, don't just stand there.
Go get it down.
Put those tiny gloves to use.
That's why you're here, dude.
[exclaims] I cannot believe
that actually worked.
Oh, I wish I had a way to thank you.
Oh, please.
Praveena, do you ski?
No, but I snowboard.
Any chance you want to come with us
this weekend to Min Ho's dad's ski cabin?
You're inviting me to
the Kris Jenner of Korea's vacation home?
Hell yeah, I wanna come.
[giggles] Cool.
- I can't wait.
- Nice.
[energetic music fades]
- [cell phone chimes]
- [Yuri] Wow.
[chuckles] What are you doing?
[Yuri] I want to document your work
before the unveiling of your masterpiece
at the Seoul Art Festival.
It is going to kill.
[Juliana] I'm actually really excited
for you to see it finished.
[exhales]
[sighs deeply]
Remember last spring
when I told you I liked you?
We were in here.
I couldn't forget that if I tried.
- [Yuri] Mm.
- Although I did already know.
Why else would Yuri Han be spending
so much time around art supplies?
I got paint on my brand-new Loewe bag
because of you.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
- [chuckles]
- [cell phone chimes]
- What do you think?
- [Yuri sighs]
Ski weekend? Could be fun.
[sighs] I'm supposed to go to Daegu
to see my keun imo with my mom.
Right. Okay.
[groans]
Screw it. Let's go.
[Praveena sighs]
What?
Come on. I'm not saying yes
because Kitty's going.
It just seems like I can't go a minute
without Kitty just busting in
and Kitty-ing all over everything.
Well, Kitty can bust in
wherever she wants,
but she is not busting
into this relationship.
You're cute.
[serene music playing]
[birds singing]
- [music fades]
- Yuri! Wait up.
You will not believe
what I found in the time capsule.
[Yuri] "Eve Song's Heritage Project,
Directed by Jina Lim." Oh my God.
I know.
- I've been waiting to watch it with you.
- Aw.
I also cannot find
any VHS players anywhere.
I know a place that rents them,
but I do have to be back
for Juliana's art opening.
Oh. I can go alone.
[chuckles] No, are you kidding?
We're in this together.
Just like them.
- Let's go.
- [giggles]
[indistinct chatter]
[cell phone vibrates]
- [Yuri] Here it is.
- [Kitty] Oh.
Wait, it's closed.
- Oh no, it's permanently closed.
- [sighs]
Wait. Their new location is at...
Is it far?
Your face is telling me it's far.
Oh no, it's not. [inhales sharply]
But it is rush hour,
so we should get going.
We are not going
back to school empty-handed.
- We can watch it after the festival.
- What would I do without you?
- [chimes jingle]
- [light, romantic music plays]
[chimes jingle]
[music fades out slowly]
Uh, I'm gonna go get us a cab.
[softly] Okay.
- [excited chatter]
- [energetic dance music playing]
Juliana? Your painting is wonderful.
[sighs] Thanks.
Oh, that's you and Yuri.
Yeah.
She was supposed to be here to see it.
You're really talented, Juliana.
Thanks.
[sighs deeply]
[tense music playing]
[Praveena] Kitty cat.
- [Kitty] Hey.
- There you are.
- Come on. Let's go grab some tteokguk.
- [quietly] Okay.
[somber music playing]
Wait, babe, babe, babe.
I'm so sorry. My phone died.
I needed you here. And obviously,
whatever you were doing with Kitty
was more important to you
than being here for me.
- No, you don't understand. That's--
- I think I do.
Wait, Juliana.
[in Korean] Thank you.
- [in English] Thank you.
- Oh my goodness.
- I get the first bite?
- Here you go. Yes, you do.
[bright music playing]
It's so good.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- What did I tell you?
- [Yuri] Wait, Juliana!
[sighs] Kitty.
This weekend isn't gonna be
like our first date, right? Because that--
Was not cool.
No, and I promise that it won't be.
And I was thinking that this weekend
could maybe be our chance
to find out what could be.
And my hopes, they're up here.
Because I like you. A lot.
All right. Fine.
[peppy pop music playing]
[in Korean] Bora, that's your last sweet.
Here to give me feedback?
[in English] Constructive criticism?
[in Korean] No. I know I'm a little
intense when it comes to practice.
But don't quit the contest because of me.
I promise I'll take it easy
from now on. Cool?
Honestly? I just don't know
if I'm good enough.
Honestly, you need to practice.
It's about muscle memory. You need
to practice until your body memorizes it.
If you practice, there's nothing...
[chuckles]
But you've got an amazing voice.
I wouldn't sing a duet
with you if you didn't.
[dreamy music playing]
Is that your sister?
[Dae] Mm-hmm.
She's the cute one in the family.
I think there might be more than one.
[chuckles lightly]
[music fades]
- [Q] Okay.
- [group laughs]
Oh, man, that's pretty good.
That's really good. Right?
[group chattering]
Oh, come on.
Wait. Wait, look.
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry for all of it.
I was desperate to win,
which is not an excuse,
but it's harder getting scouted
when you go to an international school.
Yeah, no shit.
My dad ran the 400 hurdles
for South Korea in the 1988 Olympics,
so if I don't get scouted to a D1 school
on scholarship at the very least,
I'm a failure.
Look, I don't have Olympians in my family.
- Lucky.
- But I have doctors.
And they're literally in the Philippines,
saving lives and being geniuses.
Meanwhile, I'm still hung up
on the C I got in bio last semester, so
I get it.
[gentle music playing]
The... failure thing.
But what you did...
it really hurt me.
Not just taking the spot
at regionals, but...
playing with my emotions to sabotage me.
I know.
If you want me
to talk to Coach Alex, I will.
It's probably too late for that now.
You'd actually do that for me, though?
[Kitty] Q!
- Hey!
- Um...
I'll catch you later?
I'm counting on it.
[chuckles]
Are you guys fighting or another F-word?
Katherine Song Covey!
Flirting!
My matchmaker spidey senses are tingling.
[scoffs] Yeah, well, don't go telling
Dae and Min Ho about it.
They're... not the biggest Jin fans.
Oh, no, I'm aware.
Did he actually used to steal
Min Ho's hair products?
- He did.
- [laughs] What? Why?
Can you blame him?
They're probably expensive.
[Kitty] We should go pack for the trip.
[knocking on door]
Oh. Hey. Juliana's not here. It's just me.
I know. She's hiding
in her art studio to avoid me. And you.
Well, I'm really glad you're here.
I am dying to watch this tape.
You didn't watch it without me?
No, like you said,
we're in this together. Come on.
[gentle music playing]
[Kitty exhales]
Hi. This is Eve Song's
family heritage project.
And I'm your host, Jina Lim!
Good to know my mom's always had
main character syndrome.
Here, Seojoon. Take the camera.
[Seojoon] Isn't this project supposed
to be about me? I should be in it.
Hey, it's about your role
in my life, Seojoon.
[Seojoon] So am I your cousin
or your cameraman?
[laughs]
Wait, I bet "Seojoon"
is Simon's Korean name.
- That's Simon talking.
- And they sound like such good friends.
- [Jina] Bicker on your own time.
- [Eve laughs]
[Jina] So, where will Eve Hyejin Song be
in 40 years?
Oh... well, hopefully you and I
will still be friends.
[Jina] Aww.
Maybe we've settled down
in neighboring houses.
[Seojoon scoffs] Eve spends
all her money on magazines.
She'll never save up enough
for her own place.
I can move in with you and Hana
if you take my advice and ask her out.
You two would make
such a great couple. [scoffs]
Anyway, by the time
this time capsule is opened,
I'll be in my fifties.
Wow. [sighs]
I'll be an award-winning journalist,
married to someone smart and kind.
And we'll have kids. At least one.
A girl, I hope.
And I hope I'll visit Korea with my mom.
I want her to show me around Bukjeon.
That's her hometown.
[Kitty crying softly]
[Eve] Maybe by then,
she'll be on speaking terms
with her sister again.
What do you think, Seojoon?
[Seojoon] I don't know.
We've been trying
to get them to talk for months.
- [Eve] And we're not giving up yet.
- [sniffles]
I came here to heal our family.
[static crackles on TV]
Why isn't it working?
[Kitty sniffles]
- Oh, Kitty.
- [sighs]
[gently] Are you okay?
I've never seen a video
of my mom at this age before.
[sniffles]
At my age.
I mean, she sounds just like Margot.
She looks exactly like Lara Jean.
She...
She was a meddler like you. [chuckles]
[laughs sadly]
When I come back from skiing,
I am going to Bukjeon,
and I am finding my family.
[softly] Yuri.
Will you come with me?
Of course.
I'll always be there for you.
What?
["Have I Been on Your Mind?"
by Roman Kayz playing]
- [chimes jingling]
- [romantic intro playing]
♪ Have I been on your mind, baby? ♪
♪ Baby, baby, ah... ♪
Covey, cars are here. Let's go.
[song ends abruptly]
[calming music playing]
[music ends]
[balloons expanding]