I wake up
And I text you first
Overthinking every word…
A week ago, I thought my life was over.
Teenage girls, am I right?
But now that I'm hydrated, showered,
and fully restocked
on my supply of Lara Jean optimism,
I'm back to my old self.
Not everything's the same.
Some wounds take longer to heal
than others.
Min Ho still won't talk to me.
But you know what? That's his problem.
Like LJ said, I can't stop living my life.
It's still our senior year, after all,
and time is flying by.
It's official!
I am sailing around the world
on my dad's yacht
next year after graduation.
If you can live
with that carbon footprint, have fun.
Wow, an eco-attack?
Yeah, I heard the insult.
I wasn't trying to hide it.
Damn, now Mihee
and Madison have beef? What is going on?
Sorry. Didn't mean to get between you two.
Again.
Jin, come on. That's not--
Good choice.
Too bad he didn't choose you back.
Hey.
You okay?
I'm fine.
I feel awful about my part in this,
so if there's anything I can do to help--
You can help by staying out of it, Kitty.
Okay. I will.
For what it's worth, I hope you know
I never meant to blow up your spot.
In hindsight,
I should have been honest with Jin.
I kind of get why you weren't.
You made a big mistake,
and you couldn't take it back.
You were scared to lose him.
And I did.
But that's not on you.
I actually managed
to make things worse all by myself.
I heard about you and Min Ho.
I'm really sorry.
Thank you.
I can't believe we both went
through breakups without each other.
I miss you telling me
things are gonna be okay,
even when I know they're not.
And I miss leaning on you.
And your rock-hard abs.
Can we please hug it out?
Let's never fight again.
Deal.
So…
What else did I miss?
Well, I applied early decision to NYU.
We're gonna be
in the same country for uni?
- Don't jinx it.
- Okay.
But maybe. JFK to LAX, baby!
Thank God we made up.
But why is everyone else fighting?
I'm out of commission for one week,
and suddenly our friend group falls apart?
I have to fix this.
Ugh!
Yuri, what are you doing?
Well, Yuri asked Yisoo
to critique her looks
for the Designer Breakthrough contest,
and…
I got two looks in before she said,
"I don't get it.
Where are you in these designs?"
She told me to rethink everything.
In two days?
I know. I thought fashion week
was going to be my comeback
after the world watched me
go down in flames.
Wait, maybe that's it.
You're not rich anymore.
Uh, wow, Kitty.
Way to kick a diva when she's down.
Listen. Listen. Listen.
Kitty is right.
- These designs were the old you.
- Exactly.
Who is the new Yuri?
I don't know.
I can't just "find myself"
and create all-new looks in 48 hours.
Okay, well, you're not going to give up.
We can fix this.
Juliana can help brainstorm new concepts,
and I'll get everyone
to pitch in and help.
How? Our friend group has more drama
than a middle school production of Wicked.
Well, I just mended things with Q,
so I'll just mend a little more.
The only drama you're gonna see
is on the runway,
because we are having this fashion show.
The mission, ten new looks, 48 hours.
All I need now is a crack team
crazy enough to pull it off.
With a little friendly matchmaking,
boom, we help Yuri blow Seoul away.
- What have you got in mind?
- You're a fashionable dude.
- How are you with a needle and thread?
- Capable.
When you're this messy inside,
you got to tailor the outside.
Plus, my nana taught me needlepoint
when I was ten.
Wonderful. Hope she
also taught you how to play nice,
because Q and Jin will be there. Goodbye.
We need someone fast.
- You're looking at him.
- With scissors.
To cut patterns.
Jin said he'd be there.
I cornered him in a boba shop
and held his oolong milk tea hostage.
- You should have led with that. I'm in.
- Great. So is Marius.
- Love you!
- Kitty…
I need a makeup pro.
Think you can bring it?
Uh, duh. My face is my résumé.
I need someone who can get
people's locks on lock. You'd be perfect.
Obvi. This doesn't just happen.
Great.
Can you get our model stage-ready?
Sorry, Kitty.
My days in the limelight are done.
Well, Yuri's are just beginning.
Come on.
You know what it's like to dream big.
Fine. I'll help behind the scenes.
We need a money man. You in?
Sure. I help my dad
with his books at the restaurant.
First rule of staying on budget,
stay on budget.
Great. Thank you.
Okay. Yuri's gonna get back to me
about music, and Juliana's on visuals.
I've gotten everyone involved.
Even Min Ho?
I think everyone would like
to see you two make up.
Yeah, well, we said
some pretty harsh things to each other.
And I've texted him a few times.
He hasn't even responded.
He hasn't wanted
to talk to me much about it either.
Ever since his dad fired him,
he's buried himself
in the studio just making music.
Wait, his dad fired him?
Yeah. He's kind of going through it.
Maybe you can try reaching out again.
I hate that he's hurting.
But…
I just can't.
Welcome to the team.
That beat really sucks.
Is it going well?
Well, it's going.
I still have to mess with it.
You've been down at the studio
a lot lately.
Are you avoiding someone?
I'm not avoiding Kitty.
She's doing her thing and I'm doing mine.
Wouldn't it be better if you two talked?
I don't know.
I just need to make music right now.
I'm not sure it’s going well.
Hey.
You know what you need right now?
Deadline.
Yuri needs music for Seoul Fashion Week,
in two days.
You want to give it a try?
Me?
I don't know if I…
No… You can do it. Absolutely.
You…
you reinvented yourself.
It's the same for Yuri.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Yuri will really appreciate it.
Do your thing.
All right.
Okay, we're down to 24 hours.
We've got our team, and yes, everyone is
definitely still mad at each other.
But I'm a matchmaker, okay?
Trust the process.
- How's it going here?
- Just doing a makeup test on Q.
You're not seriously pairing
glitter with bronzer. Overkill much?
If you can't handle my sparkle,
hop off my rainbow.
Is my face the rainbow?
Come on, you two.
You're like Elphaba and Glinda,
right before intermission.
Just talk it out.
Fine. Maybe Mihee can tell us
why she's been so aggro lately.
If you have to ask, you'll never know.
Well, at least they're talking.
On to the boys.
Kitty, would you mind telling Marius
he's sewing too loudly?
It's grating.
Someone's just jealous
I'm nimble with a thimble.
You're better at shit-stirring.
I didn't exactly have to twist Q's arm for
him to hop on the back of my bike, did I?
Hold on. Um, what?
Yeah. I didn't make the best decisions
when we weren't talking,
and now these two are probably
gonna never speak to me again.
Unless…
You want me to try?
I trust you.
Besides, there's absolutely no way that
you can make this any worse for me, so…
Okay.
Marius! Jin!
- Not now, Kitty!
- Don't!
These people are entrenched.
My matchmaking skills
are seriously being tested.
Well, pride is
the hardest thing to swallow.
So, what's the strategy
with that anyways, matchmaking?
Number one, get them in the same space.
Two, convince them
to give each other a chance,
and number three, hope for the best.
Interesting.
Speaking of matches,
are you and Min Ho ever gonna make up?
Doesn't really look like it right now.
And you're okay with that?
Not really.
It kind of feels like
my soul has been ripped apart,
and I'm slowly trying
to piece it back together.
I wish we could just
get past what happened,
but we're at an impasse.
Or stubborn.
Oh, I forgot to mention,
I'm gonna scrap
the playlist for the runway
and go with something original.
What? Do we have time for that?
Yeah, I got an old friend to help.
It's gonna be great.
Okay, can't wait to hear it.
We only have two hours
until the fitting deadline.
Wait, what?
I need more time to craft my looks.
There's no way I'll make that.
What happens if you don't?
I lose my runway models.
Do any of your old friends
happen to be runway models?
No.
Actually, I don't want it
to be anyone from my old life.
My models should reflect who I am now.
Okay, everybody, listen up!
I am
I, I, I, I am…
It's runway day, people!
Give me a strut, two, three!
Pop that butt, two, three!
Let's just take five.
This isn't working.
I need to intervene before Mihee
roundhouse-kicks Madison on the runway.
Clock's ticking.
Hey, girl! Madison's hair is a rat's nest.
She's gonna totally embarrass herself
on the runway.
- Can you do something?
- Mm. She is helpless.
Hey, um, Mihee's makeup is a disaster.
Can you give her a glow-up?
- She's lost without me.
- Totally.
- Okay, this one.
- Great.
Okay, this one is all done.
- Ooh, lush!
- That is sick!
Okay, calm down, you guys.
Yuri made enough designs for everyone.
Matching motorcycle jackets
for you two, perhaps?
She designed this one for me.
Oh, unless, of course,
she obviously made it for me.
- I didn't mean to.
- Yuri, I am so sorry.
Holy shit.
This is it!
Okay, Kitty, remember when you told me
you felt like your soul
was being ripped apart?
Well, that's how I felt
when I lost everything
and I pieced myself back together, right?
That's what I should do with my look.
That's my story.
- I love it.
- Wait, me too. Do we have enough time?
- We have to try.
- Okay, come on. Guys, come on.
Yuri!
Thank you.
Okay.
Okay, these three are good.
The boys are waiting.
On it.
I think the boys need an intervention too.
Okay, hustle up. Q, your pants.
Marius, your shirt.
Jin, your jacket.
I think I have Marius' pants.
And I have Jin's shirt.
And I have Q's jacket.
- Kitty.
- Kathy!
Okay, don't be mad at Kitty.
She's just trying to help.
So can we please just try to be honest
for two seconds instead of playing games?
Gonna be honest about
what happened on your joyride?
If I'm being honest,
it wasn't much of a joyride.
He got me all revved up
and then cut the engine.
I'm sorry I led you on that day.
I know that must have hurt.
It… it did.
But I kind of deserved it.
Guys, look, since I came back to KISS,
I just figured that
what you lot had going on
couldn't compete with what we had.
But I was wrong.
And I know Q felt something for me
sophomore year.
But after our little motorcycle ride,
I know that he doesn't.
And I'm a lover, not a fighter.
So I am done trying to compete.
So why'd you run to Marius
the second we broke up?
I've been asking myself that every day.
Marius was the first person
I'd ever been with.
But we had to sneak around,
and I hated that.
And this year we ended up
with another dirty little secret.
I think I wondered what it would be like
with Marius without the shame.
But as soon as I explored that, I realized
I already had exactly what I wanted.
And I'm sorry that hurt you, Jin.
I'm really sorry.
I'll admit it, you made me look
ten times better.
I mean, you are
seriously skilled with a lip liner.
Okay, Mihee?
What's going on?
The senior map?
You're sailing around the world?
We talked about taking a gap year
in Europe together, Mads.
But I guess you're moving on without me.
I was gonna surprise you.
Where do you think
my dad's yacht is taking us?
Us? Really?
Duh! You think I'd hit the beaches
in Mykonos without my best friend?
Without you, I'd have to be
one of those people with a selfie stick.
We have to get matching bikinis.
Twins.
- Come here.
- Mm.
Min Ho.
File's all done.
Thank you.
- Do you like it?
- I don't know.
I just hope Yuri likes it.
Mm.
Then, let's go play it for them.
Who's them? What are you talking about?
Yuri and her producer.
When's this music guy getting here?
We have to get back to work.
- I know. He's coming.
- He's here.
- What?
- What is this?
It's only because we care.
Practice what you preach, Kitty.
I've spent this whole day trying
to get our friends to work out their beef,
so maybe it's time we do that too.
All right.
I've apologized for what happened
on Chuseok.
But instead of hearing me out,
you've shut me out. Why?
Because, Kitty, all it took was one moment
of doubt and you were done with me.
I have enough people in my life
who treat me that way.
That is so not fair.
Listen, I don't have
a supportive family like you.
Lara Jean and Margot.
I have siblings I barely talk to.
A mum who's a continent away,
and a dad who tells me
I'll never be enough
every chance he gets.
I heard about what happened with him.
I'm sorry.
I know that must have really hurt.
But, Min Ho, I'm not your dad.
Yeah, you were supposed to be
the one person who believed in me.
Of course I believe in you.
But sometimes I make mistakes.
I am a person who makes mistakes.
You've let me down too.
How?
I had my heart set on NYU.
But then I was reimagining
a potential future here.
With you.
Then I made one mistake,
and you gave up on us
and left me completely adrift.
I know the feeling.
I wanted a future with you too, Kitty.
Well…
for what it's worth,
I will never regret what we had.
Well, thanks for trying.
I know you and Dae
had the best intentions.
But Min Ho is not willing to bend.
I'm sorry, Kitty.
Hey, are you okay?
No.
I don't think I can do this.
What? What do you mean?
I came out here to take in the moment,
and all I see are people
who knew me when I was rich
and then laughed at me when
I lost everything and fell on my face.
Sure. But look at how far you've come.
I mean, life cut you down,
and you stitched yourself back together.
I didn't do it alone.
None of us ever do.
At the end of the day,
it doesn't matter who's in front of you.
Yuri, what matters is who's behind you.
They all showed up thanks to you.
They all showed up
because they believe in you.
Welcome to Seoul Fashion Week's
Designer Breakthrough Contest.
Presenting "Fire and Lace" by Lilly Yo.
Okay.
If I'm gonna do this,
there is one more thing I need
for this show to be a success.
I made you a dress
with your 18th birthday in mind
because I wanted to make it special,
but I don't think we should wait.
Tonight's the night.
Oh, like me on the runway?
- No, I cannot do that right now.
- Yes.
Kitty, you can.
Look, I know you don't feel amazing
right now, but you truly are.
I mean, look at everything you've done
to make everyone else shine.
You deserve to shine too.
So go out there and blow everyone away.
Come here.
And now, presenting
"Riches to Rags" by Yuri Han.
Call me.
Wow, Yuri actually pulled this off.
And now, the moment
we've all been waiting for.
I'm proud to present Seoul Fashion Week's
Designer Breakthrough Award
to someone who's not new to fashion,
but who is
an exciting new voice in our world.
Ladies and gentlemen…
my protégé, Yuri Han!
Oh my God!
Wait. Okay, wait,
you guys should come with me. Yes!
Congratulations.
Whoo!
I don't know where
I'd be without you, Kitty.
Definitely not here.
Well, there's nowhere else I'd rather be.
I am so proud of you.
Mm!
And I don't think I'm the only one.
- Hi.
Juliana, that logo was amazing.
And all the help you gave me with
the looks, and last-minute changes…
You know I'm always down to help you.
Plus, I have some time on my hands
since Praveena and I broke up.
Oh, um…
Sorry, I didn't know that.
Yeah, it was my loss. Kind of my fault.
But I think it was right for us.
I'm actually pretty proud
of how we handled it.
We're gonna stay friends.
You guys seemed good. What happened?
Uh…
She sensed that
I had feelings for someone else.
Hey!
I heard you were the guy
behind that sick track.
Congrats.
The audience was so into it.
Yeah, it felt good.
Thanks, Gigi, for believing in me.
Uh, no, none of that.
You believed in yourself.
Once you do that, you stop
expecting other people to fill that void.
And you stop blaming them when they don't.
Kitty let you down once,
out of a million other times
she showed up for you.
That's who she is.
Are you really ready to give up on her?
No.
I just don't know how to begin again.
I do.
Get out of your own way
and tell her how you really feel.
We did it.
We threaded the needle and stitched
our little KISS family back together.
As for this matchmaker, I was a bit rusty.
But it turns out, I still got it.
Kitty!
Hey. Um, can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah, for sure.
Look, I know I've been stubborn.
I just--
Sorry.
Wait, it's NYU.
My decision's in.
That can wait.
No, please. You should check.
I got in. I got into NYU!
That's brilliant!
Now you have at least one option.
You won't be a complete layabout.
Oh. I actually applied early decision
just for the best chances of getting in,
so that means…
You're going.
I'm moving to New York next year.
Congratulations, Covey.
I'm happy that
your dreams are coming true.
Um, what were you saying before?
It's not important.
You should go tell everyone the news.
Okay.
And I know that you would choose me
Over anybody else
And I know that I'm the one you love
But then, why you go
And be with everybody else
Am I not enough, am I not enough?
Or am I not enough?
Am I not enough? Or am I not enough?
Am I not enough for now?
Am I not enough, am I not enough?
Or am I not enough?
- Am I not enough?
- You would choose me over anybody else
Am I not enough, am I not enough?
Or am I not enough?
Am I not enough? Or am I not enough?
Am I not enough?
Go and be with everybody else
And I know that
I'm the one you want
You would choose me over anybody else