A reason, a season or a lifetime.
What are you talking about?
Every relationship fits into one of those
categories. I read it in a magazine.
The point is, Madison and I are over.
And looking back,
I believe I was with her for a reason.
Long legs?
No, she showed me
I'm ready for something real.
Wow.
Only you could come out of getting dumped
somehow feeling better about yourself.
How are things with Florian?
He's going through some stuff,
but I'm here for him.
- Good morning.
You look so beautiful today.
- I'll make the coffee.
- I'll grab the mugs.
It's too early to be this cheery.
I am this cheery, not only because I have
the most perfect boyfriend in the world,
but it has come to my attention that
I am failing almost all of my classes.
So if I don't do amazing on the finals,
I will flunk out of school.
And that brings you cheer because...?
If I dwell on the fact that
I was considered super-smart at home
and here I can barely keep up,
I will start sobbing.
We have a week before finals.
We're gonna make study plans,
and everyone will help you.
- I'm very busy, so...
- Everyone.
Guys, Kitty and I are finally together.
I'm not gonna let her
fail out of this school now.
Well, I'm in.
- I'll help with chem.
- Thank you.
She definitely needs
to work on her Korean.
What did you call me?
Exactly.
I'll take the other subjects.
Dae has been top of our class,
like, every semester,
so you're in good hands.
Or I'll fail out,
have to leave my true love,
and disgrace my mother's legacy,
which is even greater than I thought.
So...
no pressure.
Oh, Professor Finnerty.
Principal Lim. Hello.
What a coincidence.
Actually, I followed you here.
I was hoping we could talk.
Oh...
If you're here to beg me to do a solo
at the end of the term talent show,
it's off the table for teachers. Okay?
No, I...
Um...
There's no graceful way to say this.
I am your son.
Not that you asked or anything.
But don't worry, I grew up happy.
I was adopted by amazing people.
I love my parents.
What?
Why would you think I'm your mother?
Well, I was curious,
so a few years ago,
I did one of those ancestry tests
and that led me to a nephew of Lee's.
And it took some time,
but I figured that Lee
must be my biological father.
So you came to teach at KISS.
To meet him?
Yes.
Lee doesn't know.
I figured.
No one knows, but me and...
Kitty Song Covey.
She told you I was your mother?
Yes, but she...
It doesn't matter.
She, um, also gave me this.
Good, you're home.
The Millers are flying in and attending
the end-of-semester talent show.
Apparently Madison is dancing.
Oh.
- Yeah. Twice.
- Mm.
It's such a relief Madison
is doing so well at KISS.
It shows the Millers that we surround
ourselves with the highest quality.
Dear...
We have to use this opportunity
to finalize the acquisition.
For that to happen,
everything needs to go smoothly.
Yuri's Dad.
I need to talk.
Oh, sure.
Sit. Talk to me.
It's...
something from my past.
Is Yuri home?
I don't hear any unbearable music,
so I guess not.
To be honest, I have a son.
When I was 16...
I used my American friend's name...
at the hospital to cover it up.
I didn't think he'd ever find me.
But today, he did.
Did he want money?
No.
He wants to get to know me.
And to know what kind of person
his birth father is.
- Pay the boy to go away.
- But...
This cannot be revealed to the public!
Ever.
I know that.
What are you talking about?
Mom, you have a son?
Yuri, wait!
Yuri!
I have a brother I've never met,
that you were never gonna tell me about.
Professor Lee is the dad, isn't he?
What are you doing?
Who is my brother?
- That's not your concern.
- Why?
Because you're gonna pay your son off,
like he's nothing but a problem to solve?
And for what?
To keep this miserable family
looking perfect from the outside?
You were never supposed to know
any of this.
Just like I wasn't supposed to know
you shipped Juliana away.
- Yuri, that was for your own good.
- No, it wasn't.
It's because you're ashamed.
And all my life, I thought it was of me,
but really, you're ashamed of yourself.
You're young and spoiled.
So were you when you had a baby.
How's that secret working out for you now?
I had to keep it a secret.
You think that was easy for me?
I was a pregnant teenager,
that would have destroyed
halmeoni and hal-abeoji.
I had to do what was best
for my family then,
and I am doing
what is best for my family now.
Well, your best sucks.
I love Juliana.
Do you understand?
And you sent her away
to protect your image.
You care about that
more than you care about me
or your son, who wants to get to know you.
It's more complicated than that,
and it's in the past.
It's not in the past.
He's here.
And, Mom, I'm right here.
In the present.
I'm gay.
Full stop. End of discussion.
But you and Dae...
You liked him, didn't you?
You can find another boy you like.
I never liked him.
The whole thing was fake.
I have to live a fake life
just so you'll keep on loving me.
And I'm done doing that.
All right, so,
what are the three natural laws
that statistical thermodynamics postulate?
- No natural laws. That's a trick question.
- Exactly.
Okay, moving on to chemical compounds.
You'd think I'd be good at chemistry.
It's basically matchmaking.
Yeah. Except, you know,
people aren't chemicals.
Yeah.
Once bonded, they don't stay
united in fixed proportions.
Okay. What's happening?
Oh, nothing.
No, I'm happy with Dae
'cause I wanted to be with him
for so long, and now I am.
- So no more dreams about...?
- No.
No, I'm with Dae.
Fully, completely, 100%.
And we're not pushing down
an immense crush on Yuri?
No, no, I'm just avoiding her
because Alex and me promised
not to say anything about, you know.
So just being cautious
so I don't blurt it out by mistake.
Right, right.
Yuri was just shiny
and caught my attention,
but I'm not a raccoon.
I can choose to look away from the shine.
Uh...
Coming!
Yuri.
Yuri, what's up?
I just came out to my mom.
I'm gay.
Oh, my God, welcome.
Oh! I feel amazing.
Scared, but free.
And I'm moving in with you guys.
Uh...
So, yeah, I have a secret brother.
Can you believe this?
I cannot, no.
Are you okay?
Do you know who he is?
No, I asked her directly
if Professor Lee was the father,
and she wouldn't tell me anything.
That's brave of you to ask.
She just wants to shove my brother aside,
just like she did with Juliana.
That sucks.
I am furious with her.
But I am excited about him.
I've always wanted a sibling.
I just wish there was a way
I could find him on my own.
You promised not to tell.
Maybe he'll find you one day.
I hope so.
- Yuri, I really wanna be a good friend...
- You are a good friend.
Hm...
You know that day we found the yearbook
and saw the photo of our moms,
and my mom was wearing a tight shirt,
and your mom was...?
Oh, my God, yes.
She was wearing that big-ass tent
to hide her pregnancy.
It's all piecing together now.
And your mom probably knew.
Yeah. I bet they were really good friends.
We're the next generation.
Timeline of the later Three Kingdoms.
890 to 936.
- The first political state?
- Gojoseon.
What is happening?
I moved in.
What? Why?
Are you a throuple now?
- No.
I'm gay.
I came out to my mom.
I moved out of the penthouse.
Scared. Excited.
Wait, you've been gay this whole time?
It's not a choice.
I know. I mean...
So you and Dae,
you were in a fake relationship?
Kitty was right?
I told you I know matchmaking.
You're not mad at Dae?
He lied, and lied, and lied.
- I was mad, but then I forgave him.
- Wow.
You're as trusting as my dad's third wife.
Hey, Kitty and I are good.
Leave it alone.
I'm not good.
You lied to me too, a lot.
I wouldn't do that to a friend
or someone I care about.
I just wouldn't.
Damn, never seen
that side of Min Ho before.
Finals. Makes everyone crazy.
I can't take it anymore.
Just leave me here to die.
- It's only three more days. You can do it.
- I need a break.
I cannot digest one more fact,
or I'll puke.
All right, that's enough.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's get your blood pumping.
Let's do some jumping jacks. Okay?
- Yeah!
- A glass of cold water does the trick.
I'm happy to dump some over your head.
- I know what we need.
- Please don't say Adderall.
No, have you seen me
and Eunice on that stuff?
I would never. What we need is music.
We all need coffee. Who's coming with me?
Why'd you come
if you were going to be like this?
Like what?
I'm mad at you right now.
Listen, I'm sorry I lied to you,
but this has nothing to do with you.
I just mean,
how could you do that to Kitty?
Why are you so concerned about Kitty?
Hey.
Isn't that Florian?
I think it is.
Q said Florian's been acting
all distracted lately.
Do you think Biceps is why?
Should we send the photo?
No, we don't know what it is for sure yet.
Maybe I'll never move back home.
I'll figure it out,
but I'm staying with Kitty for now.
- Can she hear us?
- Nope.
She's blasting a study mix I made for her.
Oh!
You made a mix for her?
Yeah, she's a friend.
Don't worry.
It's a Don't Fail Out of School mix,
not a I'm Hot for You mix.
Well, you talk about her a lot,
and now you're living with her, so...
She's just a friend, I promise.
That's what you used to say about me.
Stop it.
Besides, she's totally straight.
If you've done well all semester,
you should have no issues with the final.
It is fair.
Hard, but fair.
Yes?
What if you have not
done well all semester?
- Probable doom.
- Okay.
But I'm not unreasonable.
Any student of mine
who chooses to participate
in the end-of-term talent show,
will get a ten-point boost
on their lowest grade.
Oh, good.
I just learned a new TikTok dance.
- I can juggle.
- No, no.
You must perform a traditional
Korean art form with dignity.
Hey, my mom made me take
fan dance lessons forever.
I can teach you.
- Dancing with you? Yeah, great.
- Mm-hm.
I love the smell
of finals in the morning.
Probably because you're a star athlete
and you know you're gonna
pass all your classes.
Probably.
Hey, guys. Sit with us.
Hey, guys.
Hello.
So, Florian, how's studying going?
Did you stay in all night?
Nose in the books?
Yeah, all night.
- Interesting, yeah.
- Interesting.
We needed a break,
so we went for a coffee run.
Well, better get back to it.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Bye!
What is going on with you guys?
Why are you acting so weird?
We didn't know how to tell you. Sorry.
Thank you.
So the idea of this is the fans,
the Hanbok we wear,
the choreography, the music
all come together to create the image
of butterflies and flowers in spring.
It's gorgeous.
It's like this.
Open, close.
I don't know if I can keep
hiding all these secrets from Yuri
and stay this close to her.
What?
I'm nervous.
Whatever.
It's only the whole school watching.
Come on, it can't be any worse
than when you fell into the cupcakes.
Kitty...
you are the girl
that flew halfway across the world
to go after what she wants.
What could possibly make you nervous?
You.
Me? Why would I make you nervous?
- Oh, do you want to get that?
- Um, it's okay.
I'll call later.
You're more important to me right now.
I need you to get this dance down.
You need that extra credit.
I can't lose you now.
I can't lose you either.
Kitty, what are you...?
We're late, sorry.
- Why are you looking at me?
- Why do you think?
Are you sure
it's okay to wear this hanbok?
Babe, in this context, yes.
Are you cheating on me?
What?
No.
- Min Ho and Dae think you are.
- Well, Min Ho and Dae are wrong.
You're lying. They saw you.
I was hoping you'd have
some kind of explanation.
I... I do.
I love you.
What?
Q, I love you.
- That's not an explanation.
- Listen.
I love you so much that
I've let other parts of my life fall away,
like doing homework.
And I love you so much that
I can't picture not being here with you.
I love you too.
And I wanna believe you,
but you need to tell me what's going on.
I'm cheating...
but not on you.
Kitty!
I'll see you tonight.
Don't forget your fans.
- I won't.
- Okay.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, just pre-performance nerves
and worrying about if I passed.
Are you sure that's it?
Mm-hm.
Do you hear that?
It sounds like it's coming
from the chemistry lab.
I need to go talk to Alex,
but I'll meet up with you later.
I know that hold music.
Are you leaving?
Yeah. I'm, um, leaving tonight.
But you're gonna miss the talent show.
I think it's best if I skip it
and leave quietly.
Oh. But you're gonna be back
next semester, right?
No.
I came to Korea
to learn about my biological parents.
And I did.
My father doesn't know that I exist,
and I don't wanna upend his life.
My mother asked for some time to process
and has ignored me ever since.
Makes a guy feel unwanted.
I'm so sorry, Alex.
What about Yuri?
She's not like Jina.
She wants a relationship with you.
So Yuri knows who I am?
No, but she knows
that she has a half-brother,
and she's really excited to meet him.
I wasn't the one
who told her that or anything.
It was really hard, trust me,
but I've learned not to meddle.
You've learned a lot of things, Kitty.
I passed.
One down, six to go.
Just think about it. Okay?
For Yuri.
Mr. and Mrs. Miller, hello.
- How nice to see you.
- Nice to see you.
Yes, I like to mix business with pleasure.
A real time saver.
Maybe we can close up
this business tonight.
- Agreed.
- Drinks first.
And then we should go find Madison.
I mean, come on, can we have fun,
please, just for, like, five seconds?
You know your daughter
hasn't been sleeping at home, right?
Of course, I know.
Tell her to return home immediately.
And I trust...
you took care of that other problem.
Problem?
I never said it was a problem.
Do you know how hard I work
to maintain our perfect family image?
But I don't know
who I'm putting in all this effort for.
Yuri, you, me.
Not a single one of us is happy.
So you're saying you're unhappy?
You are spoiled.
I said the same thing to Yuri.
That she was spoiled.
I was wrong to say it.
I'm going to find my daughter.
Oh, the fan dance is up next.
Come on.
I cheated on the finals.
So I wouldn't fail out
and have to go live in Greece.
It's not like I gave you mouth sores.
I'm an athlete.
I believe in good sportsmanship
and that cheating is wrong.
I'm not hurting anybody.
I'm just helping myself.
Fireworks. For my second performance.
K-Pop! Thank you.
- Hey.
Oh, you tied your bow wrong.
Can I just...?
Um, before, at rehearsal...
- I...
- Yuri!
I want you to come back home.
I'll talk to Alex.
I'll make sure you can get to know him.
Alex? Alex, who?
Oh, I just assumed that Kitty...
Wait, Alex is my brother?
Our teacher, Alex?
And you knew?
Yuri, I can explain.
How could you not tell me?
I thought Alex was my brother
and that my mom
was the one who was pregnant.
It wasn't until we snuck out
of detention that day
- and went to Lee's house...
- Wait, you've known since detention?
How could you hide this from me?
- It wasn't my place to...
- To be honest?
Guys, I'm trying to focus.
- I wasn't not honest, I just...
- Lied by omission.
You lied all semester
about being with Dae on purpose,
and I got past it, and now we're friends.
We were friends.
Oh, no!
Fire!
No!
Oh, no. Oh, no.
I got you. Stop squirming.
It's all out. You're good.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm okay. Min Ho helped.
I would have helped her.
- I got here first.
- I'm here now.
What was all the drama on stage?
Um... I'm not sure.
Pull yourself together!
I'm going to find the Millers.
♪ Nowhere to go, no one to hold ♪
♪ There's something hidden
In the past... ♪
He didn't leave.
Daniel, follow me.
- Why?
- Mom, what are you doing?
I have no idea.
What's going on with you?
You can always tell me anything, Kitty.
Okay.
I've really been trying not to...
but...
Just say it.
I have feelings for somebody else.
I knew it.
I saw the way he looked at you.
I'm gonna kill him.
♪ Why do you love me? ♪
♪ Why don't you love me? My baby ♪
♪ Why do you hurt me? ♪
♪ Why don't you love me? ♪
♪ Why don't you love me? My baby ♪