God. Min Ho, can you at least
put a shirt on when I'm eating?
Hey, it's not my fault
you can't handle this.
You're right.
I can't handle it.
I'm right?
You're too bloody hot.
♪ I'll change your mind, ay ♪
♪ You'll not waste my time ♪
♪ Yeah... ♪
Oh, my God.
Alex! Wait!
Are you okay?
I was worried that something bad might
have happened since the text silence.
No. Yeah, it's all good.
Just had a lot going on, you know?
Iguana's run loose in the Italians' dorm,
and I'm afraid it's gonna get turned
into a belt if I don't find it soon.
Plus, a lot of midterm prep.
I hope you've been studying.
I have, but I've also been busy
trying to figure out
what my mom ever saw in Korean Snape.
Kitty, you really need
to focus on studying.
- And Professor Snape was good in the end.
- Right.
But what if we go talk to him, right?
- Get to know him and figure him out.
- Not now.
Why? His house is literally right here.
We can go together.
It's the whole reason
you came here to teach.
I came here to learn about him,
to get to know him,
to see if I want a relationship with him.
I love my dad. The dad who raised me.
I don't need to rush into this.
I get it.
But I know some people that you'll
definitely wanna have a relationship with.
My sisters. Our sisters.
I was thinking we could FaceTime them.
Margot might be frosty at first,
but when she...
Kitty, we can't just
upend everyone's lives.
- What if we're wrong?
- Well, what if we're right?
- Then we'll be enhancing everyone's lives.
- Stop.
I know you're just trying to help,
but not everyone's on your timetable.
I have tests to organize,
and you have tests to study for.
Don't give up. This is for Mom.
You haven't lost the battle yet.
I just wanted to talk to him,
and then Alex said
that not everybody's on my timetable.
So now I'm just wondering
about Professor Lee and...
How about, instead of fixating
on all this Alex drama,
we concentrate on what you are gonna wear
to Min Ho's Madness Party?
- I'm not going.
- What?
Why? It's the event of the year.
Because Dae and Yuri
will probably be there.
Yuri will be there. She's DJing.
But Dae never goes to these things
so you don't have to worry.
I'm not worried.
I don't care to spend time with somebody
who can't acknowledge
a meaningful gesture.
Here we go.
He didn't even say "thank you"
for the necklace.
Not even an emoji.
That necklace was my mom's.
I gave it to Dae when his mom died.
Okay. While I would love to sit here
and talk about this again,
I'd rather shove scissors in my ears.
Yeah.
Seriously, this whole week,
all I've been hearing is,
"Dae, necklace, Yuri, Alex,
necklace, Alex, Yuri, Dae, necklace."
You're like a robot that's malfunctioning,
stuck on a loop.
And you came here to have
new experiences and live your life.
You know what Min Ho's Madness Party is?
A new experience.
Ugh. God, I can't believe I was just
about to stay in on a Friday night,
pouting about a boy.
- Yeah.
- Oh, no.
I'm turning into LJ.
Sure.
Okay, but tonight we're gonna
go out into the great big world
and be a new kind of Kitty.
New kind of Kitty who...?
Who'll find someone to kiss?
Well, I always thought
Dae would be my first kiss,
and now he's the only boy
in the world who can't be.
I know, I know,
but think of all the possibilities.
Seriously.
Use that matchmaker skill on yourself.
Switch it up.
Okay.
I could kiss somebody tonight.
Yeah! I will kiss somebody tonight.
Yes, girl.
Wow. Aren't you meeting Dae tonight?
Yeah. I'm heading out now.
Dinner, probably a movie.
Don't worry, I won't be back crazy late.
I never worry when you're with Dae.
You two really
bring out the best in each other.
- Mom.
- Your grades are up.
You're not getting into any trouble.
I'm proud of you.
But most of all...
I'm happy you're happy.
Have a good time.
Is something wrong?
My mom seems to think I'm very happy.
Even though this is
the worst I've ever felt.
Things are working out as planned, but...
She doesn't know you very well.
Ugh, it'll be weird DJing without Juliana
for the first time today.
I'll cheer you on.
And you have to do the same for me.
I've never been to one of these before.
A "rager" -type place.
That's what Altan calls it.
I wouldn't know, I've never raged before.
Don't worry. They're not much.
This place is so big.
And so loud!
Yes, that's the point!
Loosen up for once, Dae.
I rented the whole place out for us.
My rules, my guest list.
Really?
I mean, how did she get in?
♪ Walk in like a boss
Where my money at? ♪
♪ See me and I'm looking like
100 racks ♪
♪ I don't show up
If they don't run a check... ♪
Who are you?
- Hey, wanna dance?
- Not now.
♪ Ain't gonna ask you again
Where my money at ♪
♪ Shooters and they aiming
Where ya tummy at ♪
♪ Messing with the squad
You ain't wanting that ♪
♪ 'Cause we know you soft as a gummy bag ♪
♪ Lookin', lookin', lookin'
Yeah, you looking at a ♪
♪ Cooking, cooking, cooking
I been cooking with the... ♪
No!
No, no, no. Oh, my eyes!
It's like looking directly into the sun.
- Oh, my God.
- You look so good.
Are you wearing athleisure?
To the event of the year?
I need to go over the dress code
with the doorman.
I told you
everyone was gonna lose their mind.
Dae is here.
Oh, God. Why does he look so good?
Why is he walking towards me?
Why do I still care so much?
He even smells good from here.
Nope. I am here to meet a new boy to kiss.
What are you doing?
I'm getting ready to get this whole
"meeting new people" thing started.
Never actually had alcohol before,
but liquid courage, right?
There's actually no alcohol in these.
Mocktails only.
Underage drinking in Korea, huge no-no.
People get canceled for that.
Well, lucky for us...
I'm French.
Thank you.
To new experiences.
Let's do this.
Kitty, you look amazing...
Sorry.
Too frowny.
Not my speed.
Hmm, maybe?
Hi. I see your eyeballs.
You are boy shopping.
- I love this vibe for you.
- I'm having the best time.
Me too.
This is exactly what I needed.
Like an escape from family drama
- and stupid school pressure...
- Stupid school, yes.
It's like, why is school
so hard all of a sudden?
- I have no idea.
- Here.
- Mm-hm.
- Thank you.
So pretty.
Thank you.
- No. No.
- No, no, no.
- Oh, no? Okay. Okay.
- No, no. Let's go.
- Immediately.
- He's weird.
He's cute.
And he's taken.
I used to be taken.
And I found out he's a cheating,
lying A-hole who can't even say thank you.
Kitty, wait.
Thank you.
Thanks again.
Man who knows how to say "thank you."
I like it.
I'm Geon.
Kitty.
Nice to meet you.
It's an honor.
The hottest girl in here is talking to me.
You think the Portland Stalker
is attractive?
Don't call yourself that.
It's actually kind of growing on me.
Hey, I don't like to judge
until I've properly met someone.
Now that I have,
I'm certain those rumors were all lies.
Oh, tell me more.
There's no way
any guy leaves you for Yuri.
Oh, well...
Seriously, she's not even pretty.
And her nose is a little... not little.
That's not nice.
Girls like Yuri are just overcompensating.
But you?
You're gorgeous and smart.
You think talking bad about Yuri
scores you points with me?
Well...
that don't impress me much.
Seriously?
Is Shania Twain just not a thing here?
God, where is Q when you need him?
Whatever!
Yuri and I may not be friends,
but who are you
to talk about her like that?
Women are not just here
for your judging pleasure.
Also, FYI, I have seen Yuri up close
and I can confidently tell you
her nose is annoyingly perfect.
Jerk.
I was just saying I'm on your side.
L-O-V-E, guys. It's "love."
All I ask for is one night to myself
to work on my own love life,
but no, here I am, on the clock.
Sorry, are you talking to me?
To both of you.
You have what each other needs.
Talk amongst yourselves.
You do have what I need.
♪ And she looking like a zombie
In her Off-White ♪
♪ Yeah, she looking
Yeah, she looking for a hand out ♪
♪ She think 'cause she with me
She in a band now ♪
♪ Pull up in the truck
Pack it up like a limousine ♪
♪ Looking like a blast from the past
Look like Billie Jean ♪
♪ And you're the only ten I see
And I hope you like Hennessy ♪
♪ And why, why, why, why, why
Why, why, why, why, why ♪
♪ Aren't you into me?
♪ You only call me on the weekend ♪
♪ You only love me when we freakin' ♪
♪ You got me jumpin' off the deep end ♪
♪ You only call me on the ♪
♪ You only call me on the weekend ♪
♪ Wait a minute, wait a minute
We was just gettin' started ♪
♪ I don't wanna
I don't wanna be broken-hearted ♪
- ♪ Every time ♪
- ♪ Every time... ♪
I know you've never been
to a party like this before, but...
Come on.
I...
Get over here!
Okay, dance!
No, I'm out.
Watch me.
No. I'm never gonna do that.
You're at a party.
Like this.
Yeah, that's it.
Whoa. Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Whoa. What is this?
What is this? How are you so good?
Why are you smiling so much?
Because I like you.
No. Don't be like that.
No, no, not like that.
I just meant thanks for bringing me here
and helping me have fun
and take my mind off things.
That's why I like you.
As a friend.
Okay.
Kitty!
Kitty! Kitty!
Do not show weakness.
Give him bitch face.
- Hey.
- How are we doing?
- Amazing.
I made some matches.
And now
I'm going to perform the ultimate trick
and match myself with somebody
who knows how to say "thank you."
- What?
- Okay.
- Time we slow you down and get some water.
- Yes.
No. No. I've only had 13.
Thirteen drinks?
Sips.
Thirteen sips.
Not that it's any of your business.
I wanna dance. Let's dance.
- No. Enough.
- Let's dance.
Okay, Florian and I,
we're gonna go take a lap.
- I wanna dance. Dance right now.
- Kitty.
Can you give us a second?
Not everyone's on Kitty time.
You sound like Alex.
Huh, calling Alex
is a really good idea right now.
Am I drunk?
- Drink some water!
- No, this is a good idea.
Hello?
Hey, I just need to say this.
I'm sorry for meddling
and pushing and pestering.
I was just...
I was so excited to have a brother.
Brother.
"Bro-ther."
It is such a funny word
when you say it so many times.
The point is,
I'm getting over Dae tonight.
Am I hurt? Yes.
But just like my mom
got over the mystery man and found my dad,
I can do this.
Kitty?
Are you okay?
I just wanted to apologize.
Beer?
This is not one of my London parties.
We are in Seoul,
meaning no underage drinking.
Give me that.
Kitty, are you at a party with alcohol?
I plead the Fifth!
We're not in the United States.
There is no Fifth.
And it's way past your curfew,
and you're struggling with your grades.
- You could get in real trouble.
- I cannot hear you very well.
Rubik rocks!
Did he just say Rubik?
Kitty? Hello?
Alex?
- Alex!
- Kitty?
- Kitty!
- Yeah, no, I cannot hear you.
I am going to text you instead.
Goodbye.
"You are awesome. My mom would agree.
And Eve Song knows who's awesome.
Apart from Professor Lee.
Now I need to go back to the party.
Bye...
yee."
I rhymed.
Hey there.
We have a problem.
Please don't make my night any worse.
I already have a headache.
There's a party. I don't know where.
I do.
A dinner and a movie, my ass.
I wanted to thank you
for helping me reflect
on how I talk about others,
especially women.
Thank you.
The fact that you're actually
thanking me for something
is a welcome change in my life.
Cheers.
Mm.
I wanna kiss someone.
I'm ready to kiss someone.
I'm gonna kiss someone.
Nope.
Remember how gross he seemed
before you were drunk?
Yeah, well, he hasn't changed that much
in the past hour.
Whatever.
You can do much better. Trust me.
Okay, snacks. Stat.
Eat this.
Drink...
this.
And then come watch my set.
It's like she cares about me.
Am I really that drunk,
or is Yuri Han a good person?
Everybody!
Everybody, get back to your dorms!
Alex. Thank God you're here.
- Help me stop these barbarians.
- You don't think I'm trying?
Last year, an idol's family was ruined
because of an underage drinking scandal.
I refuse to put my mother through that.
I'll take the left side,
you take the right.
Okay.
Yup.
Hey, guys.
Sorry to interrupt. Q, do you know
what I've done to upset Kitty?
You mean,
besides having another girlfriend
when she literally flew
across the world to be with you?
Yes, besides that.
It just feels like she suddenly
hates me more than ever and...
I really don't know what I did.
Dae, I really don't wanna
get involved in all this.
Dude, just give me a clue.
Come on, just help the poor kid out.
Yeah.
The necklace, Dae, the necklace.
Titanic?
What?
Kitty's heartbroken you didn't thank her
or even acknowledge
that she gave the necklace back to you.
Gave it back to me?
Yeah. On Chuseok.
It was delivered by messenger.
Welcome to the stage, Yuri!
On Chuseok.
Please collect your belongings
and make your way back to campus!
Please tell me you're not here as a guest,
but as a concerned teacher
trying to put an end to this mayhem.
That. Definitely that.
Uh, but don't worry,
I've almost got it shut down.
No, you don't.
They don't respect you.
Everyone, stop what you're doing!
We need to find the speakers
and unplug them.
Uh...
Get off the table.
I see the speakers.
Follow me.
♪ Even while we sleep ♪
♪ We will find you
Acting on your best behavior ♪
♪ Turn your back on Mother Nature ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
She's amazing.
Wait, what am I saying?
This is Yuri, my enemy.
Why does it feel like I've been zapped
by a million volts of electricity
when I look at her?
Kitty.
- I think Yuri took the necklace.
- I know Yuri makes you breathless.
- No, I said...
- I get it now. You're in love with Yuri.
It broke my heart, but I don't blame you.
Okay. Everyone! Everyone! Every...
Hey, you.
It's okay to not want that.
With us,
it'd be nothing serious, just fun.
♪ So sad they had to fade it ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world... ♪
It's good.
I'm ready to find somebody new too.
- I'm a little busy right now!
- Are you the one who took my necklace?
The one Kitty sent me on Chuseok.
For a minute I got it twisted.
I actually thought we were friends.
Your set last night was epic.
Thanks.
So, what are we gonna do
about all this tension?
Of hating each other?
I think that's wearing off.
No.
This tension.
♪ Crushed, you know that I'll be up
Waiting all night long ♪
♪ Left me with your smoking gun ♪
♪ You cloud up my vision
A head-on collision ♪
♪ A 90 into a dead end ♪
♪ What bad decisions ♪
♪ I'll turn the ignition
And do it all over again ♪
♪ I'm seeing smoke signals ♪
♪ I just can't let you go ♪
♪ No, I just can't let you go ♪