Maybe it's not our time.
- Or maybe…
- Wait!
Can I join you?
Okay, this is happening.
I'm about to go
on a world tour with Min Ho.
Wait, did you actually mean join me on…
- The world tour.
- The world tour? Sorry?
What? No. The world tour?
- I thought you were asking to come with.
- I thought that you meant…
- For the whole summer.
- The whole summer?
No. No, no, no. That would be crazy.
I mean, us? Imagine spending
the whole summer together.
- We would drive each other nuts.
- Okay, so what did you mean?
Hi, Kitty.
Wait, are you coming to Busan too?
Because tonight's kickoff party
is going to be amazing.
- I've never been on a yacht before.
- I have not either.
I could kill some time with you in Busan
before I fly home for the summer tomorrow.
Um, sure.
But you might wanna bring
a change of clothes
because that outfit's not gonna cut it.
- What is wrong with my skort?
- Ow.
There's literally a dress code,
you animal.
Yacht chic.
Okay, give me like five minutes to throw
some stuff in a bag. I'll be back.
What? Wait, no one told me
I could bring friends.
Okay, so maybe inviting myself
on a hopefully romantic
but definitely epic world tour with Min Ho
was going a bit overboard.
But I'm not giving up yet.
Our ship could still set sail. On a yacht!
So, did you tell him how you feel?
I was going to, but then I chickened out.
Oh wow. A matchmaker
who's unable to match herself.
That's kind of tragic if you think…
Sorry, continue.
So then I asked
if I could join him instead.
- On the tour?
- Yes.
- For the summer?
- Yes, but… then no.
I am so lost.
I am too, but I do know I have 14 hours
and six minutes to tell Min Ho how I feel
and see if he feels the same way.
Okay, so, do you…
do you have a game plan? What's…
No, I don't know, okay? He told me
he wants to swear off all relationships.
What if you just ask him?
What if he doesn't feel the same way
and then I ruin our friendship forever?
- Oh wow. Okay.
- Wait, you should come with us.
Come to Busan.
Help me suss out how he feels.
- Please?
- Sorry. Jin and I have plans. Remember?
- It's my last night before training camp.
- Please, Q.
Is there any way you can come
to this super fun yacht party
he's taking me to?
On second thought, it does seem like
an all-hands-on-deck situation,
so I will be there as your wingman.
We, Jin and I,
will be there as your wingmen.
Do you wanna help me,
or do you wanna eat tiny foods on a boat?
Both. You know how I feel
about finger foods.
- The tinier, the better.
- I know.
- Settled. It'll be the four of us.
- Great.
- Vibes ahoy. Smooth sailing.
- Fabulous. Thank you.
Find your own way there
because Min Ho's waiting for me.
Remember, just the four of us.
Eunice just invited us
to a yacht party in Busan.
Oh! Oh! Can we borrow your dad's heli?
Oh, uh, actually, it's in the shop.
Broken propeller or something.
- I'll book us train tickets.
- We can pretend to be normies.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ew, pass.
Oh my God, I look so cute in this.
It's so heli-worthy.
Whatever. I'm gonna buy it anyway.
Actually, on second thought…
Let's go to Busan.
Yay!
Busan! Whoo-hoo!
Can you just act a little more excited?
I wanted to spend time together
before you left for LA.
Just the two of us?
And we will.
We just gotta help Kitty mac on Min Ho.
And then it'll be you, me,
and the beautiful view of a sunset
from a billionaire's yacht.
All right. Busan, here we come.
Can I come too?
You guys are going to Busan, right?
Um… That is right.
Yeah, we are going to Busan. Hey, hey…
If this is about Eunice,
she's gonna be busy launching
her pop star career. So I wouldn't…
Actually, it's about Yuri.
I need to talk to her about some… stuff.
And she's coming too, apparently.
- Ah.
- She's going too, apparently.
Yeah. Would you look at that?
Uh…
I can't believe the legendary Yisoo
is dressing me tonight.
- I'm so excited!
- So you've said.
Eight times.
This is just the beginning, Eunice.
Get used to being the center of attention.
Did I just get demoted
to third wheel on our first date?
I need a plan.
Uh, Min Ho, do you think we'll have time
for sightseeing before the party tonight?
Yeah. What… what
did you have in mind, Covey?
Mm, maybe Gwangalli Beach?
Apparently, they light up the bridge
just as the sun goes down.
Oh my God. That is so romantic!
If you want a great view,
we could probably
squeeze in a trip to the cable cars.
Oh…
- Yeah, I would love that.
- Yes, I am so in!
I'm pretty sure my dad's gonna
keep you busy getting ready for tonight,
so it'll probably just be me and Kitty.
- Who invited the girls?
- I did!
And the boys?
That was kind of me.
Oh. Okay.
I guess a group thing will be fun.
Mm.
So much for romantic alone time.
Hi!
- Oh my gosh. This is so cool!
- Yeah!
Yuri, I was hoping we could talk?
Uh, Mihee-ah,
let's go over there.
Okay.
Kitty, I am so sorry.
Things just spiraled,
but I gave you my word.
I'm going to help you. Wingman's honor.
Thank you. This crowdsourcing
is steamrolling the vibes.
Yeah, I get you, but we'll figure it out.
- I promise.
- Thank you.
- Hey!
- Where are we going first?
I just go get it
I get what I want, no sweating
On me, I'm betting
- I get what I want, go-getter
- Go, go
Go, go, I go and get it
- Go, go, I go and get it
- Go, go
Tell me, baby
Should I bite my tongue
Or should I keep it going?
I could talk forever
Like a mile a minute
Something deep inside of me
Won't let me quit it
- All you gotta do is just
- Trust me
I know what you're feeling
Don't be scared to lean in
Just follow my lead and let me in
I'm a go-getter
I just go get it
I get what I want, no sweating
On me, I'm betting
I get what I want, go-getter
Anything I want, put in my bag
If I let it go, I'mma get it back
Everybody know that I do it like that
Do it like that
Like a boomerang, coming right back
I look good, and you want it bad
Everybody know
That I do it like that…
- Go, go, go, go, go
- I go and get it
Wow, this view is beautiful.
I agree.
I… I mean, Busan is beautiful
this time of year.
Wait, is Min Ho nervous?
Am I making him nervous?
There's only one way to find out.
- Min Ho, I--
- I'm glad you invited yourself.
You know how much
I value our friendship, right?
Our friendship?
Yeah. Yes, of course.
So if I were to tell you that…
Or if I told you that I…
What I'm trying to get at is--
Oh.
I should take this.
Hey, where the hell are you?
Hi, Dad. Wait, whoa. Are you in the bath?
Where else would I be
three hours before a party?
- How soon can you get to the hotel?
- I don't know. Why?
I've given it a lot of thought. And, uh…
I want you to be Eunice's manager.
What, really?
After everything that
happened with Stella,
you'd give me
another chance to prove myself?
You showed a lot of courage.
And I believe in you.
But I need to know
that you will take this job seriously.
We need to make sure that Eunice
rides the momentum of the contest win
and seals a brand deal with Yisoo.
So, give Eunice whatever she needs,
make sure she's on time,
and keep her out of trouble.
Yeah, got it. I'll head
back to the hotel right now, Dad.
- Thank you. I won't let you down.
- Good. That's what I want to hear.
I'm sorry, I have to go, Kitty.
Dad trusting me with this is a big deal.
And I can't screw this up.
You don't have to explain.
I totally get it. This is huge.
I'm happy for you.
I'm really lucky to have you.
- I'll see you tonight?
- Break a leg.
Okay, so my timing sucks,
but I still have eight hours
and ten minutes to tell Min Ho how I feel.
Joon Ho!
Joon, how you feeling?
- You made a great entrance.
- Yeah.
This is glitzy as hell.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh! VIP gift bags.
- Wait, we're VIP, right?
Ooh, free gift bags.
SOS911! Can I get a quick picture?
Ahoy, mate.
I do not want to hear it.
I clearly had no idea
what yacht chic meant.
How'd things go with your dad?
Um, great. I'm supposed
to introduce Eunice tonight.
I don't usually feel nervous
with this sort of stuff,
but for some reason, tonight I do.
Tell you what, if you're feeling jittery,
just look for me in the crowd.
Act like you're just talking to me.
Yeah?
- Thanks, Covey.
- Sure.
Min Ho! Come here!
All right, I better go do my job.
- I'll look for you in the crowd.
- I'll be there.
Min Ho! Come here!
All right. All right.
Settle down, girls. All right.
SOS911, over here.
- You're the best, SOS911!
- Can we get a shot?
Kitty, gift bags!
Hi!
This is insane.
Wait, isn't that Tae-Oh
from Autumn's Last Orchid?
Where?
How can someone be
that talented and that hot?
Maybe we can meet him.
Whoa.
Look, he's talking to Eunice.
They'd make a hot couple.
Really? I don't see it.
Look this way!
Yuri, hey! Hi.
You look amazing.
Thank you. Uh…
What're you guys doing here?
- Madison invited us.
- Ah.
- Great.
- So, Yuri, any big plans this summer?
Yeah, um, actually, so you know
my mom is at a spa in Thailand.
And it is annoyingly chic,
so I will go join her there.
- You know, relax, recharge.
- Wow. Sounds fabulous.
Very White Lotus coded,
minus the whole murder thing.
Yeah.
It was really nice talking to you.
- Whoa! Wait. That's actual champagne.
- Thank you.
I know.
Thank you, bye.
You know who's looking real good? Min Ho.
Right? He is so fine.
Moon is making him go on tour this summer.
So, we'll all get to have a little taste.
Oh, uh, miss, could we get some
of those yuzu caviar bellinis over here?
Uh…
Hi. Champagne? Yes?
- Yes.
- Do you want one?
- Coming right up.
- Thank you.
You can kiss my bellinis. Ugh.
Hey, can I get another, please… Kitty?
I thought you were a waitress.
Yes, no, that does seem to be
a thing that's happening.
- Mm.
- God, this dress. I just… I wanted to…
Impress Min Ho.
Yeah. I saw you two at the cable cars.
- So, how's that going?
- Um… I mean, I like him.
A lot. And I have
three hours and 34 minutes
before I leave to tell him that.
And I am very scared
that he won't feel the same way.
We might not be on the same page at all.
I get it. But you're just gonna
have to put yourself out there.
I know. Does it even make sense, though?
Like, his world is so glamorous,
and I am being mistaken for the waitstaff.
Yeah, that waitress look
isn't doing you any favors.
But… I saw some Yisoo dresses backstage,
and there's one
that's very attention-grabbing.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Oh, like, for me to… Oh.
- Yes!
Wow.
I've never worn anything
this fancy before.
Or this heavy.
That's just the weight of being hot, babe.
You look incredible.
All right.
Well…
What are you waiting for?
Go take Min Ho's breath away.
- Mm.
- Thank you!
Bye.
Okay.
Yes, Yisoonim.
Tonight we have to be well-prepared.
Of course.
Eunice's dress is going to be iconic.
Let's run a test.
My custom dress! Where is it?
One moment.
Are you kidding me?!
Thanks, everyone! I will see you guys
on the Sugar Daddy Tour!
So, this next performer…
will be, uh…
I mean, this next performer
is insanely talented.
Soon to be Korea's next breakout star.
Oh no, it's out.
What? Poor Yuri.
She's gotta be freaking out.
Focus!
Excuse me. Sorry.
Squeeze by you. I'm so sorry.
Thank you so much. Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
And as her manager and her dear friend,
I couldn't be more proud
to watch her rise.
So, without further ado, Eunice!
I think she's a little bit shy.
So, let's have
another shout-out for Eunice!
What's going on?
I can't find my dress anywhere!
What do you mean,
can't find your dress? Just come out.
Start the music.
Ooh.
It lights up! It's really good.
This is really good.
That's probably Eunice's dress.
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no. No.
Well, there goes Eunice's brand deal.
- I can't believe I did this.
- Did she steal it?
Come on, let's light up like firework
Oh, Yuri.
Kitty? Is that you?
Hey. I just saw the news.
You okay?
Mm.
Not really.
I've had a lot of champagne.
- You good?
- Not really.
I'm so sorry I put you in a stolen dress.
I mean, I've been broke for,
what, three weeks?
And I'm already committing grand larceny.
You were just trying to help.
Why didn't you tell me what was going on?
Because it's humiliating.
I thought if I ignored it,
it wouldn't be true. But it is.
Have you talked to Dae about it?
- I can't deal with him right now.
- Do not shut him out.
Whatever Dae is gaining
from this settlement,
I can guarantee
he does not want to lose you.
How about this?
You talk to Dae,
and I will stop being a coward
and finally tell Min Ho how I feel.
Deal.
Mm.
Well, if it isn't our main attraction.
Mr. Moon, I am so sorry about the dress.
I did not mean to ruin
Eunice's moment. Or Min Ho's.
And yet, you did.
Look, I know you mean well,
but you're trying to fit
in a world you don't understand.
And right now, Min Ho needs
to do damage control for Eunice.
And not be distracted by you.
You don't want to be
the thing that stands in his way, do you?
Of course not.
Then you leave him alone.
Sitting here, trying to run it back
I can't seem to let it go
I'm waiting here in the aftermath…
Kitty, wait! Kitty!
That was such a disaster!
What am I going to do?
What am I going to do about the tour?
Everyone was too busy watching the stage.
No one even noticed the dress.
They were only looking at you.
Don't worry so much.
Thanks, Dae.
Have a great summer, and…
I'll really miss you.
Cold nights putting up a fight
Against the odds are always for me
A little red, no common sense…
Hey, Dae.
Hey.
Sorry I've been avoiding you.
Honestly, I know
none of this is your fault.
But…
I just didn't think
anyone would understand.
I'm the only one of our friends
who doesn't have any money.
Uh…
Sorry.
I'm not saying I can help the situation,
but don't endure it alone.
Just talk to me.
Holding it back, yeah, holding it back
I can't shake this feeling
All I wanted
was to tell Min Ho how I feel.
But his dad is right.
I can't get in the way
of what's important to him.
So I guess it's time to go home.
LJ? What's up?
Kitty!
- You left. What-
- It was easier if I didn't say goodbye.
Especially after all the trouble I caused.
Enough… with the mixed signals.
I thought you wanted
to come to tour with me.
But then you didn't.
I felt like you wanted
to be alone with me.
But then you invited all our friends.
And then you talk about
how much you value our friendship.
I do, though, and I'm scared to risk…
All I wanted all night was to get up
the courage to tell you how I feel
and see if you feel the same way.
The truth is,
I was asking to go on tour with you.
I thought so.
- But then--
- I got nervous.
Well, it's not too late.
Come with me.
We can still spend the summer together.
And you can tell me
all about your feelings for me.
Honestly, I want that more than anything.
Because I like you, Min Ho.
Like, I really, really like you.
And I really like you too, Covey.
So will you come with me?
I…
can't.
Lara Jean just called me.
She's going through
a rough patch with Peter,
and she asked me to join her in New York.
- But--
- I'm sorry.
My sister needs me.
Of course, I understand.
I mean, I'm… I'm sorry.
Family comes first, right?
Please stop talking.
Hold your head up high
This is our time
Together we will rise up
Step into the light
We were born to come alive
Hold your head up high
This is our time
Here.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Min Ho!
We're doing body shots!
And we need your hot body!
Whoo!
Yes! Whoo!
- Let's go!
- You know what? I'm all right.
- Kitty and I were just about to--
- Come on, Min Ho!
Don't make me celebrate alone!
No worries. I will take good care of her.
Come on.
You go ahead. Stay with Eunice.
I have a flight to catch anyway.
I'll see you in three months.
Trust me. It'll fly by.
All right, girls. Move over.
Let's go!
Yes! Let's go!
Three months.
It'll fly by. Just like Min Ho said.
Then again,
a lot can change in three months.
Beat drop with a big flash
- Know I did that
- Yeah
Day one, know I been bad
- Can't touch that
I'm the highlight
Yeah, tonight, it's all 'bout me
You know it's my site
History
One look, give 'em whiplash
- Beat drop with a big flash
- Yeah
- Know I did that
Day one, know I been bad
- Can't touch that
Whip, whiplash, whip, whiplash
Whip, whiplash