I have feelings for somebody else.
I knew it.
I'm gonna kill him.
Whoa.
Dae, stop! Wait!
You call yourself my friend?
- What are you talking about?
- Don't pretend like you don't know!
What are you doing? Let go.
Dae, stop.
Stop it, it's not Min Ho.
This has nothing to do with him.
Sorry. I thought you two...
And I think...
you two were better off as pen pals.
Deep down, she probably thinks so too.
What did he say?
Nothing.
Dae, I'm sorry.
I didn't think that I could feel
something for somebody else.
So don't.
I tried,
Dae.
I really, really tried.
Who is it?
It's Yuri.
Yuri?
- How could it be Yuri?
- I don't know.
It just...
Just happened.
I... When? When did you start liking her?
The night of Min Ho's party.
That long ago?
Then why did you even
get back together with me?
How could I not?
Dae, I came here to be with you.
- But now you suddenly like girls.
- No.
I guess, but I like boys too.
It's a lot to understand. I know that. I...
- I'm barely understanding it myself...
- Kitty, stop. Just...
I can't do this right now.
No, I can't do this ever.
You're my son?
Yes.
- How?
- Daniel, I'm sorry.
I didn't tell you
because I didn't wanna hold you back.
You had that opportunity
to study music in the States and I...
I didn't want you to give up
your whole future because of me.
Give up what? Being a rock star?
Like that was ever gonna happen.
I heard you sing. You're really good.
You are really good.
I hope you can believe that
I only ever wanted the best for you.
Alex.
Can you and I go somewhere and talk?
I'd like that. Yeah.
Wait.
Can we all talk?
- I am too angry to talk to you right now.
- I know.
Even more reason to talk.
Please, Daniel.
- Honey, are you okay?
- No.
I'll get on the next flight.
Where's my passport? Tree, get up.
No, Dad, it's not an emergency.
Don't wake up Trina.
Tree, go back to sleep.
What's wrong, honey?
I got in a fight with Dae.
Because I have feelings
for my friend Yuri, who's a girl.
Oh. Oh, thank God.
Thank God I'm bi? Or pan? Or fluid?
Whatever pan or fluid is,
thank God you're safe and healthy.
I'm safe and I'm healthy but...
I'm also sad, Dad.
And I'm really, really confused.
Well, that sounds about right
for a 17-year-old
abroad for her junior year of high school.
I'm sorry to hear you so down, Kitten,
but you're one of
the strongest people I know.
Well, I don't feel very strong right now.
Well, you are.
Just like your mom.
And sadness and confusion,
that's just part of growing up.
You certainly sound like you're growing.
I might also be failing all of my classes.
All of them?
Okay. All right, that's...
Look, besides school work,
is there anything else important
that you learned there?
I learned that mom
had infinite love to give.
Her time here might have been short,
but she made a really big impact
on people's lives.
You went to find her.
You found yourself.
You did what you wanted to do.
Honey, I'm proud of you.
Thanks, Dad.
Hey.
Why the big suitcase?
It's only winter break,
you can leave some stuff here.
Just expecting the worst.
Look, I know things seem bad right now
but tomorrow will be better.
You're gonna pass your finals,
you'll talk to Dae.
You'll work it out.
The thing is, I don't even know
how I want it to work out.
I hate that I hurt him.
But I have feelings for Yuri
and they're not going away.
She is still ignoring all of my texts.
Maybe I don't know anything about love.
Hey, remember when you came here
and your lips were still virgin?
Never touched another person's
or even had a sip of soju.
Coming to Korea
has opened me up in a lot of ways.
- If I fail out now...
- You won't.
Because I need my matchmaker here.
I'm retiring. Too old for this shit.
All right, enough of that.
Let's go make you some night-night tea.
Extra honey.
Well, at least I made one good match here.
You and Florian.
Yeah, about that.
I thought Florian
might have been cheating on me.
It turns out he was just cheating.
What are you talking about?
He got so caught up in our relationship
that he fell behind in his studies.
Been there.
Except it's more complicated than that.
His mom wants him to go back to Greece
and his dad wants him in France.
- They're fighting over him in the divorce.
- Okay. Not been there. Wow.
And he begged them to stay here
and they agreed,
so long as he kept his grades up,
but because of me...
he kind of forgot to study.
So he met up
with an old KISS student and...
bought some tests off of him.
Wait, Florian cheated on finals?
I mean, it's kind of romantic.
Don't you think?
He did it to stay here, with me.
I don't know if that's romantic.
It's kind of rude, especially when
everyone else is studying so hard.
Okay. Judgey.
I mean, I don't love it, but...
- I love him.
- Just saying.
- It feels yucky that he did that.
- Okay, hold on.
Dae and Yuri lied to you and made you feel
crazy for months and you forgave them.
So why are you all high and mighty
about not forgiving Florian
when all he did was cheat on tests?
- Which doesn't hurt anybody.
- Honestly, it shows bad character.
I don't want you to get hurt.
So, you're being hypocritical
about morality for my sake?
Yes, because I care.
You don't deserve this night-night tea.
What are you doing?
Watching you sleep.
It's creepy.
It's not, it's maternal.
You saying that word is also creepy.
I used to watch you sleep
all the time when you were a baby.
Why?
To make sure you were breathing
and comfortable and safe.
I never stopped
wanting those things for you.
I just went about
watching over you in the wrong way.
I don't wanna look back on my life
when I'm 50 and be filled with regrets.
I am not 50.
I don't regret having a baby.
I regret how I handled it afterwards.
I called Alex and invited him
to spend some time with us this holiday.
And also, I contacted Juliana's parents.
We discussed the...
You can say it out loud.
Your relationship.
And came to the conclusion
that we want our daughters to be happy.
As much as teenagers can be happy.
Juliana is on her way back here.
- Her flight arrives this evening.
- Oh, my God! Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh, wait. What about dad?
What will he say?
I don't know.
And frankly, I'm tired of caring.
You deserve to be happy too, Mom.
The grades are up! The grades are up!
You took the top spot.
Oh, my God, I'm staying.
You took Dae's spot.
- Uh, I really didn't mean to, Q.
- No, but you did.
Dae's my best friend.
This is really messed up.
Q! What does it say?!
You passed!
You're staying another semester.
- Wait, I'm still mad at you.
- Yeah, I'm still mad at you too.
- What is she doing here?
- Does she live in this dorm?
Katherine Song Covey.
What are you doing here
this early in the morning?
Are you wearing pajamas?
Hello. Hi.
I'm not really sure what you're saying
but if I could just say this one thing,
I have been living in the boys' dorm.
Okay, I admit it.
But the roommate that you put me with,
she had a 24-hour webcam
going at all times
and she put her tissues everywhere.
One time it was even on my pillow.
- Ooh.
- Thank you.
So furthermore,
if I'm going to get in trouble...
Kitty.
This is not about you getting in trouble.
It's about you getting expelled.
Expelled? But...
But I passed all of my classes.
We know.
But with your specific scholarship,
there are clear rules about conduct,
and by living in the boys' dorms,
you broke the rules.
I'm sorry,
but you will not be asked back to KISS.
This is my last meal.
You're getting kicked out,
you're not on death row.
And I don't know how you can eat something
that spicy this early in the day.
Madison, focus.
Everyone else is mad at me right now.
So, Madison, this is all on you.
You need to be my hype man
and convince me that I can fight this.
Okay.
That I can plead my case
and prove to the people at the school
that I belong here.
You do.
That I deserve another chance!
They say go big or go home, right?
I might be doing both.
Oh.
Professors, fellow students...
Principal Lim.
Whoo!
KISS has meant more to me
than I could ever express
standing on top of this table.
But I'm gonna try.
It's where I learned about my mom.
I found her favorite tree.
She loved it even when it wasn't in bloom
because somehow...
she always saw the beauty in things.
Even when they weren't at their best.
I learned that she could play guitar.
And...
Hey.
Do you want to get down from there?
I might have been raised by white people
but I do know that it's frowned upon
to put your feet where you eat in Korea.
This is a plot twist.
Now I'm the one who's leaving.
I can't believe
that you lived in that dorm
right under my nose the whole time.
Professor Lee was right.
I do suck at being an authority figure.
You're good at other stuff.
I'm really gonna miss you.
I mean, there's always KakaoTalk.
Yeah, but no calls from nightclubs.
At least until you're 21.
Fair.
- Did you use my buckwheat hand cream?
- No.
- Did you take my anti-aging serum?
- No. Get out.
- Did you take his serum?
- No.
But I did use his buckwheat hand cream.
I'm really sorry.
About before.
I'm really sorry too.
What Florian did was so messed up.
And now I have to figure out
what to do about it.
It's hard to just turn your feelings off
for someone you care about.
I get it.
I can't believe
you're really not coming back.
I know.
I'm gonna miss you most of all, roomie.
Stop trying to make me cry, you witch.
Well, I'm out.
Cheers, dude.
I'll see you after the break.
Bye, Kitty. Be good.
Maybe he doesn't realize
I'm not coming back.
He knows, he's just...
Min Ho.
I liked your speech in the cafeteria.
- You did?
- Yes.
Then why did you walk out?
I'm the head of the school.
I can't let anyone see me cry.
You're so much like your mother.
She never backed down
when she believed in something.
- Thank you.
- I have something for you.
Your mom sent this to me
after she got back home
and I never responded.
I wish I had.
I have something for you too.
If you want it.
Oh, my tape.
Oh!
Daniel, Professor Lee,
made this for me after our first date.
I downloaded all the songs
when I thought it was for my mom
and Daniel has some
very cool taste in music.
This wasn't meant to make you sad.
No, it's nostalgia.
Sad and happy all at once.
Daniel was my first love.
And no matter how much time passes...
that stays the same.
I think I can understand that.
So you didn't get first...
but second's pretty good, right?
No, it's not, at all.
If I'm not first in class,
I lose my room and board scholarship.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, Kitty.
Kitty...
She passed.
Mm-hm.
She can stay.
I can't imagine this place
without her now.
I need to tell her everything
that I was too mad to tell her yesterday.
I'm gonna fight for her.
Right, so about that...
I promise she did
wanna say goodbye in person
but then she had to go to the airport.
She left this for you.
I'll, uh, give you some alone time.
- Dae Heon?
- Dad? I need your help.
I don't think we'll make it in time.
We should just give up.
The Kims don't give up.
Hold tight!
For Customs,
please have your passport ready.
Welcome to Seoul, Korea.
♪ I'll be up ♪
♪ Waiting for you ♪
♪ For you... ♪
Flight 74, departure
to Los Angeles, please move to...
Kitty!
♪ To call... ♪
I was scared
I was never gonna see you again.
- I have things to tell you.
- Let me go first.
I don't regret anything
with the two of us.
I don't regret coming here.
I don't regret the last few years.
It was all worth it.
Dae.
For me...
you were the perfect first boyfriend.
Were?
Whatever happens in the future...
you will always be the first girl I loved.
And you'll always be
the first boy I loved.
♪ I'll be up ♪
♪ Waiting for you ♪
♪ To come ♪
Yuri?
Kitty.
I can't believe you're here.
What are you doing here?
Maybe it's a coincidence
or maybe it's fate, but you're here.
And I may never see you again
so I need to tell you this to your face.
Before I came to KISS, I thought I knew
everything there was to know about love.
But, then I met you.
Yuri!
Juliana!
You're here.
I missed you.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
Kitty was just here.
Yeah. I saw her. She left.
- Oh, I wanted to introduce you guys.
- Yuri, I'm not here to meet Kitty.
- I'm here for you.
- I know.
I've been waiting
for this moment for months.
I can't believe you're finally here.
But I do need
to make a phone call to my mom.
Real quick.
Oh, Mom. Yeah. Juliana's here.
Everything's fine except...
I don't think you should expel Kitty.
Are you expelling the boys too?
My time at KISS definitely
wasn't what I thought it would be.
It was so much more.
I made so many new friends.
Friends that I know
I'll keep a whole lifetime.
I learned, I grew up, I expanded.
My world got so much bigger.
Because of you. And because of Simon.
Simon?
Who's Simon?
So I was right.
Mom had another first love
that wasn't Dad?
- What are you doing here?
- On this plane?
Or in coach?
Both.
I'm on this plane
because I'm going to see my mom in L.A.
I'm in coach because...
I thought maybe you could use a friend.
And I thought you didn't even
care enough to say goodbye.
Um, who said I cared?
Oh, um...
Did you make up with Dae?
Yes.
We made up, but we also broke up.
I'm okay.
I mean, we were only pen pals.
I'm always gonna care about him,
but it was time.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Kitty, I need to tell you something.
Is that my pores
are finally better
because I've stolen your cleansing balm?
Kitty.
I think I fell in love with you.
A little bit.
Or...
a lot.
Please fasten your seatbelts.
We are preparing for takeoff.
♪ Started in the strangest way ♪
♪ Didn't see it coming ♪
♪ Swept up in your hurricane ♪
♪ Wouldn't give it up for nothing ♪
♪ Now I'm all caught up
In the highs and the lows ♪
♪ It's a shock to my system ♪
♪ I don't wanna run away so I stay ♪
♪ My head gets messy when I try to hide ♪
♪ The things I love about you in my mind ♪
♪ I don't really know a lot about love
A lot about love, a lot about love ♪
♪ But you're in my head
You're in my blood ♪
♪ And it feels so good, it hurts so much ♪
♪ I don't really know a lot about love
A lot about love, a lot about love ♪
♪ But you're in my head
You're in my blood ♪
♪ And it feels so good, it hurts so much
So much ♪
♪ It feels so good, it hurts so much ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪