It's been a month since
Min Ho and I officially started dating.
I've always known him
as Min Ho, my friend.
But as Min Ho, my boyfriend?
Well, our relationship
just hits different.
In the obvious ways.
But in the surprising ways too.
Like, he's a total gentleman. Who knew?
Even though I can get my own banchan,
thank you very much.
But okay, it's sweet that
he pays attention to the little things.
I like to think
I'm opening up his world a little too.
With my Sunset List, for example,
which he finds
completely embarrassing half the time.
But I'm his girlfriend now, so I get
to make him be embarrassing with me.
I think he secretly likes it.
We were friends for so long,
I thought I knew everything
there is to know about him.
But as it turns out,
we're still getting to know each other.
If only a pesky thing called school
would stop getting in the way
of our relationship.
Of course, the hardest class at KISS
is the one I need to graduate.
And I get that Jiwon said
no more special cousin favors,
but she could at least, like,
pity me for my sucky Korean.
What about me? I'm fluent.
For Monday, read Yi Kwang-su's Mujong,
a ten-page essay
on the Japanese occupation of Korea
for historical context.
Have a good weekend.
Jiwon, I love Korean Lit
as much as the next teen,
but Professor Lee doesn't even assign
this much homework in his class.
Oh, I'm aware.
When I showed him my syllabus,
he nearly wept with joy.
That's great.
Well, this weekend, Min Ho is shooting
a music video for Eunice's debut single,
and I really want to be there
to support him.
So is there any chance
I could just get a small extension?
No, Kitty. You're already
too focused on your boyfriend
and not on what really matters,
this class.
I love my cousin, but I am not
a fan of my teacher right now.
Hi.
Um, Professor Ahn.
I was just heading to the supply closet.
I was wondering if you needed
any Post-it Notes, staples?
I may be new, but I can assure you
that my classroom is well-stocked,
Professor Finnerty.
Great. Well, if you did need anything,
my office is just down the, um, hall.
How did I not see this sooner?
It's a grumpy sunshine match
made in heaven!
I am telling you,
Alex and my cousin have serious chemistry.
- I don't see it.
- Me neither.
What are we talking about?
What a cute couple
Alex and Jiwon are going to make.
I shall call them "Jilex."
I don't see it.
Oh my God, can everyone stop doubting
my matchmaking skills and trust me?
All right, calm down.
Fine, you can do your thing.
Besides, we've got a thousand things
to do before Eunice's video shoot.
I can't believe your dad
rented the aquarium for Eunice.
Will Baby Moo Moo make a cameo?
Baby who-who?
Baby Moo Moo, the newborn manatee,
only the most viral thing
on the planet right now?
Yeah, unfortunately no Baby Moo Moo,
but I did cast Tae-Oh
for Eunice's video shoot.
Ew, the handsy limo guy?
I know, he's not exactly my first choice,
but he's Dad's client.
Oh, but guess who's designing
Eunice's costumes?
- Yisoo.
- Wow! After my dress fiasco on the yacht?
That's amazing. I didn't think your dad
would get over that, let alone Yisoo.
I have no idea what changed her mind,
but Eunice and I are meeting
her new assistant later
to go over costumes.
Well, I have to get going
on my Korean lit homework.
But I'd rather spend time with you.
- Mm.
- I have to go.
Yeah, but what if we squeeze in
a quick Korean lesson?
- Bye.
- Are we that annoying?
- God, I hope not.
I was thinking I need a Korean lesson too.
Want me to teach you?
Exactly.
It's all about the tongue.
Oh, is it now?
Try to keep the tip of your tongue
lightly pressed behind your front teeth.
What am I even saying anyway?
It means, "You are so handsome."
I think I'm going to be…
…sick.
- Oh! Is she okay?
- Yeah, she's just stressed.
Honestly, I am as well.
There's a lot riding on her debut.
After all the money
Dad spent on the video,
we really can't afford a flop.
All right, I better go check on her.
By the way, can you keep an eye out
for Yisoo's assistant?
She should be here any minute now.
Yeah, and don't be stressed.
You've got this. And I've got you.
Okay.
Damn. Who is that?
Oh my God, she's coming towards me.
Oh my God, she's here!
Excuse me, by chance
do you know where Min Ho Kang is?
- Oh, um…
- Ah.
Sorry, Thought you spoke Korean.
You must be Yisoo's assistant.
- Min Ho's super excited to meet you.
- Noona?
Hey,
you don't come greet your noona?
- What are you doing here?
- You know, I just wanted to surprise you.
What a great surprise!
You look amazing.
I can't believe you're here!
Is it me,
or is Min Ho blushing? Who is this girl?
Uh, my Korean's not perfect,
but I heard you say noona?
Do you already know each other?
I'm sorry, Kitty, this is Gigi. She's a
family friend.
Wait, so you're working for Yisoo?
I mean, you already had impeccable style.
But this is next level! Does this mean
you're moving back to Seoul?
- What happened to FIT?
- Okay, take a breath.
That's a cool job
for someone still in college.
I took a semester off
after I landed the Yisoo job,
but I had no idea
you were Eunice's manager until--
Damn! Did I miss the big reunion?
Mwah.
- What's up, Kathy?
- Wait. Is this your doing?
Well, when I heard
you were working for Yisoo,
I figured you were the perfect person
to get this one back on track.
Plus, you two together again? Fire!
I can't believe you got Yisoo to give me
and Eunice a second chance.
Don't act so surprised.
I'd take a bullet for you.
- Literally.
- Noona…
You're the best.
So, I'll see you at the video shoot.
That's the gig.
Yisoo fired her part-time third assistant,
so until she hires someone else,
I'm doing both jobs.
That sounds like a huge responsibility
for someone who stole her dad's--
I did not steal my dad's Porsche.
We borrowed it.
Yeah, that was a crazy night.
How crazy are we talkin'?
Long story.
Mm.
So, um, should we go find Eunice?
Bye.
Gigi's pretty lush, isn't she?
It'll be great for Min Ho
to have a family friend at the shoot.
The more the merrier.
A family friend?
Is that all you call Gigi?
It's just a funny way to put it.
Don't get me wrong, I mean,
Min Ho's family
absolutely adores Gige, but…
You know, his feelings were just
a little bit more intense.
Oh, like, Min Ho used to have
a crush on her or something?
I mean, can you blame him? She's so cool.
I mean, hard agree. But just real talk,
she wasn't just a crush.
She was Min Ho's first love.
Hey. How'd you sleep?
Fine. Did anyone see you sneak out?
No, I think the coast was clear.
Oh! I was thinking maybe, if you're free,
would you want to come
to the Zanele Muholi exhibition?
Or we could go dancing
at that club in Itaewon.
Okay. Okay, let's do culture.
- Let's do culture.
- Yeah.
- Okay. I'll see you later.
- Okay, bye.
Black sesame latte, right?
I can buy my own coffee.
I'm hoping we can move past
our weirdness for Juliana's sake.
I saw on Instagram you like these,
so I figured I'd get you one
as a peace offering.
Please take it.
Thanks.
Find anything interesting
on Gigi's socials?
Other than photos of her looking chic?
There's one at Nobu with Min Ho's mom,
and one at Coachella with Min Ho's dad.
Did I mention that his family loves her?
Min Ho is with you now.
Why does any of this matter?
I don't know.
Maybe because his dad made it clear
he doesn't think I belong in his world,
and Gigi clearly does.
I mean, they both
obviously have all this history,
they both speak Korean, and they both look
annoyingly good in jorts. So…
- No wonder she was his first love.
- First loves ain't all that.
Really? How long did it take you
to get over Juliana?
I… will let you know.
Mm-hmm.
Whatever. The only reason
I even brought Gigi up
is because she's looking for someone
to be Yisoo's part-time third assistant.
You'd be perfect for the job.
I don't know. I was the one
that put you in that stolen Yisoo dress.
Yes. In hindsight, not your finest moment,
but you had a lot going on that night.
Anyway, you could come with me
to Eunice's video shoot,
help Gigi with the wardrobe stuff.
And assist you in keeping tabs
on Min Ho while Gigi's around?
To be a good assistant,
you gotta learn to multitask.
And to be a good girlfriend,
you gotta chill.
Yuri's right. I'm spiraling for nothing.
Min Ho's always been Team Kitty.
And it's about time I show him
I'm Team Min Ho.
- Hey. Uh, Min Ho's just getting ready.
- Ah.
I think he's a bit stressed
about the video.
Yeah.
Oh, and speaking of,
I've been thinking about
going to the shoot to support Eunice.
I'm sure she would love that.
- You look amazing.
- Oh.
- Hi.
But it's not that kind of date.
Look, I know you're stressed,
so I booked us a spa date.
I got your favorite facialist
to do that serumy thing.
And matching sweatsuits.
Shoot. I'm so sorry, Covey.
Something came up. I've just been so busy.
Gigi and I have
an emergency wardrobe meeting.
Eunice vetoed all her costumes.
Oh, uh, that sounds so stressful.
I'm sorry.
Yes, but luckily, Gigi's quite talented.
She's already putting together
a whole new concept.
Wow. Gigi to the rescue.
What is the story with you two anyway?
Uh, we've basically been friends
since we were toddlers.
Gigi's mum's an actress too.
We used to mess around the red carpets.
Sounds glamorous. When was
the last time you two saw each other?
Don't know.
Before she left for FIT, I guess.
- What's with all the questions?
- Mm.
I'm gonna go.
Marius told me
that Gigi was your first love.
And it made me feel kinda weird
watching you be all goofy around her.
With all your inside jokes,
and, well, she is unnervingly cool.
You have nothing to worry about.
Whatever feelings I had, it's in the past.
And whatever you and I have
is in the present.
And besides,
if it wasn't for the costume crisis,
I'd be on the perfect spa date
with my perfect girl.
That's you, by the way.
I might even wear that fire hazard.
I promise not to let you
walk past any open flames.
Mm.
See you at the shoot.
If I'm gonna be a good girlfriend,
I need to be there for Min Ho
this weekend.
Which means I need to win Jiwon over
with a perfect date of her own.
Jiwon! I heard some teachers
are going to the Cat Café this weekend.
- Maybe you and Alex could--
- No, thank you.
- What about gelato?
- Uh, I have grading.
Have you heard of Baby Moo Moo?
Baby Moo Moo? Who hasn't?
She's the hottest ticket in Seoul.
The entire aquarium is sold out for weeks.
What if I told you I could get you in?
Then would you give me
a tiny extension on that essay?
For a national treasure?
Oh my gosh. I cannot believe
I get to see Baby Moo Moo!
I mean, it's no Australian Dugong,
which I understand
is a close cousin to the manatee.
And speaking of cousins…
What?
Professor Finnerty,
what are you doing here?
Kitty invited me.
I didn't know you'd be here.
What a pleasant surprise.
Ah.
Please tell me this isn't
some kind of secret blind date.
Well, I should be getting to set now.
But you two get your Moo Moo on.
I will, uh, check in later.
Have fun.
Action!
At the start you had my heart
Oh, you were my everything!
Then you tried to dull my light
Your mistake, ugh, boring!
I can't be tamed, don't say my name
'Cause I'm your only claim to fame
I'm too smart, too hot
Too busy, too pretty
To get caught up in your games
All the boys wanna see me
All the girls wanna be me
At the end of the night
All the guys and the girls
Close their eyes and dream me
It ain't surprising
I'm hypnotizing
I get them so excited when they dream
'Cause I'm Euniq!
- Cut!
Okay, Kitty. Be cool.
Oh God. I didn't overdress, did I?
Hey, Kitty. You look amazing.
Oh, this? It's nothing.
Oh, well, I go full dirtbag
on shoot days, so…
Confirming. I overdressed. Crap.
Um…
- Hi.
- Oh, this is Yuri.
- She volunteered to help today.
And I'm also willing to work for money
if you're still looking
for a third assistant.
Oh, also, I saw on Instagram
that you like iced turmeric lattes.
You must have scrolled really far back.
I think I got this, like, a year ago?
But… thanks.
Okay, I'm gonna be over there.
Uh, have you seen Min Ho?
Yeah, they're over there,
arguing about whether or not
Tae-Oh should be wearing a shirt.
Got it.
This is such a big day for Min Ho.
I just want everything to go well.
I'm sure, especially after all that stuff
with Eunice's dress on the yacht.
Uh, Marius told me.
Hmm. Well, it was
an honest mistake, I swear.
Obviously.
Uh, I… I think that's my cue.
Maybe I can help too.
Why would you be shirtless in an aquarium?
Do I have to say it?
Ah.
Tae-Oh, I understand what you're saying.
But Yisoo made this tank top
especially for you.
Really?
If they were arguing
in English, I'd problem-solve this.
But they're not, so I need to figure out
how else to make myself useful.
What are you doing here?
The same as you. I'm supporting Min Ho.
Please, the only reason
you're supportive is if it benefits you.
As if you're here
purely out of the goodness of your heart.
What other reason would I have?
I don't know. Gee, maybe you wanted
to take a selfie with Baby Moo Moo.
Okay, maybe I had
an impromptu photo shoot this morning.
Well, I mean, no one can blame you.
She is cute.
And you have a knack
for taking a one-of-a-kind self-portrait.
You deleted the pic I sent you
this summer like you promised, right?
Q, relax. You can trust me.
Thought I wouldn't go far
But I'm a star
You thought you hurt me
But boy, I'm in charge
While you chase girls
Who wish they were me
I'll be trapping boys like Jay Park
All the boys wanna see me
Cut!
This isn't working, and we're late.
I hate this choreo!
Well, it's too late to change it.
Okay, then can we
at least take five? I have to pee.
Can't you just hold it?
No, not when we're surrounded by water!
Can somebody please get me green juice?
That will just make you pee even more.
- I've never seen her like this.
- Hey, don't worry. I will get her juice.
Min Ho, I think I know what's wrong.
Eunice and Tae-Oh probably hooked up
on tour, now she feels weird around him.
Are you serious?
If their fans figure this out,
both their careers will be ruined.
And my dad will kill me.
My dad will kill me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't worry. I think I have an idea.
Have you seen where Min Ho went?
Yeah, he just went along with Gige.
I'm glad I got them back together.
They make a brilliant team, don't they?
You're watching
Baby Moo Moo do the backstroke,
and you're not even smiling.
Something's up.
Gigi was Min Ho's first love.
Dae was your first love.
You got over him, right?
No, but Gigi and Min Ho
still have a connection.
I've been watching them all day
and I don't know how to be there
for Min Ho. Not like she does.
I wish Marius never even told me.
Wait. You're telling me Marius
put Gigi and Min Ho back in touch
and made sure
you knew about their history?
This guy loves leveraging secrets
to mess with people.
- Oh my God, I'm so screwed!
- Oh my God, I'm being played.
You first.
Marius is totally just using Gigi
to make me feel insecure about Min Ho,
and gaslighting me.
But that ends now.
I am not being sidelined. Okay, your turn.
So, over the summer
I may have sent Marius a photo
that you don't send when
you're in a committed relationship.
- Q!
- I know, and I'm not proud of it.
And it's not an excuse, but…
Jin hadn't visited me at USC,
and I was super lonely.
Marius told me he deleted the photo,
but I don't know if I believe him.
If he wants to mess with
your relationship,
that photo's gonna do it.
And if you don't want Marius
leveraging that against you,
I think you have to tell Jin the truth.
There's no other way.
Okay. Wish me luck.
What are you doing?
You can't iron silk on high heat.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry. I didn't know.
My maid used to do this for me.
This was our only backup dress.
I get that you want to help, but… don't.
Oh. Sorry.
Hey, is Eunice around?
What's that?
Macarons. I ordered them overnight.
Eunice loved them on her Paris tour stop.
I just wanted to remind her
what she's working so hard for.
- Are you okay?
- No, I totally messed up.
There's no way I'm getting this job now.
Hey, if you want this job
half as much as I want Eunice back,
don't give up.
Wish me luck.
Action!
You
- Cut!
Oh my God. I'm so sorry, guys.
I thought that was on silent.
- Q, we are already delayed.
- You are so right.
Guys, no more delays. Come on.
Phones in the bin.
Hey, you signed an NDA.
Um… thanks. Thank you.
Thank you, Dae.
Always a team player. You too.
Oh, thank you, guys.
You'll get it at the end of the day.
All right, listen up, everyone!
Gigi, Eunice, and I
just worked out a new scene.
All right, the song "EUNIQ"
is about a unique woman, not a man.
By the way, brilliant idea, Gige.
So, Tae-Oh will be in the background,
and can someone get my star a fresh juice?
- That's my cue!
- I got it.
Are you kidding me? Dude…
- Are you okay?
- I am so sorry.
I can't believe I'm doing this again.
Please, please let me help.
Maybe you shouldn't, Covey.
Gigi, can you fix this?
- No, I'm not a designer.
- I can fix the dress.
Yes, yes, great idea.
If anybody can turn this dress
into something incredible, it's Yuri.
Let me try. I know what I'm doing.
And frankly,
we don't really have any other choice.
Please, allow me.
I told you I deleted it.
I'm just supposed to believe you?
You thrive on chaos.
You reached out to Gigi to mess
with Kitty and Min Ho's relationship.
Yeah, because Kitty
messed with ours first.
For the last time,
we're not in a relationship. I'm with Jin.
I deleted the picture, but you can't
delete the fact that you sent it.
Obviously, you still have
feelings for me, Q.
I don't know
why you're so afraid to admit that.
'Cause I'm Euniq, Euniq, Euniq
She's fine, I guess, but can't compete
Is that that kid's shirt?
Yep, I dyed Dae's shirt
with the green juice,
and the yellow is from the iced turmeric
latte you didn't take a single sip of.
You know, any kiss-ass can buy coffee,
but it takes real talent to save a dress.
If you wanna be Yisoo's third assistant,
I'll get you an interview.
Euniq, hey!
Cut! Okay, that's a wrap!
- Eunice! Here--
- Thank you so much!
Hey, you think I can meet up
with Eunice later?
Ah…
I'm not sure.
She seems pretty busy, don't you think?
Then, can you give her these macarons?
I want her to know--
Dae, I don't know how to say this…
I think Eunice hooked up
with Tae-Oh on tour.
I'm sorry.
No, thanks for telling me.
- Hey.
I know I've been acting a little crazy.
I just wanted to be
a supportive girlfriend
and have your back.
But then, Gigi showed up,
and you guys are so in sync,
and you have all this history
and you just seem,
like, effortless together.
So, I guess I felt…
Threatened?
Don't be.
Kitty, you and I aren't effortless, but…
I do like that you make me do things
I wouldn't normally do.
Like doing that stupid Gangnam dance.
And you do have my back.
You believe in me
more than I believe in myself sometimes.
And sure, maybe you go overboard
now and then, but…
I wouldn't change a thing.
Really?
Yes. And thanks
to that Senior Sunset List,
we're making
some amazing memories together.
Well, I'm happy to do
more things you like too.
You mean like our spa date?
Which I hope is still on.
I'll even wear the sweatsuit.
Well, as much as I would love a massage,
I have a ten-page essay due Tuesday.
Tell you what, let me wrap up here,
grab my stuff,
and I'll help you with your essay.
I'll even bring over
some sheet masks while I'm at it.
You got this, and I've got you.
Hi, roomies.
You're in a good mood.
I got a job interview with Yisoo.
- Oh my God.
- What? That's sick.
Oh, and I totally ripped off
your coffee move, which worked.
Just not in the way I expected.
You can tell me all the details
over an iced chai when you get the job.
- Okay.
- You've met your match.
Oh my God.
I didn't realize
you two were getting so close.
- Care to catch me up?
- I think we're becoming friends.
- Stay down.
- Oh.
Oh, you… Okay.
You've met your master.
Hey. How'd it go with Alex?
I don't know, Kitty.
He left right after you did.
What? Why?
Because if we'd known this was a setup,
we wouldn't have come.
There are rules against teachers dating.
If Principal Lee found out,
we could be fired.
- I didn't mean to cause--
- I'm not an idiot, Kitty.
I've seen Clueless.
Whatever spark
you think we have doesn't exist.
I find his cheerfulness annoying,
his accent unintelligible,
and his love of boat shoes just deranged.
Wow, okay. I thought
the preppy look kind of worked for him--
Stop. This isn't about me and Alex at all.
It's about you.
You manipulated me so you could
spend more time with your boyfriend,
who I still think
you're too focused on, by the way.
And you put my job in danger, again.
You definitely don't have
your priorities straight,
so I'm gonna help you with that.
I'm taking back your extension
and adding ten pages to your essay.
No, if I don't pass your class,
I'm not gonna graduate.
Then I suggest you hit the books. Hard.
I was so busy
living in the moment with Min Ho
that I forgot
my actual future is on the line.
If I don't pass Jiwon's class,
I'm screwed.
That's the moral of the story, babe
They say it's better to have loved
And lost
Than never to have loved at all
That could be a load of shit
But I just need to tell you all
Some mistakes get made
That's all right, that's okay
You can think that you're in love
When you're really just engaged
Some mistakes get made
That's all right, that's okay
In the end, it's better for me
That's the moral of the story